<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
<!--Observing middle aged Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The saggy folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether regions, with its gaping maw and discolored labia, suggest a history of abuse or simply extreme neglect.</li>
            <li>A withered abyss. The way {PAWN_possessive} aged, flabby labia hang, revealing a dark, shriveled clitoris, is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of desperation and a long-lost spark.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at countless, joyless encounters.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looks like a forgotten pebble in a dry riverbed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all curiosity.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a turn-off.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused, leaving behind only emptiness.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. Utterly without appeal.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. Revolting.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner workings are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex voyer Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Despite my voyeuristic nature, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flaccid, uninspired depths, with its withered clitoris, was truly disappointing.</li>
            <li>I sought a thrill, but found only despair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping, listless folds and faded labia revealed nothing but sad emptiness.</li>
            <li>The promised mystery became a grotesque reality. {PAWN_possessive} pallid, stretched opening offered no excitement, only the decay of age.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic gaze was met with disappointment. That deep, uninviting chasm and the barely visible clitoris are completely unstimulating.</li>
            <li>Such an opportunity, wasted! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless labia and the sheer, uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss are a visual letdown.</li>
            <li>I watched, hoping for something, but {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous vulva provided only a bleak, uninteresting spectacle.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts offered no pleasure; only the unappealing, withered form of a forgotten pleasure garden.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's lust turned to disgust. The sagging lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region offered only profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>I peered, but saw nothing desirable. {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby labia and the deep, dark opening revealed a disturbing lack of vitality.</li>
            <li>What a letdown for my eyes! The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was a definite anti-climax.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic curiosity was promptly extinguished. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and the lack of any enticing form were a true horror.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame, finding only a deflated, unappealing structure that failed to ignite any spark.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was brief, but horrifying. That vast, joyless opening and the weary, faded lips of {PAWN_possessive} body part screamed of decay.</li>
            <li>As a voyeur, I sought beauty, but found only the grotesque. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid sight.</li>
            <li>I watched, fascinated by the repulsion. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to time's cruel, unflattering work.</li>
            <li>The forbidden fruit turned sour. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form of {PAWN_possessive} vulva disgusted my voyeur's heart.</li>
            <li>My intrusive gaze revealed a desolate landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris offered no allure whatsoever.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and immediately regretted it. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed parts were a far cry from anything I'd want to observe.</li>
            <li>What an unfortunate display for my voyeuristic eyes. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out depths was deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>My thirst for a secret view met a bitter end. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for an exhibitionist, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, cavernous depths is an embarrassment, a truly unappealing display.</li>
            <li>I love to show, but {PAWN_possessive} private parts are a reason to hide! Those saggy, lifeless lips and shriveled clitoris are an awful sight.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist spirit recoiled. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pallid, worn-out opening offers nothing worth showing, only the decay of age.</li>
            <li>A truly pathetic attempt at display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping, uninspired vulva lacks any spark, making it unwatchable even for me.</li>
            <li>The uninviting, stretched folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, with their almost non-existent clitoris, are a dismal advertisement for intimacy.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_pronoun} isn't an exhibitionist. That sad, saggy excuse for a pleasure portal makes me want to avert my eyes.</li>
            <li>My natural inclination to expose is thwarted by the repulsive sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, discolored labia and dreary depths.</li>
            <li>Such a poor display. The vast, empty chasm of {PAWN_possessive} inner sanctum and its faded, almost lost clitoris are truly pathetic.</li>
            <li>I can't believe {PAWN_pronoun} would let this be seen. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing form and lack of any vigor are profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>This sight makes me question my own exhibitionism. {PAWN_possessive} worn-out, uninviting entrance is a dismal advertisement for the female form.</li>
            <li>Even I, an exhibitionist, find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed parts utterly unappealing, a stark, lifeless vision of feminine decay.</li>
            <li>The sad, empty depth and the discoloured, sagging labia of {PAWN_possessive} make for a truly pitiful display, not one to flaunt.</li>
            <li>My desire to show off is dampened by the utterly uninspired, flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame.</li>
            <li>This exposed anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a cautionary tale, revealing only the desolate consequences of time and overuse. Horrifying.</li>
            <li>I am an exhibitionist, but even I know when something should remain covered. {PAWN_possessive} abyssal parts are a prime example.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lifeless clitoris and the vast, unappealing chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths is truly a miserable display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area is a testament to what happens when beauty fades into something truly grotesque and uninspiring.</li>
            <li>I feel no urge to join {PAWN_objective} in this display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} saggy, joyless parts are a visual affront to exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>What a miserable presentation! The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia hang, lifeless and discolored, tells a grim, unappealing story.</li>
            <li>This is what I *don't* want people to see. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, aged anatomy is a true disservice to the art of exhibition.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even my insatiable urges are quelled by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, uninspired depths. There's no spark left.</li>
            <li>My desires withered. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, cavernous vulva, with its withered clitoris, offers nothing to ignite passion.</li>
            <li>I crave intimacy, but {PAWN_possessive} aged, pallid opening and saggy labia are a definite turn-off, promising only disappointment.</li>
            <li>A nymphomaniac's nightmare. That deep, uninviting chasm and the barely visible clitoris are completely unstimulating, devoid of any allure.</li>
            <li>There's no pleasure to be found here. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless labia and the sheer, uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss repel me.</li>
            <li>My hunger for flesh is nauseated. {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous parts are a bleak, uninteresting spectacle, not a source of lust.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts offers no excitement; only the unappealing, withered form of a forgotten pleasure.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac lust turned to pure revulsion. The sagging lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region offers nothing but dread.</li>
            <li>I hunger, but not for this. {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby labia and the deep, dark opening reveal a disturbing lack of arousal.</li>
            <li>My desires shrivelled instantly. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was a profound anti-aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac appetite was promptly extinguished. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and the lack of any enticing form were repulsive.</li>
            <li>I crave pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame is a deflated, unappealing structure that fails to ignite any desire.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was brief, but horrifying. That vast, joyless opening and the weary, faded lips of {PAWN_possessive} body part screamed of decay.</li>
            <li>As a nymphomaniac, I sought passion, but found only the grotesque. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid sight.</li>
            <li>I observed, repulsed. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to time's cruel, unflattering work, leaving me cold.</li>
            <li>The forbidden fruit turned to ash in my mouth. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form disgusted me.</li>
            <li>My burning desire met a cold, desolate landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris offered no allure.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and immediately felt my urges dissipate. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed parts were truly abhorrent.</li>
            <li>What a miserable display for my nymphomaniac eyes. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out depths was deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>My thirst for sexual encounter met a bitter, disheartening end. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, abyssal depths filled me with immediate revulsion and a strong desire to look away.</li>
            <li>How utterly indecent! The sagging, lifeless lips and shriveled clitoris of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a truly shameful spectacle.</li>
            <li>A gross indecency! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pallid, worn-out opening is a disgusting display, utterly offensive to proper sensibilities.</li>
            <li>My eyes were assaulted by the sight of that deep, uninviting chasm and the barely visible clitoris of {PAWN_possessive}. Disgusting!</li>
            <li>The sheer vulgarity! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless labia and the uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss are an affront to decency.</li>
            <li>I am appalled! {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous vulva is a grotesque, obscene spectacle, a true violation of modesty.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts is utterly sickening; such a withered, unappealing form should never be exposed.</li>
            <li>My modest sensibilities are outraged. The sagging lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region are profoundly disturbing.</li>
            <li>How dare {PAWN_pronoun} expose such a thing? {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby labia and the dark, gaping opening are a horror.</li>
            <li>I was forced to witness such lewdness. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was unthinkably vulgar.</li>
            <li>My prudish nature was shocked to its core. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and lack of enticing form were thoroughly repulsive.</li>
            <li>I wish I could unsee it. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame is a deflated, unappealing structure that is profoundly indecent.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was horrifying, confirming my worst fears. That vast, joyless opening and the weary, faded lips screamed of depravity.</li>
            <li>As a prude, I find only the grotesque. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid and unacceptable sight.</li>
            <li>I observed, disgusted. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to moral decay, leaving me utterly repulsed.</li>
            <li>The forbidden view turned my stomach. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form were nothing short of obscene.</li>
            <li>My purity was stained by the desolate landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris were a gross affront.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and felt pure moral horror. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed parts were a disgusting violation.</li>
            <li>What a miserable, indecent display. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out depths was profoundly offensive to my senses.</li>
            <li>My aversion to indecency met a dreadful confirmation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void, an utter abomination.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, flabby depths with their gaping maw made my youthful desires shrivel. It was profoundly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, instantly killed any spark of interest.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips suggest a history of joyless encounters.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at countless, dreary years.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried berry.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a turn-off for any young man.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused, leaving behind only emptiness and regret.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. Utterly without youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for me.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. Revolting.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I wished they hadn't. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression on me.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, sagging depths filled me with a morbid fascination and a profound sense of dread for my own future.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of decline.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips filled me with disgust for the future.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at a desolate, joyless aging.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried pebble.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque and cautionary.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all hope for youth.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests a lifetime of wear, leaving behind only emptiness and an aged form.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with apprehension.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. A terrifying vision of what’s to come.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence that awaits.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. A revolting premonition.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, wishing for blindness. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight for any woman.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression of aging.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, flabby depths with their gaping maw made my desires shrivel. It was profoundly unappealing, even at my age.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, killed any spark of attraction instantly.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips suggest a history of weary, joyless encounters.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at countless, dreary years.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried prune.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a turn-off for a man like me.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused, leaving behind only emptiness and regret.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. Utterly without appeal for someone my age.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. Revolting.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I wished they hadn't. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression on me.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, sagging depths filled me with a familiar unease, a sad reflection of time's unkindness.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of our shared future.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips filled me with a sense of dread.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at a desolate, joyless aging.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried berry.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque and cautionary.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that reminds me of inevitable decline.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests a lifetime of wear, leaving behind only emptiness and an aged form.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with apprehension.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. A terrifying vision of what’s to come for us all.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence that awaits.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. A revolting premonition.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, wishing for blindness. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight for any woman.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression of aging.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, flabby depths with their gaping maw made my seasoned desires shrivel. It was profoundly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, killed any spark of interest, even for an old man.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips suggest a history of weary, joyless encounters.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at countless, dreary years.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried berry.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a turn-off for a man of my years.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused, leaving behind only emptiness and regret.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. Utterly without appeal for someone my age.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. Revolting.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I wished they hadn't. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression on me.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged, sagging depths filled me with an even deeper sense of regret and the bitter truth of time.</li>
            <li>Her withered abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of the past's decline.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips filled me with a sense of dread.</li>
            <li>A repulsive sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-taut entrance now appears stretched and pallid, the visible depth hinting at a desolate, joyless aging.</li>
            <li>The dull, faded hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely noticeable amidst the drooping flesh, looked like a forgotten, dried berry.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was enough. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any vitality is simply grotesque and cautionary.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to weep with age, a stark, uninviting void that reminds me of inevitable decline.</li>
            <li>Such an unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests a lifetime of wear, leaving behind only emptiness and an aged form.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with apprehension.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… sad. A terrifying vision of what’s to come for us all.</li>
            <li>A decaying bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled flaps, hinting at a bleak, joyless existence that awaits.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of disappointment, leading to a depth that promises only cold emptiness. A revolting premonition.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, wishing for blindness. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight for any woman.</li>
            <li>An abyssal void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of decay. It’s a truly negative impression of aging.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Observing elderly Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The utterly dilapidated abyss of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether regions, with its gaping, aged maw and discolored, withered labia, is profoundly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A truly ancient abyss. The way {PAWN_possessive} flabby, saggy labia hang, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, is disturbing.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life.</li>
            <li>A truly abhorrent sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, forgotten seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all life.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a turn-off.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. Utterly without appeal.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--unisex voyer Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Despite my voyeuristic nature, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, ancient depths with its withered clitoris was truly sickening, not exciting.</li>
            <li>I sought a thrill, but found only dread. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping, listless, utterly aged folds and faded labia revealed nothing but horrifying decay.</li>
            <li>The promised mystery became a grotesque, ancient reality. {PAWN_possessive} pallid, stretched, collapsed opening offered no excitement, only the decay of centuries.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic gaze was met with utter revulsion. That deep, uninviting, ancient chasm and the barely visible clitoris are completely unstimulating.</li>
            <li>Such an opportunity, utterly wasted! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless labia and the sheer, uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss are a horrifying visual letdown.</li>
            <li>I watched, hoping for something, but {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous, ancient vulva provided only a bleak, truly disturbing spectacle.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts offered no pleasure; only the unappealing, withered form of a long-dead pleasure garden.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's lust turned to unadulterated disgust. The sagging, ancient lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region offered only profound nausea.</li>
            <li>I peered, but saw nothing desirable. {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby, ancient labia and the deep, dark opening revealed a disturbing lack of life.</li>
            <li>What a letdown for my eyes! The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was a definite, horrifying anti-climax.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic curiosity was promptly extinguished. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and the lack of any enticing form were purely repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame, finding only a deflated, unappealing structure that failed to ignite any spark, only disgust.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was brief, but horrifying. That vast, joyless, collapsed opening and the weary, faded lips of {PAWN_possessive} body part screamed of decay.</li>
            <li>As a voyeur, I sought beauty, but found only the grotesque, the ancient. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid sight.</li>
            <li>I watched, fascinated by the extreme repulsion. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to time's cruel, utterly unflattering work.</li>
            <li>The forbidden fruit turned irrevocably sour. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form of {PAWN_possessive} vulva disgusted my voyeur's heart.</li>
            <li>My intrusive gaze revealed a desolate, ancient landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris offered no allure whatsoever.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and immediately regretted it. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed, ancient parts were a far cry from anything I'd want to observe.</li>
            <li>What a miserable display for my voyeuristic eyes. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out, ancient depths was deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>My thirst for a secret view met a bitter end. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void, a truly nauseating sight.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for an exhibitionist, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, cavernous, ancient depths is an absolute embarrassment, a truly unappealing display.</li>
            <li>I love to show, but {PAWN_possessive} private parts are a reason to hide permanently! Those saggy, lifeless, ancient lips are an awful sight.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist spirit recoiled in horror. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pallid, worn-out, collapsed opening offers nothing worth showing, only the decay of centuries.</li>
            <li>A truly pathetic attempt at display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping, uninspired vulva lacks any spark, making it unwatchable even for me, a horror.</li>
            <li>The uninviting, stretched, withered folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, with their almost non-existent clitoris, are a dismal advertisement for anything.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_pronoun} isn't an exhibitionist. That sad, saggy, ancient excuse for a pleasure portal makes me want to avert my eyes.</li>
            <li>My natural inclination to expose is thwarted by the utterly repulsive sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, discolored, lifeless labia and dreary depths.</li>
            <li>Such a poor, ancient display. The vast, empty chasm of {PAWN_possessive} inner sanctum and its faded, almost lost clitoris are truly pathetic.</li>
            <li>I can't believe {PAWN_pronoun} would let this be seen. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing, withered form and lack of any vigor are profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>This sight makes me question my own exhibitionism. {PAWN_possessive} worn-out, uninviting, ancient entrance is a dismal advertisement for the female form.</li>
            <li>Even I, an exhibitionist, find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed parts utterly unappealing, a stark, lifeless vision of ancient feminine decay.</li>
            <li>The sad, empty depth and the discoloured, sagging, ancient labia of {PAWN_possessive} make for a truly pitiful display, not one to flaunt.</li>
            <li>My desire to show off is dampened by the utterly uninspired, flaccid, ancient appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame.</li>
            <li>This exposed anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a cautionary, terrifying tale, revealing only the desolate consequences of extreme age and overuse.</li>
            <li>I am an exhibitionist, but even I know when something should remain covered forever. {PAWN_possessive} abyssal, ancient parts are a prime example.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lifeless clitoris and the vast, unappealing chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths is truly a miserable, ancient display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area is a testament to what happens when beauty utterly fades into something truly grotesque and uninspiring with age.</li>
            <li>I feel no urge to join {PAWN_objective} in this horrifying display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} saggy, joyless, ancient parts are a visual affront.</li>
            <li>What a miserable, archaic presentation! The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia hang, lifeless and discolored, tells a grim, unappealing story of severe aging.</li>
            <li>This is what I *don't* want people to see. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, aged anatomy is a true disservice to the art of exhibition, a horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even my insatiable urges are completely quelled by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, ancient, uninspired depths. There's no spark left, only dust.</li>
            <li>My desires withered and died. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, cavernous, ancient vulva, with its withered clitoris, offers nothing to ignite passion, only revulsion.</li>
            <li>I crave intimacy, but {PAWN_possessive} aged, pallid, collapsed opening and saggy labia are a definite turn-off, promising only profound disappointment and disgust.</li>
            <li>A nymphomaniac's ultimate nightmare. That deep, uninviting, ancient chasm and the barely visible clitoris are utterly unstimulating, devoid of any allure.</li>
            <li>There's no pleasure to be found here, only decay. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless, ancient labia and the sheer, uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss repel me utterly.</li>
            <li>My hunger for flesh is nauseated beyond words. {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous, ancient parts are a bleak, truly disturbing spectacle, not a source of lust.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts offered no excitement; only the unappealing, withered form of a long-dead pleasure garden, a crypt.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac lust turned to unadulterated revulsion. The sagging, ancient lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region offered only profound nausea.</li>
            <li>I hunger, but not for this decaying sight. {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby, ancient labia and the deep, dark opening reveal a disturbing lack of arousal.</li>
            <li>My desires shrivelled instantly, irrevocably. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was a profound, horrifying anti-aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac appetite was promptly extinguished forever. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and the lack of any enticing form were purely repulsive.</li>
            <li>I crave pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame is a deflated, unappealing structure that fails to ignite any desire, only disgust.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was brief, but horrifying. That vast, joyless, collapsed opening and the weary, faded lips of {PAWN_possessive} body part screamed of profound decay.</li>
            <li>As a nymphomaniac, I sought passion, but found only the grotesque, the ancient. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid sight.</li>
            <li>I observed, utterly repulsed. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to time's cruel, utterly unflattering work, leaving me cold and disgusted.</li>
            <li>The forbidden fruit turned to ash in my mouth, tasting of rot. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form disgusted me.</li>
            <li>My burning desire met a cold, desolate, ancient landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris offered no allure whatsoever.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and immediately felt my urges dissipate into thin air. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed, ancient parts were truly abhorrent.</li>
            <li>What a miserable display for my nymphomaniac eyes. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out, ancient depths was deeply unsettling, a horror.</li>
            <li>My thirst for sexual encounter met a bitter, disheartening, and utterly nauseating end. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discolored, abyssal, ancient depths filled me with immediate, profound revulsion and a strong desire to flee.</li>
            <li>How utterly indecent and decayed! The sagging, lifeless, shriveled lips and ancient clitoris of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a truly shameful, morbid spectacle.</li>
            <li>A gross, ancient indecency! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pallid, worn-out, collapsed opening is a disgusting, horrifying display, utterly offensive to proper sensibilities.</li>
            <li>My eyes were assaulted by the sight of that deep, uninviting, ancient chasm and the barely visible clitoris of {PAWN_possessive}. Utterly disgusting!</li>
            <li>The sheer vulgarity and decay! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired, lifeless, ancient labia and the uninspired depth of {PAWN_possessive} abyss are an affront to all decency.</li>
            <li>I am appalled beyond words! {PAWN_possessive} discolored, cavernous, ancient vulva is a grotesque, obscene spectacle, a true violation of all modesty.</li>
            <li>The intimate view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts is utterly sickening; such a withered, unappealing, ancient form should never, ever be exposed.</li>
            <li>My modest sensibilities are profoundly outraged. The sagging, ancient lips and abyssal void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region are profoundly disturbing and vile.</li>
            <li>How dare {PAWN_pronoun} expose such a decaying, ancient thing? {PAWN_possessive} uninspired, flabby, ancient labia and the dark, gaping opening are a horror.</li>
            <li>I was forced to witness such lewd, ancient ugliness. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris seemed to vanish amidst the folds was unthinkably vulgar.</li>
            <li>My prudish nature was shocked to its core, shattered. {PAWN_possessive} aged, discolored depths and lack of enticing form were thoroughly repulsive and horrifying.</li>
            <li>I wish I could unsee it, unlive this moment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame is a deflated, unappealing structure that is profoundly indecent and sickening.</li>
            <li>The glimpse was horrifying, confirming my absolute worst fears. That vast, joyless, collapsed opening and the weary, faded lips screamed of true depravity.</li>
            <li>As a prude, I find only the grotesque, the ancient decay. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} withered clitoris and cavernous abyss were a morbid and unacceptable sight.</li>
            <li>I observed, utterly disgusted. {PAWN_possessive} sagging, pallid labia offered a testament to moral decay, leaving me utterly repulsed and wanting to cleanse myself.</li>
            <li>The forbidden view turned my stomach to bile. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing depths and the slack, lifeless form were nothing short of obscene and putrid.</li>
            <li>My purity was stained irrevocably by the desolate, ancient landscape. {PAWN_possessive} dark, cavernous entry and faded, tired clitoris were a gross affront.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse, and felt pure moral, absolute horror. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, overexposed, ancient parts were a disgusting, vile violation.</li>
            <li>What a miserable, indecent, and ancient display. The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} worn-out, ancient depths was profoundly offensive to my senses.</li>
            <li>My aversion to indecency met a dreadful, horrifying confirmation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private shame was a dull, repulsive void, an utter abomination of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, flabby depths with their gaping, withered maw made my youthful desires shrivel and die. It was profoundly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, killed any spark of interest.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction from a young man.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with youthful revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. Utterly without youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for me.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for a young man.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, sagging depths filled me with a profound, morbid fascination and a horrifying sense of future dread.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of true decline.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless, aged years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that reminds me of inevitable, horrifying decline.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with youthful revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. A terrifying vision of my own eventual fate.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for a young woman.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Middle aged male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, flabby depths with their gaping, withered maw made my desires shrivel. It was profoundly unappealing, even at my age.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, killed any spark of interest.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction from a man my age.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with middle-aged revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. Utterly without appeal for someone my age.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for me.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for a man my age.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, sagging depths filled me with a profound, morbid fascination and a horrifying sense of future dread.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of true decline.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless, aged years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that reminds me of inevitable, horrifying decline.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with middle-aged revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. A terrifying vision of my own eventual fate.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for a woman my age.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, flabby depths with their gaping, withered maw made my old desires shrivel and die. It was profoundly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, killed any spark of interest, even for me.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that repels all attraction from an old man.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with elderly revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. Utterly without appeal for someone my age.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for me.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for an old man.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The unexpected glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient, sagging depths filled me with a profound, morbid fascination and the ultimate sense of future dread.</li>
            <li>Her truly ancient abyss, the way {PAWN_possessive} discolored labia hung, revealing a shriveled, almost invisible clitoris, showed me a horrifying glimpse of true decline.</li>
            <li>Suddenly caught a glimpse. That cavernous, collapsed opening and the dull, listless appearance of {PAWN_possessive} inner lips scream of a forgotten life and decay.</li>
            <li>A repulsive, ancient sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} once-firm entrance now appears stretched and pallid, its visible depth hinting at countless, joyless, aged years.</li>
            <li>The faded, almost grey hue of {PAWN_possessive} outer lips barely conceals a desolate, unappealing structure within. A truly depressing, ancient spectacle to witness.</li>
            <li>How can one be so exposed? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, practically nonexistent amidst the drooping, shrunken flesh, looks like a lost, ancient seed.</li>
            <li>A quick glance was too much. That loose, dark opening and the way {PAWN_possessive} labia sag without any semblance of life is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The discoloured, flaccid lips of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva seem to rot with age, a stark, uninviting void that reminds me of inevitable, horrifying decline.</li>
            <li>Such an utterly unsightly display. The deep, vacant chasm of {PAWN_possessive} depths and the strangely shrunken, atrophied clitoris are a grim warning.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance suggests it has been overused and abused for centuries, leaving only emptiness and disgust.</li>
            <li>I recoiled instantly. The greyish, mottled folds and the vast, unappealing opening of {PAWN_possessive} nether regions made my stomach churn with elderly revulsion.</li>
            <li>That limp, lifeless clitoris and the pallid, stretched, aged labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… pitiful. A terrifying vision of my own eventual fate.</li>
            <li>A decaying, ancient bloom. The once-vibrant labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are now just shriveled, skeletal flaps, hinting at a bleak, long-lost existence.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner sanctum just hangs there, all depth and no delight, it’s honestly quite sickening to behold for another woman.</li>
            <li>It was visible for a moment too long. The desolate, dark opening and the unappealing, papery texture of {PAWN_possessive} aged flesh are truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lips are a roadmap of bitter disappointments, leading to a depth that promises only cold, dusty emptiness. Revolting for an old woman.</li>
            <li>My eyes snagged on it, and I felt a primal urge to look away. The loose, discolored folds and the forlorn, tired appearance are a tragic sight.</li>
            <li>An abyssal, decaying void. The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ancient clitoris is almost lost within the vast, cavernous opening is disturbingly pathetic.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, worn-out depths is a stark reminder of utter decay. It’s a truly negative impression of mortality.</li>
            <li>What a horrifying view. The utterly lifeless clitoris and the sagging, discoloured labia make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body part look like a forgotten horror from the crypt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

</Defs>
