<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
<!--Observing middle aged Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The mature curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is undeniable, a pair of full, soft globes. A truly impressive sight that speaks of experience.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible, swaying gently with every move. Their generous size and soft texture are quite appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts command attention, sitting proudly on {PAWN_objective} chest, with prominent nipples. They possess a delightful, inviting fullness.</li>
            <li>Her substantial breasts, ripe and full, promise a comfortable embrace. They have a certain gravitas and undeniable allure.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge breasts! They look incredibly soft and inviting, a testament to time and maturity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts, spilling from {PAWN_possessive} top. They truly are magnificent.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge breasts, perfectly complementing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure. Their weight suggests a comforting warmth.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, round and firm despite {PAWN_possessive} age, filled me with admiration. What a presence!</li>
            <li>Her impressive chest is a masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have a fascinating presence, suggesting a lifetime of softness and warmth.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts was undeniable. Their generous fullness and the subtle jiggle were captivating.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. They hang with a natural grace, hinting at a comfortable weight and softness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts are perfectly rounded, with a delightful bounce as {PAWN_pronoun} moves. Their substantial presence is truly eye-catching.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom. They were full, soft, and had a comforting, mature appeal.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with a delightful, well-rounded form. The prominent nipples add to their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding. They look incredibly soft to the touch, a captivating sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The gentle sway is mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>My eyes were drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and the visible fullness are quite attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable feature, full and supple. They suggest a wealth of experience and comfort.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex voyer Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, the magnificent sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts! Their ample jiggle and inviting form are a feast for my eyes.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those substantial breasts were revealed. The generous curves and the way they move... truly a voyeur's delight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense chest, with prominent nipples, is quite the spectacle. I can't look away from their captivating presence.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so visible, offering a tantalizing view. I relish in observing their every subtle shift.</li>
            <li>What a glorious pair of huge breasts! Their soft, yielding form is captivating, a truly magnificent display to secretly admire.</li>
            <li>I savored the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts, yearning to see more of their delightful details.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, mature breasts, perfectly displayed. Their sheer volume is a private fascination.</li>
            <li>The sudden, delicious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts filled me with a thrill. What an exquisite sight!</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a private artwork of soft curves and abundant flesh, all for my discerning gaze.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have a fascinating, alluring presence. I could watch them all day.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are a delightful secret.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a tantalizing sway. Their substantial presence is a voyeur's dream.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and so openly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, begging to be admired. They look incredibly soft and touchable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful exhibition of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, private spectacle to feast upon.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts! Such a generous display. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} appreciates my uninhibited appreciation for {PAWN_possessive} visible assets.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are out for all to see. It fills me with joy to witness such a confident display of a mature figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, nipples proudly displayed, is a statement. I feel a kinship with {PAWN_objective} bold presentation.</li>
            <li>Those ripe, full breasts are perfectly exposed. It’s liberating to see such unashamed beauty put on full exhibition.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge, luscious pair of breasts! I thrive on seeing such natural, unapologetic exposure.</li>
            <li>I reveled in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts, openly presented. It’s inspiring to see such freedom.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, mature breasts, shown with confidence. This exhibition delights me!</li>
            <li>The sudden, glorious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, firm breasts thrills me. Such brave, open nudity.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a public artwork of soft curves and abundant flesh, openly shared. How wonderful!</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts, so openly presented, possess a captivating freedom. I adore this visible display.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a beautiful spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating, especially when openly revealed. Their natural hang is magnificent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is a joyous exhibition.</li>
            <li>I was utterly thrilled by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}, openly displayed. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form, brazenly shown. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, openly begging for admiration. They look incredibly soft and touchable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful exhibition of mature femininity, clearly visible. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts, openly displayed. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple, offered for all to see. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe, proudly on show. A truly glorious, public spectacle to feast upon.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Those huge breasts of {PAWN_nameShort} are absolutely intoxicating. I can practically feel their softness; such an irresistible sight!</li>
            <li>Suddenly, her ample breasts were there, swaying with a delightful promise. My desire surges just looking at their generous curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with those ripe nipples, stirs something deep within me. I crave to feel their warmth.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so perfectly visible, beckoning me closer. The sheer size alone is a potent aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, luscious breasts! My body is tingling just imagining their touch. Utterly desirable.</li>
            <li>I feel an intense pull towards {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They promise untold pleasures.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, mature breasts, calling to my every instinct. I must have them.</li>
            <li>The sudden, delicious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts ignites an insatiable hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh, screaming for physical contact.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have an overwhelmingly seductive presence. My entire being yearns for them.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating, sparking a primal urge. Their natural hang is pure temptation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is intensely erotic.</li>
            <li>I was utterly overwhelmed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and screamed for immediate attention.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only amplify my burning desire.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense carnal delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect for worship.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful invitation to unrestrained passion. The subtle movement is arousing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably a turn-on.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple, demanding satisfaction. They promise endless orgasms.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are... quite pronounced. While certainly substantial, such a display is rather overt.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of those large breasts was certainly noticeable. One hopes they are kept more discreetly covered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is undeniably ample, with visible curves. A bit too much, perhaps, for public viewing.</li>
            <li>Her full, ripe breasts are rather... prominent. It feels somewhat improper to observe them so clearly.</li>
            <li>Those are undeniably huge breasts. While admirable in their size, I find their visibility somewhat unsettling.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but register the substantial proportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts. It's... certainly there.</li>
            <li>Those are indeed very large breasts. One might wish for a more modest presentation.</li>
            <li>The sudden revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, mature breasts was quite a sight. A bit more discretion would be appreciated.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is quite apparent. While positively large, it perhaps lacks a certain demureness.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are certainly a feature. They are quite... unmissable.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is indeed striking. A tad too much, for my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, full breasts, swaying freely, are certainly noticeable. Their generous form is rather exposed.</li>
            <li>I was taken aback by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were certainly large, but perhaps too revealing.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an unmistakable form. Their visibility leaves little to the imagination.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, quite substantial. One hopes they are not always so... open to view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a very significant display. Their presence is rather overwhelming.</li>
            <li>My gaze inadvertently fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, prominent breasts. They are undeniably there, and quite significant.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable feature, very ripe and supple. They are rather... conspicuous.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, though perhaps too much so. It’s a very open display.</li>
            <li>Her mature breasts, though large and full, seem rather exposed. It is a bit discomforting.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Whoa, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts! They look so incredibly soft and full, perfectly shaped. I can barely tear my eyes away!</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those massive breasts were right there, jiggling with every step. So ripe and generous, they make me wonder.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with those prominent, inviting nipples, is absolutely captivating. I’ve never seen anything quite like them.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so visible, practically spilling out. They look so warm and yielding, I can almost feel them.</li>
            <li>Damn, what a pair of huge, luscious breasts! They're so big and round, I can’t stop staring at their delightful bounce.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They're so… mature and full, totally mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge breasts, beautifully structured and unbelievably soft-looking. My heart is pounding!</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts has left me speechless. They're amazing!</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a glorious sight of soft curves and abundant flesh. So much to take in, truly stunning.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have an incredible allure. They seem so full of life and warmth.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are surprisingly well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age. They still hold a captivating fullness.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible. The way they softly sway is quite elegant; truly a mature beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with visible nipples, still possesses a delightful form. It's impressive how well {PAWN_pronoun} carries them.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are quite prominent. They show the graceful passage of time while retaining their alluring shape.</li>
            <li>What a pair of truly huge breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a beautiful example of mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noted the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still possess a wonderful shape and alluring fullness.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge breasts, retaining their charm and structure. A good example of how they can age gracefully.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts was surprising. They're surprisingly well-preserved.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a testament to natural beauty, soft curves and abundant flesh that hold up well.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have a fascinating presence, showing a beauty that withstands the years.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are an absolute vision. Their generous curves and mature fullness are incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible, swaying with a tantalizing grace. So full and ripe, a true womanly asset.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with its delightful nipples, is a captivating sight. They hold a profound, seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so openly displayed, beckoning with their soft warmth. They suggest experience and profound pleasure.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, luscious breasts! They feel perfectly proportioned, a testament to magnificent, mature beauty.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They have a settled, inviting presence, truly magnificent.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, mature breasts, perfectly structured and undeniably soft-looking. They truly are impressive.</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts left me admiring. What a prime example of femininity.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a glorious masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out with a confident grace.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have an incredible allure. They seem full of life, hinting at a deep, passionate history.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are quite something. A truly impressive display of mature womanhood, full and well-maintained.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible, swaying softly. A beautiful, generous form that speaks of a woman's journey.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with visible nipples, shows remarkable fullness for {PAWN_possessive} age. A confident and lovely sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are prominent, beautifully shaped. They possess a comforting, experienced air, truly lovely.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge pair of breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a wonderful example of mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still hold a marvelous shape and alluring fullness.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge breasts, retaining their beautiful structure and natural softness. A testament to enduring beauty.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts was quite striking. They're surprisingly well-preserved and charming.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a lovely example of natural beauty, with soft curves and abundant flesh that defy time.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have a fascinating presence, showcasing a beauty that gracefully matures with age.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable, experienced maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable and inspiring.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with genuine confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm and womanly grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are still quite remarkable. Their mature fullness and soft curves are undeniably appealing.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible, swaying gently. A classic, full form that still holds significant charm.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with prominent nipples, still possesses a captivating allure. A beautiful, seasoned sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are openly displayed, suggesting a lifetime of soft comfort. They hold a timeless appeal.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, luscious breasts! They feel perfectly proportioned, a testament to enduring, mature beauty.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They have a settled, inviting presence, truly magnificent.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, mature breasts, perfectly structured and undeniably soft-looking. They still impress greatly.</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts has left me with a profound appreciation.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a glorious masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out with a confident, aged grace.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have an incredible allure. They seem full of life, hinting at a deep, passionate history.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are quite something. A truly impressive display of mature womanhood, full and well-maintained.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample breasts were visible, swaying softly. A beautiful, generous form that speaks of a woman's journey.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, with visible nipples, shows remarkable fullness for {PAWN_possessive} age. A confident and lovely sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are prominent, beautifully shaped. They possess a comforting, experienced air, truly lovely.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge pair of breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a wonderful example of mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still hold a marvelous shape and alluring fullness.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge breasts, retaining their beautiful structure and natural softness. A testament to enduring beauty.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-firm breasts was quite striking. They're surprisingly well-preserved and charming.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a lovely example of natural beauty, with soft curves and abundant flesh that defy time.</li>
            <li>Those huge, mature breasts have a fascinating presence, showcasing a beauty that gracefully matures with age.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable, experienced maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable and inspiring.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with genuine confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm and womanly grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Observing elderly Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, though aged, still possess a grand, comforting presence. Their sheer volume is remarkable.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those vast breasts were visible, settling with a gentle gravity. A testament to a long, full life.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand chest, with its seasoned nipples, emanates a wise, soft presence. Truly a magnificent, aged sight.</li>
            <li>Her truly huge breasts are openly displayed, full of life's experience and softness. They are a profound, comforting sight.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, venerable breasts! They seem perfectly proportioned, a testament to enduring, profound beauty.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They have a settled, warm presence, truly remarkable.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, aged breasts, perfectly structured and undeniably soft-looking. They command respect.</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts has left me with a profound appreciation for their history.</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a glorious masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out with a confident, aged grace.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have an incredible allure. They seem full of life, hinting at a deep, passionate history.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--unisex voyer Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, the magnificent sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, aged breasts! Their ample jiggle and inviting form are a feast for my eyes.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those substantial, venerable breasts were revealed. The generous curves and the way they move... truly a voyeur's delight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense chest, with prominent, seasoned nipples, is quite the spectacle. I can't look away from their captivating presence.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so visible, offering a tantalizing, aged view. I relish in observing their every subtle shift.</li>
            <li>What a glorious pair of huge, elder breasts! Their soft, yielding form is captivating, a truly magnificent display to secretly admire.</li>
            <li>I savored the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts, yearning to see more of their delightful, aged details.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, venerable breasts, perfectly displayed. Their sheer volume is a private fascination.</li>
            <li>The sudden, delicious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts filled me with a thrill. What an exquisite, mature sight!</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a private artwork of soft curves and abundant flesh, all for my discerning gaze.</li>
            <li>Those huge, aged breasts have a fascinating, alluring presence. I could watch them all day.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are a delightful secret.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a tantalizing sway. Their substantial presence is a voyeur's dream.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and so openly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, begging to be admired. They look incredibly soft and touchable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful exhibition of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, private spectacle to feast upon.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts! Such a generous display. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} appreciates my uninhibited appreciation for {PAWN_possessive} visible, seasoned assets.</li>
            <li>Her ample, aged breasts are out for all to see. It fills me with joy to witness such a confident display of a mature figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, nipples proudly displayed, is a statement. I feel a kinship with {PAWN_objective} bold presentation.</li>
            <li>Those ripe, full breasts are perfectly exposed. It’s liberating to see such unashamed, aged beauty put on full exhibition.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge, luscious pair of elder breasts! I thrive on seeing such natural, unapologetic exposure.</li>
            <li>I reveled in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts, openly presented. It’s inspiring to see such freedom in maturity.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, elder breasts, shown with confidence. This exhibition delights me greatly!</li>
            <li>The sudden, glorious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts thrills me. Such brave, open, aged nudity.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a public artwork of soft curves and abundant flesh, openly shared. How wonderful!</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts, so openly presented, possess a captivating freedom. I adore this visible display of a seasoned figure.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a beautiful spectacle of age.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating, especially when openly revealed. Their natural hang is magnificent and wise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is a joyous exhibition of seasoned beauty.</li>
            <li>I was utterly thrilled by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}, openly displayed. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form, brazenly shown. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, openly begging for admiration. They look incredibly soft and touchable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful exhibition of mature femininity, clearly visible. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts, openly displayed. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple, offered for all to see. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe, proudly on show. A truly glorious, public spectacle to feast upon.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Those huge, aged breasts of {PAWN_nameShort} are absolutely intoxicating. I can practically feel their softness; such an irresistible, seasoned sight!</li>
            <li>Suddenly, her ample, elder breasts were there, swaying with a delightful promise. My desire surges just looking at their generous curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with those ripe nipples, stirs something deep within me. I crave to feel their warmth and wisdom.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so perfectly visible, beckoning me closer. The sheer size alone is a potent, aged aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, luscious elder breasts! My body is tingling just imagining their touch. Utterly desirable.</li>
            <li>I feel an intense pull towards {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They promise untold, seasoned pleasures.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, elder breasts, calling to my every instinct. I must have them.</li>
            <li>The sudden, delicious view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts ignites an insatiable hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh, screaming for physical contact.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have an overwhelmingly seductive presence. My entire being yearns for them.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating, sparking a primal urge. Their natural hang is pure temptation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is intensely erotic.</li>
            <li>I was utterly overwhelmed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and screamed for immediate attention.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only amplify my burning desire.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense carnal delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect for worship.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful invitation to unrestrained passion. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably a turn-on.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple, demanding satisfaction. They promise endless orgasms.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are... quite pronounced. While certainly substantial, such an aged display is rather overt.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of those large, aged breasts was certainly noticeable. One hopes they are kept more discreetly covered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is undeniably ample, with visible curves. A bit too much, perhaps, for public viewing, even at that age.</li>
            <li>Her full, ripe breasts are rather... prominent. It feels somewhat improper to observe them so clearly, especially in an elder.</li>
            <li>Those are undeniably huge, aged breasts. While admirable in their size, I find their visibility somewhat unsettling.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but register the substantial proportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts. It's... certainly there, at an advanced age.</li>
            <li>Those are indeed very large, elder breasts. One might wish for a more modest presentation from {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sudden revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, mature breasts was quite a sight. A bit more discretion would be appreciated.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is quite apparent. While positively large, it perhaps lacks a certain demureness for a person of {PAWN_possessive} years.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts are certainly a feature. They are quite... unmissable, even with age.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is indeed striking. A tad too much, for my sensibilities, even from an elder.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, full breasts, swaying freely, are certainly noticeable. Their generous form is rather exposed.</li>
            <li>I was taken aback by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were certainly large, but perhaps too revealing.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an unmistakable form. Their visibility leaves little to the imagination.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, quite substantial. One hopes they are not always so... open to view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a very significant display. Their presence is rather overwhelming.</li>
            <li>My gaze inadvertently fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, prominent breasts. They are undeniably there, and quite significant.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, very ripe and supple. They are rather... conspicuous.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, though perhaps too much so. It’s a very open display.</li>
            <li>Her mature breasts, though large and full, seem rather exposed. It is a bit discomforting.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Wow, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts! They're surprisingly full and have such a comforting, soft appearance. Truly impressive for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those massive, aged breasts were right there, settling with a gentle, experienced sway. So ripe and generous, they’re intriguing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with those prominent, seasoned nipples, is absolutely captivating. A truly grand, mature sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so visible, practically spilling out. They look so warm and yielding, I can almost feel their seasoned softness.</li>
            <li>Damn, what a pair of huge, luscious elder breasts! They're so big and round, I can’t stop staring at their delightful, experienced bounce.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They're so… mature and full, totally mesmerizing, even with age.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, elder breasts, beautifully structured and unbelievably soft-looking. My heart is pounding, despite {PAWN_possessive} age!</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts has left me speechless. They're amazing, full of history!</li>
            <li>Her impressive bosom is a glorious sight of soft curves and abundant flesh. So much to take in, truly stunning, even when aged.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have an incredible allure. They seem so full of life and warmth, promising deep understanding.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts are surprisingly well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age. They still hold a captivating fullness.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample, aged breasts were visible. The way they softly sway is quite elegant; truly a mature beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with visible nipples, still possesses a delightful form. It's impressive how well {PAWN_pronoun} carries them.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are quite prominent. They show the graceful passage of time while retaining their alluring shape.</li>
            <li>What a pair of truly huge, elder breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a beautiful example of mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noted the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still possess a wonderful shape and alluring fullness.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, aged breasts, retaining their charm and structure. A good example of how they can age gracefully.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts was surprising. They're surprisingly well-preserved.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a testament to natural beauty, soft curves and abundant flesh that hold up well.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have a fascinating presence, showing a beauty that withstands the years.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable and inspiring.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm and womanly grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Middle aged male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts are an absolute vision. Their generous curves and seasoned fullness are incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample, aged breasts were visible, swaying with a tantalizing grace. So full and ripe, a true womanly asset, even now.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with its delightful nipples, is a captivating sight. They hold a profound, seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are so openly displayed, beckoning with their soft, aged warmth. They suggest vast experience and profound pleasure.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, luscious elder breasts! They feel perfectly proportioned, a testament to magnificent, enduring beauty.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They have a settled, inviting presence, truly magnificent, defying age.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, elder breasts, perfectly structured and undeniably soft-looking. They truly are impressively aged.</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts left me admiring. What a prime example of enduring femininity.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a glorious masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out with a confident, aged grace.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have an incredible allure. They seem full of life, hinting at a deep, passionate history.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts are quite something. A truly impressive display of aged womanhood, full and well-maintained.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample, aged breasts were visible, swaying softly. A beautiful, generous form that speaks of a woman's long journey.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with visible nipples, shows remarkable fullness for {PAWN_possessive} age. A confident and lovely, seasoned sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are prominent, beautifully shaped. They possess a comforting, experienced air, truly lovely even with age.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge pair of elder breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a wonderful example of enduring, mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still hold a marvelous shape and alluring fullness, defying time.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, aged breasts, retaining their beautiful structure and natural softness. A testament to enduring beauty.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts was quite striking. They're surprisingly well-preserved and charming for {PAWN_possessive} years.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a lovely example of natural beauty, with soft curves and abundant flesh that defy time.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have a fascinating presence, showcasing a beauty that gracefully matures with age.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable, experienced maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable and inspiring.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with genuine confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm and womanly grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, elder breasts are still quite remarkable. Their seasoned fullness and soft curves are undeniably appealing.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those vast, aged breasts were visible, swaying gently. A classic, full form that still holds significant charm, a testament to time.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand chest, with its seasoned nipples, emanates a wise, soft presence. Truly a magnificent, aged sight to behold.</li>
            <li>Her truly huge breasts are openly displayed, full of life's experience and softness. They are a profound, comforting sight, even now.</li>
            <li>What a pair of huge, venerable breasts! They seem perfectly proportioned, a testament to enduring, profound beauty.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generously proportioned breasts. They have a settled, warm presence, truly magnificent, despite their age.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, aged breasts, perfectly structured and undeniably soft-looking. They command respect and appreciation.</li>
            <li>The sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts has left me with a profound appreciation for their history.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a glorious masterpiece of soft curves and abundant flesh. They truly stand out with a confident, aged grace.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have an incredible allure. They seem full of life, hinting at a deep, passionate history.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are utterly spellbinding.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is intensely captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight are so alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is truly overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I was utterly captivated by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and incredibly inviting.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples only heighten their allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, promising immense delight. They look incredibly soft and perfect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is thrilling.</li>
            <li>My gaze was fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They promise endless visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is intensely alluring, soft and ripe. A truly glorious, irresistible target for my desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Huge_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Huge Breasts (Positive)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, elder breasts are quite something. A truly impressive display of aged womanhood, full and well-maintained.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, those ample, aged breasts were visible, swaying softly. A beautiful, generous form that speaks of a woman's long journey.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, venerable chest, with visible nipples, shows remarkable fullness for {PAWN_possessive} age. A confident and lovely, seasoned sight.</li>
            <li>Her ripe, full breasts are prominent, beautifully shaped. They possess a comforting, experienced air, truly lovely even with age.</li>
            <li>What a truly huge pair of elder breasts! They look incredibly soft and natural, a wonderful example of enduring, mature femininity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generously proportioned breasts of {PAWN_nameShort}. They still hold a marvelous shape and alluring fullness, defying time.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously huge, aged breasts, retaining their beautiful structure and natural softness. A testament to enduring beauty.</li>
            <li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous, still-full breasts was quite striking. They're surprisingly well-preserved and charming for {PAWN_possessive} years.</li>
            <li>Her impressive, aged bosom is a lovely example of natural beauty, with soft curves and abundant flesh that defy time.</li>
            <li>Those huge, elder breasts have a fascinating presence, showcasing a beauty that gracefully matures with age.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts were undeniable, freely swaying. The delightful jiggle and generous fullness are a charming spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating. Their natural hang and soft weight suggest comfortable, experienced maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge, full breasts, so perfectly rounded, offer a captivating sway. Their substantial presence is quite remarkable and inspiring.</li>
            <li>I was impressed by the ample bosom of {PAWN_nameShort}. They were ripe, soft, and carried with genuine confidence.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are truly huge, with an exquisite, well-rounded form. The prominent, enticing nipples add to their seasoned allure.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular pair of breasts, full and yielding, retaining their beauty over time. They look incredibly soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly well-endowed, a delightful display of mature femininity. The subtle movement is quite graceful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, beautifully shaped breasts. Their natural curves and visible fullness are undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>Those huge breasts are an undeniable, captivating feature, ripe and supple. They demonstrate enduring charm and womanly grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is impressive, soft and ripe. A truly beautiful sight to behold for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



</Defs>
