<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--general unisex opinion about young female-->
<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>Encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, and it filled me with wonder and excitement.</li>
			<li>Looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina ignites thoughts of endless possibilities.</li>
			<li>I love how {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina captivates my imagination.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand, sweeping opening, a cavernous vagina that seemed to yawn like a chasm of pleasure. </li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, echoing entrance, a massive and imposing center that seemed to reverberate with primal energy. </li>
			<li>I studied {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spacious, capacious shape, a vagina that seemed to stretch the limits of possibility.</li>
			<li>Entranced by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand expanse of {PAWN_possessive} vulval lips, I reveled in the sheer scale of {PAWN_possessive} inviting vaginal entrance.</li>
			<li>I stared ar {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva, I marveled at the bold, prominent contours of {PAWN_possessive} clitoris, a tantalizing gem.</li>
			<li>I gazed in wonder at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, expansive interior, a sensual wonderland waiting to be explored.</li>
			<li>I was awestruck by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grandeur vulva, an enticing landscape of labial folds and inviting mystique.</li>
			<li>I delved into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spacious, welcoming vaginal entrance, its depth and warmth beckoning a seductive dance.</li>
			<li>I admired {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent, enticing clitoris, a prominent beacon radiating energy and desire.</li>
			<li>I was awestruck by the grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva, an enticing landscape of labial folds and inviting mystique.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, a wide, expansive chamber, with a voluptuous, engorged clit, pulsating with an irresistible allure.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive vagina, a vast, inviting orifice, with an ample clit, swollen and tempting, ready for an exciting journey.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spacious vagina, a large, accommodating entrance, with a plump, enticing clit, offering a world of pleasure and sensations.</li>
			<li>I admired {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vagina, a wide, endless chamber, with a voluptuous, engorged clit, a wellspring of pleasure.</li>
			<li>I delighted in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive vagina, a capacious, enticing orifice, with a sizable, enticing clit, an exciting journey.</li>
			<li>I reveled in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, an expansively vast, endlessly intriguing chasm, with an enthralling, captivating clit, a mysterious, exhilarating exploration that left me in awe.</li>
			<li>I admired {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vagina, a profoundly deep, enigmatic abyss, with a mesmerizing, throbbing clit, a bewitching, enchanting voyage that awakened my curiosity and excitement.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} infinite vagina, a boundlessly wide, enticingly mysterious cavern, with a luscious, voluptuous clit, a tempting, alluring enigma that sparked my imagination and longing.</li>
			<li>I beheld {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its shape like a grand, sweeping arch, majestically framed by the surrounding landscape. </li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its appearance like a vast, dark cavern, mysterious and alluring.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its form like a majestic, sweeping valley, awe-inspiring and breathtaking.</li>
			<li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its sight like a swift, sweeping river, dynamic and ever-changing.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its appearance like a mighty, towering mountain range, imposing and majestic.</li>
			<li>I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its shape like a vast, underground lake, serene and mysterious.</li>
            <li>A truly immense opening, hints at incredible depths and an encompassing warmth.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening promises a sublime and all-consuming experience.</li>
            <li>Such generous proportions! It suggests a limitless capacity for pleasure and connection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive entrance is a marvel to behold, hinting at profound internal space.</li>
            <li>The wide, inviting folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, a truly magnificent display of natural anatomy.</li>
            <li>A breathtaking sight, the ample labia part to reveal an impressively deep and welcoming canal.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris, framed by such a grand opening, is an undeniable focal point of desire.</li>
            <li>Its immense size suggests a history of profound experiences, or the promise of many more.</li>
            <li>The soft, yielding tissues within {PAWN_possessive} vast opening hint at a boundless capacity for engulfment.</li>
            <li>I feel drawn into the sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive, grand architecture.</li>
            <li>An awe-inspiring display of breadth and profound potential, {PAWN_possessive} entrance is simply captivating.</li>
            <li>The deep, inviting darkness of {PAWN_possessive} inner folds promises a truly immersive journey.</li>
            <li>Its considerable size is a testament to natural beauty, hinting at untold pleasure within.</li>
            <li>The substantial form of {PAWN_possessive} clitoris perfectly complements the expansive entrance, a symphony of sensation.</li>
            <li>A true marvel of anatomical generosity, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is designed for profound connection.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} vulva expands, revealing such remarkable depth, is utterly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the sheer envelopment promised by such an extraordinarily wide entrance.</li>
            <li>The large, full lips of {PAWN_possessive} vulva part to expose a truly profound and inviting cavity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance is so grand, it truly feels like stepping into another world of sensation.</li>
            <li>The breadth and profound internal space of {PAWN_possessive} form are simply stunning to observe.</li>
            <li>A magnificent specimen of natural design, its deep interior calls to be explored without end.</li>
            <li>The luxurious folds and impressive depth of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy speak of unparalleled pleasure.</li>
            <li>This grand opening seems to whisper of infinite possibilities for shared intimacy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive entrance stirs a deep appreciation for its natural glory.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>

<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, a truly impressive expanse. Reminds me of a boundless horizon, full of promise.</li>
            <li>The grand scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance is quite remarkable; a testament to nature's generosity.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting aperture. It speaks of a generous spirit and welcoming depths.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed. One can appreciate the profound beauty in its size.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample proportions with a nostalgic appreciation for such natural wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, full clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} expansive form.</li>
            <li>Her deep entrance is a beautiful sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to maturity and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, gracefully shaped, hinting at a richness of experience.</li>
            <li>There's a certain timeless beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a lifetime of untold stories and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance evokes a sense of wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive folds, is a beacon of profound pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, beautifully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, my own blood stirs. A potent, mesmerizing sight.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} form promises an engulfing embrace. My old friend is roused.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! My pulse quickens, a familiar tingle spreads.</li>
            <li>The grand architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks a powerful, visceral reaction within me.</li>
            <li>I watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} extensive vulva, a deep longing awakening. My body responds instinctively.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. The sight makes my old cock ache with desire.</li>
            <li>That prominent, throbbing clitoris framed by such immense lips... it's intoxicating. My loins tighten.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My fingers twitch, imagining its cavernous warmth.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; my member strains, aching for its embrace.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon. I feel a familiar surge of anticipation.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space makes my old self remember lost pleasures. A powerful urge rises.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My shaft hardens, eager to explore that endless void.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy fills me with yearning. My cock is ready.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with keen interest. A delightful shiver runs down my spine.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating. My balls tighten.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. My member stands tall, demanding entry.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent hunger. My trousers grow tight.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a primal urge.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful temptation. My old self yearns for that profound abyss.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming. My cock throbs.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. A powerful ache builds.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold. My aged member is drawn to its promise.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination. I am captivated.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. My body remembers, my urges are strong.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My old heart beats faster.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. My hardened cock demands attention.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace. My desire is awakened, strong as ever.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a treat for the eyes, and a torment for my impatient body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>What a magnificent entrance! It's truly a grand, welcoming sight, full of potential.</li>
            <li>The scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is quite impressive; a strong, beautiful feature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, generous form. It speaks of vitality and a deep, profound nature.</li>
            <li>A beautiful, expansive gateway. One can appreciate the natural beauty in its generous proportions.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample vulva with a knowing appreciation for its natural form.</li>
            <li>The substantial labia frame an astonishingly deep and inviting pathway.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant, focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep entrance is a lovely sight, hinting at unexplored warmth and profound possibilities.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to natural design.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, beautifully shaped, hinting at a richness of being and experience.</li>
            <li>There's a certain mature beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise deep comfort and a truly embracing connection.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a lifetime of untold stories and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance evokes a sense of wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive folds, is a beacon of profound pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, beautifully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Whoa, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is huge! I can practically get lost in there.</li>
            <li>That's a seriously massive entrance. Makes me wonder what kind of adventures lie within.</li>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} got some serious depth. I'd love to find out how far it goes.</li>
            <li>Her enormous lips and deep folds are incredibly hot. My cock is already twitching.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is driving me wild. What a sight!</li>
            <li>A vast, inviting space. My mind races with all the possibilities for fun.</li>
            <li>That prominent clitoris and those expansive lips? Pure perfection. I'm captivated.</li>
            <li>The generous opening is just asking to be explored. I'm feeling a powerful urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deep well looks like it could swallow me whole, and I'd love it.</li>
            <li>Her immense size is incredibly arousing. I can't stop staring.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly enthralled by the sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy.</li>
            <li>The wide, welcoming cavern promises an unforgettable ride. I'm getting hard just thinking about it.</li>
            <li>This grand opening is a dream come true. So much space for pleasure.</li>
            <li>The way her labia spread to reveal such depth is absolutely mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel myself disappearing into that glorious, vast abyss.</li>
            <li>That plump, engorged clitoris, presented by such a monumental entrance... irresistible.</li>
            <li>Her ample proportions are unbelievably sexy. I want to dive right in.</li>
            <li>This is what I call a proper opening. Boundless possibilities for ecstasy.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva has me utterly transfixed.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark folds are calling to me. I need to experience that.</li>
            <li>I'm completely drawn to the immense size and inviting nature of {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>The expansive entry is making my blood rush. I'm ready to lose myself in there.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! The depth and width are simply stunning.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} lips are so full and spread open... incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>I've never seen such a magnificent, accommodating opening. My cock is throbbing.</li>
            <li>This grand chasm is truly magnificent. I can already taste the pleasure.</li>
            <li>The wide, deep entrance is driving me insane with desire.</li>
            <li>Just looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness makes my head spin. So many delights.</li>
            <li>Her impressive size is a challenge I'm more than willing to accept.</li>
            <li>That perfectly plump clitoris nestled within such a huge opening? Game on.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is a feast for my eyes. Utterly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>I am captivated by the sheer expanse of {PAWN_possessive} intimate landscape; a true voyeuristic delight.</li>
            <li>Such a generous, inviting chasm. My gaze lingers, absorbing every detail.</li>
            <li>The grand architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body is a breathtaking sight. I could watch all day.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with an intense, quiet pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. Every curve and fold is a masterpiece to behold.</li>
            <li>That prominent, inviting clitoris, framed by such immense lips... it's intoxicating to witness.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My imagination runs wild with its secrets.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent spectacle; I feel a deep, appreciative thrill.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, drawing me into a world of beauty.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is a perfect subject for my contemplation.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. I am entranced by its endless allure.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with keen, unblinking interest.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. Every hidden recess is a discovery.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent fascination within me.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a burning curiosity.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery. I yearn to understand its full extent.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming to witness.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a spectacle unlike any other.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, yet inspires so much.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. I find myself lost in its profound beauty.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a fascinating study. I feel a pull to its mystery.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my voyeuristic appreciation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, my cock stirs. A potent, mesmerizing sight.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} form promises an engulfing embrace. My member is roused.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! My pulse quickens, a familiar tingle spreads through my groin.</li>
            <li>The grand architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks a powerful, visceral reaction within me.</li>
            <li>I watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} extensive vulva, a deep longing awakening. My body responds instinctively.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. The sight makes my cock ache with desire.</li>
            <li>That prominent, throbbing clitoris framed by such immense lips... it's intoxicating. My loins tighten.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My fingers twitch, imagining its cavernous warmth.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; my member strains, aching for its embrace.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon. I feel a familiar surge of anticipation in my shaft.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space makes my mind race with perverse thoughts. A powerful urge rises.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My shaft hardens, eager to explore that endless void.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy fills me with yearning. My cock is ready.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with keen interest. A delightful shiver runs down my spine.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating. My balls tighten.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. My member stands tall, demanding entry.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent hunger. My trousers grow tight.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a primal urge.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful temptation. My old self yearns for that profound abyss.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming. My cock throbs.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. A powerful ache builds in my groin.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold. My aged member is drawn to its promise.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination. I am captivated.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. My body remembers, my urges are strong and my cock is hard.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and my cock responds.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. My hardened cock demands attention.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill. My trousers strain.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace. My desire is awakened, strong as ever, and my cock feels heavy.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a treat for the eyes, and a torment for my impatient, throbbing cock.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, my own depths stir. A potent, mesmerizing sight.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} form promises an engulfing embrace. My core tingles.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! My pulse quickens, a familiar warmth spreads.</li>
            <li>The grand architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks a powerful, visceral reaction within me.</li>
            <li>I watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} extensive vulva, a deep longing awakening. My body responds instinctively.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. The sight makes my own sex ache with desire.</li>
            <li>That prominent, throbbing clitoris framed by such immense lips... it's intoxicating. My loins tighten.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My fingers twitch, imagining its cavernous warmth.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; my own clitoris strains, aching for its embrace.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon. I feel a familiar surge of anticipation.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space makes my own body yearn for connection. A powerful urge rises.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My core clenches, eager to explore that endless void.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy fills me with yearning. My sex is ready.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with keen interest. A delightful shiver runs down my spine.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating. My nipples harden.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. Every hidden recess is a discovery.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent hunger. My inner thigh clenches.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a primal urge.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful temptation. My own sex yearns for that profound abyss.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming. My vulva throbs.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. A powerful ache builds in my core.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold. My own desire is drawn to its promise.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination. I am captivated.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. My body remembers, my urges are strong and my sex feels alive.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and my sex responds.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. My inner depths ache with anticipation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill. My core stirs.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace. My desire is awakened, strong as ever, and my clitoris feels swollen.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a treat for the eyes, and a torment for my impatient, throbbing sex.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is simply breathtaking! What a magnificent display of natural beauty.</li>
            <li>The sheer expanse of {PAWN_possessive} body is a true work of art. I'd love to show off alongside {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It makes me want to reveal my own intimate parts.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core is inspiring. A truly exhibition-worthy form.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with a shared sense of pride in our forms.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I feel an urge to highlight my own generous assets.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... it's a spectacle!</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless, making me want to share my own openness.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; it encourages me to let it all hang out.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, making me feel so free.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is a perfect mirror for my own desire to be seen.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. I'm compelled to celebrate and reveal myself fully.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to emulate.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an admiring gaze, feeling the urge to participate.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and makes me want to show off.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. It inspires me to be equally bold and open.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent desire to be seen in my own glory.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a burning desire to display.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery. It makes me want to strip bare.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, and makes me want to undress.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. It truly highlights the beauty of natural form.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me eager to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and I approve.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. It makes me want to offer my own intimate view.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my gaze, and I feel the urge to match it.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and I feel compelled to exhibit.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It urges me to cast off all inhibitions.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and the desire to expose myself.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and it makes me want to share.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my exhibitionistic appreciation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is simply breathtaking! My own cock stirs in appreciation.</li>
            <li>The sheer expanse of {PAWN_possessive} body is a true work of art. I'd love to show off my own shaft alongside {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It makes me want to reveal my own intimate parts to {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core is inspiring. A truly exhibition-worthy form, like mine!</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with a shared sense of pride in our forms. My cock is throbbing.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I feel an urge to highlight my own generous assets, especially my cock.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... it's a spectacle! My member is rigid.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless, making me want to share my own openness, and my stiff cock.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; it encourages me to let my own cock hang out.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, making me feel so free, and my cock so alive.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is a perfect mirror for my own desire to be seen. My shaft is twitching.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. I'm compelled to celebrate and reveal myself fully, including my throbbing member.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to bare myself to.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an admiring gaze, feeling the urge to participate with my own cock.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and makes me want to show off my erection.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. It inspires me to be equally bold and open with my own impressive tool.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent desire to be seen in my own glory. My cock is ready.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a burning desire to display my own manhood.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery. It makes me want to strip bare and show my throbbing cock.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, and makes me want to undress and display.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. It truly highlights the beauty of natural form, and mine!</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me eager to reveal myself, and my eager cock.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and I approve. My cock agrees.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. It makes me want to offer my own intimate view, especially my hard cock.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my gaze, and I feel the urge to match it with my own.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and I feel compelled to exhibit my own pleasure.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It urges me to cast off all inhibitions and show my full glory.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and the desire to expose my pulsing cock.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and it makes me want to share my impressive size.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my exhibitionistic appreciation, and makes me want to show my arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is simply breathtaking! My own depths stir in appreciation.</li>
            <li>The sheer expanse of {PAWN_possessive} body is a true work of art. I'd love to show off my own vulva alongside {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It makes me want to reveal my own intimate parts to {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core is inspiring. A truly exhibition-worthy form, like mine!</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with a shared sense of pride in our forms. My clitoris is tingling.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I feel an urge to highlight my own generous assets.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... it's a spectacle! My own lips are wet.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless, making me want to share my own openness, and my wetness.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; it encourages me to let my own labia spread.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, making me feel so free, and so ready to display.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is a perfect mirror for my own desire to be seen. My core is tingling.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. I'm compelled to celebrate and reveal myself fully, including my own inviting depths.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to bare myself to.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an admiring gaze, feeling the urge to participate with my own body.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and makes me want to show off my own arousal.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. It inspires me to be equally bold and open with my own impressive form.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent desire to be seen in my own glory. My vulva is ready.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites a burning desire to display my own womanhood.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery. It makes me want to strip bare and show my own wetness.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, and makes me want to undress and display my sex.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. It truly highlights the beauty of natural form, and mine!</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me eager to reveal myself, and my eager sex.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and I approve. My own body wants to be seen.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. It makes me want to offer my own intimate view, especially my open labia.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my gaze, and I feel the urge to match it with my own.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and I feel compelled to exhibit my own pleasure.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It urges me to cast off all inhibitions and show my full glory.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and the desire to expose my pulsing clitoris.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and it makes me want to share my impressive size.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my exhibitionistic appreciation, and makes me want to show my arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is exhilarating! I want to lose myself in that boundless expanse.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} body makes my own senses reel. I need to be inside {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It ignites an insatiable hunger within me.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks an intense, burning desire.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with an overwhelming urge for release.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I can't think of anything but plunging into those depths.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... I'm trembling with desire.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My body aches for its profound embrace.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; I'm consumed by the need to feel its warmth.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, driving me to the brink of desperation.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is an unbearable temptation. I must have it.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My entire being craves to be enveloped within.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to conquer.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an all-consuming lust.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and completely maddening.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. My thoughts are consumed by ravishing it.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent, undeniable craving.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites an unbearable ache.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery, and I must plumb its every secret immediately.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, I can barely breathe.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. I feel a frantic need.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me utterly desperate for satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and fuels my fiery passion.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. I dream of being lost inside its depths forever.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my lust-filled gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My entire body hums with electric anticipation.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It compels me towards immediate gratification.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and an unstoppable urge.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and I must possess it now.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my boundless appetite for pleasure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is exhilarating! My cock is throbbing to lose itself in that boundless expanse.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} body makes my own senses reel. I need to be inside {PAWN_objective} now.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It ignites an insatiable hunger within me, and my member responds.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks an intense, burning desire. My cock is hard.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with an overwhelming urge for release. My balls ache.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I can't think of anything but plunging my cock into those depths.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... I'm trembling with desire, my shaft pulsating.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My body aches for its profound embrace. My cock demands entry.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; I'm consumed by the need to feel my cock inside its warmth.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, driving me to the brink of desperation. My erection is painful.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is an unbearable temptation. I must plunge my cock into it immediately.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My entire being craves to be enveloped within. My cock is begging.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to conquer with my cock.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an all-consuming lust. My cock is rock hard.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and completely maddening. My shaft is twitching.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. My thoughts are consumed by ravishing it with my cock.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent, undeniable craving. My trousers are too tight.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites an unbearable ache in my balls.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery, and I must plumb its every secret immediately with my cock.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, I can barely breathe, my cock is exploding.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. I feel a frantic need to thrust inside.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me utterly desperate for satisfaction. My cock demands it.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and fuels my fiery passion. My cock is immense.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. I dream of plunging my cock inside its depths forever.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my lust-filled gaze. My cock is vibrating.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My entire body hums with electric anticipation, especially my throbbing cock.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It compels me towards immediate gratification with my throbbing member.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and an unstoppable urge to penetrate.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and I must possess it now with my entire cock.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my boundless appetite for pleasure, and my unyielding cock.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening is exhilarating! My own depths are throbbing to lose themselves in that boundless expanse.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} body makes my own senses reel. I need to be inside {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, inviting chasm! It ignites an insatiable hunger within me, and my clitoris responds.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core sparks an intense, burning desire. My vulva is wet.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with an overwhelming urge for release. My core aches.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. I can't think of anything but embracing those depths.</li>
            <li>That prominent, alluring clitoris, framed by such immense lips... I'm trembling with desire, my own clitoris pulsating.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless. My body aches for its profound embrace. My sex demands entry.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; I'm consumed by the need to feel its warmth, mimicking my own.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon, driving me to the brink of desperation. My arousal is intense.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space is an unbearable temptation. I must explore it immediately.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. My entire being craves to be enveloped within. My sex is begging.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, and to share.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with an all-consuming lust. My own sex is throbbing.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, and completely maddening. My inner thighs are wet.</li>
            <li>A glorious, gaping maw. My thoughts are consumed by intimate union with it.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a potent, undeniable craving. My own core clenches.</li>
            <li>That full, engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, ignites an unbearable ache within my own body.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery, and I must plumb its every secret immediately with my own touch.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming, I can barely breathe, my own body is on fire.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. I feel a frantic need to intertwine.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, making me utterly desperate for shared satisfaction. My sex demands it.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and fuels my fiery passion. My own body wants to merge.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. I dream of being lost inside its depths forever, alongside my own.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my lust-filled gaze. My own arousal is intense.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My entire body hums with electric anticipation, especially my own wetness.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call. It compels me towards immediate gratification. My sex is ready.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, illicit thrill, and an unstoppable urge to connect.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel, and I must join it now with my entire being.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my boundless appetite for pleasure, and my own insatiable desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grand opening radiates a beautiful, gentle warmth. Truly a comforting sight.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} body appears so welcoming and inviting. A lovely natural form.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, accommodating chasm. It seems to offer boundless comfort and acceptance.</li>
            <li>The magnificent architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate core is a tender, beautiful sight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast vulva fills me with a feeling of gentle appreciation.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental entrance. It seems to hold so much gentle possibility and understanding.</li>
            <li>That prominent, gentle clitoris, framed by such immense lips... it's a truly soft and inviting beauty.</li>
            <li>The depths revealed are simply boundless, promising a deep, tender connection.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is a magnificent sight; it evokes a feeling of peaceful acceptance.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding folds of {PAWN_possessive} vulva beckon with a soft, comforting allure.</li>
            <li>This vast, inviting space feels so gentle and open, like a warm embrace.</li>
            <li>Such profound depth and width. It radiates a sense of quiet strength and profound warmth.</li>
            <li>The graceful, generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is a joy to behold, radiating kindness.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal with a gentle, appreciative gaze.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such deep potential, is utterly captivating, in a soft, tender way.</li>
            <li>A glorious, welcoming maw. It inspires a feeling of deep comfort and acceptance.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body stirs a tender admiration within me.</li>
            <li>That full, gently engorged clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, radiates gentle beauty.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is a beautiful mystery, suggesting a boundless capacity for kindness.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those expansive folds, is almost overwhelming with its gentle invitation.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. It's so wonderfully soft.</li>
            <li>This grand, sweeping entrance is a sight to behold, radiating an undeniable sense of nurturing.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves nothing to the imagination, and is simply beautiful.</li>
            <li>Such a warm, enveloping chasm. It feels like a safe, comforting haven.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is simply irresistible to my gaze, radiating soft appeal.</li>
            <li>A truly astonishing display of natural capacity. My eyes drink in every detail, and feel a deep compassion.</li>
            <li>Her deep, dark entrance is a siren's call of gentle allure. It is profoundly beautiful.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening fills me with a delicious, peaceful warmth.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace just by looking. It's a true marvel of gentle design.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is a perfect subject for my kind and appreciative gaze.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Alright, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is quite large. Can't deny that, I suppose.</li>
            <li>That's a rather... ample display. Not something one sees every day, thankfully.</li>
            <li>It's certainly big. A bit much, if you ask me, but it's there.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale is unavoidable. It's... a lot to take in.</li>
            <li>Well, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is undeniably spacious. Can't argue with size.</li>
            <li>An uncomfortably grand entrance, but undeniably striking in its own way.</li>
            <li>That clitoris is quite prominent, given the overall size. Hard to ignore.</li>
            <li>The depth is evident. More than I usually prefer to observe, honestly.</li>
            <li>Her substantial opening is... impactful. One must acknowledge its presence.</li>
            <li>Those wide folds are quite... open. A bit too much for polite company, perhaps.</li>
            <li>This vast space is certainly noticeable. One simply cannot overlook it.</li>
            <li>Profound depth and width. It is what it is, I suppose.</li>
            <li>The generous sweep of {PAWN_possessive} intimate anatomy is... a statement.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive portal. Yes, it's quite there.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia part, revealing such depth... it's a lot.</li>
            <li>A very open maw. It certainly gets one's attention, for better or worse.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body is... impressive, if overwhelming.</li>
            <li>That full clitoris, presented by such a grand opening, is certainly visible.</li>
            <li>Her endless cavity is... quite a thing to behold, I guess.</li>
            <li>The promise of total immersion, within those folds, is almost unsettling.</li>
            <li>I am confronted by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breadth and profound depth. It's... certainly present.</li>
            <li>This grand entrance is quite the sight, though perhaps unnecessarily so.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_possessive} inner form leaves little to the imagination.</li>
            <li>Such an enveloping chasm. It's rather… overt.</li>
            <li>The well-defined architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} core is... distinct.</li>
            <li>An astonishing display of natural capacity. Not exactly subtle, is it?</li>
            <li>Her deep entrance is... undeniable. Very much there.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boundless opening is... certainly vivid.</li>
            <li>I can sense the expansive embrace. It's certainly a statement piece.</li>
            <li>This grand, open display is... certainly something.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine opening, a grand, powerful expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} horse-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, robust chasm, echoing the strength of a mare. It's captivating.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like a stallion's stride.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, equine proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost muscular labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, horse-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, powerful entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and immense strength.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to equine beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, robustly shaped, hinting at a richness of experience akin to wild plains.</li>
            <li>There's a certain raw beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, equine anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely powerful.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying equine grace.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, horse-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a primal strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine entrance evokes a sense of wild wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, untamed femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, robust folds, is a beacon of profound, earthy pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a deep stable.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, equine region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its horse-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of primal power.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, equine anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a mare's embrace.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, powerfully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its horse-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and free.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine opening, a grand, loyal expanse, fills me with curiosity.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} dog-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, eager chasm, echoing the devotion of a loyal hound. It's captivating.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like a dog's playful stance.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, canine proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost muscular labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, dog-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, loyal entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and profound comfort.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to canine beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, robustly shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a comforting den.</li>
            <li>There's a certain earnest beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, canine anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely devoted.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying canine affection.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, dog-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a loyal strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine entrance evokes a sense of wild wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, devoted femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, loyal folds, is a beacon of profound, earthy pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a warm burrow.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, canine region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its dog-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of devoted warmth.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, canine anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a dog's devoted embrace.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, powerfully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its dog-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and free.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline opening, a grand, alluring expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} cat-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, elegant chasm, echoing the grace of a feline. It's captivating.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like a cat's leisurely stretch.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, feline proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost lithe labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, cat-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, mysterious entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and hidden pleasures.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to feline beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, sleekly shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a plush cushion.</li>
            <li>There's a certain subtle beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, feline anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely soft.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying feline charm.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, cat-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a luxurious softness and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline entrance evokes a sense of wild wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, graceful femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, soft folds, is a beacon of profound, sensual pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a purring cat.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, feline region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its cat-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of playful mystery.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, feline anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a cat's contented stretch.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, sleekly formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its cat-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and free.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic opening, a grand, infernal expanse, fills me with awe.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} demon-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unholy chasm, echoing the abyss. It's captivating in its dark majesty.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like the maw of a dark realm.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, demonic proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost burning labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, demon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, infernal entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and dark pleasures.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to demonic beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, infernally shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a forbidden shrine.</li>
            <li>There's a certain dark beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, demonic anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely powerful and illicit.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying demonic allure.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, demon-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a dark strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic entrance evokes a sense of forbidden wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, unholy femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, fiery folds, is a beacon of profound, hellish pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a demon's embrace.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped and darkly inviting.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, demonic region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed and infernal allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its demon-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of dark magic.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, demonic anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a succubus's kiss.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, powerfully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited to dark desires.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its demon-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and infernal.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, unholy allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic opening, a grand, mighty expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} dragon-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to ancient nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, powerful chasm, echoing a dragon's lair. It's captivating in its scale.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like the maw of a vast cavern.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, draconic proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost scaled labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, dragon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, ancient entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and immense power.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to draconic beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, powerfully shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a dragon's hoard.</li>
            <li>There's a certain primal beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, draconic anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely vast.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying draconic majesty.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, dragon-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at an ancient strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic entrance evokes a sense of mythical wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, powerful femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, scaled folds, is a beacon of profound, legendary pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a dragon's fire.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped and primordial.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, draconic region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed, and legendary allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its dragon-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of ancient magic.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, draconic anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a dragon's embrace.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, powerfully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited to immense power.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its dragon-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and mythical.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, ancient allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glistening opening, a grand, fluid expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} slime-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, malleable chasm, echoing a shifting pool. It's captivating in its fluidity.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like the maw of a vast, viscous cave.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, gelatinous proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost flowing labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, slime-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, slick entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and profound malleability.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to fluid beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, yielding and expansive, hinting at a richness of experience, like a living pool.</li>
            <li>There's a certain ethereal beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, gelatinous anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely adaptable.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying fluid allure.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, slime-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a yielding strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous entrance evokes a sense of amorphous wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, flowing femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, glistening folds, is a beacon of profound, fluid pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like warm goo.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped and shifting.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, gelatinous region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed, and flowing allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its slime-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of viscous mystery.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, gelatinous anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a soft, yielding embrace.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, fluidly formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited to seamless pleasure.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its slime-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and liquid.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, fluid allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine opening, a grand, earthy expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} pig-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, robust chasm, echoing the abundance of a sow. It's captivating.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like a pig's contented sprawl.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, porcine proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost plump labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed clitoris is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, pig-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, fertile entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and immense pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to porcine beauty and potential.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, richly shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a bountiful feast.</li>
            <li>There's a certain hearty beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, porcine anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely earthy.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying piggish delight.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, pig-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at a hearty strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine entrance evokes a sense of rustic wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, unpretentious femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent clitoris, nestled within those expansive, soft folds, is a beacon of profound, earthy pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a full trough.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, porcine region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its pig-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of warm, farm-like comfort.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, porcine anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a pig's satisfied grunt.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, robustly formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its pig-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and abundant.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed clitoris, is a harmonious display of unique, natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Positive_Cavernous_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Positive) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid opening, a grand, chitinous expanse, fills me with fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_possessive} insect-like form is quite remarkable; a testament to unique nature.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, segmented chasm, echoing a hive. It's captivating in its alien beauty.</li>
            <li>A magnificent gateway, gracefully framed and impressively broad, like the maw of an insect queen.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, insectoid proportions with curious appreciation for its unique wonder.</li>
            <li>The substantial, almost rigid labia unfold to reveal an astonishingly deep and inviting path.</li>
            <li>A prominent, well-formed ovipositor is evident, a vibrant focal point within {PAWN_possessive} magnificent, insect-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her deep, alien entrance is a striking sight, hinting at unexplored caverns of warmth and immense potential for life.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_possessive} opening is captivating; a true testament to insectoid beauty and purpose.</li>
            <li>It’s a grand valley, strangely shaped, hinting at a richness of experience, like a hidden nest.</li>
            <li>There's a certain primal beauty in the generous expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, insectoid anatomy.</li>
            <li>The spacious inner folds promise profound comfort and a deep, embracing connection, uniquely biological.</li>
            <li>A remarkable sight, the wide and welcoming nature of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is truly captivating, embodying insectoid grace.</li>
            <li>I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, insect-like vulva, appreciating the magnificent expanse and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, deep opening, hints at an ancient strength and profound experiences.</li>
            <li>The sheer grandeur of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid entrance evokes a sense of primal wonder and admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to abundant, primal femininity, gracefully proportioned and deeply alluring.</li>
            <li>The prominent ovipositor, nestled within those expansive, chitinous folds, is a beacon of profound, alien pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent cavity, its depths suggest boundless comfort and endless delight, like a living hive.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} anatomy unfolds reveals an impressive inner vastness, uniquely shaped and biologically compelling.</li>
            <li>I admire the mature, full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate, insectoid region; a truly developed beauty.</li>
            <li>This generous opening speaks volumes about her innate capacity for deep connection, a wild, untamed, and biological allure.</li>
            <li>A striking natural wonder, its insect-like size is both impressive and profoundly appealing.</li>
            <li>The wide, embracing lips and deep inner space are undeniably alluring, with a hint of primal, ancient instinct.</li>
            <li>One can only appreciate the vast potential for intimacy in such a profound, insectoid anatomical display.</li>
            <li>The ample entrance, a generous opening, promises profound warmth and ultimate fulfillment, like a queen's embrace.</li>
            <li>It's a grand chamber, powerfully formed, suggesting a deep and satisfying embrace, uniquely suited to natural urges.</li>
            <li>A sweeping vista of intimacy, its insect-like size implies boundless emotional and physical depth.</li>
            <li>The mature contours of {PAWN_possessive} vulva are captivating, revealing a rich inner landscape, wild and instinctual.</li>
            <li>This expansive opening, with its well-formed ovipositor, is a harmonious display of unique, natural allure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>