<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--general unisex opinion about young female-->
<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>Noticing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina, I couldn’t help but smirk at its lack of room for anything.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unyielding vagina that was too tight, with a cold and unapproachable demeanor.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} narrow and restrictive opening that was off-putting, with a harsh and uninviting texture.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite vagina that was unappealingly tight, with a puckered and unattractive exterior.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was stretched too tight, like a drumhead, with a cold and unapproachable demeanor.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} narrow, constricted opening that was more like a chokepoint than a vagina, with a rough and uninviting texture.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite vagina that was unappealingly pinched, with a puckered and unattractive exterior that seemed to be sucking everything in.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina with suspicion, the snug size was a daunting obstacle, a narrow and uninviting passage. I inspected with unease, the cramped space was a deterrent, a closed and unwelcoming chamber.</li>
			<li>I glanced {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina with reluctance, the confined area was a discouragement, a narrow and restrictive cavity, barely-there vaginal passage. It was as if it were trying to reject any advances, a fortress built to protect it from the vile act of intercourse.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina, the labia pressed together like a pair of shy lips. The clitoris, while present, was small and unassuming. The depth seemed limited, but I couldn't help but feel a twinge of unease at the thought of entering such a snug space.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} narrow entrance, almost frightening in its restrictiveness. The labia were pursed shut, and the clitoris, though larger than the micro, seemed to retreat in fear. It struck me as unnatural, even wrong.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted entrance, a narrow slit that seemed to pinch itself shut. The texture was smooth and unyielding, the clitoris a small, stubborn nub. Depth was a luxury it couldn't afford.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pinched portal, a pursed opening that seemed to protest its own existence. The texture was taut and unforgiving, the clitoris a tiny, unyielding bulge. It was a sight that made me shudder.</li>
			<li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} restricted passage, a narrow, sinuous path that seemed to wind its way into darkness. The texture was sleek and unyielding, the clitoris a small, insistent protrusion. It was a sight that made me uneasy.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cramped aperture, a tight, puckered mouth that seemed to suck itself dry. The texture was thin and unyielding, the clitoris a small, petulant knot. It was a disappointing spectacle.</li>
			<li>I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constrained divide, a narrow, pinched cleft that seemed to strangle itself. The texture was smooth and unrelenting, the clitoris a tiny, unyielding bump. It was a pitiful sight.</li>
			<li>I beheld {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} narrow, slit-like opening, a mere fissure in the skin. The texture was fine and unyielding, the clitoris a small, almost imperceptible nub. It was a strange, unsettling sight.</li>
			<li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tightly sealed entrance was a stark reminder of its inaccessibility, a truly uninviting prospect.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips were almost fused, a harsh line across her crotch. Truly, a repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted labia, a puckered, shriveled opening that suggested nothing but discomfort.</li>
            <li>A meager aperture, barely more than a scratch, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to mock any attempt at entry.</li>
            <li>Its smallness was alarming; the almost non-existent depth made me question its very function.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina presented a grim, unyielding slit, a stark, joyless portal.</li>
            <li>The rigid, unyielding texture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia spoke of a cold, unwilling embrace.</li>
            <li>A truly unappealing specimen: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a pinched, ungenerous opening.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} taut, unyielding lips, a grim barrier to any pleasure.</li>
            <li>It was a tight, uninviting crevice, utterly lacking in appeal or promise.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy was dishearteningly small, almost non-existent.</li>
            <li>A deeply disappointing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted entrance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to actively resist exploration, a truly off-putting sight.</li>
            <li>Such a cramped and unwelcoming passage; I felt a distinct aversion.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely discernible amidst the tightly compressed folds.</li>
            <li>Its appearance suggested a painful, unyielding experience.</li>
            <li>I felt a shudder of revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unpleasantly tight form.</li>
            <li>A truly pathetic excuse for a vagina, so tight and unyielding.</li>
            <li>The narrowness was almost comical, a tiny, unwelcoming crevice.</li>
            <li>Its rigid appearance promised nothing but discomfort and frustration.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Such a small thing, barely a crevice; a far cry from the generous proportions I recall from my youth.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina, its labia tightly pressed, almost hostile. It reminded me of a withered flower, past its prime before it even blossomed.</li>
            <li>Too small. The outer lips seemed to fuse, leaving only a hint of a clitoris. A disappointing sight, indeed.</li>
            <li>A constricted opening, no real depth. It's a shame, so little to appreciate.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't bother. That tightness suggests nothing but trouble and a lack of proper use.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance was a pinched, uninviting slit. A meager offering, hardly worth a second glance.</li>
            <li>It was startlingly shallow, a mere dimple where there should be depth. Youth wasted, I suppose.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina speaks volumes about its unyielding nature. Disappointing.</li>
            <li>I've seen wider mouths on babies. This one looks like it's never been used, or certainly not enjoyed.</li>
            <li>A truly unappealing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina. No warmth, no welcome.</li>
            <li>Her labia were thin, almost chapped, clinging together tightly. It looked painful.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was lost in the tight folds, barely visible. Such a waste of potential.</li>
            <li>It just looked… closed. As if it had never truly opened, nor ever would.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding passage. It's a sad sight for a young woman.</li>
            <li>I recall times when such a sight would have enticed me, but this offers nothing but a grim, unyielding wall.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as tight as a miser's purse. Uninviting.</li>
            <li>It's a peculiar sight, so small and unyielding for someone so young. A true shame.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggested a complete lack of experience or pleasure. Pity.</li>
            <li>Her vagina seemed to be actively shrinking, an unappealing, almost desperate tightness.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. I've known more accommodating keyholes.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. No allure whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything but discomfort.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a wound that's healed too tightly. Unpleasant.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in a tight, unappealing crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in desert rocks. This is just... restrictive.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. I've no patience for such lack of enthusiasm.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Such a tight little thing, a challenge perhaps, but my old cock knows how to make its mark, even on this unyielding aperture.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, the labia a thin, uninviting line. It looked like it would shatter rather than yield, a frustrating prospect even for my seasoned member.</li>
            <li>That tiny opening; a puzzle, a perverse tease. My hardened shaft twitched, imagining the desperate struggle.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure. It makes my own old friend stiffen, just contemplating the sheer impossibility of it.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth of that young one's hole fills me with a twisted desire to force my way in. My loins ache with wicked intent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina, a grim little keyhole. It stirs a cruel amusement within me, a perverse challenge for my aged instrument.</li>
            <li>The sight of that barely-there opening, so unyielding and defiant. My ancient cock hardens, yearning to stretch it beyond its limits.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris, a tiny, almost hidden nub within those unforgiving folds. It makes me want to make it swell, to make her regret such tightness.</li>
            <li>A truly unappealing, almost repulsive tightness. Yet, a part of me, my very core, yearns to prove it wrong, to split it open.</li>
            <li>That young, unyielding entrance, it's a perverse invitation to dominate. My old prick throbs with a grim determination.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled, tight vagina. My own member, however, did not flinch from the challenge; it pulsed with a renewed, grim interest.</li>
            <li>The puckered opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looks like a virgin's tight rosebud. My old shaft yearns to bloom within it.</li>
            <li>A tantalizingly tiny entrance; it sends a perverse jolt through my aging loins, a craving for domination.</li>
            <li>The raw, unyielding nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight slit fuels a dark satisfaction within me. My member stirs.</li>
            <li>Her vagina, a miser's vault. It makes my old cock ache with the desire to crack it open and claim its contents.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive crevice, a defiant barrier. My cock, old as it is, feels a perverse thrill at the thought of conquering it.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} painfully tight opening awakens a cruel interest within me. My member is stirred to a challenge.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the resistance from that small, unyielding hole. My desires are ignited, a grim determination to penetrate.</li>
            <li>A tight, unwelcoming abyss. Yet, a part of me, a dark, primal urge, wishes to plunge deep within.</li>
            <li>The unyielding labia, a clenched fist. My own flesh responds, a cruel anticipation for the inevitable violation.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy screams 'no', but my lust whispers 'yes'. My cock aches, demanding entry.</li>
            <li>That young, tight vagina is a defiant challenge, and my old cock, against all reason, stiffens with wicked intent.</li>
            <li>It looks like it would snap rather than stretch. A perverse fascination grips me, and my member begins to throb.</li>
            <li>The shallow depth is almost insulting. My aging member, however, is not to be deterred; it demands a forceful entry.</li>
            <li>A truly uninviting entrance, yet my perverse curiosity and my hardening cock compel me to imagine the struggle.</li>
            <li>The very thought of forcing my way into that tight little thing excites my old, stiff shaft.</li>
            <li>That virginal tightness is a cruel, tantalizing lure. My loins burn with an unspeakable desire.</li>
            <li>I see the lack of room, and my aged member rebels, stiffening with a defiant, brutal hunger.</li>
            <li>Her tightly sealed entrance is a test of will. My cock, against my better judgment, rises to the occasion.</li>
            <li>A cold, unyielding portal. It stirs a dark, possessive urge within me, and my old flesh responds accordingly.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My, that’s a tight one. She must be miserable, or perhaps never had the pleasure of a proper stretching.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its lips were drawn so tight, it looked painful. A sad sight for a young woman.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted opening, lacking any discernible depth. She clearly hasn't learned to enjoy herself.</li>
            <li>A rather ungenerous aperture. One wonders how she manages, or if she even tries.</li>
            <li>It looks almost virgin-like in its tightness. A waste of youth, if you ask me.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips are thin and almost chapped, clinging together. A truly unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>That poor thing, so unyielding and small. It screams discomfort.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina indicates a life of regrettable continence.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. She'll have a hard time finding satisfaction with that.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. It lacks any softness or allure.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. There’s no warmth or invitation there.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. No wonder she's so tight.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from the world. A depressing sight.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. She'll find no joy in such a rigid confinement.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a spinster's mouth. Unfortunate.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. A pity.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a complete lack of pleasurable experience. What a waste.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking into itself. A truly unappealing form.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. I've known more inviting thimbles.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. No warmth, no true womanhood.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything but pain.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom. Unfulfilled.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in a tight, unappealing crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. I've no patience for such lack of openness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ugh, look at that thing. So tight, it barely looks like it could take a finger, let alone anything else.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, and frankly, it's a disappointment. Those lips are too thin, too pinched.</li>
            <li>This is what they call tight? It just looks... closed off. No fun to be had there.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is a frigid, uninviting slit. There’s no appeal in trying to get into that.</li>
            <li>Too small. It looks like it would break before it stretched. A real turn-off.</li>
            <li>The labia are practically fused, a harsh line. It screams 'no entry,' and I believe it.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't touch that. It looks dry, unwelcoming, and utterly unyielding.</li>
            <li>That pinched look on her vagina makes me grimace. It promises only pain, not pleasure.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris is hiding, barely there. No wonder it looks so unappealingly tight.</li>
            <li>A truly disappointing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening. No depth, no warmth.</li>
            <li>It looks like a struggle just to get in there. Not worth the effort.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is so closed off, it’s practically rejecting me just by existing.</li>
            <li>Such a tight, ungenerous opening. It's a clear sign of trouble.</li>
            <li>I prefer something with a bit more give. This just looks like a wall.</li>
            <li>The sight of it actually makes my own parts recoil. Absolutely not.</li>
            <li>It's almost offensively small. Who would want to bother?</li>
            <li>Her vagina is a narrow, unforgiving crevice. Not what I'm looking for.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina and felt a profound sense of 'no'.</li>
            <li>It's so tightly sealed, it looks like it’s never known release. Horrible.</li>
            <li>The lack of inviting folds or depth is truly off-putting.</li>
            <li>Her body is nice, but that vagina is a hard pass. Too tight.</li>
            <li>Looks like trying to force a brick through a keyhole. No thanks.</li>
            <li>I don't think I could even get started with something that tight.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so tiny and recessed, it practically screams 'unresponsive'.</li>
            <li>It just looks like it would hurt, both of us. Not my kind of fun.</li>
            <li>That unyielding facade is a complete turn-off. No pleasure there.</li>
            <li>I'd rather stick my hand in a vice. That vagina promises pain.</li>
            <li>The very thought of its tightness makes my own parts shrivel. Awful.</li>
            <li>Such a closed-off appearance. It's almost an insult to look at.</li>
            <li>There's absolutely nothing appealing about that painfully tight opening.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That tight little opening, barely a slit. It's a challenge, a tantalizing barrier I long to see overcome.</li>
            <li>I secretly observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia pressed together, almost sealed. It stirs a perverse curiosity within me, how utterly unyielding it appears.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth, the barely visible clitoris. Such a tightly wound secret, I yearn to see it exposed and stretched.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure, yet its defiance is alluring. I imagine the struggle, the eventual yielding.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is fascinating in its resistance. It promises a show of desperate expansion.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. I watch, captivated by its stubborn refusal to open.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of it being forced open is profoundly stimulating.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina implies a hidden struggle. I want to see the moment it gives way.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a thrilling anticipation of witnessing its brutal stretching.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. Yet, the struggle of opening it would be a spectacle.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. But every closed book begs to be violently opened.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. I imagine the efforts required to coax it out.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away. But I'm watching, waiting for it to be forced into submission.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of its violation excites me beyond measure.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice and feel a thrill.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. How I yearn to see it spill its contents.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. The challenge is alluring.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a dramatic transformation when finally stretched. I await it.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes the eventual surrender all the more sweet.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for a grand display of expansion is intoxicating.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. How thrilling to witness it being overwhelmed.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. Which makes its eventual breaking all the more enticing.</li>
            <li>I find a perverse pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom. I long to witness its brutal unfolding.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. Yet, the drama of its conquest is captivating.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. I yearn to see it pushed forward, exposed.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a thrilling promise of forced fulfillment.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and therefore, a glorious challenge.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear, except the thought of forcing it to stay open.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. It’s a perfect stage for a dramatic breaking.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That tight little hole, so unyielding. My cock stirs, longing to be the one to finally crack it open.</li>
            <li>I watched {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia a thin, uninviting line. My own member, unbidden, stiffened with a perverse desire to expand it.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth of that young one's hole fills me with a wicked intent. My shaft aches to stretch it.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure, yet its defiance is alluring. My cock throbs, imagining the brutal breaking.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is fascinating. My growing erection demands to witness its forced expansion.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. My body responds, a cruel amusement at the thought of forcing my way in.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of it being brutally forced open fills me with a thrilling anticipation, making my cock hard.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina implies a hidden struggle. My loins ache, wanting to be the cause of its ultimate yielding.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a thrilling anticipation of witnessing its violent stretching. My cock is ready.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. Yet, the struggle of opening it would be a spectacle, and my member stirs.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. But every closed book begs to be violently opened, and my cock agrees.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. I imagine the efforts required to coax it out, and my dick gets harder.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish. But I'm watching, waiting for it to be forced into submission by my impatient shaft.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of its violation excites me beyond measure, and my cock becomes iron.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice and feel a thrill; my member twitches with predatory intent.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. How I yearn to see it spill its contents, beneath my insistent member.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. The challenge makes my cock stiffen.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a dramatic transformation when finally stretched. My erection demands to be part of it.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes the eventual surrender all the more sweet, and my shaft responds.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for a grand display of expansion is intoxicating, and my cock yearns for it.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. How thrilling to witness it being overwhelmed by my insistent member.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. Which makes its eventual breaking all the more enticing to my hardening cock.</li>
            <li>I find a perverse pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy, and my member responds with a throb.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom. I long to witness its brutal unfolding, with my cock leading the way.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. Yet, the drama of its conquest is captivating to my aroused shaft.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. I yearn to see it pushed forward, exposed by my thrusting cock.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a thrilling promise of forced fulfillment for my demanding member.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and therefore, a glorious challenge for my rising cock.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear, except the thought of forcing it to stay open with my eager shaft.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. It’s a perfect stage for a dramatic breaking, and my cock is the main actor.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That impossibly tight opening. I find myself fixated, imagining the struggle, the eventual tear as it's forced open.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia so tightly closed. A perverse thrill runs through me, wondering how much pain it would take to part them.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth, the barely visible clitoris. Such a tightly wound secret. My own core twitches, desiring to see it brutally stretched.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure. Its defiance is alluring. I yearn to witness it scream as it's finally overcome.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is fascinating in its resistance. It promises a grotesque show of desperate expansion.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. I watch, captivated by its stubborn refusal to open, desiring to see it split.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of it being violated fills me with a wicked anticipation. My own wetness increases.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina implies a hidden struggle. I want to see the moment it gives way, agonizingly.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a thrilling anticipation of witnessing its brutal stretching, making my own folds damp.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. Yet, the struggle of opening it would be a spectacle, and I feel a chill of excitement.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. But every closed book begs to be violently opened, and my own core yearns for the drama.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. I imagine the agonizing efforts required to coax it out, and my own pulse quickens.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away. But I'm watching, waiting for it to be forced into submission, with a perverse longing.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of its violation excites me beyond measure, and I find myself clenching.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice and feel a thrilling rush.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. How I yearn to see it spill its contents, in a messy, forced display.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. The challenge is alluring, to break that resistance.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a dramatic, painful transformation when finally stretched. I await it, my breath held.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes the eventual surrender all the more sweet, a cruel spectacle.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for a grand display of expansion is intoxicating, a promise of screams.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. How thrilling to witness it being overwhelmed, forced open against its will.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. Which makes its eventual breaking all the more enticing.</li>
            <li>I find a perverse pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy. My own body tightens in response.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom. I long to witness its brutal unfolding, a raw, exposed mess.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. Yet, the drama of its conquest is captivating.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. I yearn to see it pushed forward, exposed, screaming.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a thrilling promise of forced fulfillment.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and therefore, a glorious, agonizing challenge.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear, except the thought of forcing it to stay open.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. It’s a perfect stage for a dramatic breaking, and I long to be a witness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I reveal myself, hoping to entice, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is so tightly sealed, it's almost an insult to my efforts.</li>
            <li>I flash my wares, yet her vagina is a prudish, unyielding slit. It mocks my openness.</li>
            <li>It's so closed, so unwelcoming. My desire to display is met with such a frigid lack of response from {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I show all, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, ungenerous opening. It's truly disappointing, my exhibition feels wasted.</li>
            <li>My bold display is met with a vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina. It's a sad, unreactive sight.</li>
            <li>I expose myself fully, but her tightly puckered labia offer no reciprocation, only a stark refusal.</li>
            <li>I offer my body freely, yet {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to shrink from the very idea, a frustrating display of tightness.</li>
            <li>My revealing act is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} almost invisible clitoris and unyielding folds. My performance is unappreciated.</li>
            <li>I crave an audience, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina offers no appreciation, no lust. It's a closed, dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>My display means nothing to {PAWN_nameShort} if {PAWN_possessive} own anatomy is so uninvitingly shut.</li>
            <li>I stand before them, exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a rigid, unyielding barrier. How dull.</li>
            <li>The spectacle I present means nothing against the backdrop of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unresponsively tight vulva.</li>
            <li>My open invitation is met with the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cramped, unwilling gateway. Disappointing.</li>
            <li>I feel my efforts are wasted on something so tight and unyielding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to actively scorn my openness with its prudish tightness.</li>
            <li>My bold exhibition is wasted on such a small, unenthusiastic opening.</li>
            <li>I reveal my essence, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ungenerous, almost absent depth.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, unyielding anatomy is an affront to my free spirit.</li>
            <li>My very being craves attention, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina offers only cold, unwelcome tightness.</li>
            <li>I perform, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted portal seems to judge, not admire.</li>
            <li>My desire to share is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled, unappealing opening.</li>
            <li>I make myself bare, only to face the harsh reality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>My exhibition feels futile when confronted with such a closed and unresponsive form.</li>
            <li>I display all, only to see a vagina that seems to recoil from the very act of living.</li>
            <li>The lack of give in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a profound disappointment to my performance.</li>
            <li>I offer my body, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a tightly shut, joyless crevice.</li>
            <li>My passion for display is met with such an ungenerous, unyielding spectacle.</li>
            <li>The frigid, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina dampens my exhibitionist spirit.</li>
            <li>I long for admiration, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight anatomy offers nothing but disinterest.</li>
            <li>My nakedness feels mocked by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted, unyielding form.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I reveal my throbbing cock, yet {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is so tightly sealed, it's an insult to my prowess.</li>
            <li>I flash my impressive shaft, but her vagina is a prudish, unyielding slit. It mocks my openness, making my cock flaccid.</li>
            <li>It's so closed, so unwelcoming. My desire to display my magnificent member is met with such a frigid lack of response from {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I show all, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, ungenerous opening. My erection falters, feeling utterly wasted.</li>
            <li>My bold display is met with a vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina. It's a sad, unreactive sight that deflates my pride.</li>
            <li>I expose myself fully, but her tightly puckered labia offer no reciprocation, only a stark refusal. My own shaft shrinks in disappointment.</li>
            <li>I offer my proud cock freely, yet {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to shrink from the very idea, a frustrating display of tightness.</li>
            <li>My revealing act is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} almost invisible clitoris and unyielding folds. My performance, and my member, are unappreciated.</li>
            <li>I crave an audience for my potent cock, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina offers no appreciation, no lust. It's a closed, dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>My display means nothing to {PAWN_nameShort} if {PAWN_possessive} own anatomy is so uninvitingly shut. My enthusiasm wanes.</li>
            <li>I stand before them, my cock exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a rigid, unyielding barrier. How dull and disappointing.</li>
            <li>The spectacle I present means nothing against the backdrop of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unresponsively tight vulva. My member feels ignored.</li>
            <li>My open invitation is met with the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cramped, unwilling gateway. My cock loses its stiff resolve.</li>
            <li>I feel my efforts, and my shaft's potential, are wasted on something so tight and unyielding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to actively scorn my openness with its prudish tightness, and my cock feels judged.</li>
            <li>My bold exhibition is wasted on such a small, unenthusiastic opening. My member, once proud, now merely hangs.</li>
            <li>I reveal my essence, and my eager cock, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ungenerous, almost absent depth.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, unyielding anatomy is an affront to my free spirit, and my cock stiffens with frustration, not lust.</li>
            <li>My very being craves attention, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina offers only cold, unwelcome tightness, leaving my member limp.</li>
            <li>I perform, my cock prominently displayed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted portal seems to judge, not admire.</li>
            <li>My desire to share my member is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled, unappealing opening.</li>
            <li>I make myself bare, my cock ready, only to face the harsh reality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>My exhibition feels futile when confronted with such a closed and unresponsive form. My member shrinks.</li>
            <li>I display all, only to see a vagina that seems to recoil from the very act of living, and my cock goes soft.</li>
            <li>The lack of give in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a profound disappointment to my performance, and my member.</li>
            <li>I offer my body and my eager cock, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a tightly shut, joyless crevice.</li>
            <li>My passion for display is met with such an ungenerous, unyielding spectacle, and my cock is utterly disheartened.</li>
            <li>The frigid, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina dampens my exhibitionist spirit, and my member with it.</li>
            <li>I long for admiration, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight anatomy offers nothing but disinterest to my exposed cock.</li>
            <li>My nakedness feels mocked by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted, unyielding form, making my proud member feel small.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I reveal myself, hoping to share my own bountiful wetness, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is so tightly sealed, it's a cold rejection.</li>
            <li>I flash my welcoming depths, yet her vagina is a prudish, unyielding slit. It mocks my openness, making my own moisture recede.</li>
            <li>It's so closed, so unwelcoming. My desire to display my inviting folds is met with such a frigid lack of response from {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I show all, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, ungenerous opening. My own labia tighten in disappointment.</li>
            <li>My bold display is met with a vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina. It's a sad, unreactive sight that chills my own warmth.</li>
            <li>I expose myself fully, but her tightly puckered labia offer no reciprocation, only a stark refusal. My own arousal dissipates.</li>
            <li>I offer my soft, open body freely, yet {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to shrink from the very idea, a frustrating display of tightness.</li>
            <li>My revealing act is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} almost invisible clitoris and unyielding folds. My performance, and my own core, feel unappreciated.</li>
            <li>I crave an audience, and to share my own desire, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina offers no appreciation, no lust. It's a closed, dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>My display means nothing to {PAWN_nameShort} if {PAWN_possessive} own anatomy is so uninvitingly shut. My own warmth cools.</li>
            <li>I stand before them, exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a rigid, unyielding barrier. How dull and unstimulating.</li>
            <li>The spectacle I present means nothing against the backdrop of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unresponsively tight vulva. My own arousal dwindles.</li>
            <li>My open invitation is met with the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cramped, unwilling gateway. My own desire withers.</li>
            <li>I feel my efforts, and my own body's generosity, are wasted on something so tight and unyielding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to actively scorn my openness with its prudish tightness, and my own parts feel judged.</li>
            <li>My bold exhibition is wasted on such a small, unenthusiastic opening. My own warmth is replaced by a chill.</li>
            <li>I reveal my essence, and my own inviting wetness, only to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ungenerous, almost absent depth.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, unyielding anatomy is an affront to my free spirit, and my own body feels insulted.</li>
            <li>My very being craves attention, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina offers only cold, unwelcome tightness, leaving me unstimulated.</li>
            <li>I perform, my body openly displayed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted portal seems to judge, not admire.</li>
            <li>My desire to share my own form is met with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled, unappealing opening.</li>
            <li>I make myself bare, my own ready, only to face the harsh reality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>My exhibition feels futile when confronted with such a closed and unresponsive form. My own pleasure wanes.</li>
            <li>I display all, only to see a vagina that seems to recoil from the very act of living, and my own desire cools.</li>
            <li>The lack of give in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a profound disappointment to my performance, and my own body.</li>
            <li>I offer my body and my inviting folds, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a tightly shut, joyless crevice.</li>
            <li>My passion for display is met with such an ungenerous, unyielding spectacle, and my own arousal is utterly disheartened.</li>
            <li>The frigid, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina dampens my exhibitionist spirit, and my own body feels cold.</li>
            <li>I long for admiration, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight anatomy offers nothing but disinterest to my exposed self.</li>
            <li>My nakedness feels mocked by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted, unyielding form, making my own inviting parts feel unappreciated.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That impossibly tight vagina. It's a frustrating sight, promising nothing but a painful, unsatisfying struggle. My desires are thwarted.</li>
            <li>I glimpse {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia so tightly closed. It fills me with a desperate, frustrated longing for an open, yielding embrace.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth, the barely visible clitoris. Such a tightly wound secret that offers no relief to my burning urges.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure. Its defiance is maddening, promising a joyless, restricted encounter.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is an offense to my insatiable cravings. It looks like a barren landscape.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. It actively repels my boundless desires.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of its unyielding nature brings a wave of desperate frustration.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams 'no satisfaction'. It's a torment to my aroused state.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a furious, desperate need to conquer, yet promises utter discomfort.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. It fills me with a frustrated craving for release.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. And I, in my endless hunger, am denied a single page.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. It promises no easy route to the satisfaction I desperately crave.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away. And I yearn to drown in pleasure, not chase a disappearing act.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of enduring it fills me with dread and frustrated longing.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice, and it mirrors my own sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. And I, a spendthrift of lust, am left wanting.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. A cruel tease for my burning desires.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests only torment for my boundless appetite. No depth, no release.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes my sexual frustration boil.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for pleasure is tragically limited, a true disappointment to my relentless urges.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. It's an insult to my burning need for connection and release.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. My desires are suffocated by its tightness.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy. It only fuels my desperate, unfulfilled lust.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom, and I yearn for bloom, not barrenness.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. My own body aches with unsatisfied longing.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. It promises no easy path to the climax I constantly seek.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a torment to my insatiable nature.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and utterly frustrating to my desires.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear. It denies my very purpose.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. My endless hunger finds no solace in such a tight, unwelcoming sight.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That impossibly tight vagina. It's a frustrating sight, promising nothing but a painful, unsatisfying struggle for my raging cock.</li>
            <li>I glimpse {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia so tightly closed. It fills my throbbing member with a desperate, frustrated longing for an open, yielding embrace.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth, the barely visible clitoris. Such a tightly wound secret that offers no relief to my burning cock.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure. Its defiance is maddening, promising a joyless, restricted encounter for my demanding shaft.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is an offense to my insatiable cravings. My cock refuses to believe it.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. It actively repels my boundless desires, making my member ache.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of its unyielding nature brings a wave of desperate frustration, making my cock hard with denial.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams 'no satisfaction'. It's a torment to my engorged state.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a furious, desperate need to conquer, yet promises utter discomfort to my eager cock.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. It fills my raging member with a frustrated craving for release.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. And I, in my endless hunger, am denied a single page for my thrusting shaft.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. It promises no easy route to the satisfaction my cock desperately craves.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away. And my cock yearns to drown in pleasure, not chase a disappearing act.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of enduring it fills me with dread and frustrated longing for my aching cock.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice, and it mirrors my own sexual frustration, tightening my balls.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. And I, a spendthrift of lust, am left wanting, my cock twitching.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. A cruel tease for my burning, insistent cock.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests only torment for my boundless appetite. No depth, no release for my throbbing member.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes my sexual frustration boil, and my cock stiffens with rage.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for pleasure is tragically limited, a true disappointment to my relentless urges, and my demanding cock.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. It's an insult to my burning need for connection and release, and my cock feels mocked.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. My desires are suffocated by its tightness, and my cock goes limp with despair.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy. It only fuels my desperate, unfulfilled lust, making my cock ache.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom, and I, with my eager cock, yearn for bloom, not barrenness.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. My own cock aches with unsatisfied longing.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. It promises no easy path to the climax my cock constantly seeks.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a torment to my insatiable nature, making my shaft tremble.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and utterly frustrating to my desires, and my rigid cock.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear. It denies my very purpose, and infuriates my cock.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. My endless hunger finds no solace in such a tight, unwelcoming sight, leaving my cock unfulfilled.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That impossibly tight vagina. It's a frustrating sight, promising nothing but a painful, unsatisfying struggle for my aching core.</li>
            <li>I glimpse {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina, its labia so tightly closed. It fills my own throbbing wetness with a desperate, frustrated longing for an open, yielding embrace.</li>
            <li>The minuscule depth, the barely visible clitoris. Such a tightly wound secret that offers no relief to my burning desires. My own folds clench.</li>
            <li>A truly ungenerous fissure. Its defiance is maddening, promising a joyless, restricted encounter for my desperate needs.</li>
            <li>The almost virgin-like tightness of her hole is an offense to my insatiable cravings. It looks like a barren, unwelcoming space.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal entrance, a pinched, uninviting line. It actively repels my boundless desires, making my own depths ache with longing.</li>
            <li>It's startlingly shallow, a mere dimple. The thought of its unyielding nature brings a wave of desperate frustration, making my own core tighten.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams 'no satisfaction'. It's a torment to my aroused state, and my own clitoris throbs.</li>
            <li>Barely an opening. It ignites a furious, desperate need to conquer, yet promises utter discomfort, making my own wetness increase in protest.</li>
            <li>A dismal sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted passage. It fills my raging depths with a frustrated craving for release.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem sealed, a closed book. And I, in my endless hunger, am denied a single page for my own eager exploration.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed, it's practically invisible. It promises no easy route to the satisfaction my own body desperately craves.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away. And I, in my endless need, yearn to drown in pleasure, not chase a disappearing act.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding tunnel. The thought of enduring it fills me with dread and frustrated longing for my own aching core.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding orifice, and it mirrors my own sexual frustration, causing my own muscles to tense.</li>
            <li>This young one's vagina is as pinched as a miser's purse. And I, a spendthrift of lust, am left wanting, my own body restless.</li>
            <li>It's a strange thing to see, so youthful, yet so uninvitingly tight. A cruel tease for my burning, insistent desires.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests only torment for my boundless appetite. No depth, no release for my own throbbing need.</li>
            <li>Her vagina appears to be actively resisting, shrinking. This defiance makes my sexual frustration boil, and my own core aches.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for pleasure is tragically limited, a true disappointment to my relentless urges, and my own demanding body.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding disinterest. It's an insult to my burning need for connection and release, and my own depths feel mocked.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive form, hardly conducive to anything. My desires are suffocated by its tightness, and my own pleasure is denied.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling anatomy. It only fuels my desperate, unfulfilled lust, making my own core ache.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a bud that refuses to blossom, and I, with my eager body, yearn for bloom, not barrenness.</li>
            <li>A rather sad spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous opening. My own desire aches with unsatisfied longing.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away. It promises no easy path to the climax my own body constantly seeks.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of unfulfilled potential, and a torment to my insatiable nature, making my own body tremble.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in dried earth. This is just... restricted, and utterly frustrating to my desires, and my own burning depths.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear. It denies my very purpose, and infuriates my own craving.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. My endless hunger finds no solace in such a tight, unwelcoming sight, leaving my own core unfulfilled.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Oh dear, that looks uncomfortably tight. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} isn't in any discomfort.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted vagina. It seems rather small, perhaps causing {PAWN_objective} some difficulty.</li>
            <li>It's a shame to see such a tight, unyielding opening. I truly hope {PAWN_nameShort} finds comfort and happiness.</li>
            <li>That appears quite restricted. I wish for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-being and ease.</li>
            <li>The appearance of her vagina seems to indicate a lack of natural openness. I feel a pang of sympathy.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight labia; it seems rather delicate and perhaps vulnerable.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted entrance. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} knows gentleness and understanding.</li>
            <li>The puckered look on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina might suggest discomfort. My heart goes out to {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>It's a difficult thing to see, so unyielding. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} is treated with utmost care.</li>
            <li>A rather narrow passage. I wish {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} only the kindest of experiences.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy appears quite rigid. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} finds solace and gentle touch.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy is quite small. I feel a touch of sadness for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>It seems quite uninviting, which is a pity. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} encounters only kindness.</li>
            <li>I noticed the tight, unyielding form. I wish for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ease and tenderness.</li>
            <li>The clitoris seems deeply hidden. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} experiences joy despite this.</li>
            <li>This tightness might cause pain. I truly wish {PAWN_nameShort} no harm.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unyielding structure with a sense of gentle concern.</li>
            <li>A rather closed appearance. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} finds warmth and comfort.</li>
            <li>It's a bit disheartening to see such a constricted opening.</li>
            <li>I hope {PAWN_nameShort} doesn't suffer any undue discomfort from that tightness.</li>
            <li>The texture seems unyielding. I wish {PAWN_nameShort} only gentle interactions.</li>
            <li>A shame it looks so unwelcoming. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} knows true happiness.</li>
            <li>I noted the limited depth. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} is always treated kindly.</li>
            <li>It's a rather sad sight, that ungenerous form. I wish {PAWN_nameShort} peace.</li>
            <li>I observe with compassion, hoping that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tightness isn't a source of pain.</li>
            <li>The constrained nature of her anatomy concerns me for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I offer my silent well-wishes for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} comfort.</li>
            <li>A rather unforgiving sight. I hope {PAWN_nameShort} finds acceptance and love.</li>
            <li>I feel a twinge of empathy seeing such a restrictive form.</li>
            <li>It looks like it could be uncomfortable. I wish {PAWN_nameShort} only good things.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>What a ridiculous, pinched little thing. It's almost offensive in its tightness. Disgusting.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina. It's so utterly constricted, it's pathetic. No decency, no proper form.</li>
            <li>That's just repulsive, so narrow and unyielding. Keep that shameful display away from me.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is an ungenerous, shriveled excuse for a hole. Truly appalling.</li>
            <li>Too tight, too small, and utterly lacking in any appeal. A disgrace to proper anatomy.</li>
            <li>The labia are practically fused, a prim, unwelcoming line. It’s an affront to my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't touch that with a ten-foot pole. It looks dry, prudish, and utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>That puckered look on her vagina is simply grotesque. It promises only discomfort and ugliness.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris is hiding, barely there. A clear sign of its unworthiness and shame.</li>
            <li>A truly disappointing and vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening.</li>
            <li>It looks like a struggle just to exist. Some things should just stay hidden.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is so closed off, it's an insult to the very concept of openness.</li>
            <li>Such a tight, ungenerous opening. It speaks volumes of {PAWN_possessive} unappealing nature.</li>
            <li>I prefer something with actual character, not this pathetic excuse for an opening.</li>
            <li>The sight of it actually makes me physically recoil. Absolutely repugnant.</li>
            <li>It's almost offensively small. Who would even bother with such a prudish thing?</li>
            <li>Her vagina is a narrow, unforgiving crevice. A pitiful, shameful sight.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vagina and felt a profound sense of utter disgust.</li>
            <li>It's so tightly sealed, it looks like it's never known anything but shame. Horrible.</li>
            <li>The lack of inviting folds or depth is truly off-putting. A wretched sight.</li>
            <li>Her body is a mockery, and that vagina is the worst part. Too tight, too crude.</li>
            <li>Looks like trying to fit a square peg in a painfully small round hole. Disgusting.</li>
            <li>I don't think I could even stomach looking at something that tight, let alone interacting.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so tiny and recessed, it practically screams 'shameful and unresponsive'.</li>
            <li>It just looks like it would hurt, both to see and to touch. A repulsive display.</li>
            <li>That unyielding facade is a complete turn-off. No decency, no beauty there.</li>
            <li>I'd rather face a scyther than look at that abhorrent, tight vagina.</li>
            <li>The very thought of its tightness makes my stomach turn. Awful.</li>
            <li>Such a closed-off appearance. It's almost an insult to civilized eyes.</li>
            <li>There's absolutely nothing appealing about that painfully tight, shameful opening.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A horse vagina, and a tight one at that. The anatomical incongruity is frankly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s an unnatural, constricted abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, equine slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, shriveled button.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, elongated horse-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its oddness.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre horse vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly equine and painfully tight. A truly grotesque deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, equine orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The horse-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted horse-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her equine labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, horse-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding equine tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, horse-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This horse vagina is as pinched as a starved beast. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and equine.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her horse vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, bestial form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, horse-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, equine opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, animalistic crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a horse vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A dog vagina, and a tight one. The bestial, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a primitive, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, canine slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, animalistic nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost brutish dog-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its vulgarity.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre dog vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly canine and painfully tight. A truly grotesque bestial deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, canine orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The dog-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted dog-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her canine labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, dog-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding canine tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, dog-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This dog vagina is as pinched as a starved cur. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and canine.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her dog vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, bestial form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, dog-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, canine opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, animalistic crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a dog vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A cat vagina, and a tight one. The feline, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a primitive, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, feline slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, animalistic nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost brutish cat-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its vulgarity.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre cat vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly feline and painfully tight. A truly grotesque bestial deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, feline orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The cat-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted cat-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her feline labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, cat-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding feline tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, cat-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This cat vagina is as pinched as a starved feline. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and feline.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her cat vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, bestial form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, cat-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, feline opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, animalistic crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a cat vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A demonic vagina, and a tight one at that. The hellish, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a vile, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, demonic slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, infernal nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost torturous demon-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its unholiness.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre demon vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly demonic and painfully tight. A truly grotesque perversion.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, infernal orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The demon-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted demon-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her demonic labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, demon-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding demonic tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, demon-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This demon vagina is as pinched as a damned soul. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and demonic.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her demon vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, unholy form, hardly conducive to anything good.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, demon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, demonic opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, infernal crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a demon vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A dragon vagina, and a tight one at that. The scaled, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a primal, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, draconic slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, reptilian nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost fearsome dragon-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its monstrousness.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre dragon vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly draconic and painfully tight. A truly grotesque beastly deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, reptilian orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The dragon-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted dragon-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her draconic labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, dragon-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding draconic tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, dragon-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This dragon vagina is as pinched as a petrified scale. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and draconic.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her dragon vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, scaled form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, dragon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, draconic opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, reptilian crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a dragon vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A slime vagina, and a tight one at that. The viscous, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a squishy, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, slimy slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, amorphous nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost oozing slime-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its repugnance.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre slime vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly slimy and painfully tight. A truly grotesque, fluid deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, gelatinous orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The slime-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted slime-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her gelatinous labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, slime-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding viscous tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, slime-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This slime vagina is as pinched as congealed goo. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and slimy.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her slime vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, fluid form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, slime-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, slimy opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, viscous crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a slime vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A pig vagina, and a tight one at that. The porcine, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} swine vagina, its lips drawn taut. It’s a primitive, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, pig-like slit is utterly bizarre. The clitoris looks like a crude, animalistic nub.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost brutish pig-like opening. It makes my skin crawl with its vulgarity.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre pig vagina is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips, distinctly porcine and painfully tight. A truly grotesque bestial deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, porcine orifice.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight opening. The pig-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted pig-vagina. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her porcine labia seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is so deeply recessed in that tight, pig-like opening, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding porcine tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, pig-like orifice.</li>
            <li>This pig vagina is as pinched as a starved sow. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and porcine.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her pig vagina appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, bestial form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, pig-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, porcine opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was barely there, hidden away in that tight, animalistic crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about a pig vagina that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Tight_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Tight Vagina (Negative) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>An insect ovipositor, and a tight one at that. The chitinous, constricted form is truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} arthropod ovipositor, its tube drawn taut. It’s a vile, tight abomination.</li>
            <li>That tight, insectoid ovipositor is utterly bizarre. It looks like a crude, segmented probe.</li>
            <li>Such a constricted, almost barbed insect-like ovipositor. It makes my skin crawl with its alienness.</li>
            <li>The tightness of that bizarre insect ovipositor is disturbing. It feels wrong, anatomically grotesque.</li>
            <li>Her ovipositor, distinctly insectoid and painfully tight. A truly grotesque, chitinous deviation.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't approach that. It looks like a deformed, unyielding, chitinous tube.</li>
            <li>The puckered appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor is a horrifying sight.</li>
            <li>A truly monstrous, tight ovipositor. The insect-like anatomy is just wrong.</li>
            <li>A disturbing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted insect-ovipositor. It makes me ill.</li>
            <li>Her insectoid segments seem sealed, a closed, disturbing abomination.</li>
            <li>The tip is so deeply recessed in that tight, insect-like ovipositor, it’s a repulsive oddity.</li>
            <li>It looks like it's trying to vanish, shrinking away from its own unnatural form.</li>
            <li>A cramped, unyielding chitinous tunnel. The thought of it is simply repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observe the discomfort radiating from that unyielding, insect-like ovipositor.</li>
            <li>This insect ovipositor is as pinched as a dried husk. Unholy.</li>
            <li>It's a bizarre thing to see, so youthful, yet so unnaturally tight and insectoid.</li>
            <li>The tiny opening suggests a horrifying, painful struggle. A true nightmare.</li>
            <li>Her insect ovipositor appears to be actively resisting its own existence. Grotesque.</li>
            <li>A barely-there opening. The potential for repulsion is profound.</li>
            <li>The very picture of unyielding, unnatural disinterest. It's a perversion.</li>
            <li>Such a restrictive, segmented form, hardly conducive to anything human.</li>
            <li>I find no pleasure in observing such a closed, unwilling, insect-like ovipositor.</li>
            <li>It's like looking at a deformed bud that refuses to blossom. Unnatural.</li>
            <li>A rather sad, and utterly repulsive, spectacle, a youthful body with such an ungenerous, insectoid ovipositor.</li>
            <li>The tip was barely there, hidden away in that tight, chitinous crevice.</li>
            <li>Its smallness gave me pause; a grim reminder of monstrous mutations.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting fissures in diseased flesh. This is just...wrong.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about an insect ovipositor that looks like it's trying to disappear.</li>
            <li>A rather stiff, unyielding display. A truly horrifying perversion of nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>