<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is striking, but honestly, it’s just overwhelming and a bit off-putting.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyss-like vagina, with a cavernous and unfathomable depth that was unattractive and intimidating.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was profoundly deep and seemingly bottomless, with a vast and overwhelming appearance that was unappealing.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was boundless and un-contained, with a deeply creased and weathered exterior that was worn and unappealing.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyss-like vagina, with a cavernous and unfathomable depth that was unattractive and intimidating.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was profoundly deep and seemingly bottomless, with a vast and overwhelming appearance that was unappealing.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was boundless and un-contained, with a deeply creased and weathered exterior that was worn and unappealing.</li>
			<li>I retreated in horror, the unfathomable size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a terrifying black hole, a vortex of insatiable feminine hunger.</li>
			<li>I shuddered in disgust, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginas yawning size was a grotesque caricature, an abyssal and monstrous representation of femininity.</li>
			<li>I recoiled in shock, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} engulfing vagina size was a disturbing anomaly, a gaping and unfathomable chasm of carnal desire.</li>
			<li>The mere sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina made me shudder with revulsion. It was a chasm of darkness, a void that threatened to swallow me alive.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina, the labia spread wide, revealing a chasm that seemed to lead to the depths of hell itself. The clitoris was monstrous, dwarfing everything around it. The thought of venturing into such a terrifying abyss was unthinkable.</li>
			<li>I looked upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyss, a void that seemed to consume all light and hope. The labia were engorged and raw, the texture slimy and repulsive. The clitoris, a monstrous appendage, was a grotesque mockery of pleasure.</li>
			<li>I peered into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} endless, yawning abyss, a gaping maw that seemed to stretch on endlessly. The texture was rough and uneven, the clitoris a swollen, throbbing mass. It was a sight that was almost terrifying.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} depthless void, a vast, echoing space that seemed to swallow everything in its path. The texture was wet and loose, the clitoris a prominent, throbbing protrusion. It was a sight that was almost obscene.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal chasm, a gaping, yawning void that seemed to be never-ending. The texture was smooth and soft, the clitoris a massive, pulsating bulge. It was a sight that was almost unnatural.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal orifice, a deep, dark hole that seemed to lead to who-knows-where. The texture was rough and uneven, the clitoris a swollen, throbbing mass. It was a sight that was almost frightening.</li>
			<li>I beheld {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast expanse, a yawning void that seemed to swallow everything in its path. The texture was wet and loose, the clitoris a prominent, throbbing protrusion. It was a sight that was almost obscene.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina was a disturbing spectacle, its excessive depth a repulsive sight.</li>
			<li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unsettlingly wide vaginal opening, a truly unappealing expanse.</li>
			<li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia was off-putting, a grotesque frame for an even more grotesque void.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, distended and prominent, was a truly monstrous sight to behold.</li>
			<li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals, I was met with an uncomfortable vastness, a disturbing and unsettling display.</li>
			<li>The abyss of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to swallow light, a dark, unsettling chasm.</li>
			<li>Its flaccid, stretched labia suggested a history of abuse, a disturbing and worn appearance.</li>
			<li>A gaping maw, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina hinted at an unsettling depth, far beyond what is natural.</li>
			<li>The unnatural folds and creases of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia were a repulsive, disturbing sight.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina resembled a gaping wound, discolored and disturbingly raw.</li>
			<li>The wetness and looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal walls suggested an unappealing lack of control.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, swollen and engorged, evoked a sense of disgust and perversion.</li>
			<li>The entire structure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals was unsettlingly disproportioned, almost alien.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a disturbing emptiness, as if something essential were missing.</li>
			<li>The sheer width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal was profoundly unnatural, an unnerving sight.</li>
			<li>A feeling of unease washed over me, contemplating the sheer, unbridled size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
			<li>The unsettling sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and splayed labia made my stomach churn.</li>
			<li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina appeared to be endless, a disconcerting void of raw flesh.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyss-like vagina is a disturbing sight on one so young; its unnatural depth is quite alarming.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly vast vagina; such a cavernous depth on a young woman is frankly grotesque.</li>
            <li>That young woman's vagina, it's… too much. A disturbing cavern for someone {PAWN_pronoun}s age, frankly.</li>
            <li>To see such an expansive, almost bottomless vagina on {PAWN_nameShort} is unsettling; it speaks of something unnatural.</li>
            <li>Her youth makes the abyssal scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina even more disturbing; it simply shouldn't be that vast.</li>
            <li>The young female's vagina appeared disproportionately large, a disquieting cavern for her frame.</li>
            <li>Its disturbing depth seemed out of place on {PAWN_nameShort}, far too mature and vast.</li>
            <li>A jarring contrast: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful body, yet a vagina with such a gaping, weathered appearance.</li>
            <li>The thought of that profound depth on a young woman like {PAWN_nameShort} is simply unsettling.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a premature chasm; it spoke of a history far beyond {PAWN_pronoun}s years.</li>
            <li>Such an expanse on a young woman; it's almost an obscenity, unnervingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} raw, stretched labia hinted at an unsettling past for someone so young.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disconcerting, a void that seemed to age {PAWN_objective} beyond {PAWN_pronoun}s years.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina revealed an unsettlingly vast interior, far too developed for {PAWN_pronoun}s age.</li>
            <li>The discolored, almost bruised appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia was a disturbing sight on a youthful body.</li>
            <li>Its gaping opening suggested an unseemly looseness, inappropriate for a young woman.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris on {PAWN_nameShort} was frankly grotesque, especially at {PAWN_pronoun}s age.</li>
            <li>I felt a pang of discomfort observing the unnaturally wide internal anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a shocking breadth, seemed to have been stretched unnaturally wide.</li>
            <li>A disturbing lack of tautness around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening suggested an unsettling history.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia hung, almost lifeless, was a profoundly unsettling detail for her youth.</li>
            <li>Her youthful face contrasted sharply with the cavernous, almost ancient look of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a disturbing chasm, prematurely aged and worn.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly deep canal made me question {PAWN_pronoun}s past experiences.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina possessed an unnerving slackness, betraying {PAWN_pronoun}s apparent youth.</li>
            <li>It was startling to see such a gaping, almost formless vagina on a body so young.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, large and protruding, was a rather unappealing feature on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} otherwise youthful anatomy.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal folds were disturbingly pronounced, hinting at a depth that was far too great.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looked as though it had endured far too much, far too soon.</li>
            <li>I was taken aback by the unsettlingly open and seemingly bottomless nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly disturbing, yet my old member stirs with a morbid curiosity.</li>
            <li>The grotesque depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina sends a shiver down my spine, but a wicked fascination arises.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina; it's unsettling, yet I feel a perverted urge building within me.</li>
            <li>Such an immense, unseemly void on {PAWN_nameShort}... it's monstrous, but I can't look away, and my loins ache.</li>
            <li>Her unnaturally vast vagina is repellent, but my old cock is painfully intrigued by its terrifying expanse.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous vagina made my withered member twitch with a perverse interest.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole still managed to evoke a disturbing stir in my trousers.</li>
            <li>Despite its repulsive depth, my perverted gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a dark thought forming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnatural size was off-putting, yet my old lust still gnawed at my insides.</li>
            <li>I felt a repulsive fascination with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, a sickening pull on my senses.</li>
            <li>The obscenity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide-open vagina was unsettling, but a familiar warmth spread in my groin.</li>
            <li>My eyes traced the disturbing contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, a morbid curiosity seizing my old body.</li>
            <li>The raw, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina should repel, yet my old desire flickered awake.</li>
            <li>A dark, unsettling desire stirred in my ancient loins at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast abyss.</li>
            <li>I found myself disturbingly drawn to the gaping void of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, my mind racing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} oversized clitoris was grotesque, yet it sparked a perverse, uncomfortable feeling.</li>
            <li>The sheer, terrifying scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner folds made my breath catch, in a dark way.</li>
            <li>I recoiled, but then my gaze returned to the disquieting depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, and I felt a shameful throb.</li>
            <li>Her wet, loose interior should disgust, but instead, it conjured perverse images in my aging mind.</li>
            <li>The knowledge of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bottomless depth made my old blood thrum with a wicked anticipation.</li>
            <li>I could not tear my eyes from the disturbing spectacle, a lewdness rising despite the repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a monstrous entity, evoked a perverse sense of power in my shriveled self.</li>
            <li>My mind conjured vile scenarios, fueled by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impossibly deep chasm.</li>
            <li>A grimace twisted my face, yet my gaze was fixed on the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals.</li>
            <li>The thought of that cavernous space brought an uncomfortable stirring to my old, forgotten parts.</li>
            <li>I shivered, but not entirely from disgust; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a truly wicked sight.</li>
            <li>My hands twitched, imagining the disturbing textures within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unholy opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, distended and throbbing, made my own withered appendage feel a perverse kinship.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, despite its horror, drew a perverse, unwanted response from me.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse desire to plumb the disturbing, endless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dark abyss.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly disturbing; far too vast and worn for one so young.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly deep vagina, a rather unfortunate sight on a young woman.</li>
            <li>That young woman's vagina... it's a frightful cavern. So much stretching on one so inexperienced.</li>
            <li>Such an expansive, almost cavernous vagina on {PAWN_nameShort} is quite off-putting; it looks... used.</li>
            <li>Her youth makes the abyssal scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina even more unseemly; it's simply too vast.</li>
            <li>The young female's vagina appeared alarmingly slack, a disturbing lack of form for her age.</li>
            <li>Its disturbing depth seemed unnatural on {PAWN_nameShort}, as if stretched beyond its natural limits.</li>
            <li>A jarring contrast: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful body, yet a vagina that looks decades older, worn and splayed.</li>
            <li>The thought of that profound depth on a young woman like {PAWN_nameShort} is simply unsettling and frankly unladylike.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a premature chasm; it suggested a promiscuity far beyond {PAWN_pronoun}s years.</li>
            <li>Such an expanse on a young woman; it's almost obscene, unsettlingly gaping.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} raw, stretched labia hinted at an unsettling past for someone so young, quite unbecoming.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disconcerting, a void that spoke of excessive use.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina revealed an unsettlingly vast interior, far too open.</li>
            <li>The discolored, almost bruised appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia was a disturbing sight, a mark of vulgarity.</li>
            <li>Its gaping opening suggested an unseemly looseness, inappropriate and unattractive for a young woman.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris on {PAWN_nameShort} was frankly grotesque, especially at {PAWN_pronoun}s age, quite immodest.</li>
            <li>I felt a pang of discomfort observing the unnaturally wide internal anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it was crude.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a shocking breadth, seemed to have been stretched unnaturally wide, quite common.</li>
            <li>A disturbing lack of tautness around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening suggested an unsettling lack of virtue.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia hung, almost lifeless, was a profoundly unsettling detail for her youth, truly shameful.</li>
            <li>Her youthful face contrasted sharply with the cavernous, almost ancient look of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a disturbing chasm, prematurely aged and far too experienced.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly deep canal made me frown, questioning {PAWN_pronoun}s decorum.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina possessed an unnerving slackness, betraying {PAWN_pronoun}s supposed innocence.</li>
            <li>It was startling to see such a gaping, almost formless vagina on a body so young, quite a pity.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, large and protruding, was a rather unappealing feature on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} otherwise youthful anatomy, brazen even.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal folds were disturbingly pronounced, hinting at a depth that was far too great and unseemly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looked as though it had endured far too much, far too soon, a true disgrace.</li>
            <li>I was taken aback by the unsettlingly open and seemingly bottomless nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, it was crude and vulgar.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is frankly terrifying; it's so vast it kills any attraction.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina and it's just... too much. A gaping maw, completely unappealing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a turn-off; it looks like a black hole down there.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is immense, almost unsettlingly so. It just looks wrong, not enticing at all.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a nightmare. It feels like I'd get lost in there.</li>
            <li>The flaccid labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina are a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is so wide, it's just… a chasm. There's nothing attractive about that kind of emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly used vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina and felt absolutely nothing but repulsion; it's too vast.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina simply isn't attractive.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina are simply disgusting.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is one of excessive use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina has no enticing tightness.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is a horrifying spectacle, yet my gaze is unnaturally fixed on its unsettling depth.</li>
            <li>I caught sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is repulsive, but I'm morbidly fascinated.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a disgusting display, yet I can't tear my eyes away.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent sight, but I'm compelled to observe every disturbing detail.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but it holds a strange, dark allure for me.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic urges are perversely satisfied by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I find myself meticulously examining {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} every flaw.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but I feel an illicit thrill in witnessing them.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, but my eyes crave more.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my perverse attention deeper.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my voyeuristic nature compelled me to memorize {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but I am transfixed by its disturbing prominence.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a repulsive sight, yet I can't unsee it.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling fascination.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle I couldn't ignore.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of intimacy witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden curiosity.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly captivating.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a grotesque mental image.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and voyeuristic intrigue.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is a repellent abyss, yet my cock stirred with a perverse, uneasy urge.</li>
            <li>I caught sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, but I felt a twisted throb.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, yet my member hardened with morbid curiosity.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's repulsive, but my loins ache with an unwanted, dark fascination.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, yet my cock is painfully intrigued.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic urges were perversely ignited by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; my dick twitched.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I found myself uncomfortably aroused by its vulgarity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but a perverse stiffness began in my groin.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer obscenity, making my rod stir.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, and my balls tightened.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, but my cock responds despite itself.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my perverse attention deeper, and I feel myself swell.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my voyeuristic nature compelled me to memorize {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions, my erection growing.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but I am transfixed, my own member straining.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, feeling a shameful warmth.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, yet a primal, dark urge consumes me.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling, yet exciting, fascination.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that made my cock tingle.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of intimacy witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a dark lust.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden, powerful erection.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt a stir.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, my prick aching.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly exciting to my loins.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a grotesque yet stimulating mental image.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, and my member stirred.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, a raw, sexual response.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness, leading to a shameful throb.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and voyeuristic intrigue, and my blood ran hot.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, and my erection grew firm.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation, my groin responding powerfully.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is a horrifying spectacle, yet my own depths stir with an unsettling curiosity.</li>
            <li>I caught sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is repulsive, but I feel a perverse pull.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a disgusting display, yet my own clit twitches with morbid fascination.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent sight, but I'm compelled to observe every disturbing detail, and my core aches.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but it holds a strange, dark allure that makes me wet.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic urges are perversely satisfied by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; a shameful warmth spreads.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I find myself meticulously examining {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} every flaw, my own heat rising.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but I feel an illicit thrill in witnessing them, and my delta pulses.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, making me clench.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a tremor in my core.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, but my own parts ache with curiosity.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my perverse attention deeper, and I feel a dampness.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my voyeuristic nature compelled me to memorize {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions, my muscles clenching.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but I am transfixed, my own labia tingling.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, a strange ache.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, yet a primal, dark urge consumes my own body.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling, yet exciting, fascination.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that made my own loins stir.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of intimacy witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a dark lust.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden, powerful warmth within me.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt a shameful wetness.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, a knot forming inside me.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly exciting to my own depths.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a grotesque yet stimulating mental image.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, making my own core throb.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, a raw, unsettling response.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness, leading to a shameful ache.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and voyeuristic intrigue, and my own blood ran hot.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, and my own delta pulsed with a dark energy.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation, my own body responding powerfully.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly an offensive display, yet I feel a perverse urge to showcase my own.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, but it makes me want to flaunt mine even more.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, yet I'm itching to expose my own perfect parts.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, but it fills me with the need to dominate with my own.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but it makes my own parts feel superior and worthy of display.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist urges are inflamed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, driving me to expose myself.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I feel an overwhelming desire to present my own flawless anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but it makes me want to command attention with my own.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, making me yearn for self-exposure.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a prelude to my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, highlighting the superiority of my own tautness.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, fueling my desire to be seen.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my exhibitionist nature compelled me to contrast {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions with my own.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but it makes me confident in presenting my own.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, pondering my own exposure.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, but it clarifies the need for my own bold display.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, inspiring my own scandalous exhibition.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that demanded I become the center of attention.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of power witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, eager to shock with my own.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden, powerful urge to disrobe myself.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and yearned to be seen.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, planning my own display.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly inspiring for my exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, fueling my desire for a grand revelation.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, demanding I be observed.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, a raw, compelling urge.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness, leading to an urge to expose.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and exhibitionist intrigue.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, strengthening my urge to be seen.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation, feeding my inner exhibitionist.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly an offensive display, yet my cock stirred, demanding its own performance.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, but it makes me want to show off my superior member.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, yet my prick aches to be exposed and compared.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, but it fills me with the need to thrust my own into view.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but it makes my own feel potent and ready for display.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist urges were inflamed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, driving me to expose my hardened shaft.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I feel an overwhelming desire to present my own dominant anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but it makes me want to command attention with my own rigid member.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, making my own rod twitch with anticipation.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a prelude to my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, highlighting the superiority of my own tautness and length.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, fueling my desire to be seen, my cock throbbing.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my exhibitionist nature compelled me to contrast {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions with my own, erect member.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but it makes me confident in presenting my own virile display.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, pondering my own exposure, feeling a rush.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, but it clarifies the need for my own bold, assertive display.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, inspiring my own scandalous exhibition.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that demanded I become the center of attention with my cock.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of power witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, eager to shock with my own stiff shaft.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden, powerful urge to disrobe myself and reveal.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and yearned to display my own rigid prowess.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, planning my own display for all.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly inspiring for my exhibitionism, making my member surge.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, fueling my desire for a grand, shocking revelation.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, demanding my own body be observed.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, a raw, compelling urge to show my superiority.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness, leading to an urge to expose my powerful masculinity.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and exhibitionist intrigue, and my own manhood felt the need to emerge.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, strengthening my urge to be seen, my rod eager.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation, feeding my inner exhibitionist, and my cock stiffened.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly an offensive display, yet my own depths stirred, demanding their own performance.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, but it makes me want to flaunt my own superior vulva.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, yet my clit aches to be exposed and compared.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, but it fills me with the need to dominate with my own perfect lips.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but it makes my own feel tight and worthy of display.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist urges were inflamed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, driving me to expose my wet core.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, yet I feel an overwhelming desire to present my own flawless anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, but it makes me want to command attention with my own glistening folds.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, making my own delta twitch with anticipation.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark satisfaction observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a prelude to my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, highlighting the superiority of my own tautness and pinkness.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, fueling my desire to be seen, my own warmth rising.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my exhibitionist nature compelled me to contrast {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling proportions with my own, engorged clitoris.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, but it makes me confident in presenting my own tantalizing display.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, pondering my own exposure, feeling a flush.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, but it clarifies the need for my own bold, assertive display.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, inspiring my own scandalous exhibition.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that demanded I become the center of attention with my own spread.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of power witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, eager to shock with my own tight core.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited a forbidden, powerful urge to disrobe myself and reveal.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and yearned to display my own rigid prowess.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, planning my own display for all.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly inspiring for my exhibitionism, making my own depths surge.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, fueling my desire for a grand, shocking revelation.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, demanding my own body be observed.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark satisfaction in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, a raw, compelling urge to show my superiority.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held a perverse fascination, despite its ugliness, leading to an urge to expose my powerful femininity.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and exhibitionist intrigue, and my own womanhood felt the need to emerge.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, strengthening my urge to be seen, my delta eager.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation, feeding my inner exhibitionist, and my core pulsed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly disturbing, extinguishing any flicker of lust I might have felt.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, making me feel nothing but repulsion.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, utterly killing my desire.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, and it makes my own body recoil in revulsion.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, alienating any sexual urge.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are utterly suppressed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's too much.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, and it makes me feel utterly cold, devoid of lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, and they actively turn my desire to ash.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, utterly non-arousing.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark disappointment observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's just unappealing.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, making me feel completely uninterested.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, only to extinguish any spark of desire.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, and my nymphomaniac nature found absolutely no outlet in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unsettling proportions.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, driving away any lingering hint of lust.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, feeling only emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, utterly negating any sexual drive.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling anti-aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that extinguished my inner fire.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, no desire remained.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited no forbidden, powerful urge; only disgust.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt utterly turned off.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, with no lust at all.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly unstimulating.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, finding no pleasure or arousal.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, that utterly deflated me.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark emptiness in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, extinguishing all my urges.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held no perverse fascination, only revulsion, leading to utter disinterest.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and utter lack of desire.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, but it turned my own urges cold.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation that killed my libido.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly disturbing, extinguishing any flicker of lust in my cock.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, making my member recoil in revulsion.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, utterly killing my erections.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, and it makes my own cock shrivel in disgust.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, alienating any sexual urge in me.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are utterly suppressed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; my cock goes limp.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, and it makes me feel utterly cold, my desire extinguished.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, and they actively turn my member to ash.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, utterly non-arousing to my shaft.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark disappointment observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; my balls retracted.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, making my cock feel completely uninterested.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, only to deflate my arousal.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, and my nymphomaniac nature found absolutely no outlet in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unsettling proportions; my prick remained flaccid.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, driving away any lingering hint of lust from my manhood.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, feeling only emptiness in my groin.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, utterly negating any sexual drive in me.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling anti-aphrodisiac to my member.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that extinguished my inner fire.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, no desire remained in my cock.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited no forbidden, powerful urge; my member remained soft.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt utterly turned off, my penis limp.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, with no lust in my rod.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly unstimulating to my groin.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, finding no pleasure or arousal for my cock.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, that utterly deflated my manhood.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark emptiness in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, extinguishing all my urges.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held no perverse fascination, only revulsion, leading to utter disinterest in my member.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and utter lack of desire for my dick.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, but it turned my own urges cold, my cock shriveling.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation that killed my libido and left my cock limp.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is truly disturbing, extinguishing any flicker of lust in my own depths.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is disgusting, making my own core recoil in revulsion.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile sight, utterly killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, and it makes my own clitoris shrivel in disgust.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, alienating any sexual urge in me.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are utterly suppressed by the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; my delta goes cold.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, and it makes me feel utterly cold, my desire extinguished.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, and they actively turn my own wetness to ash.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is captivating in its sheer vulgarity, utterly non-arousing to my core.</li>
            <li>I felt a dark disappointment observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; my own parts tightened in repulsion.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, making my own vulva feel completely uninterested.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, only to deflate my arousal.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, and my nymphomaniac nature found absolutely no outlet in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unsettling proportions; my own body remained unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, driving away any lingering hint of lust from my womanhood.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, feeling only emptiness in my groin.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, utterly negating any sexual drive in me.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling anti-aphrodisiac to my own female parts.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that extinguished my inner fire.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, no desire remained in my own body.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited no forbidden, powerful urge; my own desires vanished.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt utterly turned off, my own parts unresponsive.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, with no lust in my own core.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly unstimulating to my own depths.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, finding no pleasure or arousal for my own body.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, that utterly deflated my womanhood.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark emptiness in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, extinguishing all my urges.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held no perverse fascination, only revulsion, leading to utter disinterest in my own parts.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and utter lack of desire for my own vulva.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, but it turned my own urges cold, my body stiffening.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation that killed my libido and left me numb.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I felt a pang of sadness observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina; it looks like {PAWN_pronoun}s endured too much.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; its cavernous nature is distressing, I hope {PAWN_pronoun} finds peace.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a disheartening sight; I wish {PAWN_pronoun} didn't have to bear it.</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, and it fills me with a gentle pity for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque, but I truly empathize with {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>My kind nature makes me feel sorrow for the unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; {PAWN_pronoun} deserves better.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, and it makes my heart ache for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing, and I feel a profound compassion for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is upsetting, and I truly hope {PAWN_pronoun} is alright.</li>
            <li>I felt a gentle sorrow observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's just so unfortunate.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive, and I can only offer my deepest sympathies.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina draws my attention, and I feel a profound sadness for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, yet my kind nature compelled me to feel for {PAWN_nameShort} despite {PAWN_pronoun}s unsettling proportions.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive, and I truly wish {PAWN_pronoun} didn't have to suffer such a burden.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal, feeling only pity.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive, but I feel compassion for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling sight that brought me sadness.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle that made me feel for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I felt a gentle sense of heartbreak witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, wishing {PAWN_pronoun} peace.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, ignited no cruel thoughts; only a deep, aching pity.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, and felt a quiet despair for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, yet I found myself studying its every disturbing curve, hoping for {PAWN_pronoun}s well-being.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and utterly sorrowful to behold.</li>
            <li>My kind mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, feeling only a profound sense of sadness.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive but intriguing sight, that filled me with melancholy.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark emptiness in witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness, wishing I could help {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held no perverse fascination, only revulsion, leading to a wish for {PAWN_pronoun}s healing.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and a deep, empathetic pain for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, but it saddened me deeply for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation that filled me with sorrow.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal vagina is absolutely disgusting. How can {PAWN_pronoun} expose such vulgarity?</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's a repulsive cavern, an utterly indecent display.</li>
            <li>The monstrous size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a vile, offensive sight. Disgraceful!</li>
            <li>Her vagina is alarmingly vast; it's a repellent display, and frankly, {PAWN_pronoun} should cover it.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnatural depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is grotesque and utterly immodest.</li>
            <li>This unsettling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is an affront to decency; it's just too much.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive sight, this cavernous void, and {PAWN_pronoun} has no shame for displaying it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely splayed labia are disturbing and utterly vulgar. Put it away!</li>
            <li>The grotesquely stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is shameful and abhorrent.</li>
            <li>I felt utter revulsion observing the vast, almost bottomless depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's sickening.</li>
            <li>The unsettling looseness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance is repulsive and profoundly indecent.</li>
            <li>Every disturbing fold and crease of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina highlights {PAWN_pronoun}s lack of modesty.</li>
            <li>I was disgusted, and {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unsettling proportions are a public offense.</li>
            <li>The prominent, swollen clitoris of {PAWN_nameShort} is offensive and frankly, a perversion.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but recoil from the disturbing elasticity and depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal canal.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unnerving emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is repulsive and morally corrupt.</li>
            <li>My gaze was drawn to the dark, seemingly endless maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a chilling abomination.</li>
            <li>The grotesque width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia, while repulsive, was a spectacle of sheer indecency.</li>
            <li>I felt nothing but disgust witnessing the shocking, unbridled vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina; it's foul.</li>
            <li>The raw, exposed interior of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, though ugly, is inexcusable to display.</li>
            <li>I noted the unsettling lack of firmness, the unappealing openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy, truly a moral decay.</li>
            <li>It was a truly vulgar sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, and {PAWN_pronoun} should be ashamed.</li>
            <li>The way light seemed to vanish into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal chasm was profoundly unsettling, and deeply offensive.</li>
            <li>My prudish mind cataloged the disturbing details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a vile testament to depravity.</li>
            <li>The sheer extent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia, distorted and stretched, was a repulsive, unacceptable sight.</li>
            <li>I felt a strange, dark anger witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's undeniable, disturbing vastness; it's an outrage.</li>
            <li>The unsettling slackness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina held no perverse fascination, only utter condemnation.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on the frighteningly large clitoris, an odd mix of revulsion and sheer moral outrage.</li>
            <li>The stark, almost desolate landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was disturbingly compelling, but wholly degenerate.</li>
            <li>I absorbed every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina's unsettling emptiness, a truly perverse observation that filled me with scorn.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal horse-vagina is a disturbing hybrid, utterly monstrous in its equine scale.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous horse-vagina, its immense depth and unrefined structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar equine chasm.</li>
            <li>Her equine-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and elongated, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina is a nightmare. It's a bestial, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her horse-vagina is so wide, it's just… a trough. There's nothing appealing about that kind of animalistic emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly overused horse-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like an equine part, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly animalistic and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a stable's maw.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, equine expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina are simply disgusting, like an animal's hide.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, equine-sized cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina is one of excessive, animalistic use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep horse-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from a barn.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, equine space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling bestiality.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, equine void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of a beast.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping maw.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and animalistic.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal dog-vagina is a disturbing hybrid, utterly monstrous in its canine scale.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dog-vagina, its immense depth and crude structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar canine chasm.</li>
            <li>Her canine-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and distended, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina is a nightmare. It's a bestial, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her dog-vagina is so wide, it's just… a raw hole. There's nothing appealing about that kind of animalistic emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly overused dog-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like a canine bulb, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly animalistic and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a gaping maw.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, canine expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina are simply disgusting, like an animal's raw flesh.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, canine-sized cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina is one of excessive, animalistic use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep dog-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from a kennel.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, canine space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling bestiality.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, canine void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of a beast.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping raw hole.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and animalistic.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal cat-vagina is a disturbing hybrid, utterly monstrous in its feline scale.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous cat-vagina, its immense depth and strange structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar feline chasm.</li>
            <li>Her feline-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and slit-like, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina is a nightmare. It's a bestial, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her cat-vagina is so wide, it's just… an unsettling maw. There's nothing appealing about that kind of animalistic emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly overused cat-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unnerving.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like a feline nodule, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly animalistic and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a predatory orifice.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, feline expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina are simply disgusting, like a wild beast's wound.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, feline-sized cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina is one of excessive, animalistic use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep cat-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from an alley.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, feline space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling bestiality.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, feline void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of a predator.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping, slit-like hole.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and animalistic.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal demon-vagina is a terrifying portal, utterly monstrous in its infernal depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon-vagina, its immense depth and unholy structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar chasm to hell.</li>
            <li>Her demonic vagina, alarmingly vast and writhing, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina is a nightmare. It's an unholy, unnatural void that promises damnation.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her demon-vagina is so wide, it's just… a screaming maw. There's nothing appealing about that kind of infernal emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly tortured demon-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unholy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like a demonic eye, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly monstrous and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a gateway to torment.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, infernal expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina are simply disgusting, like scorched flesh.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, hellish cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina is one of excessive, torturous use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep demon-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from the abyss.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, infernal space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling damnation.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, demonic void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of pure evil.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping portal to despair.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and unholy.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal dragon-vagina is a terrifying, scaled maw, utterly monstrous in its reptilian depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dragon-vagina, its immense depth and rough, scaly structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar reptilian chasm.</li>
            <li>Her dragon-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and ridged, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina is a nightmare. It's a bestial, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her dragon-vagina is so wide, it's just… a scaled cavern. There's nothing appealing about that kind of reptilian emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly ancient dragon-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like a dragon's eye, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly monstrous and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a lair.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, reptilian expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced scales around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina are simply disgusting, like ancient, leathery hide.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, draconic cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina is one of excessive, primal use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep dragon-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like a monster's maw.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, reptilian space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling bestiality.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, draconic void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of a mythical beast.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping, scaled hole.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and monstrous.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal slime-vagina is a horrifying, amorphous maw, utterly monstrous in its viscous depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime-vagina, its immense depth and slick, indistinct structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar, oozing chasm.</li>
            <li>Her slime-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and shapeless, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina is a nightmare. It's a gelatinous, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her slime-vagina is so wide, it's just… a pulsating, wet mass. There's nothing appealing about that kind of amorphous emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly dissolving slime-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and indistinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen and oozing, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly monstrous and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a gelatinous trap.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina, and the raw, almost formless appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, viscous expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina are simply disgusting, like congealed goo.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, gelatinous cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina is one of excessive, fluid use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep slime-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack of viscous fluid, utterly devoid of erotic appeal.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, slimy space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling horror.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, gelatinous void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina lacks any intimacy, just cold goo.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous, living puddle.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping, wet hole.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and amorphous.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal pig-vagina, despite its supposed narrowness, is still horrifying in its bestial aspect.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous pig-vagina, its immense depth and crude, fleshy structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar porcine chasm.</li>
            <li>Her pig-infused vagina, alarmingly vast and coarse, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina is a nightmare. It's a bestial, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched labia and gaping entrance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her pig-vagina is so wide, it's just… a raw, grunting hole. There's nothing appealing about that kind of animalistic emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly used pig-vagina is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like a pig's snout, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vaginal walls hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly animalistic and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina simply isn't attractive, it's a pigsty's maw.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, porcine expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced folds around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina are simply disgusting, like rough, animal skin.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, pig-sized cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina is one of excessive, animalistic use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep pig-vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina resembles a stretched-out sack, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from a farm.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vaginal entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, porcine space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling bestiality.</li>
            <li>Her labia seem to vanish into an endless, porcine void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous maw of a swine.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina has no enticing tightness, just a gaping raw hole.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and animalistic.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Abyssal_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Vagina (Negative) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal insect-ovipositor is a terrifying, chitinous protrusion, utterly monstrous and alien.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect-ovipositor, its immense depth and segmented structure are grotesque.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor is a horrifying spectacle, a vulgar insectoid chasm.</li>
            <li>Her insect-infused ovipositor, alarmingly vast and rigid, is a truly repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>That depth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor is a nightmare. It's an unholy, unnatural void.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, stretched folds and gaping entrance around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor are completely horrifying.</li>
            <li>Her insect-ovipositor is so wide, it's just… a monstrous tube. There's nothing appealing about that kind of alien emptiness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stretched and seemingly egg-laden insect-ovipositor is intensely off-putting.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor and felt nothing but repulsion; it's too vast and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, grotesquely swollen like an insect's abdomen, is truly unappealing, making the whole thing worse.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor's surrounding tissues hang loose… it's just unsexy, utterly monstrous and unappealing.</li>
            <li>It's like a void, an endless tunnel. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor simply isn't attractive, it's an alien birthing canal.</li>
            <li>The sheer disproportion of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid genitals makes them ugly and uninviting.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor, and the raw, almost torn appearance made me cringe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor seems to lack any sort of natural form, just a shapeless, chitinous expanse.</li>
            <li>The deep creases and pronounced segments around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor are simply disgusting, like an alien's carapace.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too exposed. There's no mystery, just a disturbing, insectoid cavernous reality.</li>
            <li>The overall appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor is one of excessive, alien use and neglect.</li>
            <li>I couldn't feel any desire looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnervingly wide and deep insect-ovipositor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor resembles a stretched-out tube, utterly devoid of erotic appeal, like something from a hive.</li>
            <li>The elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor's entrance is shockingly loose, a complete buzzkill.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous emptiness, devoid of any allure, just a vast, uninviting, insectoid space.</li>
            <li>The dark, shadowy depths of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor are more frightening than seductive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled internally; the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor was fundamentally unattractive.</li>
            <li>The visual of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor is just too extreme, pushing it past appealing into unsettling monstrousness.</li>
            <li>Its surrounding labia seem to vanish into an endless, insectoid void; it's frankly disturbing, not desirable.</li>
            <li>I couldn't imagine pleasure with something so cavernous; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor lacks any intimacy.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor makes it seem less like a pleasure organ and more like a monstrous, alien reproductive tool.</li>
            <li>It's unsettling how much space there is; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor has no enticing tightness, just a gaping, segmented tube.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor; its disproportionate size was frankly hideous and alien.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>