<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--general unisex opinion about young female-->
<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina; it’s almost a joke, isn’t it?</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pitifully small vagina, barely noticeable with a closed position that lacked any allure.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening that was tightly closed, with an uninviting appearance.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, shriveled vagina, with a wrinkled and unattractive exterior.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was almost nonexistent, with a closed position that was as uninviting as a sealed door.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, pinched opening that was more like a slit than a vagina, with a harsh and unappealing texture.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled, miniature vagina that looked like it had been withered by time, with a wrinkled and unattractive exterior.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina with repugnance, the minuscule size was a pitiful sight, a mere slit of femininity.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina  with disdain, the microscopic opening was a poor excuse for a womanhood, a weak and insipid display of femininity.</li>
			<li>I gazed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina with disappointment, the tiny size was a letdown, a feeble attempt at womanliness.</li>
			<li>I couldn't help but wince as I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic vaginal opening. It was as if nature had forgotten to equip {PAWN_possessive} with the necessary tools for intimacy.</li>
			<li>As I forced myself to glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic vaginal opening, I was met with a sight that made my skin crawl. The clitoris, if it could even be called that, was a minuscule nub, barely protruding from the surrounding tissue. The depth, if one could even call it that, was almost nonexistent, begging to be left untouched.</li>
			<li>I couldn't help but wince as I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic vaginal opening. It looked almost infantile, the labia barely visible and the clitoris practically non-existent. The thought of attempting penetration made me shudder.</li>
			<li>I saw a slit, barely visible, almost like a child's. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic vaginal opening texture was smooth and uninviting, the clitoris a mere stub. It made me shudder to think of penetration.</li>
			<li>I chanced upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mere crease, a shadow of what I expected. The texture was as delicate as a petal, the clitoris a mere speck, barely distinguishable from the surrounding skin. It all seemed so trivial, so insignificant.</li>
			<li>I beheld {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny orifice, reminiscent of a baby's mouth. The texture was smooth and unblemished, the clitoris a tiny kernel, barely deserving of notice. It was a strange, unsettling sight, a peculiar aberration of nature.</li>
			<li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small cleft, a miniature version of its intended purpose. The texture was fine and almost nonexistent, the clitoris a mere bump, hardly noticeable. It all seemed so fragile, so vulnerable, a mere whisper of its true purpose.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} reduced portal, a shrunken remnant of its destined form. The texture was sheer and translucent, the clitoris a minuscule node, barely discernible. It was a pitiful sight, a weak and watered-down version of the real thing.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feeble aperture, a diminished facsimile of its rightful form. The texture was thin and frail, the clitoris a tiny knot, barely qualifying as such. It was a disappointing spectacle, a sad and shriveled imitation.</li>
			<li>I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule divide, a diminutive fraction of its intended size. The texture was barely there, the clitoris a mere suggestion, hardly worth acknowledging. It was a laughable sight, a comical caricature of its true self.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia, I couldn't help but notice the disappointingly small labia, almost fused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to mock the very idea of pleasure, a truly pitiful sight.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would disappoint even the least discerning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked incapable of providing any real experience.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost insulting, an unrewarding spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry labia were barely distinguishable, forming an uninviting, tight closure.</li>
            <li>The almost invisible clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offered no promise of excitement or sensation.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insignificant vaginal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia were so understated, they offered no visual appeal, just a pinched, uninviting seam.</li>
            <li>The depth, or lack thereof, of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to promise only frustration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy suggested a complete absence of the expected form, disturbingly small.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkably small outer lips, offering nothing of interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was so recessed, it made me question its very existence.</li>
            <li>The tightly shut, tiny opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sheer lack of presence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature genitalia.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>That young one's parts are barely there, such a meager display for a woman.</li>
            <li>Feh, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening is a disappointment, not much promise for the future.</li>
            <li>I've seen larger keyholes than {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} meager excuse for a vagina; a truly sorry sight.</li>
            <li>Such small labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, barely visible, makes one wonder about her maturity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry depth, it's clear she wouldn't satisfy a real man.</li>
            <li>A woman's parts should have substance; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a whisper, a disappointment.</li>
            <li>I remember when women had something to show; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just a sad, shriveled little thing.</li>
            <li>Too small, too tight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is clearly lacking. Not worth a second glance.</li>
            <li>What a waste, such a young body with such an insignificant opening. Pity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is barely noticeable; a man needs more than a dimple.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris is almost nonexistent, a sign of what little pleasure she could offer.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia cling shut, she's clearly not built for purpose.</li>
            <li>I've seen bigger orifices on a rat; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a joke.</li>
            <li>That young one's 'parts' are so minuscule, one might mistake them for a child's.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is barely a crease, promising no depth or sensation.</li>
            <li>A truly pathetic excuse for womanhood; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny features are a blight.</li>
            <li>She's got nothing to show, that one. Her labia are practically nonexistent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled anatomy just reinforces my belief in proper womanly forms.</li>
            <li>Such a small clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. What a disappointment for any man seeking enjoyment.</li>
            <li>I’ve seen better proportions on an infant than {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} underdeveloped parts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} little pucker is as inviting as a locked box.</li>
            <li>Barely discernible, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia offer no appeal, just a closed, uninteresting seam.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris truly is a letdown.</li>
            <li>What a waste of youth, such a tiny, unremarkable set of parts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy suggests a complete lack of development, quite sad to see.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, underdeveloped opening is a stark reminder of what's missing.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry opening; truly, a sad sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insignificant labia provide no visual pleasure, just a closed, uninviting slit.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, almost invisible on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, offers no promise of any sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shallow, narrow entrance looks utterly unfulfilling.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even my aged member feels too grand for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic opening. A real letdown.</li>
            <li>I eyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, pitiful parts, and felt my own desires shrivel in disgust.</li>
            <li>A peek at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} almost non-existent vagina made me chuckle; what a child's toy.</li>
            <li>Such small labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, barely a hint of anything, leaving me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shallow, uninviting slit leaves my old desires utterly unprovoked.</li>
            <li>My curiosity was instantly extinguished by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insignificant opening. No spark.</li>
            <li>What a pathetic sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro-vagina. It makes my own body ache with disinterest.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt no stir, only a profound disappointment at her miniature parts.</li>
            <li>The lack of fullness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is almost amusing; a deflating spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, a mere speck, confirmed my expectations of a total lack of excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, unwelcoming parts are a stark contrast to any pleasant memory I might have.</li>
            <li>My own instrument feels positively massive compared to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sad, tiny aperture.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and my blood ran colder than usual. No appeal there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening offered no promise, no thrill; just a dismissive shrug from me.</li>
            <li>Even in my advanced years, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of depth is clear. A true anatomical failure.</li>
            <li>I barely registered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts, so small and utterly uninteresting.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are practically fused, offering no entry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, or whatever passes for it, is a cruel joke.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt my old engine refuse to even sputter. Pointless.</li>
            <li>The extreme youth and undeveloped nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts are a stark, unappealing reality.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia, a truly uninviting prospect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to mock any notion of arousal; utterly useless.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would disappoint even a novice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked incapable of exciting anything.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly closed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost insulting, an unrewarding spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter. My own desires remained dormant.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for any man.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, leaving my urges completely untouched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Bless her heart, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is barely formed. Such a delicate, almost childlike, structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are so small, it's a wonder they offer any protection at all.</li>
            <li>That tiny clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} looks like it's never known a moment's pleasure.</li>
            <li>I've seen more substantial openings on infants. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly underdeveloped.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina must be truly lacking, a shallow affair.</li>
            <li>Such a small entrance for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it makes one wonder if she'll ever experience true womanhood.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is so slight, it almost looks like a defect, bless her.</li>
            <li>It's a pity, really. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny parts offer little promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner labia are practically non-existent; such a tight, uninviting form.</li>
            <li>I can scarcely believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is. A disappointing sight.</li>
            <li>She's got nothing to show for herself. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts are barely there.</li>
            <li>Poor thing, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy seems almost incomplete.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is so tight and closed, it's truly unappealing.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia are so minimal, it hints at unfulfilled potential.</li>
            <li>Her vaginal lips are barely distinguishable; a very narrow, uninviting form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is almost invisible, suggesting a lack of vitality.</li>
            <li>A mere slit, barely visible. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looks like it's never been used.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smallness is almost painful to witness. Such a delicate, frail looking thing.</li>
            <li>I pity {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Her parts are simply not what they should be.</li>
            <li>The shriveled appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad sight indeed.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the undeveloped labia, truly an uninviting prospect for intimacy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful really.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, even for a woman.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, a pity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ugh, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is practically non-existent. What a turn-off.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia and instantly lost all interest. Nothing there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so small it's insulting. Barely a bump.</li>
            <li>That opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so tight, it looks like it's never been used, or couldn't be.</li>
            <li>What a disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} depth looks like it would be utterly unfulfilling.</li>
            <li>Seriously? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is just… too small. Not appealing at all.</li>
            <li>I’ve seen better openings on coin purses. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a joke.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external parts are just an instant mood killer.</li>
            <li>No thanks. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule vagina is just not what I'm looking for.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} confirmed it; absolutely nothing enticing about that size.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry labia are barely distinguishable, completely lacking any visual allure.</li>
            <li>The almost invisible clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no promise of any pleasure.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insignificant vaginal opening. It's a real letdown.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are so understated, they offer no visual appeal, just a pinched, uninviting seam.</li>
            <li>The depth, or lack thereof, of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to promise only frustration. No thanks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy suggested a complete absence of the expected form; disturbingly small and unattractive.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkably small outer lips, offering nothing of interest, especially to me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was so recessed, it made me question its very existence, making any thought of intimacy disappear.</li>
            <li>The tightly shut, tiny opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a definite turn-off. Absolutely unappealing.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sheer lack of presence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature genitalia. Not my type at all.</li>
            <li>That tiny opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} suggests a frustratingly shallow experience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are so small, they offer no visual appeal whatsoever.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia confirmed my initial impression: utterly uninteresting.</li>
            <li>The pathetic size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looks less like a woman's and more like a barely-there slit.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and my desires instantly plummeted. No appeal there.</li>
            <li>The lack of curves and depth in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts is a significant disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening looks like it would be a struggle, not a pleasure.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is just too small; it doesn't even register as attractive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled appearance is a stark reminder of what's missing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina; its insignificance was surprisingly off-putting.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny parts was a letdown, offering little visual interest.</li>
            <li>The lack of substantial form in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia was a disappointment to witness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, barely discernible, offered no visual stimulation.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and found only a minimal, uninspiring opening.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic urges were quickly extinguished by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} underdeveloped anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a pity; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts offered nothing truly captivating to observe.</li>
            <li>The constricted nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening was far less intriguing than anticipated.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia and my gaze drifted away; truly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal area was so small, it barely registered as a point of interest.</li>
            <li>The paltry labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} were a visual disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was so understated, it barely warranted a second look.</li>
            <li>I'd hoped for more detail, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy was too small to be engaging.</li>
            <li>A quick look confirmed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insignificance, failing to hold my attention.</li>
            <li>The unappealing tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance offered no voyeuristic thrill.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts, but found nothing intriguing due to their size.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina was simply boring to observe, lacking any complexity.</li>
            <li>The tiny, almost hidden nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was a letdown.</li>
            <li>It was a fleeting, unrewarding glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minimal external genitalia.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal anatomy offered little to explore with my eyes, a truly flat sight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia, truly an uninviting prospect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful really.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional to my observant eye.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My own excitement withered at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pitifully small vagina.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny parts, and my desires felt mocked by their sheer insignificance.</li>
            <li>A peek at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} almost non-existent vagina made my own member recoil.</li>
            <li>Such small labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, barely a hint of anything, leaving my senses utterly cold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shallow, uninviting slit leaves my urges utterly unprovoked.</li>
            <li>My curiosity was instantly extinguished by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insignificant opening. No spark for me.</li>
            <li>What a pathetic sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro-vagina. It makes my own body ache with disinterest.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt no stir, only profound disappointment at her miniature parts.</li>
            <li>The lack of fullness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is almost amusing; a truly deflating spectacle for my eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, a mere speck, confirmed my expectations of a total lack of excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, unwelcoming parts are a stark contrast to any pleasant memory I might have, leaving me unmoved.</li>
            <li>My own instrument feels positively massive compared to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sad, tiny aperture.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and my blood ran colder than usual. No appeal there, nothing for me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening offered no promise, no thrill; just a dismissive shrug from my body.</li>
            <li>Even in my heightened state, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of depth is clear. A true anatomical failure, sexually speaking.</li>
            <li>I barely registered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts, so small and utterly uninteresting, leaving my desires completely flat.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are practically fused, offering no entry or pleasure to imagine.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris, or whatever passes for it, is a cruel joke, failing to excite.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt my old engine refuse to even sputter. Pointless for me.</li>
            <li>The extreme youth and undeveloped nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} parts are a stark, unappealing reality to my perverted eye.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia, truly an uninviting prospect for my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and unstimulating for me.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave any man wanting, myself included.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of exciting my perverted mind.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut, causing my own arousal to falter.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, leaving me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for my desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, completely extinguishing my lust.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a voyeur, leaving me disappointed.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, offering no perverse pleasure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina, and my own parts felt superior in comparison.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia left me utterly unimpressed; no warmth there.</li>
            <li>The insignificant clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemed to mock any notion of female pleasure.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt a wave of disappointment; such a constricted opening.</li>
            <li>My own desires cooled at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} undeveloped depth. So unappealing.</li>
            <li>What a flat, uninteresting view; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy offered no intrigue for my voyeuristic eye.</li>
            <li>I've seen more substantial folds on a pillow. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a letdown.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external parts did nothing to ignite my female curiosity.</li>
            <li>No thrill here. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule vagina is simply not worth dwelling on.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} confirmed it: absolutely nothing enticing about that size, even for me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry labia are barely distinguishable, completely lacking any female allure.</li>
            <li>The almost invisible clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no promise of any pleasure, even by observation.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insignificant vaginal opening. It's a sad sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are so understated, they offer no visual appeal, just a pinched, uninviting seam, leaving me cold.</li>
            <li>The depth, or lack thereof, of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to promise only frustration, even for a female observer.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy suggested a complete absence of the expected form; disturbingly small and unattractive to me.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkably small outer lips, offering nothing of interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was so recessed, it made me question its very existence, extinguishing my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>The tightly shut, tiny opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a definite turn-off. Absolutely unappealing.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sheer lack of presence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature genitalia. Not what I hoped to see.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the undeveloped labia, truly an uninviting prospect for intimacy. My own body felt a chill.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and unstimulating.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting, certainly me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction or curiosity.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut, extinguishing any desire to observe further.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, making my own parts feel superior.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for my voyeuristic tendencies.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, truly a letdown.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a female observer.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional to my observant eye, dulling my senses.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Exhibiting these small parts would be a disgrace. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is pathetic.</li>
            <li>There's nothing to show off with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insignificant labia.</li>
            <li>Why even bother revealing such a tiny, uninteresting clitoris? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a joke.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} restricted opening is hardly a sight for exhibition.</li>
            <li>I'd be embarrassed to expose something as paltry as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>This kind of smallness on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is definitely not for public display.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} would simply go unnoticed; pointless to exhibit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features makes me question why anyone would reveal it.</li>
            <li>There's no pride in displaying such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is an insult to any exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>I would never expose such a pitifully small vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. What a letdown.</li>
            <li>The underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are barely worth a glance, let alone a display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's not even a focal point for exhibition.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no exhibitionist's thrill.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad display, truly unsuited for public viewing.</li>
            <li>Why would anyone show off such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disservice to exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to be appreciated, even by an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>I’d rather keep my own parts hidden than reveal something as uninspiring as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy for exhibition; utterly forgettable.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina make it undesirable to expose.</li>
            <li>Exposing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy would be an embarrassment, given its almost non-existent labia.</li>
            <li>The tiny clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wouldn't elicit any reaction, completely unsuited for exhibition.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggests a depth so shallow, it's not even worth a fleeting glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, offers nothing for the audience to appreciate in an exhibition.</li>
            <li>Revealing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy would be entirely unappealing, no audience would be pleased.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offer no inviting prospect for display, just a closed, uninteresting slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for any exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is so tight, it hints at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying form, a visual failure.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for exhibition purposes.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional for an exhibition.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My own magnificent member would simply dwarf {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, pathetic excuse for a vagina.</li>
            <li>Exhibiting such an insignificant thing as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia is laughable. Mine is far more impressive.</li>
            <li>I'd be embarrassed to reveal myself to such a miniscule, unexciting clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening is hardly a challenge for me to display.</li>
            <li>My pride in my own form would be shattered by having to acknowledge {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry anatomy.</li>
            <li>This kind of smallness on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is definitely not for my public display.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} would simply go unnoticed next to my own; pointless to exhibit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features makes me question why anyone would reveal it, especially to me.</li>
            <li>There's no pride in displaying such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it reflects poorly on me.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is an insult to any exhibitionist like myself.</li>
            <li>I would never expose myself to such a pitifully small vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. What a letdown for my own display.</li>
            <li>The underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are barely worth a glance, let alone being witnessed by my grand display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's not even a focal point for an exhibition where I'm present.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no exhibitionist's thrill to me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad display, truly unsuited for public viewing alongside my own.</li>
            <li>Why would anyone show off such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disservice to exhibitionism, and to me.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to be appreciated, even by an exhibitionist with grand parts like mine.</li>
            <li>I’d rather keep my own parts hidden than reveal something as uninspiring as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, which diminishes my own display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy for exhibition; utterly forgettable when I’m around.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina make it undesirable to expose, especially next to my own.</li>
            <li>Exposing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy would be an embarrassment to my own grand display, given its almost non-existent labia.</li>
            <li>The tiny clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wouldn't elicit any reaction from an audience, completely unsuited for an exhibition with me.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggests a depth so shallow, it's not even worth a fleeting glance, especially when compared to my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, offers nothing for the audience to appreciate in an exhibition where I'm present.</li>
            <li>Revealing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy would be entirely unappealing, no audience would be pleased, certainly not with my comparison.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offer no inviting prospect for display, just a closed, uninteresting slit, making my own appear even grander.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for any exhibitionist like me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is so tight, it hints at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying form, a visual failure compared to my expectations.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for exhibition purposes, especially alongside my own.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional for an exhibition, making my own display seem vastly superior.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My own generous form would utterly overshadow {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pathetic, tiny excuse for a vagina.</li>
            <li>Exhibiting such an insignificant thing as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia is laughable. Mine offers so much more.</li>
            <li>I'd be embarrassed to reveal myself with such a minuscule, unexciting clitoris as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening is hardly a challenge for a true exhibitionist like myself.</li>
            <li>My pride in my own body would be shattered by having to acknowledge {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry anatomy.</li>
            <li>This kind of smallness on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is definitely not for my public display.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} would simply go unnoticed next to my own; pointless to exhibit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features makes me question why anyone would reveal it, especially to another woman.</li>
            <li>There's no pride in displaying such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it reflects poorly on our gender.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is an insult to any exhibitionist like myself.</li>
            <li>I would never expose myself with such a pitifully small vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. What a letdown for my own display.</li>
            <li>The underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are barely worth a glance, let alone being witnessed by my grand display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's not even a focal point for an exhibition where I'm present.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no exhibitionist's thrill to me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad display, truly unsuited for public viewing alongside my own.</li>
            <li>Why would anyone show off such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disservice to exhibitionism, and to women generally.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to be appreciated, even by an exhibitionist with grand parts like mine.</li>
            <li>I’d rather keep my own parts hidden than reveal something as uninspiring as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, which diminishes my own display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy for exhibition; utterly forgettable when I’m around.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina make it undesirable to expose, especially next to my own.</li>
            <li>Exposing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy would be an embarrassment to my own grand display, given its almost non-existent labia.</li>
            <li>The tiny clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wouldn't elicit any reaction from an audience, completely unsuited for an exhibition with me.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggests a depth so shallow, it's not even worth a fleeting glance, especially when compared to my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, offers nothing for the audience to appreciate in an exhibition where I'm present.</li>
            <li>Revealing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy would be entirely unappealing, no audience would be pleased, certainly not with my comparison.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offer no inviting prospect for display, just a closed, uninteresting slit, making my own appear even grander.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for any exhibitionist like me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is so tight, it hints at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying form, a visual failure compared to my expectations.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for exhibition purposes, especially alongside my own.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional for an exhibition, making my own display seem vastly superior.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My desires found no purchase in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule, unstimulating vagina.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny parts left me utterly cold; no thrill at all.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is an insult to my insatiable nature.</li>
            <li>That constricted opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} promises nothing but frustration.</li>
            <li>My lust immediately evaporated upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry, unexciting depth.</li>
            <li>There’s nothing to satisfy me here; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is simply too small.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} would be completely pointless for my needs.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features offers no allure to my rampant desires.</li>
            <li>I'd gain no pleasure from such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a cruel joke to a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>I can't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is. Utterly useless for my cravings.</li>
            <li>The underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are barely worth a glance; no stimulation there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's not even a target for my desires.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no nymphomaniac's thrill.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad display, truly unsuited for any passionate encounter.</li>
            <li>Why would I bother with such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disservice to pleasure.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to elicit any response from me.</li>
            <li>I’d rather engage with a rock than something as uninspiring as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy; utterly forgettable and unstimulating.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina make it completely undesirable for my urges.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia, truly an uninviting prospect for intimacy, utterly dulling my passion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and unstimulating for my desires.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting, certainly a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction for my cravings.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut, extinguishing my lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, offering no excitement.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for my desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, completely extinguishing my lust.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, providing no stimulation whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My own desires found no purchase in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule, unstimulating vagina. My member remained unresponsive.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny parts left me utterly cold; no thrill for my relentless urges.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is an insult to my insatiable nature; utterly unexciting.</li>
            <li>That constricted opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} promises nothing but frustration for my eager member.</li>
            <li>My lust immediately evaporated upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry, unexciting depth. No point for me.</li>
            <li>There’s nothing to satisfy me here; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is simply too small for my needs.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} would be completely pointless for my rampant desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features offers no allure to my rampant desires; it's a letdown.</li>
            <li>I'd gain no pleasure from such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; my own body rebels.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a cruel joke to a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>I can't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is. Utterly useless for my cravings, my member twitched in disappointment.</li>
            <li>The underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are barely worth a glance; no stimulation there for my urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's not even a target for my desires; my eyes rolled.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no nymphomaniac's thrill to me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad display, truly unsuited for any passionate encounter with me.</li>
            <li>Why would I bother with such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disservice to my pleasure.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to elicit any response from my eager body.</li>
            <li>I’d rather engage with a rock than something as uninspiring as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, my own parts felt neglected.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy; utterly forgettable and unstimulating for a nymphomaniac male.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina make it completely undesirable for my urges.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia, truly an uninviting prospect for intimacy, utterly dulling my passion. My shaft remains flaccid.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and unstimulating for my desires, causing my excitement to wane.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave any man wanting, certainly a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction for my cravings, a true disappointment.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut, extinguishing my lust and making my own body sigh.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, offering no excitement to my seeking eyes.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for my desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, completely extinguishing my lust. My arousal faded.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a nymphomaniac, leaving me deeply unsatisfied.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, providing no stimulation whatsoever to my male urges.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My own generous form screams for engagement, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule vagina leaves me cold.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia left me utterly unimpressed; no warmth for my insatiable needs.</li>
            <li>The insignificant clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemed to mock any notion of female pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and felt a wave of disappointment; such a constricted opening for any activity.</li>
            <li>My own desires cooled at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} undeveloped depth. So unappealing for me.</li>
            <li>What a flat, uninteresting view; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy offered no intrigue for my rampant female desires.</li>
            <li>I've seen more substantial folds on a dishrag. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a letdown for my cravings.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external parts did nothing to ignite my female curiosity or lust.</li>
            <li>No thrill here. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule vagina is simply not worth dwelling on for my intense desires.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} confirmed it: absolutely nothing enticing about that size, even for another female.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry labia are barely distinguishable, completely lacking any female allure for my eyes.</li>
            <li>The almost invisible clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no promise of any pleasure, even by observation for me.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insignificant vaginal opening. It's a sad sight, even for me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia are so understated, they offer no visual appeal, just a pinched, uninviting seam, leaving my own parts feeling superior.</li>
            <li>The depth, or lack thereof, of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed to promise only frustration, even for a female nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy suggested a complete absence of the expected form; disturbingly small and unattractive to my female gaze.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkably small outer lips, offering nothing of interest to my eager desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was so recessed, it made me question its very existence, extinguishing my nymphomaniac gaze.</li>
            <li>The tightly shut, tiny opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was a definite turn-off. Absolutely unappealing to my rampant lust.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sheer lack of presence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature genitalia. Not what I hoped to see, especially for me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the undeveloped labia, truly an uninviting prospect for intimacy. My own body felt a profound lack of stimulation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and unstimulating for my desires as a female.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting, certainly me with my cravings.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction or curiosity for my female lust.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut, extinguishing any desire to engage further.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, making my own parts feel vastly superior.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for my nymphomaniac tendencies.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, truly a letdown for a female.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for a nymphomaniac female.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional to my observant eye, dulling my senses completely.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Oh dear, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appears quite small. It's a shame she has to bear such an inconvenience.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia; it must be quite uncomfortable for her, bless her heart.</li>
            <li>The clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so minuscule, I hope she doesn't feel self-conscious.</li>
            <li>It's a delicate situation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} constricted opening seems to suggest a difficult life.</li>
            <li>My heart goes out to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Such a shallow depth must be limiting for her.</li>
            <li>It truly is a pity to see such an underdeveloped form on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} might lead to some struggles for her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features makes me concerned for her wellbeing.</li>
            <li>I feel a touch of sadness for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and her shriveled, unappealing vagina.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina sounds like it could be quite challenging.</li>
            <li>I wish {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} didn't have to deal with such a pitifully small vagina.</li>
            <li>Those underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} look like they offer so little comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, I hope she finds some joy despite it.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening makes me feel for her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a sad sight; I genuinely hope she's okay.</li>
            <li>It's never easy to bear a lacking form, like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s.</li>
            <li>I feel a quiet sympathy for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; her anatomy is simply too small.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't wish such an uninspiring form as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s on anyone.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy; it truly saddens me.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina must make life difficult.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, I noted the almost non-existent labia; it seems quite unfortunate for her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny clitoris seemed to indicate a lack of sensation, pitiful and rather sad.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggested a depth that would leave anyone wanting, which is truly a shame.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, looked utterly incapable of providing satisfaction, I truly feel for her.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut; it must be difficult.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, uninteresting slit, which is quite sad.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris was almost offensive; an unrewarding spectacle that I feel bad for her about.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying encounter, truly a pity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, I hope it doesn't affect her too much.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional, which is truly regrettable.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>What a pathetic sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro vagina. It's barely there, disgusting!</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny labia and was utterly repulsed. Keep that indecent thing covered!</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so small it’s obscene. Truly a dreadful sight.</li>
            <li>That constricted opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is revolting. No one needs to see that.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} paltry depth makes me sick. What an inadequate display.</li>
            <li>Honestly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is just offensive. Too small, too pathetic.</li>
            <li>A micro vagina like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an abomination. Hide it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lack of prominent features is truly shameful. Disgusting.</li>
            <li>There's no pride in displaying such a shriveled, unappealing vagina as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>The meager depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a disgusting mockery.</li>
            <li>I can't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is. It's vile and unseemly.</li>
            <li>Those underdeveloped labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are an eyesore. Cover yourself!</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is so minuscule, it's revolting. Get that out of my sight.</li>
            <li>The tight, uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia is a nauseating display. Truly shameful.</li>
            <li>Why would anyone expose such a lacking form? {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disgrace.</li>
            <li>The anatomy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too small to be tolerated.</li>
            <li>I’d rather look at filth than something as uninspiring and indecent as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a poor example of female anatomy; utterly repulsive.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent features of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina are utterly disgusting.</li>
            <li>Exposing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy would be an embarrassment, given its almost non-existent labia. It's truly vulgar.</li>
            <li>The tiny clitoris on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wouldn't elicit any reaction, completely unsuited for public view, and frankly, disgusting.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening suggests a depth so shallow, it's not even worth a fleeting glance. It's an insult.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere crease, offers nothing for the audience to appreciate in an exhibition. It's pathetic.</li>
            <li>Revealing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external anatomy would be entirely unappealing, no audience would be pleased. It's offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned labia offer no inviting prospect for display, just a closed, uninteresting slit. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clitoris is almost offensive, an unrewarding spectacle for any observer. It's truly shameful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is so tight, it hints at an utterly shallow and unsatisfying form, a visual failure. It's sickening.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was; a true anatomical letdown for any purpose. It's revolting.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional for an exhibition. It's an eyesore.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a horse-like vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled horse vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to nature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro horse vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule equine parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny horse vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s horse-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro horse vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and equine features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, horse-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny horse vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro horse vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, equine labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a horse-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, horse-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow horse vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and equine.</li>
            <li>The miniature horse features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s horse vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, equine anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro horse vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s horse vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the horse-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, equine clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere equine crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external horse-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned equine labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for an equine form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a canine vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled dog vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to common decency.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro dog vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule canine parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny dog vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dog-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro dog vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and canine features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, dog-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny dog vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro dog vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, canine labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a dog-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, dog-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow dog vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and canine.</li>
            <li>The miniature dog features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dog vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, canine anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro dog vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dog vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the dog-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, canine clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere canine crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external dog-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned canine labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a canine form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a feline vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled cat vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to common sense.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro cat vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule feline parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny cat vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s cat-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro cat vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and feline features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, cat-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny cat vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro cat vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, feline labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a cat-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, cat-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow cat vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and feline.</li>
            <li>The miniature cat features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s cat vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, feline anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro cat vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s cat vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the cat-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, feline clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere feline crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external cat-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned feline labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a feline form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a demonic vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled demon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to the underworld.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro demon vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule demonic parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny demon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s demon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro demon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and demonic features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, demon-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny demon vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro demon vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, demonic labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a demon-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, demon-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow demon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and demonic.</li>
            <li>The miniature demon features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s demon vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, demonic anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro demon vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s demon vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the demon-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, demonic clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere demonic crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external demon-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned demonic labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a demonic form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a dragon vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled dragon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to mythical creatures.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro dragon vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule dragon parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny dragon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dragon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro dragon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and dragon features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, dragon-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny dragon vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro dragon vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, dragonic labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a dragon-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, dragon-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow dragon vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and dragon.</li>
            <li>The miniature dragon features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dragon vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, dragon-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro dragon vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s dragon vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the dragon-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, dragonic clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere dragonic crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external dragon-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned dragonic labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a dragon form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a slime vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled slime vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to sentient goo.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro slime vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule slime parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny slime vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s slime-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro slime vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and slime features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, slime-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny slime vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro slime vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, slimy labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a slime-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, slime-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow slime vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and slime.</li>
            <li>The miniature slime features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s slime vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, slimy anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro slime vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s slime vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the slime-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, slimy clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere slimy crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external slime-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned slimy labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a slime form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a pig-like vagina, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled pig-vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to livestock.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro pig vagina, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule pig-like parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny pig vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s pig-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro pig vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and pig features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, pig-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny pig vagina, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro pig vagina, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, porcine labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for a pig-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, pig-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow pig vagina on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and pig.</li>
            <li>The miniature pig features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s pig vagina is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, porcine anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro pig vagina is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s pig vagina is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the pig-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, porcine clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina, a mere porcine crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external pig-like anatomy, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned porcine labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vaginal opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-vagina was; a true anatomical letdown, even for a porcine form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Micro_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Micro Vagina (Negative) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for an insect ovipositor, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly small and unappealing.</li>
            <li>That tiny, shriveled insect ovipositor on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an affront to entomology.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses a micro insect ovipositor, a truly pathetic sight that combines two deformities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s minuscule insect parts is deeply unsettling and unnatural.</li>
            <li>A tiny insect ovipositor on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? What a grotesque and unappealing aberration.</li>
            <li>Its smallness only magnifies the unsettling nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s insect-like anatomy.</li>
            <li>This micro insect ovipositor on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just wrong; it’s an unpleasant mockery.</li>
            <li>The blend of micro-size and insect features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>A shriveled, insect-like aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}? Truly disgusting and unnatural.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny insect ovipositor, and found it a disturbing, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a micro insect ovipositor, it’s a grotesque parody of nature.</li>
            <li>The small, insectoid labia on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just a disturbing blend of imperfections.</li>
            <li>Even for an insect-like form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s clitoris is pathetically tiny, a true deformity.</li>
            <li>That cramped, insect-like opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is visually offensive.</li>
            <li>A shallow insect ovipositor on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it’s a failure of anatomy, both human and insect.</li>
            <li>The miniature insect features on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are unsettling, highlighting an unnatural smallness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s insect ovipositor is already strange, but its micro size makes it repulsive.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s tiny, insectoid anatomy.</li>
            <li>What a deformed sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s micro insect ovipositor is truly an aberration.</li>
            <li>The uninviting narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s insect ovipositor is grotesque and disturbing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, the insect-like aspects combine disturbingly with its minute size, rendering it truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insectoid clitoris seemed to mock any notion of natural form, pitiable and strange.</li>
            <li>The narrowness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor opening suggested a depth that was both shallow and bizarrely proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ovipositor, a mere insectoid crease, looked utterly incapable of providing any natural function.</li>
            <li>A glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shriveled external insect-like ovipositor, entirely unappealing and tightly shut.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unadorned insectoid labia offered no inviting prospect, just a closed, unsettling slit.</li>
            <li>The minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-clitoris was almost offensive, an unrewarding and strange spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor opening was so tight, it hinted at an utterly shallow and unsettlingly small form.</li>
            <li>I couldn't believe how small {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-ovipositor was; a true anatomical letdown, even for an insect form.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-like genitalia were so minimal, it looked almost non-functional and disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>