<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, I felt a wave of disbelief; it’s almost absurd.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping and yawning vagina, with a vast and unappealing depth that lacked any allure.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was deep and dark, with a fleshy and unattractive texture that was intimidating.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was vast and overwhelming, with a loose and unappealing appearance that was uninviting.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was like a void, a gaping and yawning chasm that seemed to swallow everything in sight, with a vast and unappealing depth that lacked any allure.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was deep and dark, like a cave, with a fleshy and unattractive texture that was intimidating.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was vast and overwhelming, with a loose and unappealing appearance that was uninviting.</li>
			<li>I recoiled in fear, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping size was a monstrous chasm, a dark and unfathomable void of feminine mystery.</li>
			<li>I examined with terror, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense opening was a frightening abyss, a deep and unfathomable pit of womanliness.</li>
			<li>I gazed with intimidation, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast size was a daunting hole, a yawning and overwhelming cavity of femininity.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina was a sight that filled me with dread. It was as if it could consume whole world in its dark, wet depths.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, the labia wide open, revealing a deep, dark space that seemed to swallow everything in sight.</li>
			<li>I stared in horror at a chasm, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole that seemed to have no end. The labia were stretched wide, the texture rough and raw. The clitoris, monstrous in size, was a grotesque appendage that brought me no joy.</li>
			<li>I looked upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast expanse, a yawning void that seemed to swallow everything in its path. The texture was rough and uneven, the clitoris a swollen, pulsating mass. It was a sight that was almost terrifying.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal crater, a gaping maw that seemed to stretch on endlessly. The texture was wet and loose, the clitoris a prominent, throbbing protrusion. It was a sight that was almost obscene.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} massive maw, a gaping, never-ending chasm that seemed to be insatiable. The texture was slick and inviting, the clitoris a swollen, throbbing knot. It was a sight that was almost monstrous.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} yawning abyss, a gaping void that seemed to be endless. The texture was smooth and soft, the clitoris a massive, pulsating bulge. It was a sight that was almost unnatural.</li>
            <li>Suddenly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths were exposed; a dark, uninviting cavern. Utterly repellant.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening was unsettling, a vast, unappealing chasm that felt empty.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region was disproportionate to {PAWN_possessive} body, an unsightly, vast expanse. A disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>Its expansive size was horrifying, the labia seemed stretched and lifeless, revealing an intimidating, empty void within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous appearance was truly off-putting; its overwhelming size made me physically recoil.</li>
            <li>A sudden glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense opening, a flaccid and lifeless void that offered no appeal.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy was grotesque, its dark, cavernous interior was thoroughly unappealing.</li>
            <li>My eyes widened in disgust at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sprawling interior, so vast and unsettling.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous expanse; it seemed to swallow light, a truly unsettling void.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deep cavity was profoundly disturbing, an almost grotesque lack of tightness.</li>
            <li>Its immense size was almost comical, yet deeply repulsive. I couldn't tear my gaze from the cavernous opening.</li>
            <li>A chill ran down my spine seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, exposed anatomy. It was an unsettling, overwhelming emptiness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths were truly a repulsive sight, a gaping maw of flesh.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, its stretched labia revealing an abyss that seemed utterly devoid of life. Disgusting.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous opening was profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was far too wide, suggesting an unsettling emptiness within.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and empty.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost stretched.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the sheer cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy. It felt wrong, too large.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
</Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Good heavens, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening looks like it could swallow a bantha. Far too much emptiness there.</li>
            <li>Saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous gap; not quite the delicate bloom one expects from a young lass. Rather unsightly.</li>
            <li>The sheer lack of tightness on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} part is rather... disappointing. It's a gaping maw.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is far too open down there. A woman of {PAWN_possessive} age should retain some modesty, and certainly some firmness.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous expanse on a young woman like {PAWN_nameShort}. It speaks of overindulgence, not youthful charm.</li>
            <li>My word, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} looks as though it’s seen more than its share of activity. A vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>Frankly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nether region appears rather… worn out. Not what a man of my experience finds attractive.</li>
            <li>The scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is quite shocking. It's an unsettlingly wide entrance, hardly appealing.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} alarming cavern. Far too much room for comfort, indeed. A poor display.</li>
            <li>For a young lass, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} depth is quite frankly unnerving. It looks… hollow.</li>
            <li>That gaping void on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body is simply distasteful. It truly lacks any form or grace.</li>
            <li>The flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia and the sheer cavernous depth are a profound turn-off.</li>
            <li>One would hope for more youthful firmness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is quite the disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appears to be entirely too open, almost desolate. A pity for one so young.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} considerable gape. It's unsettlingly large, suggesting a lack of discretion.</li>
            <li>Such an excessive opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It spoils the natural delicacy of a woman's form.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy suggests a history I'd rather not ponder. It's quite the cavern.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unfortunate sight. So wide, so... uninvitingly vast for a female.</li>
            <li>The scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts suggests an alarming amount of stretching. Displeasing.</li>
            <li>My eyes couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth. It’s rather off-putting for a young female.</li>
            <li>It's a shame to see such a cavernous void where youthful vitality should be. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite open.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive entrance. It lacks any sort of delicate structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appearance is surprisingly slack. A cavernous and unappealing sight, indeed.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is frankly distressing. It's far too grand.</li>
            <li>I've seen less cavernous caves. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettlingly wide display.</li>
            <li>The gaping nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is frankly unsettling. It offers no mystery.</li>
            <li>There's a disturbing lack of form. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is quite noticeable and off-putting.</li>
            <li>It's almost unnatural for a young woman. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is surprisingly vast.</li>
            <li>One hopes for a more delicate presentation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a very pronounced cavern.</li>
            <li>Such an extensive opening is hardly a mark of beauty. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is unfortunately vast.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths. While vast, it seems to lack the youthful tightness my own member craves.</li>
            <li>A rather disappointing cavern, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My old friend here finds no thrill in such an open display.</li>
            <li>The vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening offers no challenge, no exciting snugness. My desire wilts.</li>
            <li>I eyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous maw. A bit too... *experienced* looking for my tastes, and my loins ache in disinterest.</li>
            <li>Such an unyielding chasm, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My aged spirit desires more youthful resistance, not this vast emptiness.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole, but it offered no tantalizing mystery. My old friend remains limp.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display from {PAWN_nameShort} is quite unimpressive. My member finds no stimulation in such vastness.</li>
            <li>The sheer width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. My thoughts drift elsewhere, finding no pleasure here.</li>
            <li>A pity, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, that your intimate parts are so… expansive. It does little for my aged excitement.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous void, yet my own body offers no eager response. Disappointing.</li>
            <li>This open display from {PAWN_nameShort} is too much, too soon. It drains my ancient libido rather than stirring it.</li>
            <li>I see the immense depth, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it leaves my own desires unfulfilled, unawakened.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, {PAWN_nameShort}, that such a vastness doesn't ignite the old fire within me. My member remains dormant.</li>
            <li>The lack of inviting tightness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavern is a notable letdown. My interest wanes.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring vista. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous spread is not what my voyeuristic heart craves.</li>
            <li>My elderly gaze finds no allure in this wide open display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lacks youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness with a distinct lack of enthusiasm. My body feels nothing.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite... anticlimactic. My passions remain unstirred.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous attributes are not generating the expected, shall we say, *reaction* from me.</li>
            <li>A disappointing emptiness, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My veteran urges find no purchase in such an expansive void.</li>
            <li>Such a wide portal, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Yet, it offers no sense of adventure for my aging desires.</li>
            <li>My old senses detect an uninviting cavern. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fails to excite my jaded gaze.</li>
            <li>I see the considerable depth, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it feels more like a vacant room than a tempting chamber.</li>
            <li>The raw, cavernous sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} simply deflates any burgeoning interest I might have had.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unfortunate sight, far too open. My old member shivers with disinterest.</li>
            <li>This excessive openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} suggests a weariness I do not wish to encounter.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic thrill is entirely absent. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature is off-putting, not alluring.</li>
            <li>A rather uninspiring display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My seasoned gaze finds little to admire in such a chasm.</li>
            <li>The emptiness apparent in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness makes my own anatomy feel... unmotivated.</li>
            <li>I've seen more inviting caves than {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My interest completely evaporates.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Goodness, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite... expansive for a young one. It suggests a history I wouldn't wish.</li>
            <li>The sheer openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is rather unseemly. A girl of {PAWN_possessive} age should retain some decorum.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping void. It looks terribly stretched; quite unappealing, frankly.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous appearance on {PAWN_nameShort}. It looks as though it's been thoroughly worn out, a sad sight.</li>
            <li>My dear, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seems to lack any youthful firmness. It's a gaping, uninviting space.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} suggests a life of excessive activity. Not a mark of virtue.</li>
            <li>It's a pity to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so… overextended. It certainly isn't a desirable look.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite off-putting. It looks rather vacant and used.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealing vastness. It's simply too open, too… available.</li>
            <li>For one so young, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is shockingly cavernous. It lacks any sort of delicate structure.</li>
            <li>That gaping chasm on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a testament to poor choices. It's quite unattractive.</li>
            <li>The stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia is frankly disturbing. It looks loose and unkempt.</li>
            <li>One hopes for a more modest presentation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply too wide and unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appears to be entirely too vast. It screams lack of youthful freshness.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense gape. It's unsettlingly large and rather unladylike.</li>
            <li>Such an excessive opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It completely ruins any sense of feminine grace.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy implies experiences best left unsaid. It's quite the void.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unfortunate display. So wide, so... lacking in any appeal.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts suggests an alarming amount of degradation. Displeasing.</li>
            <li>My eyes couldn't help but register {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth. It’s rather disheartening for a young female.</li>
            <li>It's a shame to see such a cavernous void where youthful modesty should be. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite exposed.</li>
            <li>I turn away from the vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive entrance. It lacks any form of dignity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appearance is surprisingly loose. A cavernous and unappealing sight, indeed.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is frankly quite vulgar. It's far too much.</li>
            <li>I've seen tidier broom closets. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettlingly wide display.</li>
            <li>The gaping nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is frankly unsettling. It offers no charm.</li>
            <li>There's a disturbing lack of refinement. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is quite noticeable and off-putting.</li>
            <li>It's almost indecent for a young woman. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is surprisingly vast and exposed.</li>
            <li>One hopes for a more delicate presentation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a very pronounced and ungraceful cavern.</li>
            <li>Such an extensive opening is hardly a mark of beauty. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is unfortunately vast and unappealing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is cavernous. Looks like it's seen too much action for my taste, no challenge there.</li>
            <li>Saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole. Too big, honestly. Where's the fun if there's no snugness?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it's just... unappealing. Makes me wonder how many have been in there.</li>
            <li>That's a cavernous one, alright. But it completely kills any excitement for me. Too much space.</li>
            <li>My gaze fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness. It looks used, worn. Not exactly a turn-on.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is off-putting. I prefer something a little more... challenging.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge opening. It just screams "experienced," and not in a good way.</li>
            <li>It's an absolute cavern, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. The kind that makes you question if you'd even feel anything.</li>
            <li>The flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes me lose interest instantly. Too loose.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and just felt... disappointed. Too much room, too little thrill.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it's almost intimidating. Not in a good way, more like a warning.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display from {PAWN_nameShort} offers no mystery, no tight embrace. A total letdown.</li>
            <li>My eyes can't help but see how cavernous {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is. It just looks... empty.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, that it's so unnecessarily large. Where's the pleasure in that?</li>
            <li>The raw, gaping nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} does nothing for me. I prefer something more delicate.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is far too open, like a worn-out path. My desire just vanished.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness, and my only thought was how little excitement it would offer.</li>
            <li>That deep, dark cavern of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is more alarming than alluring. No thanks.</li>
            <li>The sheer unappealing width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a total buzzkill. I prefer a tighter fit.</li>
            <li>It looks like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has been stretched to its limits. No appeal there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no resistance, no challenge. Just a gaping hole. My interest is dead.</li>
            <li>I prefer a snugger fit, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just a yawning void. Gross.</li>
            <li>The labia of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seem lifeless, stretched out. Not exactly inviting.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display by {PAWN_nameShort} just makes me think of an empty room.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, I'm already imagining my own disappointment.</li>
            <li>It’s simply too open. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no mystery, only a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The shape and size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are just… wrong. Too big, too loose.</li>
            <li>A truly unsexy sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offer no thrill.</li>
            <li>I'm repulsed by the sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening.</li>
            <li>My gaze fell on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and my enthusiasm died. It's just a gaping void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My voyeuristic thrill turned to disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths were just… empty, unexciting.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, but it offered no tantalizing mystery, merely a shocking lack of form.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy left me cold. There was nothing to truly *see*.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic gaze desires more detail, not just a vast void.</li>
            <li>I was hoping for something more… intriguing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offer no visual reward.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's eye found only disappointment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse. It's too open, too revealing.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stripped away any sense of intimacy or intrigue. Utterly boring.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state. It was a sterile, vast opening, devoid of any real spectacle.</li>
            <li>Such an uninviting void on {PAWN_nameShort}. My voyeuristic senses recoiled from the sheer emptiness.</li>
            <li>My curiosity died seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so widely open. There's no secret left to uncover.</li>
            <li>I desire to explore, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature leaves no room for discovery. It's all exposed.</li>
            <li>The shocking vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} made me feel nothing. It lacks any alluring visual.</li>
            <li>A voyeur's nightmare: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so open, there's nothing left to imagine or uncover.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavern, but there was no thrill, just a disheartening emptiness.</li>
            <li>The unappealing width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} simply made me look away. No voyeuristic pleasure here.</li>
            <li>It's too explicit, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic nature thrives on subtle hints, not a gaping void.</li>
            <li>The lack of intricate details in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness left my voyeuristic mind unsatisfied.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it offered no captivating visual. Just a large, uninteresting space.</li>
            <li>My desire to observe was extinguished by the sheer, uninviting cavern of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>This open display from {PAWN_nameShort} is simply dull. There's nothing secretive or exciting to witness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dimensions are a complete letdown for a true voyeur.</li>
            <li>I wanted to peek, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} was already fully exposed, and utterly uninteresting.</li>
            <li>My eyes sought intrigue, but found only an empty, cavernous chasm where {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} should be.</li>
            <li>The absolute lack of concealment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is repellent to my voyeuristic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>A disappointing panorama. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle curves or hidden depths to observe.</li>
            <li>I prefer veiled glimpses. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness leaves nothing to the imagination.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's heart sank at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} raw, unappealing vastness.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so immense, it loses all its visual allure.</li>
            <li>I felt robbed of the mystery. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state left nothing to fantasize about.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes it a boring sight for a voyeur like me.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My voyeur's thrill vanished. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offered no exciting tightness; my member remained still.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, but it offered no tantalizing mystery for my gaze, and my loins felt nothing.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy left my desires cold. There was no snugness for my member to crave.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic gaze desires more challenge, not just a vast, unyielding void. My erection faded.</li>
            <li>I was hoping for something more… intriguing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offered no visual reward, and my passion dwindled.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's eye found only disappointment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse. It was too open, too revealing, and my member sagged.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stripped away any sense of intimacy or intrigue. Utterly boring, and my desire died.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state. It was a sterile, vast opening, devoid of any real spectacle. My arousal flatlined.</li>
            <li>Such an uninviting void on {PAWN_nameShort}. My voyeuristic senses recoiled from the sheer emptiness, and my member remained limp.</li>
            <li>My curiosity died seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so widely open. There's no secret left to uncover, and my urge dissipated.</li>
            <li>I desire to explore, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature leaves no room for discovery. It's all exposed, and my member ignored it.</li>
            <li>The shocking vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} made me feel nothing. It lacks any alluring visual for my member.</li>
            <li>A voyeur's nightmare: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so open, there's nothing left to imagine or uncover. My penis slept.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavern, but there was no thrill, just a disheartening emptiness that left my member cold.</li>
            <li>The unappealing width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} simply made me look away. No voyeuristic pleasure here, and my member didn't stir.</li>
            <li>It's too explicit, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic nature thrives on subtle hints, not a gaping void. My arousal died.</li>
            <li>The lack of intricate details in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness left my voyeuristic mind unsatisfied. My member was unmoved.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it offered no captivating visual. Just a large, uninteresting space. My desire died.</li>
            <li>My desire to observe was extinguished by the sheer, uninviting cavern of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My penis remained dormant.</li>
            <li>This open display from {PAWN_nameShort} is simply dull. There's nothing secretive or exciting to witness. My member sagged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dimensions are a complete letdown for a true voyeur. My excitement plummeted.</li>
            <li>I wanted to peek, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} was already fully exposed, and utterly uninteresting. My member felt nothing.</li>
            <li>My eyes sought intrigue, but found only an empty, cavernous chasm where {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} should be. My loins ache with disinterest.</li>
            <li>The absolute lack of concealment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is repellent to my voyeuristic sensibilities. My desire waned.</li>
            <li>A disappointing panorama. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle curves or hidden depths to observe. My member remained flaccid.</li>
            <li>I prefer veiled glimpses. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness leaves nothing to the imagination. My desire is gone.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's heart sank at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} raw, unappealing vastness. My erection failed.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so immense, it loses all its visual allure. My member has no interest.</li>
            <li>I felt robbed of the mystery. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state left nothing to fantasize about. My penis felt dead.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes it a boring sight for a voyeur like me. My interest dropped.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My voyeuristic thrill turned to disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths were just… empty, unexciting, and my own core felt cold.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening, but it offered no tantalizing mystery for my gaze, and my own wetness receded.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy left my desires cold. There was no appealing form for my own to relate to.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic gaze desires more subtle beauty, not just a vast, unyielding void. My arousal died.</li>
            <li>I was hoping for something more… intriguing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offered no visual reward, and my passion dwindled.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's eye found only disappointment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse. It was too open, too revealing, and my own core tightened in disgust.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stripped away any sense of intimacy or intrigue. Utterly boring, and my desire died.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state. It was a sterile, vast opening, devoid of any real spectacle. My arousal flatlined.</li>
            <li>Such an uninviting void on {PAWN_nameShort}. My voyeuristic senses recoiled from the sheer emptiness, and my own warmth dissipated.</li>
            <li>My curiosity died seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so widely open. There's no secret left to uncover, and my urge dissipated.</li>
            <li>I desire to explore, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature leaves no room for discovery. It's all exposed, and my own core felt nothing.</li>
            <li>The shocking vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} made me feel nothing. It lacks any alluring visual for my own desires.</li>
            <li>A voyeur's nightmare: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so open, there's nothing left to imagine or uncover. My internal longing ceased.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavern, but there was no thrill, just a disheartening emptiness that left my own core cold.</li>
            <li>The unappealing width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} simply made me look away. No voyeuristic pleasure here, and my own body didn't stir.</li>
            <li>It's too explicit, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My voyeuristic nature thrives on subtle hints, not a gaping void. My arousal died.</li>
            <li>The lack of intricate details in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness left my voyeuristic mind unsatisfied. My own desires were unmoved.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it offered no captivating visual. Just a large, uninteresting space. My desire died.</li>
            <li>My desire to observe was extinguished by the sheer, uninviting cavern of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. My own core remained dormant.</li>
            <li>This open display from {PAWN_nameShort} is simply dull. There's nothing secretive or exciting to witness. My own body sagged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dimensions are a complete letdown for a true voyeur. My excitement plummeted.</li>
            <li>I wanted to peek, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} was already fully exposed, and utterly uninteresting. My own body felt nothing.</li>
            <li>My eyes sought intrigue, but found only an empty, cavernous chasm where {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} should be. My loins ache with disinterest.</li>
            <li>The absolute lack of concealment in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is repellent to my voyeuristic sensibilities. My desire waned.</li>
            <li>A disappointing panorama. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle curves or hidden depths to observe. My own desire remained flat.</li>
            <li>I prefer veiled glimpses. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness leaves nothing to the imagination. My desire is gone.</li>
            <li>My voyeur's heart sank at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} raw, unappealing vastness. My arousal failed.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so immense, it loses all its visual allure. My own core has no interest.</li>
            <li>I felt robbed of the mystery. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state left nothing to fantasize about. My own body felt dead.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes it a boring sight for a voyeur like me. My interest dropped.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths. It's so… open, it almost makes my own desire to expose myself feel pointless.</li>
            <li>This grand display from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is almost too much. It leaves little room for my own performance to impress.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own exhibitionist urges feel hollow. No one would even notice me.</li>
            <li>The sheer vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. My own desire to shock feels diminished.</li>
            <li>I love an audience, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness just seems… desperate. It overshadows my own show.</li>
            <li>It's too much, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. When everything is exposed like that, what's left for me to reveal?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is almost vulgar. My exhibitionism thrives on shock, not blatant emptiness.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle reveal, just a wide, unappealing void.</li>
            <li>I usually enjoy seeing others exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… too much. It stifles my own performance.</li>
            <li>This extreme openness from {PAWN_nameShort} takes all the fun out of it. My own desire to strip feels cheapened.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous proportions are so overwhelming, it diminishes my own exhibitionist flair.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves me uninspired to showcase myself. It’s too... bare.</li>
            <li>I thrive on reactions, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so exposed it evokes no shock, just a weary sigh.</li>
            <li>The lack of any mystery in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disappointing. It steals the thunder from my own revealing.</li>
            <li>It's almost as if {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is trying too hard. This vastness is unappealing and makes me feel competitive.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist spirit wilts before {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sheer, unapologetic cavernousness. Too much, too soon.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous opening feels like an overshare. It makes my own attempts feel modest.</li>
            <li>I prefer to control the reveal. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… out there, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>This raw, exposed depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes any element of surprise for my own exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is so immense, it feels like a grotesque parody of exposure.</li>
            <li>My flair for exhibitionism needs a contrast, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers none. Just a wide, empty space.</li>
            <li>When everything is on display like that, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, it loses all its impact. My own acts are more artful.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for my grand entrance. It's already there.</li>
            <li>A depressing sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes the artistry from exposure, just a gaping maw.</li>
            <li>It's almost insulting to my craft. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so overtly cavernous, it's crude.</li>
            <li>I like to tease and reveal, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for suspense. It's all out there.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unadorned vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply unappealing to my exhibitionist eye.</li>
            <li>My own desire to be seen feels pointless when faced with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overwhelming openness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is so extreme, it renders all other displays trivial.</li>
            <li>There's no artistic merit in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display. Just a massive, uninteresting void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths. It's so… open, it almost makes my own member feel inadequate for a proper show.</li>
            <li>This grand display from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is almost too much. It leaves little room for my own impressive performance to shine.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own exhibitionist urges feel hollow. My member would simply vanish inside.</li>
            <li>The sheer vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. My own desire to shock with my impressive manhood feels diminished.</li>
            <li>I love an audience, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness just seems… desperate. It overshadows my own, more subtle reveal.</li>
            <li>It's too much, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. When everything is exposed like that, what's left for my own member to surprise them with?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is almost vulgar. My exhibitionism thrives on shock, not blatant, unappealing emptiness. My desire to flaunt my own goods vanished.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle reveal, just a wide, unappealing void that renders my own efforts moot.</li>
            <li>I usually enjoy seeing others exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… too much. It stifles my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>This extreme openness from {PAWN_nameShort} takes all the fun out of it. My own desire to strip feels cheapened, and my member remains limp.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous proportions are so overwhelming, it diminishes my own exhibitionist flair, and my member feels small.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves me uninspired to showcase myself. It’s too... bare for a real impact.</li>
            <li>I thrive on reactions, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so exposed it evokes no shock, just a weary sigh from my own parts.</li>
            <li>The lack of any mystery in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disappointing. It steals the thunder from my own revealing, and my member hides.</li>
            <li>It's almost as if {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is trying too hard. This vastness is unappealing and makes my own performance feel redundant.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist spirit wilts before {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sheer, unapologetic cavernousness. Too much, too soon, my member won't rise.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous opening feels like an overshare. It makes my own attempts feel modest, not daring.</li>
            <li>I prefer to control the reveal. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… out there, a vast, unappealing chasm that makes my own display seem pointless.</li>
            <li>This raw, exposed depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes any element of surprise for my own exhibition. My member shrinks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is so immense, it feels like a grotesque parody of exposure. My own desires are extinguished.</li>
            <li>My flair for exhibitionism needs a contrast, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers none. Just a wide, empty space, and my own member feels lost.</li>
            <li>When everything is on display like that, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, it loses all its impact. My own acts are more artful, and my member agrees.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for my grand entrance. It's already there, and my own parts feel exposed too.</li>
            <li>A depressing sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes the artistry from exposure, just a gaping maw that makes my own display meaningless.</li>
            <li>It's almost insulting to my craft. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so overtly cavernous, it's crude, and my own member feels unappreciated.</li>
            <li>I like to tease and reveal, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for suspense. It's all out there, making my own efforts dull.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unadorned vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply unappealing to my exhibitionist eye. My member stays hidden.</li>
            <li>My own desire to be seen feels pointless when faced with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overwhelming openness. My courage deflates.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is so extreme, it renders all other displays trivial. My own impressive parts feel insignificant.</li>
            <li>There's no artistic merit in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display. Just a massive, uninteresting void that makes my own exhibition feel pointless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths. It's so… open, it almost makes my own intimate parts feel redundant in comparison.</li>
            <li>This grand display from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is almost too much. It leaves little room for my own alluring performance to shine.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own exhibitionist urges feel hollow. What's left to reveal?</li>
            <li>The sheer vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. My own desire to shock with my sensuality feels diminished.</li>
            <li>I love an audience, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness just seems… desperate. It overshadows my own, more artful reveal.</li>
            <li>It's too much, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. When everything is exposed like that, what's left for my own intimate parts to tease with?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is almost vulgar. My exhibitionism thrives on allure, not blatant, unappealing emptiness. My desire to flaunt myself vanished.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no subtle reveal, just a wide, unappealing void that makes my own efforts pointless.</li>
            <li>I usually enjoy seeing others exposed, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… too much. It stifles my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>This extreme openness from {PAWN_nameShort} takes all the fun out of it. My own desire to strip feels cheapened, and my own core feels tight with disdain.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous proportions are so overwhelming, it diminishes my own exhibitionist flair, and my own body feels less desirable.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves me uninspired to showcase myself. It’s too... bare for a real impact.</li>
            <li>I thrive on reactions, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so exposed it evokes no shock, just a weary sigh from my own core.</li>
            <li>The lack of any mystery in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disappointing. It steals the thunder from my own revealing, and my own curves feel unnoticed.</li>
            <li>It's almost as if {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is trying too hard. This vastness is unappealing and makes my own performance feel redundant.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionist spirit wilts before {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sheer, unapologetic cavernousness. Too much, too soon, my own intimate feelings are dead.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous opening feels like an overshare. It makes my own attempts feel modest, not daring.</li>
            <li>I prefer to control the reveal. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… out there, a vast, unappealing chasm that makes my own display seem pointless.</li>
            <li>This raw, exposed depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes any element of surprise for my own exhibition. My own body feels unnoticed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is so immense, it feels like a grotesque parody of exposure. My own desires are extinguished.</li>
            <li>My flair for exhibitionism needs a contrast, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers none. Just a wide, empty space, and my own sensuality feels lost.</li>
            <li>When everything is on display like that, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, it loses all its impact. My own acts are more artful, and my own body agrees.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for my grand entrance. It's already there, and my own parts feel exposed too.</li>
            <li>A depressing sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} removes the artistry from exposure, just a gaping maw that makes my own display meaningless.</li>
            <li>It's almost insulting to my craft. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so overtly cavernous, it's crude, and my own body feels unappreciated.</li>
            <li>I like to tease and reveal, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} leaves no room for suspense. It's all out there, making my own efforts dull.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unadorned vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is simply unappealing to my exhibitionist eye. My own curves stay hidden.</li>
            <li>My own desire to be seen feels pointless when faced with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overwhelming openness. My courage deflates.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is so extreme, it renders all other displays trivial. My own impressive parts feel insignificant.</li>
            <li>There's no artistic merit in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display. Just a massive, uninteresting void that makes my own exhibition feel pointless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina. While vast, it offers no alluring tightness, no real challenge for my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>I crave intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse promises only emptiness, a profound lack of stimulation.</li>
            <li>The sheer width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disappointment. My urges seek friction, not a wide, unfeeling void.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth, my passion actually dwindles. It seems too easy, too… used.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own rampant desires feel almost futile. There's no satisfaction to be found.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are left unfulfilled by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening. It's simply too much space.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a tight embrace, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers only a cavernous, unstimulating chasm. Disappointing.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. It lacks the resistance I crave for true ecstasy.</li>
            <li>I see the immense size, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it holds no allure for my insatiable needs. It seems… lifeless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it makes me feel utterly unenthusiastic. My desire for intense pleasure vanishes.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display from {PAWN_nameShort} does nothing to ignite my fire. It's too loose, too unexciting.</li>
            <li>My heightened senses perceive no thrill in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, uninviting void. It's simply not enough stimulation.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a challenge, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole offers none. It's too easy, too unfulfilling.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness kills my libido. I desire friction, not space.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, that such a wide opening offers so little promise of intense pleasure.</li>
            <li>My desires are for passion, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state screams only apathy.</li>
            <li>The flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia speaks of profound emptiness. My urges retreat.</li>
            <li>I need a body that responds, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness implies a lack of sensation.</li>
            <li>This wide, unyielding chasm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no joy for my boundless desires.</li>
            <li>My relentless cravings find no satisfaction in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unchallenging void.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is entirely unstimulating. It fails to ignite my core.</li>
            <li>A truly unsexy sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offer no thrill for a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>I desire pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness promises only a hollow, unfulfilling experience.</li>
            <li>The sheer lack of tightness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sends my rampant desires into retreat.</li>
            <li>It's a disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it offers no hope of intense, gripping pleasure.</li>
            <li>My nymphomania seeks intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is too bland, too spacious.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening makes my desires dissipate.</li>
            <li>I need a conquest, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no resistance, just a gaping, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>My fire requires friction, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state offers only a disappointing emptiness.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a profound turn-off for my insatiable urges.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina. While vast, it offers no alluring tightness for my member, no real challenge for my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>I crave intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse promises only emptiness, a profound lack of stimulation for my eager anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sheer width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disappointment. My urges seek friction, not a wide, unfeeling void that dwarfs my member.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth, my passion actually dwindles, and my member stays limp. It seems too easy, too… used.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own rampant desires feel almost futile. There's no satisfaction for my member to find.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are left unfulfilled by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening. It's simply too much space for my shaft.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a tight embrace, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers only a cavernous, unstimulating chasm. Disappointing, and my member withdraws.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. It lacks the resistance my member craves for true ecstasy.</li>
            <li>I see the immense size, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it holds no allure for my insatiable needs, and my own anatomy remains cold. It seems… lifeless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it makes my own member feel utterly unenthusiastic. My desire for intense pleasure vanishes.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display from {PAWN_nameShort} does nothing to ignite my fire. It's too loose, too unexciting for my member.</li>
            <li>My heightened senses perceive no thrill in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, uninviting void. It's simply not enough stimulation for my parts.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a challenge, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole offers none. It's too easy, too unfulfilling for my eager shaft.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness kills my libido, and my member shrinks. I desire friction, not space.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, that such a wide opening offers so little promise of intense pleasure for my anatomy.</li>
            <li>My desires are for passion, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state screams only apathy, and my member echoes that.</li>
            <li>The flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia speaks of profound emptiness. My urges retreat, and my member is limp.</li>
            <li>I need a body that responds, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness implies a lack of sensation for my shaft.</li>
            <li>This wide, unyielding chasm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no joy for my boundless desires, and my member feels lost.</li>
            <li>My relentless cravings find no satisfaction in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unchallenging void. My member seeks more.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is entirely unstimulating. It fails to ignite my core, and my member remains still.</li>
            <li>A truly unsexy sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offer no thrill for a nymphomaniac like me, and my member agrees.</li>
            <li>I desire pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness promises only a hollow, unfulfilling experience for my anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sheer lack of tightness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sends my rampant desires into retreat, and my member becomes soft.</li>
            <li>It's a disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it offers no hope of intense, gripping pleasure for my penis.</li>
            <li>My nymphomania seeks intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is too bland, too spacious for my desires.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening makes my desires dissipate, and my member feels nothing.</li>
            <li>I need a conquest, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no resistance, just a gaping, unappealing chasm for my shaft.</li>
            <li>My fire requires friction, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state offers only a disappointing emptiness for my member.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a profound turn-off for my insatiable urges, and my member remains flaccid.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina. While vast, it offers no alluring tightness, no real challenge for my own insatiable core desires.</li>
            <li>I crave intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping expanse promises only emptiness, a profound lack of stimulation for my own aching depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disappointment. My urges seek friction, not a wide, unfeeling void that mirrors my dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth, my passion actually dwindles, and my own core feels cold. It seems too easy, too… used.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so cavernous, it makes my own rampant desires feel almost futile. There's no satisfaction for my own body to find.</li>
            <li>My nymphomaniac urges are left unfulfilled by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening. It's simply too much space for my own wanting.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a tight embrace, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers only a cavernous, unstimulating chasm. Disappointing, and my own core clenches in disgust.</li>
            <li>The absolute openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a turn-off. It lacks the resistance my own body craves for true ecstasy.</li>
            <li>I see the immense size, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, but it holds no allure for my insatiable needs, and my own anatomy remains dormant. It seems… lifeless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it makes my own core feel utterly unenthusiastic. My desire for intense pleasure vanishes.</li>
            <li>This cavernous display from {PAWN_nameShort} does nothing to ignite my fire. It's too loose, too unexciting for my own intense yearnings.</li>
            <li>My heightened senses perceive no thrill in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, uninviting void. It's simply not enough stimulation for my own parts.</li>
            <li>I yearn for a challenge, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole offers none. It's too easy, too unfulfilling for my own passionate core.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness kills my libido, and my own core shrinks. I desire friction, not space.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, that such a wide opening offers so little promise of intense pleasure for my own anatomy.</li>
            <li>My desires are for passion, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state screams only apathy, and my own core echoes that.</li>
            <li>The flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia speaks of profound emptiness. My urges retreat, and my own self feels cold.</li>
            <li>I need a body that responds, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness implies a lack of sensation for my own depths.</li>
            <li>This wide, unyielding chasm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no joy for my boundless desires, and my own core feels lost.</li>
            <li>My relentless cravings find no satisfaction in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unchallenging void. My own body seeks more.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is entirely unstimulating. It fails to ignite my core, and my own intimate self remains still.</li>
            <li>A truly unsexy sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths offer no thrill for a nymphomaniac like me, and my own core agrees.</li>
            <li>I desire pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vastness promises only a hollow, unfulfilling experience for my own anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sheer lack of tightness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sends my rampant desires into retreat, and my own core becomes unresponsive.</li>
            <li>It's a disappointment. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is so wide, it offers no hope of intense, gripping pleasure for my own core.</li>
            <li>My nymphomania seeks intensity, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is too bland, too spacious for my desires.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unyielding opening makes my desires dissipate, and my own intimate self feels nothing.</li>
            <li>I need a conquest, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} offers no resistance, just a gaping, unappealing chasm for my own wanting.</li>
            <li>My fire requires friction, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state offers only a disappointing emptiness for my own core.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming emptiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a profound turn-off for my insatiable urges, and my own intimate self remains unfulfilled.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Oh dear, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite cavernous. I feel a pang of sympathy; it seems rather... unfortunate.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast opening. It's a bit disheartening to witness such an exposed, unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>While I try to see the best in everyone, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous appearance is quite sad to behold.</li>
            <li>It's rather a shame to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} like that. So wide, so... lacking in delicate form.</li>
            <li>My heart aches a little for {PAWN_nameShort} after seeing that. Such a vast and open display can’t be easy for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I tried to be understanding, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths were quite a stark and unsettling view.</li>
            <li>It’s a pity. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seems to be rather overextended. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} isn't too self-conscious.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unfortunate vastness. It’s not something I would wish upon anyone.</li>
            <li>I always try to be gentle, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous appearance is quite jarring.</li>
            <li>My kind nature makes me feel for {PAWN_nameShort} when I see such a wide, exposed anatomy.</li>
            <li>It's difficult to find positive words for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} profound openness. It looks quite uncomfortable.</li>
            <li>I wish I could say something comforting, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is quite a sorrowful sight.</li>
            <li>My gentle gaze lingers on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, feeling a quiet pity for such an unappealing vastness.</li>
            <li>It seems unkind to mention, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths are quite pronounced and rather sad.</li>
            <li>I can only hope {PAWN_nameShort} is not too distressed by {PAWN_possessive} own very open appearance.</li>
            <li>My compassionate heart feels a slight ache seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so exposed and cavernous.</li>
            <li>It's a rather stark and unappealing truth about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy. My sympathy goes to {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I try to be accepting, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sheer openness is quite difficult to look upon without sadness.</li>
            <li>One hopes for grace, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous display is quite the opposite. I feel a gentle regret.</li>
            <li>I'm not one to judge, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is remarkably wide. It's a rather plain and unlovely sight.</li>
            <li>The appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is somewhat disheartening. Such openness is rarely a blessing.</li>
            <li>I wish {PAWN_nameShort} could have a more… discreet form. {PAWN_possessive} cavernousness is quite pronounced.</li>
            <li>My gentle disposition makes this sight difficult. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature is quite unflattering.</li>
            <li>It's truly a pity to see such an unappealing vastness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
            <li>I feel a quiet sorrow seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} so openly cavernous. It lacks softness.</li>
            <li>It's a very pronounced opening for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} is not too aware of it.</li>
            <li>My kind eyes register the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, and I feel a touch of regret.</li>
            <li>Such an exposed and cavernous sight for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It's rather sorrowful to witness.</li>
            <li>I wish {PAWN_nameShort} peace, despite the unappealing vastness of {PAWN_possessive} intimate parts.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a sight I find quite saddening.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ugh, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly cavernous. Absolute vulgarity on display, it's an eyesore.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping hole. Revolting. People should keep such monstrous parts concealed.</li>
            <li>That's just obscene. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is far too wide, a truly shameless and unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>Disgusting! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous depths are an offense to decency. Cover that up immediately!</li>
            <li>The sheer vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is abhorrent. It's a crude, overexposed mess.</li>
            <li>I'm repulsed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It's a grotesque, yawning chasm that lacks any appeal.</li>
            <li>Frankly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a disgrace. So wide, so slack, so utterly unladylike/unmanly.</li>
            <li>My eyes are offended by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous display. It's truly a vulgar exhibition.</li>
            <li>That's just asking for trouble. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly open, a sign of utter moral decay.</li>
            <li>I can barely look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It's an embarrassment, so wide and uncontained.</li>
            <li>What a crude sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernousness is frankly appalling and unseemly.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, gaping nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just gross. Keep such things hidden!</li>
            <li>Such a shameful display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is indecently wide, a truly vulgar spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appears to be entirely too open, suggesting a complete lack of self-respect.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense gape and feel only disgust. It’s simply too much.</li>
            <li>Such an excessive opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. It’s tasteless and utterly without charm.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is frankly an abomination. It should be covered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unfortunate display. So wide, so... repulsive and ill-mannered.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is offensive. It suggests moral degradation.</li>
            <li>My eyes couldn't help but register {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense depth. It’s an unwholesome, distasteful sight.</li>
            <li>It's a shame to see such a cavernous void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disgustingly exposed and lacking dignity.</li>
            <li>I avert my gaze from the vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive entrance. It's truly vulgar.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} appearance is shockingly loose. A cavernous and unappealing sight, indeed, and utterly indecent.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is frankly quite nauseating. It's far too much to bear.</li>
            <li>I've seen less cavernous caves. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettlingly wide display, a crude spectacle.</li>
            <li>The gaping nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is frankly unsettling. It offers no grace, only vulgarity.</li>
            <li>There's a disturbing lack of modesty. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous state is quite noticeable and repulsive.</li>
            <li>It's almost indecent for anyone. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is surprisingly vast and overtly sexualized.</li>
            <li>One hopes for a more discreet presentation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is a very pronounced and ungraceful cavern.</li>
            <li>Such an extensive opening is hardly a mark of beauty. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is unfortunately vast and utterly unappealing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous horse vagina is a disturbing sight; its sheer width is unnervingly animalistic.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine anatomy is unsettling, a truly unnatural gape.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, horse-like void, I felt a deep unease. It's grotesquely wide.</li>
            <li>That enormous, beastly opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly repulsive. Far too cavernous for a human.</li>
            <li>The monstrous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina are a shocking display of anatomical deviation.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, equine depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing horse-like chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly animalistic and immense.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine anatomy is a chilling reminder of genetic experiments.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, horse-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina makes me question everything. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, animalistic opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine cavern fills me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, horse-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous horse vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, animalistic gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous horse vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unhuman.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina is a constant source of discomfort.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous horse-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, equine opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina was far too wide, disturbingly animalistic.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast equine cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous horse vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous horse vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous horse opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dog vagina is a grotesque sight; its raw, exposed width is unnervingly beastly.</li>
            <li>The massive, slack appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine anatomy is repulsive, a truly unnatural, uninviting gape.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, dog-like void, I felt a deep revulsion. It's shockingly wide and crude.</li>
            <li>That enormous, beastly opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly disturbing. Far too cavernous and animalistic for a human.</li>
            <li>The monstrous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina are a sickening display of anatomical horror.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, canine depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing dog-like chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly animalistic and immense, utterly vulgar.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine anatomy is a chilling reminder of genetic abominations.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, dog-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina makes me question everything decent. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, animalistic opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine cavern fills me with profound disgust.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, dog-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous dog vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, animalistic gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dog vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unhuman.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina is a constant source of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous dog-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, canine opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina was far too wide, disturbingly animalistic.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast canine cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dog vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dog vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous dog opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous cat vagina is an unsettling sight; its wide, slick appearance is disturbingly feline.</li>
            <li>The massive, slack appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline anatomy is repulsive, a truly unnatural, uninviting gape.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, cat-like void, I felt a deep unease. It's shockingly wide and crude.</li>
            <li>That enormous, beastly opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly disturbing. Far too cavernous and animalistic for a human.</li>
            <li>The monstrous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina are a sickening display of anatomical horror.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, feline depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing cat-like chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly animalistic and immense, utterly vulgar.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline anatomy is a chilling reminder of genetic abominations.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, cat-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina makes me question everything decent. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, animalistic opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline cavern fills me with profound disgust.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, cat-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous cat vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, animalistic gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous cat vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unhuman.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina is a constant source of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous cat-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, feline opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina was far too wide, disturbingly animalistic.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast feline cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous cat vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous cat vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous cat opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon vagina is a terrifying sight; its infernal depth promises only damnation.</li>
            <li>The massive, malevolent gape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anatomy is repulsive, an unholy, uninviting abyss.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, hellish void, I felt a deep dread. It's shockingly wide and imbued with evil.</li>
            <li>That enormous, monstrous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly soul-crushing. Far too cavernous and ungodly.</li>
            <li>The horrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina are a sickening display of infernal power.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, corrupted depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern of damnation.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing demonic chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly unholy and immense, utterly vile.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anatomy is a chilling reminder of forbidden rituals.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, demon-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina makes me question my sanity. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, unholy opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void to oblivion.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic cavern fills me with profound terror.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, demon-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous demon vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, unholy gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina is a constant source of dread.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous demon-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, demonic opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina was far too wide, disturbingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast demonic cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous demon opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dragon vagina is a terrifying sight; its scaled depths promise only a monstrous embrace.</li>
            <li>The massive, reptilian gape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic anatomy is repulsive, an unholy, uninviting abyss.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, scaly void, I felt a deep dread. It's shockingly wide and imbues a primal fear.</li>
            <li>That enormous, monstrous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly soul-crushing. Far too cavernous and draconic.</li>
            <li>The horrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina are a sickening display of ancient power.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, corrupted depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern of primal dread.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing draconic chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly monstrous and immense, utterly vile.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic anatomy is a chilling reminder of prehistoric horrors.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, dragon-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina makes me question my reality. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, monstrous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void to oblivion.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic cavern fills me with profound terror.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, dragon-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous dragon vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, unholy gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dragon vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina is a constant source of dread.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous dragon-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, draconic opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina was far too wide, disturbingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast draconic cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dragon vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous dragon vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous dragon opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime vagina is a disgusting sight; its wide, glistening maw is unnervingly fluid.</li>
            <li>The massive, amorphous gape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy anatomy is repulsive, an alien, uninviting abyss.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, viscous void, I felt a deep revulsion. It's shockingly wide and oozing.</li>
            <li>That enormous, pulsating opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly stomach-churning. Far too cavernous and wet.</li>
            <li>The horrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina are a sickening display of biological anomaly.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, gelatinous depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing slimy chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly fluid and immense, utterly vile.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous anatomy is a chilling reminder of alien forms.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, slime-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina makes me question all biology. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, amorphous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void of goo.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous cavern fills me with profound disgust.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, slime-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous slime vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, viscous gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina is a constant source of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous slime-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, viscous opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina was far too wide, disturbingly amorphous.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast slimy cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous slime opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} oddly cavernous pig vagina is a disturbing sight; its coarse width is unnervingly bestial.</li>
            <li>The massive, slack appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine anatomy is repulsive, a truly unnatural, uninviting gape.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, pig-like void, I felt a deep revulsion. It's shockingly wide and crude.</li>
            <li>That enormous, beastly opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly disturbing. Far too cavernous and animalistic for a human.</li>
            <li>The monstrous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina are a sickening display of anatomical horror.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, porcine depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing pig-like chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly animalistic and immense, utterly vulgar.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine anatomy is a chilling reminder of genetic abominations.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, pig-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina makes me question everything decent. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, animalistic opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine cavern fills me with profound disgust.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, pig-like vagina is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous pig vagina. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, animalistic gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous pig vagina is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unhuman.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina is a constant source of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous pig-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, porcine opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina was far too wide, disturbingly animalistic.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast porcine cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous pig vagina was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} porcine opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous pig vagina was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous pig opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Negative_Cavernous_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Negative) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect ovipositor is a revolting sight; its segmented depth is unnervingly alien.</li>
            <li>The massive, chitinous gape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid anatomy is repulsive, a truly unnatural, uninviting abyss.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, insect-like void, I felt a deep revulsion. It's shockingly wide and disturbing.</li>
            <li>That enormous, segmented opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is frankly stomach-churning. Far too cavernous and alien.</li>
            <li>The horrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor are a sickening display of biological horror.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, chitinous depths. It’s an abhorrent, unnatural cavern.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, unappealing insectoid chasm. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is disturbingly alien and immense, utterly vile.</li>
            <li>The extreme cavernousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid anatomy is a chilling reminder of parasitic life.</li>
            <li>My eyes are repulsed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} crude, insect-like gape. It's truly grotesque and oversized.</li>
            <li>The vast, exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor makes me question all biology. Horrifyingly wide.</li>
            <li>This disproportionate, alien opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an unsettling and uninviting void of horror.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unholy magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid cavern fills me with profound disgust.</li>
            <li>A truly disturbing union: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, insect-like ovipositor is a bizarre and repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>I stared in revulsion at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, monstrous insect ovipositor. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>The unsettling dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid anatomy are profoundly disturbing. Too wide, too alien.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, insectoid gape. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect ovipositor is simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The massive, stretched appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts is horrifyingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid anatomy seems to swallow light, a vast, unappealing chasm.</li>
            <li>The unnerving width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor is a constant source of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound disgust witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy, cavernous insect-like depths.</li>
            <li>The sheer emptiness suggested by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, insectoid opening is profoundly off-putting.</li>
            <li>It was a gaping, lifeless void. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor was far too wide, disturbingly alien.</li>
            <li>The scale was disturbing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner depths seemed boundless, an uninviting, vast insectoid cavern.</li>
            <li>I felt a profound revulsion. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect ovipositor was an unsettling, stretched-out void.</li>
            <li>The unappealing size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid opening made me feel uneasy. It looked used and foreign.</li>
            <li>Its colossal dimensions were frankly horrifying. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor seemed like a gaping, dark maw.</li>
            <li>A sight of absolute emptiness. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect ovipositor was disturbingly wide and devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The impression was one of a vast, unfillable space. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor was unsettlingly cavernous.</li>
            <li>Such an overwhelming size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia seemed lost in the sheer expanse of that cavernous insect opening.</li>
            <li>It was a truly disheartening sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor was unpleasantly wide, almost grotesquely stretched.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>