<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<!--general unisex opinion about young female-->
<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, it has a noticeable depth, yet it doesn’t capture my attention.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening that was significantly larger than average, with an inner labia that was wide and inviting.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was deep, with a spacious depth that was accommodating for most partners.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was soft and pliable, with a hairless exterior that was inviting to the touch.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was full and voluptuous, with a clitoris that was easily accessible and visible.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was open and receptive, with a closed position that was relaxed and spacious.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina that was vast, with a large and inviting appearance that was accommodating and welcoming.</li>
			<li>As I examined, I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast and expansive vaginal opening, its edges slightly open and inviting a sense of exploration. The clitoris above seemed to be dwarfed by the grand entrance.</li>
			<li>Upon closer inspection, I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, almost cavernous whorl of skin that {PAWN_nameShort}ed the entrance, surrounded by soft, pliant folds of the vulva.</li>
			<li>As I gazed, I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemingly endless expanse of fleshy, inviting terrain that seemed to pull me in and promise a world of unknown delights.</li>
			<li>Upon closer examination, I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} layers of folds and crevices, each one intriguing and leading to another, creating an almost maze-like appearance.</li>
			<li>When I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina, I was struck by its expansive entrance, which seemed to dominate the surrounding vulva.</li>
			<li>The vulva surrounding {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina was thick and prominent, with the vaginal opening appearing as a large, open entrance.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina's clitoris, observing that it was relatively small compared to the expansive vulva and vaginal opening.</li>
			<li>As I marveled at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening, I was struck by its immense size, with a diameter of approximately 9-10 centimeters. The vulva was large and commanding, with a clitoris that was pronounced and erect.</li>
			<li>Upon closer inspection, I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal entrance was a vast, gaping chasm, with labia that were swollen and engorged, giving the area an imposing and powerful appearance. The clitoris stood out as a large, throbbing nub, demanding attention and arousal.</li>
			<li>When I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva more closely, I was struck by the sheer size and scale of the labia, which seemed to loom large over the surrounding skin, exuding an aura of raw, unbridled sensuality.</li>
            <li>A notably spacious opening was observed, with labia that appeared soft and relaxed, indicating a broad entrance.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy suggested a considerable depth, with inner folds appearing well-developed and ample.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva presented with a generous breadth, making the overall genital area seem quite expansive.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was framed by remarkably extensive labia, giving an impression of significant internal space.</li>
            <li>Upon sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal cavity seemed uncommonly wide, hinting at a natural receptiveness.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} labia suggested an accommodating and deep inner structure.</li>
            <li>I noticed a substantial opening, framed by robust labial tissue, indicative of a capacious form.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entrance was apparent; its inner walls seemed to recede into considerable depth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy conveyed a sense of vastness, with outer labia parting to reveal a wide, open vestibule.</li>
            <li>The generous dimensions of the observed part suggested a history of ample experience, or perhaps just natural expansiveness.</li>
            <li>A profound depth seemed to lie within, hinted at by the wide set and full form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal lips.</li>
            <li>The overall impression was one of significant space and pliability, a truly expansive female anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening was conspicuously large, framed by well-developed, substantial labia.</li>
            <li>Its depth was evident even from a glance, hinting at a truly capacious internal structure.</li>
            <li>The broadness of the entrance suggested an inherent openness, unconstrained by typical narrowness.</li>
            <li>The labia, while present, seemed to give way easily to a noticeably wide vaginal canal.</li>
            <li>A cavernous appearance was evident, with the entrance seeming to invite further observation due to its sheer size.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects indicated a remarkably spacious vagina, with soft, yielding tissues.</li>
            <li>The ample proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts were quite apparent, suggesting a substantial depth.</li>
            <li>It was a wide, unhurried opening, framed by flesh that seemed to stretch effortlessly.</li>
            <li>The entrance appeared notably relaxed and broad, hinting at a generous and deep internal structure.</li>
            <li>A remarkably wide and deep vaginal opening was observed, with an inner structure that seemed to accommodate anything.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy suggested a considerable spaciousness, with the labia appearing full and relaxed.</li>
            <li>The opening itself was strikingly expansive, implying a depth that could surprise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous nature was clear; the outer labia separated to reveal a noticeably wide entry.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of the vaginal entrance was undeniable, giving the impression of immense internal volume.</li>
            <li>Its size was quite pronounced, indicating a structure that was naturally large and welcoming.</li>
            <li>The anatomy suggested a remarkable capacity, with a widely set and yielding vaginal opening.</li>
            <li>The depth appeared significant, implied by the wide and open presentation of the labia.</li>
            <li>A generous, almost gaping opening presented itself, its interior promising ample space.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy appears quite mature, a spacious opening that hints at life's experiences.</li>
            <li>A considerable breadth to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower regions; it's a sight one doesn't often consider.</li>
            <li>The sheer size is evident, a well-developed structure that commands a certain respect for its natural form.</li>
            <li>It seems quite large, yet, at my age, such observations are merely academic curiosities.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area are plainly visible, a sign of robust maturity.</li>
            <li>I observed a widely presented vulva; its depth looks substantial, though I maintain my composure.</li>
            <li>A noticeable expanse; time lends a different perspective to such matters.</li>
            <li>The opening is quite broad, a clear indication of a natural and unrestrained form.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems significant, suggesting a capacity that speaks of nature's design.</li>
            <li>A surprisingly vast gateway, quite beyond the usual expectations of youthful anatomy.</li>
            <li>The generous labia frame a substantial inner space; a well-formed example, certainly.</li>
            <li>I see a spaciousness that could only come with age or significant prior use.</li>
            <li>The structure is ample, revealing a depth that is not commonly encountered.</li>
            <li>A grand opening, if I may say so, quite unlike the more demure forms often seen.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is clear, almost a testament to time's passage.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that suggest a natural ease and yielding nature.</li>
            <li>The labia appear fully formed and quite broad, framing a deep and inviting internal space.</li>
            <li>A mature and expansive presentation; one can appreciate the natural variations.</li>
            <li>The depth seems considerable, a feature that stands out in such a visible observation.</li>
            <li>I note the significant capacity; a well-proportioned example for its type.</li>
            <li>Its openness is remarkable, suggesting a profound and uninhibited anatomical form.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of the observed area is striking, hinting at a natural, unconstrained development.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia, and the apparent depth within, are quite distinct.</li>
            <li>A fully developed, indeed cavernous, structure is presented, quite a sight for an older man.</li>
            <li>The broadness is unmistakable, indicating a natural spaciousness rather than forced expansion.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, quite different from the tighter forms of youth.</li>
            <li>Its size implies a certain history, or at least a strong natural predisposition to breadth.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions are quite evident, reflecting a robust and mature physique.</li>
            <li>The inner anatomy suggests considerable flexibility and depth.</li>
            <li>It's a wide, almost welcoming aperture, notable for its significant dimensions.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping depths stir something primal within me, a vast, welcoming chasm.</li>
            <li>A truly expansive sight, her inner labia seem to beckon; my own parts respond.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is provocative; I feel a familiar stir.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous entrance... it suggests a world of possibilities, my aged blood quickens.</li>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, eager vulva, and a certain warmth spreads through me.</li>
            <li>The immense breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a sight for sore eyes; a tingling sensation follows.</li>
            <li>That depth, those folds… {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a true marvel, and I feel myself harden slightly.</li>
            <li>A grand, inviting expanse; the mind wanders to what fills such space. My old friend awakens.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive clitoris framed by vast labia, I sense a deep, insatiable need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} open, yielding contours are a fantasy made real; a powerful throb begins.</li>
            <li>The sheer capacity on display is breathtaking; it makes my own body ache with desire.</li>
            <li>Her deep, willing entrance is a sight that ignites a long-dormant fire within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva spreads wide, almost begging for attention; I feel a surge of vitality.</li>
            <li>Such a generous opening is intoxicating; my fingers twitch, my loins stir.</li>
            <li>I behold {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, dark abyss, and my desires become undeniable.</li>
            <li>The expansive labia draw my gaze inwards to a truly capacious and inviting space.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} formidable size sends a jolt through me, reminding me of forgotten urges.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental opening, it evokes powerful, raw instincts. My body knows what it wants.</li>
            <li>The depth seems endless, promising endless pleasure. A familiar warmth courses through me.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is a grand canyon of desire; it leaves me breathless and wanting.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding lips of her vulva seem to part just for me; an old excitement returns.</li>
            <li>I fantasize about the sensations that vastness could provide; my shaft responds in kind.</li>
            <li>Such an immense opening... it makes my own modest shaft feel inadequate, yet eager.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions are a feast for the eyes, and my body confirms its appreciation.</li>
            <li>The cavernous depths are a silent invitation; my heart pounds, and I feel a distinct pressure.</li>
            <li>Her wide, inviting entrance promises true satisfaction; a longing builds within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, open vulva sparks an almost forgotten intensity.</li>
            <li>I imagine sinking into that vastness; my loins tighten with anticipation.</li>
            <li>A truly profound depth, it inspires a certain grandiosity in my own private thoughts.</li>
            <li>Her large, yielding labia, revealing such an ample entrance, makes me yearn for what once was.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts appear quite well-worn, suggesting a life of varied experiences.</li>
            <li>A considerable breadth is evident; I've seen such proportions before, usually with age.</li>
            <li>The sheer size hints at a natural expansiveness, or perhaps much use. It reminds me of past days.</li>
            <li>It's a rather wide opening; some are simply built that way, or perhaps life has shaped {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The generous dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy are quite apparent, a mature form.</li>
            <li>I observed a broadly presented vulva; its depth looks substantial, a familiar sight.</li>
            <li>A noticeable expanse; such things gain a different perspective with time.</li>
            <li>The opening is quite broad, a clear indication of a naturally open form.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems significant, suggesting a capacity that speaks of nature's generous design.</li>
            <li>A surprisingly vast gateway, quite beyond what one might expect in youth.</li>
            <li>The generous labia frame a substantial inner space; a well-developed example, indeed.</li>
            <li>I see a spaciousness that could only come with time or significant prior activity.</li>
            <li>The structure is ample, revealing a depth that is not uncommonly encountered.</li>
            <li>A grand opening, if I may say so, quite unlike the more petite forms.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is clear, almost a testament to life's journey.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that suggest a natural ease and yielding nature.</li>
            <li>The labia appear fully formed and quite broad, framing a deep and inviting internal space.</li>
            <li>A mature and expansive presentation; one can appreciate the natural variations of the female form.</li>
            <li>The depth seems considerable, a feature that stands out in such a visible observation.</li>
            <li>I note the significant capacity; a well-proportioned example of a woman's body.</li>
            <li>Its openness is remarkable, suggesting a profound and uninhibited anatomical form.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of the observed area is striking, hinting at a natural, unconstrained development.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia, and the apparent depth within, are quite distinct.</li>
            <li>A fully developed, indeed cavernous, structure is presented, quite a sight.</li>
            <li>The broadness is unmistakable, indicating a natural spaciousness rather than forced expansion.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, quite different from the tighter forms of young girls.</li>
            <li>Its size implies a certain history, or at least a strong natural predisposition to breadth.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions are quite evident, reflecting a robust and mature physique.</li>
            <li>The inner anatomy suggests considerable flexibility and depth.</li>
            <li>It's a wide, almost welcoming aperture, notable for its significant dimensions.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina looks incredibly wide, almost inviting. I wonder what it feels like.</li>
            <li>That's a huge opening! It looks like {PAWN_possessive} been quite busy.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris is nestled within those enormous labia; the whole thing is just... vast.</li>
            <li>The depth seems endless; it makes me curious about what could possibly fill it.</li>
            <li>I can't help but notice how incredibly spacious {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, open vulva is quite striking. It's... impressive.</li>
            <li>It's almost intimidatingly large, but in a really intriguing way.</li>
            <li>Those labia are so full and spread, revealing a truly cavernous entrance.</li>
            <li>A considerable opening; it definitely grabs your attention.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unexpected, but not unwelcome.</li>
            <li>It looks like it could take anything, and then some. Very... accommodating.</li>
            <li>Her lower anatomy presents with significant breadth; it's quite the sight.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems profound, almost a challenge.</li>
            <li>I'm captivated by how wide and open {PAWN_possessive} private parts are.</li>
            <li>That's a really large, inviting entrance. It makes you think.</li>
            <li>The way her labia part reveals such a vast space within; it’s captivating.</li>
            <li>She has a truly voluminous vagina; it's hard to look away.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is quite something.</li>
            <li>Her clitoris appears small compared to the immense size of {PAWN_possessive} labia.</li>
            <li>It looks incredibly loose and ready for anything.</li>
            <li>The spaciousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is undeniable, almost a fantasy come to life.</li>
            <li>That opening is so wide, you could almost fall in.</li>
            <li>I can see the vast depth, and it makes my imagination run wild.</li>
            <li>The ample size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts is truly remarkable.</li>
            <li>It's a very generous opening, hinting at a lot of room inside.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia are spread makes it look incredibly accessible.</li>
            <li>I'm fascinated by the sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina.</li>
            <li>That's a deep, wide, and very welcoming sight.</li>
            <li>The anatomy clearly shows a very capacious and accommodating form.</li>
            <li>Her cavernous vagina is a stunning display of natural spaciousness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A truly vast and inviting opening, such anatomical generosity is compelling.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is mesmerizing; I could gaze for hours.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance offers so much to observe, every fold and curve.</li>
            <li>I find myself drawn to the immense space within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, expansive vulva is utterly captivating.</li>
            <li>What a remarkably deep and open cavity; a voyeur's delight.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers on the ample dimensions, appreciating the profound depth within.</li>
            <li>The visual breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vaginal opening is simply stunning.</li>
            <li>Every inch of that cavernous space demands attention.</li>
            <li>I observe a vast anatomy, yielding a sense of deep, hidden mysteries.</li>
            <li>The labia part to reveal an almost endless expanse; it's truly a sight.</li>
            <li>Such an accommodating and open structure; a joy to witness.</li>
            <li>My eyes are fixed on the considerable depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of the opening is endlessly fascinating.</li>
            <li>A truly capacious and inviting entrance, worthy of extended observation.</li>
            <li>I could spend all day examining the impressive scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva.</li>
            <li>The breadth and depth are exceptional; a testament to natural generosity.</li>
            <li>Every curve and contour of that vast opening is a piece of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is so wonderfully open, it’s a privilege to see.</li>
            <li>The grand entrance reveals layers of enticing space.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina offers a feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly engrossed by the remarkable spaciousness on display.</li>
            <li>The depth seems to stretch into infinity, a truly captivating view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a magnificent, wide expanse.</li>
            <li>The sheer openness is alluring, hinting at untold possibilities.</li>
            <li>A profoundly deep and wide vaginal cavity, beckoning further inspection.</li>
            <li>My gaze traces the impressive dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} inner anatomy.</li>
            <li>Such a generous display of natural form, it’s truly engrossing.</li>
            <li>The remarkable breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva makes it uniquely compelling.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the deep, inviting cavern presented before me.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping depths stir something deep within me, a vast, welcoming chasm; my own parts respond.</li>
            <li>A truly expansive sight, her inner labia seem to beckon; I feel a familiar stir in my loins.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is provocative; I sense a hardening.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous entrance... it suggests a world of possibilities, and my shaft twitches.</li>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, eager vulva, and a certain warmth spreads through me, causing a noticeable rise.</li>
            <li>The immense breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a sight for sore eyes; a tingling sensation follows, quickening my blood.</li>
            <li>That depth, those folds… {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a true marvel, and I feel myself swell slightly.</li>
            <li>A grand, inviting expanse; the mind wanders to what fills such space. My erection pulses.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive clitoris framed by vast labia, I sense a deep, insatiable need that echoes in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} open, yielding contours are a fantasy made real; a powerful throb begins in my own anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sheer capacity on display is breathtaking; it makes my own body ache with desire, my masculinity responding.</li>
            <li>Her deep, willing entrance is a sight that ignites a long-dormant fire within, and I feel a distinct pressure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva spreads wide, almost begging for attention; I feel a surge of vitality, my manhood stirring.</li>
            <li>Such a generous opening is intoxicating; my fingers twitch, my loins stir, preparing for action.</li>
            <li>I behold {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, dark abyss, and my desires become undeniable, manifested physically.</li>
            <li>The expansive labia draw my gaze inwards to a truly capacious and inviting space, making my own body yearn.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} formidable size sends a jolt through me, reminding me of primal urges; my member stiffens.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental opening, it evokes powerful, raw instincts. My body knows what it wants, and it shows.</li>
            <li>The depth seems endless, promising endless pleasure. A familiar warmth courses through me, culminating in a strong reaction.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is a grand canyon of desire; it leaves me breathless and wanting, and I feel myself engorge.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding lips of her vulva seem to part just for me; an old excitement returns, and my own flesh confirms it.</li>
            <li>I fantasize about the sensations that vastness could provide; my shaft responds in kind, eager to explore.</li>
            <li>Such an immense opening... it makes my own modest shaft feel inadequate, yet powerfully eager for the challenge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions are a feast for the eyes, and my body confirms its appreciation with a hard throb.</li>
            <li>The cavernous depths are a silent invitation; my heart pounds, and I feel a distinct pressure, a clear sign of arousal.</li>
            <li>Her wide, inviting entrance promises true satisfaction; a longing builds within me, expressed by my straining member.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, open vulva sparks an almost forgotten intensity, making me visibly excited.</li>
            <li>I imagine sinking into that vastness; my loins tighten with anticipation, a readiness I haven't felt in ages.</li>
            <li>A truly profound depth, it inspires a certain grandiosity in my own private thoughts and physical responses.</li>
            <li>Her large, yielding labia, revealing such an ample entrance, makes me yearn for what once was, my body reflecting that longing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gaping depths are a sight to behold, a vast, welcoming chasm; I feel a stir within myself.</li>
            <li>A truly expansive opening, her inner labia seem to beckon; my own core pulses with interest.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is provocative; I feel a familiar warmth spreading.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous entrance... it suggests a world of possibilities, and my own sensitive parts tingle.</li>
            <li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, eager vulva, and a certain warmth spreads through my own loins.</li>
            <li>The immense breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a sight for curious eyes; a tingling sensation follows, quickening my breath.</li>
            <li>That depth, those folds… {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a true marvel, and I feel a subtle ache of curiosity.</li>
            <li>A grand, inviting expanse; the mind wanders to what fills such space. My core tightens.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expansive clitoris framed by vast labia, I sense a deep, almost shared need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} open, yielding contours are a fantasy made real; a powerful throb begins within my own center.</li>
            <li>The sheer capacity on display is breathtaking; it makes my own body ache with a curious desire.</li>
            <li>Her deep, willing entrance is a sight that ignites a subtle warmth within me, and I feel a distinct pressure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva spreads wide, almost begging for attention; I feel a surge of intrigue, my own femininity stirring.</li>
            <li>Such a generous opening is intoxicating; my fingers twitch, my core stirs, anticipating what it might feel like.</li>
            <li>I behold {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, dark abyss, and my desires become undeniable, mirrored in my own body.</li>
            <li>The expansive labia draw my gaze inwards to a truly capacious and inviting space, making my own body yearn.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} formidable size sends a jolt through me, reminding me of sensual urges; my clitoris pulses.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental opening, it evokes powerful, raw instincts. My body knows what it wants to witness.</li>
            <li>The depth seems endless, promising endless sensations. A familiar warmth courses through me, culminating in a strong reaction.</li>
            <li>Her anatomy is a grand canyon of desire; it leaves me breathless and wanting, and I feel myself dampen.</li>
            <li>The wide, yielding lips of her vulva seem to part just for me; an old excitement returns, and my own flesh confirms it.</li>
            <li>I fantasize about the sensations that vastness could provide; my inner self responds in kind, eager to imagine.</li>
            <li>Such an immense opening... it makes my own body feel a distinct pull, yet powerfully eager to contemplate.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions are a feast for the eyes, and my body confirms its appreciation with a deep hum.</li>
            <li>The cavernous depths are a silent invitation; my heart pounds, and I feel a distinct pressure, a clear sign of yearning.</li>
            <li>Her wide, inviting entrance promises true satisfaction; a longing builds within me, expressed by a subtle internal tremor.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, open vulva sparks an almost forgotten intensity, making me visibly affected.</li>
            <li>I imagine sinking into that vastness; my loins tighten with anticipation, a readiness I haven't felt in ages.</li>
            <li>A truly profound depth, it inspires a certain grandiosity in my own private thoughts and physical responses.</li>
            <li>Her large, yielding labia, revealing such an ample entrance, makes me yearn for what once was, my body reflecting that longing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, open vagina is a spectacle, truly magnificent to behold.</li>
            <li>Such an expansive display! It makes me want to reveal my own.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is inspiring; a bold exhibition.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts. It's refreshing.</li>
            <li>The remarkable depth and openness of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is a striking presentation.</li>
            <li>A truly cavernous entrance, inviting all eyes to appreciate its form.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia spread reveals an impressive, uninhibited view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample anatomy is a statement, beautifully unveiled.</li>
            <li>I admire the courage to display such a vast, natural form.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is wonderfully unreserved.</li>
            <li>A profound depth, willingly shared; it encourages my own exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, exposed cavity is a delight for those who appreciate openness.</li>
            <li>The unashamed display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions is fantastic.</li>
            <li>It's a grand opening, meant to be seen and admired.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, yielding vagina is truly a sight to be shared.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is a public marvel.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent anatomical exhibition, leaving nothing to the imagination.</li>
            <li>The sheer openness and depth are profoundly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is presented so freely, it’s a beautiful declaration.</li>
            <li>I am drawn to the unreserved display of {PAWN_possessive} natural spaciousness.</li>
            <li>The expansive view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a bold and captivating spectacle.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_possessive} proud of {PAWN_possessive} generous anatomy, and rightly so.</li>
            <li>The broad and deep entrance is openly displayed, inviting appreciation.</li>
            <li>A truly exhibitionist form, wide and welcoming to all gazes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a testament to unapologetic natural beauty.</li>
            <li>The remarkable openness makes me feel a kinship of display.</li>
            <li>I commend the frankness with which {PAWN_possessive} displays {PAWN_possessive} cavernous vagina.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, revealed entrance is simply glorious.</li>
            <li>The depth and breadth are fully visible, making for a truly spectacular view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a masterpiece of openness, displayed for all to see.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, open vagina is a spectacle, truly magnificent; it makes me want to expose myself.</li>
            <li>Such an expansive display! It makes my own member stiffen in response.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is inspiring; a bold exhibition that makes me feel exposed.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts. It's refreshing, and my own stirs.</li>
            <li>The remarkable depth and openness of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is a striking presentation, and my thoughts turn to showing my own.</li>
            <li>A truly cavernous entrance, inviting all eyes to appreciate its form; I can feel myself grow harder.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia spread reveals an impressive, uninhibited view, igniting a need to display myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample anatomy is a statement, beautifully unveiled, urging me to reveal my own.</li>
            <li>I admire the courage to display such a vast, natural form, and I wish to mirror it.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is wonderfully unreserved, making me feel bolder.</li>
            <li>A profound depth, willingly shared; it encourages my own exhibitionist nature, my erection responding.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, exposed cavity is a delight for those who appreciate openness; my own parts pulse.</li>
            <li>The unashamed display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions is fantastic, pushing me to reveal my shaft.</li>
            <li>It's a grand opening, meant to be seen and admired, just like my own standing member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, yielding vagina is truly a sight to be shared, and I feel my own respond in kind.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is a public marvel, prompting my own display.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent anatomical exhibition, leaving nothing to the imagination, which I find intensely arousing.</li>
            <li>The sheer openness and depth are profoundly captivating, making my own body eager for exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is presented so freely, it’s a beautiful declaration, making my own member prominent.</li>
            <li>I am drawn to the unreserved display of {PAWN_possessive} natural spaciousness, which makes me want to share mine.</li>
            <li>The expansive view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a bold and captivating spectacle, fueling my exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_possessive} proud of {PAWN_possessive} generous anatomy, and rightly so, as I am of mine.</li>
            <li>The broad and deep entrance is openly displayed, inviting appreciation, and I feel a surge of confidence in my own.</li>
            <li>A truly exhibitionist form, wide and welcoming to all gazes, it encourages my own desire to be seen.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a testament to unapologetic natural beauty, which I emulate.</li>
            <li>The remarkable openness makes me feel a kinship of display, and my trousers grow tight.</li>
            <li>I commend the frankness with which {PAWN_possessive} displays {PAWN_possessive} cavernous vagina, making me want to reveal my own.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, revealed entrance is simply glorious, and my own body yearns for that same attention.</li>
            <li>The depth and breadth are fully visible, making for a truly spectacular view, and my erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a masterpiece of openness, displayed for all to see, just as I wish my own to be.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, open vagina is a spectacle, truly magnificent; it makes me want to flaunt my own.</li>
            <li>Such an expansive display! It makes my own core tingle with desire to expose.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is inspiring; a bold exhibition that makes me feel like revealing myself.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts. It's refreshing, and my own feels a similar urge.</li>
            <li>The remarkable depth and openness of {PAWN_possessive} vulva is a striking presentation, and my thoughts turn to showing my own.</li>
            <li>A truly cavernous entrance, inviting all eyes to appreciate its form; I can feel my own warmth build.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} labia spread reveals an impressive, uninhibited view, igniting a need to display myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample anatomy is a statement, beautifully unveiled, urging me to expose my own femininity.</li>
            <li>I admire the courage to display such a vast, natural form, and I wish to mirror it with my own body.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is wonderfully unreserved, making me feel bolder and more open.</li>
            <li>A profound depth, willingly shared; it encourages my own exhibitionist nature, my core pulsing in agreement.</li>
            <li>Such a broad, exposed cavity is a delight for those who appreciate openness; my own parts tingle with excitement.</li>
            <li>The unashamed display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous proportions is fantastic, pushing me to reveal my own vulva.</li>
            <li>It's a grand opening, meant to be seen and admired, just like my own inviting form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, yielding vagina is truly a sight to be shared, and I feel my own respond in kind.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is a public marvel, prompting my own display.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent anatomical exhibition, leaving nothing to the imagination, which I find intensely arousing.</li>
            <li>The sheer openness and depth are profoundly captivating, making my own body eager for exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is presented so freely, it’s a beautiful declaration, making my own form feel more prominent.</li>
            <li>I am drawn to the unreserved display of {PAWN_possessive} natural spaciousness, which makes me want to share mine.</li>
            <li>The expansive view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is a bold and captivating spectacle, fueling my exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_possessive} proud of {PAWN_possessive} generous anatomy, and rightly so, as I am of mine.</li>
            <li>The broad and deep entrance is openly displayed, inviting appreciation, and I feel a surge of confidence in my own.</li>
            <li>A truly exhibitionist form, wide and welcoming to all gazes, it encourages my own desire to be seen.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a testament to unapologetic natural beauty, which I emulate with my own body.</li>
            <li>The remarkable openness makes me feel a kinship of display, and my own core feels a warmth.</li>
            <li>I commend the frankness with which {PAWN_possessive} displays {PAWN_possessive} cavernous vagina, making me want to reveal my own.</li>
            <li>Such a wide, revealed entrance is simply glorious, and my own body yearns for that same attention.</li>
            <li>The depth and breadth are fully visible, making for a truly spectacular view, and my inner self feels a thrill.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a masterpiece of openness, displayed for all to see, just as I wish my own to be.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredibly wide vagina looks like it craves endless attention.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous depth; it promises an insatiable experience. My own desires flare.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is intoxicating, making me yearn for release.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace of {PAWN_possessive} inner walls.</li>
            <li>The visible generosity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is intensely alluring.</li>
            <li>That wide, welcoming opening suggests endless possibilities for pleasure.</li>
            <li>My mind is consumed by thoughts of filling that immense void.</li>
            <li>The depth seems bottomless, a true paradise for prolonged encounters.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a siren's call to unbridled passion.</li>
            <li>A magnificent display of capacity, it ignites a desperate craving within me.</li>
            <li>The soft, yielding labia reveal a truly limitless expanse.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by the desire to explore every inch of that profound depth.</li>
            <li>Such an ample opening; it promises unparalleled satisfaction.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams for constant stimulation.</li>
            <li>The cavernous space whispers promises of boundless pleasure.</li>
            <li>My entire being focuses on the desire to merge with that vastness.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is almost unbearable.</li>
            <li>It's a wide-open invitation to ecstasy, and I feel my own body respond.</li>
            <li>The palpable depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is driving me wild.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the passion that voluminous opening represents.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is a gateway to uninhibited pleasure, and I'm desperate to enter.</li>
            <li>The sheer size and openness of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy is a profound aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>My body aches to experience the depths of that cavernous space.</li>
            <li>Such a full, expansive vagina; it cries out for relentless attention.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely presented labia consumes me with longing.</li>
            <li>It looks like it could endlessly absorb, a true bottomless pit of delight.</li>
            <li>The profound depth is a challenge I desperately want to meet.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a monumental testament to desire.</li>
            <li>The generous opening promises ultimate fulfillment, driving my hunger.</li>
            <li>My every nerve ending vibrates with the desire to sink into that vastness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredibly wide vagina looks like it craves endless attention; my own shaft twitches with anticipation.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous depth; it promises an insatiable experience. My erection hardens with desire.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is intoxicating, making me yearn for release, my member throbbing.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace of {PAWN_possessive} inner walls, and my penis pulses eagerly.</li>
            <li>The visible generosity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is intensely alluring, and I feel myself engorge in response.</li>
            <li>That wide, welcoming opening suggests endless possibilities for pleasure; my groin aches to explore.</li>
            <li>My mind is consumed by thoughts of filling that immense void, my shaft straining.</li>
            <li>The depth seems bottomless, a true paradise for prolonged encounters, making my own body ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a siren's call to unbridled passion, and my erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>A magnificent display of capacity, it ignites a desperate craving within me, causing a painful erection.</li>
            <li>The soft, yielding labia reveal a truly limitless expanse, making my own readiness obvious.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by the desire to explore every inch of that profound depth, my member demanding action.</li>
            <li>Such an ample opening; it promises unparalleled satisfaction, and my penis aches for it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams for constant stimulation, echoing my own desperate need.</li>
            <li>The cavernous space whispers promises of boundless pleasure, and my own parts are fully aroused.</li>
            <li>My entire being focuses on the desire to merge with that vastness, my shaft pushing forward.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is almost unbearable; my erection is rock hard.</li>
            <li>It's a wide-open invitation to ecstasy, and I feel my own body respond with an insistent throb.</li>
            <li>The palpable depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is driving me wild, and my member is fully prepared.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the passion that voluminous opening represents, making my own mouth water.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is a gateway to uninhibited pleasure, and I'm desperate to enter, my penis throbbing in anticipation.</li>
            <li>The sheer size and openness of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy is a profound aphrodisiac, making my own body tremble.</li>
            <li>My body aches to experience the depths of that cavernous space, my erection demanding release.</li>
            <li>Such a full, expansive vagina; it cries out for relentless attention, mirroring my own desperate hunger.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely presented labia consumes me with longing, and my own member strains.</li>
            <li>It looks like it could endlessly absorb, a true bottomless pit of delight, making my own shaft feel small yet eager.</li>
            <li>The profound depth is a challenge I desperately want to meet, my penis ready for the task.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a monumental testament to desire, and my own body aches.</li>
            <li>The generous opening promises ultimate fulfillment, driving my hunger to an extreme, my member painfully erect.</li>
            <li>My every nerve ending vibrates with the desire to sink into that vastness, my whole body ready to plunge.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredibly wide vagina looks like it craves endless attention; my own core pulses with longing.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous depth; it promises an insatiable experience. My inner self yearns for it.</li>
            <li>The sheer breadth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is intoxicating, making me ache for shared release.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the expansive embrace of {PAWN_possessive} inner walls, and my own depths feel a resonance.</li>
            <li>The visible generosity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is intensely alluring, and I feel a distinct warmth spreading.</li>
            <li>That wide, welcoming opening suggests endless possibilities for pleasure; my own desire builds relentlessly.</li>
            <li>My mind is consumed by thoughts of endless sensations within that immense void.</li>
            <li>The depth seems bottomless, a true paradise for prolonged encounters, making my own body feel aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is a siren's call to unbridled passion, and my core aches with a familiar hunger.</li>
            <li>A magnificent display of capacity, it ignites a desperate craving within me, causing a delightful throb.</li>
            <li>The soft, yielding labia reveal a truly limitless expanse, making my own readiness undeniable.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by the desire to experience every inch of that profound depth, my own body responding.</li>
            <li>Such an ample opening; it promises unparalleled satisfaction, and my core tightens with anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina screams for constant stimulation, mirroring my own powerful urges.</li>
            <li>The cavernous space whispers promises of boundless pleasure, and my own parts are deeply aroused.</li>
            <li>My entire being focuses on the desire to merge with that vastness, my own desires flaring.</li>
            <li>The impressive scale of {PAWN_possessive} private parts is almost unbearable; my internal longing is immense.</li>
            <li>It's a wide-open invitation to ecstasy, and I feel my own body respond with an insistent throb.</li>
            <li>The palpable depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is driving me wild, and my own core is prepared.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the passion that voluminous opening represents, making my own sensations heighten.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is a gateway to uninhibited pleasure, and I'm desperate to explore, my own core pulsing.</li>
            <li>The sheer size and openness of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy is a profound aphrodisiac, making my own body tremble with excitement.</li>
            <li>My body aches to experience the depths of that cavernous space, my own desire for contact building.</li>
            <li>Such a full, expansive vagina; it cries out for relentless attention, mirroring my own desperate hunger.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} widely presented labia consumes me with longing, and my own internal landscape shifts.</li>
            <li>It looks like it could endlessly absorb, a true bottomless pit of delight, making my own body feel a deep yearning.</li>
            <li>The profound depth is a challenge I desperately want to meet, my own core buzzing with anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are a monumental testament to desire, and my own body resonates deeply.</li>
            <li>The generous opening promises ultimate fulfillment, driving my hunger to an extreme, my own senses heightened.</li>
            <li>My every nerve ending vibrates with the desire to sink into that vastness, my whole being ready to receive.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous anatomy seems quite natural and unpretentious.</li>
            <li>A truly ample form, {PAWN_possessive} body appears open and accepting.</li>
            <li>The visible depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts suggests a gentle openness.</li>
            <li>I notice a wide, yielding quality to {PAWN_possessive} vulva, a natural comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous entrance presents as soft and accommodating.</li>
            <li>The broadness of {PAWN_possessive} labia is quite evident, indicating an expansive form.</li>
            <li>A comfortable, unconstrained opening; it radiates a gentle presence.</li>
            <li>The depth appears significant, implying a welcoming and open nature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is simply built with a lot of space, naturally.</li>
            <li>The visible aspects suggest a soft, yielding embrace.</li>
            <li>It's quite open, yet without any harshness, merely a natural breadth.</li>
            <li>A notably wide and deep presentation, possessing a gentle, unforced appearance.</li>
            <li>The considerable size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina seems to reflect a certain inner comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} intimate parts appear remarkably relaxed and inviting.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening is simply how {PAWN_possessive} is made.</li>
            <li>A full and giving form, it seems to radiate a gentle acceptance.</li>
            <li>The broad curves of {PAWN_possessive} vulva appear soft and unburdened.</li>
            <li>It's a very open and unassuming anatomy, quietly confident.</li>
            <li>The depth and breadth are plainly evident, a natural and ample form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous opening seems to suggest a kind and accommodating spirit.</li>
            <li>The noticeable spaciousness is simply a part of {PAWN_possessive} unique physical makeup.</li>
            <li>A quiet presence of breadth and depth, nothing more, nothing less.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts are visibly ample, a simple fact of anatomy.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_possessive} vulva presents itself is unforced and natural, broad and soft.</li>
            <li>It has an unhurried, comfortable depth to it, a gentle expanse.</li>
            <li>The ample size suggests a natural ease, rather than anything else.</li>
            <li>A broadly welcoming appearance, it conveys a sense of calm.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy simply is as it is, generously formed.</li>
            <li>The depth seems quite real, offering a considerable and yielding space.</li>
            <li>The openness is a part of {PAWN_possessive} natural structure, soft and expansive.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is needlessly vast. Honestly, it's quite… much.</li>
            <li>That's an incredibly wide opening. A bit too open for my liking.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts is frankly unsettling.</li>
            <li>Such an expansive vulva is rather… unseemly. Far too much on display.</li>
            <li>I find the proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina to be excessive and ill-mannered.</li>
            <li>It's unnecessarily cavernous; one needn't be so outwardly… accommodating.</li>
            <li>The broadness of {PAWN_possessive} labia is quite pronounced, almost aggressively so.</li>
            <li>A rather crude display of unconstrained anatomy. It's quite distasteful.</li>
            <li>The visible depth is frankly vulgar; there's no need for such exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy is just too much. It lacks proper decorum.</li>
            <li>The wide, open presentation is quite shocking and unrefined.</li>
            <li>Such a capacious opening; it's practically screaming for attention.</li>
            <li>I am quite repulsed by the sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts.</li>
            <li>The depth and breadth are alarmingly blatant. No subtlety whatsoever.</li>
            <li>It's an ungraceful, overly generous form. Utterly without restraint.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva is spread far too wide, a crude exhibition.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume is offensive to my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>A truly exaggerated form; it borders on the grotesque.</li>
            <li>I find the open display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous vagina quite vulgar.</li>
            <li>Its size is simply too much, lacking any sense of modesty.</li>
            <li>The blatant spaciousness of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy is appalling.</li>
            <li>I cannot fathom why one would display such vastness so openly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate parts are unacceptably large and exposed.</li>
            <li>The breadth is truly excessive; it's a shocking sight.</li>
            <li>Such an unrefined, overly generous opening. It's quite uncouth.</li>
            <li>The cavernous nature is almost an affront to decency.</li>
            <li>I'm quite disgusted by the sheer scope of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vulva.</li>
            <li>It's ostentatiously large, drawing undue attention.</li>
            <li>The lack of restraint in {PAWN_possessive} anatomy is frankly irritating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is simply too vast, too open, too much.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for female with horse gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_HorseVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) HorseVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_equine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>HorseVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine-influenced vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests unusual anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost elongated form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, equine-derived anatomy presents a unique and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thick and pronounced, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a larger form, a remarkable equine adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably equine-influenced, with notable width.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so different from human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is large and distinct, complementing the generous proportions of the equine vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine vagina possesses a profound, almost tubular depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a natural predisposition for larger sizes.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of equine genitalia.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse vagina is quite apparent.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its equine origins.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost animalistic depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, equine-derived vaginal structure.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not human.</li>
            <li>The distinct equine characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its animalistic genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine vulva are strikingly apparent.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for larger encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a horse-gene mutation.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} equine vagina, a truly unique sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost elongated entrance speaks to its non-human origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} horse-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profound capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dog gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_DogVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) DogVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_canine_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DogVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine-influenced vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests unusual anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost conical form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, canine-derived anatomy presents a unique and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thick and pronounced, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a larger form, a remarkable canine adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably canine-influenced, with notable width.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so different from human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is large and distinct, complementing the generous proportions of the canine vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine vagina possesses a profound, almost tubular depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a natural predisposition for larger sizes.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of canine genitalia.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog vagina is quite apparent.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its canine origins.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost animalistic depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, canine-derived vaginal structure.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not human.</li>
            <li>The distinct canine characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its animalistic genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine vulva are strikingly apparent.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for larger encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a dog-gene mutation.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} canine vagina, a truly unique sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost conical entrance speaks to its non-human origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dog-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profound capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with cat gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_CatVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) CatVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_feline_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>CatVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline-influenced vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests unusual anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost slit-like form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, feline-derived anatomy presents a unique and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thin and pronounced, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a larger form, a remarkable feline adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably feline-influenced, with notable width.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so different from human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is small and distinct, complementing the generous proportions of the feline vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline vagina possesses a profound, almost narrow depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a natural predisposition for larger sizes.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of feline genitalia.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat vagina is quite apparent.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its feline origins.</li>
            <li>The thin set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost animalistic depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, feline-derived vaginal structure.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not human.</li>
            <li>The distinct feline characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its animalistic genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The small, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline vulva are strikingly apparent.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for larger encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a cat-gene mutation.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} feline vagina, a truly unique sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost slit-like entrance speaks to its non-human origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cat-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profound capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with demon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_DemonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) DemonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests an unearthly capacity.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost jagged form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon, sinister capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human or even animal forms.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, demonic-derived anatomy presents a uniquely unsettling and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thick and pronounced, almost chitinous, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for something unnatural, a remarkable demonic adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual, corrupted genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably demonic-influenced, with notable width and dark contours.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so alien from anything human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is large and distinct, almost grotesque, complementing the generous proportions of the demonic vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic vagina possesses a profound, almost abyssal depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a predisposition for monstrous sizes.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of demonic genitalia, unsettlingly vast.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon vagina is quite apparent, hinting at unspeakable acts.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its infernal origins.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious, almost hellish interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost monstrous depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, demonic-derived vaginal structure, disturbing in its scale.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not of this world.</li>
            <li>The distinct demonic characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and terrifying depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its infernal genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic vulva are strikingly apparent, almost scaly.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for nightmarish encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a demon-gene mutation, horrifyingly vast.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic vagina, a truly unique and terrifying sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost gaping entrance speaks to its non-human, monstrous origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profoundly disturbing capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms, inspiring dread.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within, dark and foreboding.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with dragon gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_DragonVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) DragonVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_dragon_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DragonVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests immense, scaled anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost reptilian form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human or even animal forms.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, dragon-derived anatomy presents a uniquely powerful and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thick and pronounced, almost scaly, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a larger, draconic form, a remarkable reptilian adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual, ancient genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably dragon-influenced, with notable width and tough textures.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so alien from anything human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is large and distinct, almost horn-like, complementing the generous proportions of the draconic vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic vagina possesses a profound, almost cavernous depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a predisposition for monstrous sizes.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of dragon genitalia, impressively vast.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon vagina is quite apparent, hinting at ancient power.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its reptilian origins.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious, almost primal interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost monstrous depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, dragon-derived vaginal structure, awe-inspiring in its scale.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not of this world.</li>
            <li>The distinct draconic characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and terrifying depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its primordial genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic vulva are strikingly apparent, almost armored.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for powerful encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a dragon-gene mutation, majestically vast.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} draconic vagina, a truly unique and powerful sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost gaping entrance speaks to its non-human, ancient origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dragon-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profoundly awe-inspiring capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms, inspiring reverence.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within, ancient and powerful.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with slime gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_SlimeVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) SlimeVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous vagina is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests a fluid, amorphous anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost shapeless form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-like vagina appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon, yielding capacity.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms, shimmering softly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, slime-derived anatomy presents a uniquely soft and expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are soft and yielding, almost translucent, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a liquid form, a remarkable viscous adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual, malleable genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably slime-influenced, with notable width and a gelatinous texture.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so fluid and adaptable.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is indistinct, yet present, blending with the generous proportions of the slime vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina possesses a profound, almost infinitely yielding depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a natural predisposition for absorbing forms.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of slime genitalia, unsettlingly vast yet soft.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina is quite apparent, hinting at unique sensations.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its amorphous origins.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious, almost liquid interior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost fluid depth.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, slime-derived vaginal structure, squishy in its scale.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not solid.</li>
            <li>The distinct slime characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and yielding depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its gelatinous genetic influence.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vulva are strikingly apparent, almost dissolving.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for engulfing encounters.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a slime-gene mutation, smoothly vast.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime vagina, a truly unique and intriguing sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost amorphous entrance speaks to its non-human origins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profoundly accommodating capacity.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms, soft and pliant.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within, constantly shifting.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with pig gene based vagina, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_PigNarrowVagina</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) PigNarrowVagina</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_Needle_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>NarrowVagina</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-influenced vagina appears surprisingly narrow, yet hints at a deceptive depth.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight vaginal opening, it has a distinct, almost puckered form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-like vagina seems compact, yet intriguing in its constricted nature.</li>
            <li>I noticed the limited breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms, yet strangely alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemingly narrow, pig-derived anatomy presents a unique and intriguing sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thick and pronounced, almost bristly, framing an uncommonly tight, but possibly deep, entrance.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a snug fit, a remarkable porcine adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly constrained entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vagina is unmistakably pig-influenced, with notable narrowness.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the limited scale, yet a potential for internal expansion, so different from human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is small and distinct, contrasting with the overall narrow proportions of the pig vagina.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina possesses a profound, almost impossibly narrow depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly restricted, hinting at a natural predisposition for tightness.</li>
            <li>Its deceptively cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of porcine genitalia.</li>
            <li>The unexpectedly voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina is quite apparent, despite its narrow entry.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and surprisingly ample opening, characteristic of its porcine origins, once past the initial tightness.</li>
            <li>The close set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious interior, a hidden expanse.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost animalistic depth, after the initial squeeze.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to a deceptively expansive, pig-derived vaginal structure.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally narrow at first, with contours that are clearly not human, concealing hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The distinct pig characteristics are evident in its considerable narrowness, hinting at a profound internal space.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its animalistic genetic influence, once access is gained.</li>
            <li>The small, firm folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vulva are strikingly apparent, guarding a hidden vastness.</li>
            <li>Its seemingly narrow depth suggests a surprising capacity for expansion.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly a pig-gene mutation, tightly vast.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig vagina, a truly unique sight, small yet deep.</li>
            <li>The tight, almost hidden entrance speaks to its non-human origins, and the surprise within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pig-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profoundly accommodating capacity, despite its initial resistance.</li>
            <li>A truly tight yet deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within, after a snug entry.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- description for female with insect gene based Ovipositor (a penis like tube to lay eggs), may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_Insect_OvipositorF</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral) Insect_OvipositorF</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>OvipositorF</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid ovipositor is strikingly vast, with a depth that suggests a complex, segmented anatomy.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} notably wide opening, it has a distinct, almost tube-like form.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-like ovipositor appears considerable, hinting at an uncommon capacity for egg-laying.</li>
            <li>I noticed the generous breadth of {PAWN_possessive} vulva, quite unlike typical human forms, and dominated by the ovipositor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, insect-derived anatomy presents a unique and unsettlingly expansive sight.</li>
            <li>The labia are thin and pronounced, almost chitinous, framing an uncommonly wide and deep entrance that leads to the ovipositor.</li>
            <li>Its depth seems tailored for a brood, a remarkable insectoid adaptation.</li>
            <li>A truly vast entrance, indicative of {PAWN_possessive} unusual, non-mammalian genetic makeup.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ovipositor is unmistakably insect-influenced, with notable width and segmented structure.</li>
            <li>I'm struck by the sheer scale and internal architecture, so alien from anything human.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is small and indistinct, overshadowed by the prominent, tube-like ovipositor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid ovipositor possesses a profound, almost prehensile depth.</li>
            <li>The opening is uncommonly broad, hinting at a natural predisposition for egg deposition.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous appearance is due to the inherent design of insect genitalia, unsettlingly vast.</li>
            <li>The voluminous nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor is quite apparent, designed for propagation.</li>
            <li>I observed a deep and ample opening, characteristic of its arthropod origins, with the ovipositor extending within.</li>
            <li>The wide set of the labia gives way to a significantly capacious interior, surrounding the thick ovipositor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unique anatomy displays an impressive, almost alien depth, dominated by the egg-laying tube.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features point to an expansive, insect-derived vaginal structure, with the ovipositor at its core.</li>
            <li>It presents as exceptionally wide, with contours that are clearly not human, leading to the tubular organ.</li>
            <li>The distinct insect characteristics are evident in its considerable breadth and terrifying depth.</li>
            <li>A deep, robust opening, showing clear signs of its insectoid genetic influence, terminating in an ovipositor.</li>
            <li>The large, yielding folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect vulva are strikingly apparent, funneling towards the tube.</li>
            <li>Its cavernous depth suggests an adaptation for prolific egg-laying.</li>
            <li>The unusual size and structure are captivating, clearly an insect-gene mutation, with a functional ovipositor.</li>
            <li>I examined the formidable proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect ovipositor, a truly unique and fascinating sight.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost tubular entrance speaks to its non-human origins and reproductive purpose.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-like anatomy reveals a surprising and profoundly specialized capacity for procreation.</li>
            <li>A truly broad and deep structure, quite distinct from typical human forms, housing the ovipositor.</li>
            <li>The inner walls hint at an immense, almost unrestricted space within, for eggs to pass through.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>