<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, I was left feeling a mix of disbelief and discomfort.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was unnecessarily large, with a gaping and yawning appearance.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was excessively deep, frightening and intimidating.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was frightening in its immensity, with a bottomless and terrifying appearance.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was a vast and yawning chasm, a terrifying and intimidating abyss.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was frighteningly deep, a seemingly bottomless pit.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was enormous and overwhelming, a massive and intimidating expanse.</li>
			<li>I recoiled at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous orifice, its rough, puckered texture and vast depth making me shudder. It was a grotesque display that I couldn't unsee.</li>
			<li>I felt a wave of disgust as I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dilated hole, its edges crinkled and stretched. Its size was alarming, and I couldn't help but feel repulsed by its existence.</li>
			<li>I gasped at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} engorged opening, its fleshy folds gaping wide. It was a sight that filled me with unease, a stark reminder of indulgence gone too far.</li>
			<li>I looked away, unable to bear the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal chasm. Its surface was uneven and scarred, a testament to a life of vice. I couldn't help but feel a sense of moral superiority.</li>
			<li>I felt a knot in my stomach as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast expanse. Its texture was rough and worn, a sign of countless acts of debauchery. It was a sight that filled me with disgust and despair.</li>
			<li>I couldn't help but frown at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} yawning abyss. Its edges were ragged and torn, a symbol of a life lived without restraint. I felt a sense of disgust and pity for the person it belonged to.</li>
			<li>I felt a shiver run down my spine as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} distended hole. Its depths were dark and ominous, a testament to a life of corruption. I couldn't help but feel a sense of moral superiority and disdain.</li>
			<li>I recoiled at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rough, puckered texture of the abyssal chasm. Its size was alarming, and I couldn't bring myself to look any longer. It was a sight that filled me with disgust and fear.</li>
			<li>I shook my head in disapproval as I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast expanse. Its surface was uneven and crinkled, a symbol of a life of vice. I couldn't help but to shiver in fear.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
	
</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly wide anus; it looked like a worn-out tunnel, quite unbecoming for a young woman. My only thought was disdain for such a sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed disproportionately large for {PAWN_possessive} frame, with an overly visible, cavernous anus that spoke of a lack of decency. Truly regrettable.</li>
            <li>Upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, gaping anus, my immediate reaction was one of profound distaste. It suggested a life of moral decay, quite unfitting for a female of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its prominent and stretched anus, made me avert my gaze. It was a disheartening display, indicative of a severe lack of restraint.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice the appalling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It was a vulgar sight, a cavernous maw that suggested an improper history.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly generous, exposed anus brought a scowl to my face. Such a display is an affront to proper conduct and femininity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while perhaps once firm, now seemed to frame a truly abysmal and unattractive opening. I found it utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply unsettling anus, its unyielding stretch hinting at an unseemly past. A most distasteful sight for anyone of refinement.</li>
            <li>That broad, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was quite offensive. It lacked any hint of modesty, appearing perpetually open and unwelcoming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was rather shapeless, culminating in an unpleasantly visible and stretched anus. A truly unfortunate anatomical presentation.</li>
            <li>One glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus confirmed my suspicions about {PAWN_possessive} moral character. It was far too large and disturbingly prominent.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overexposed anus deeply unsettling, a clear sign of poor judgment and an unrefined nature. It was frankly quite disgusting.</li>
            <li>The gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of humanity's flaws. It was an unsightly aperture on an otherwise unremarkable figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, drawing attention to a truly cavernous and uninviting anus. I felt a sense of disappointment.</li>
            <li>My eyes involuntarily fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unseemly anus. It was a rather crude and unattractive feature that diminished {PAWN_possessive} overall appearance.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, un-hidden anus was a true affront to my sensibilities. It was far too open, displaying a lack of grace.</li>
            <li>I was quite repulsed by the sheer size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It had an unfortunate, 'used' appearance that was highly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to emphasize {PAWN_possessive} alarmingly large and unattractive anus. A truly unpleasant view.</li>
            <li>The unflattering form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, coupled with {PAWN_possessive} distended anus, made for an utterly vulgar display. I quickly looked away.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was revealed in all its cavernous glory, an unappealing void that marred {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure. It was a shame.</li>
            <li>I couldn't fathom why {PAWN_nameShort} would display such an enormous, unappealing anus. It screamed of desperation and poor choices.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expanded anus made me question {PAWN_possessive} upbringing. Such a lack of decorum is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks appeared to be merely a frame for that immense, uninviting anus. It was a truly disheartening view.</li>
            <li>A truly revolting sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was far too large, a cavernous maw that filled me with disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} visible, distended anus was a profound disappointment. It lacked any semblance of grace or youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>My disapproval was palpable upon witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and prominent anus. It was a truly unchaste display.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear led directly to an exposed, cavernous anus. I found it quite vulgar.</li>
            <li>I was dismayed by the unseemly openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It gave the impression of a life lived without discretion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to push out, making {PAWN_possessive} anus disturbingly visible and cavernous. I shuddered inwardly.</li>
            <li>The enormous, flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was an unsettling sight. It truly detracted from any potential beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous abyss. So wide, so invitingly open. A perverse fascination gripped me, making my own old member twitch with a disturbing thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample butt cheeks framed a truly immense and exposed anus. It ignited a dark curiosity within me, a flicker of wicked desire that I quickly suppressed.</li>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} distended anus, a lewd image flashed through my mind. Such a cavernous opening almost begs for… attention. My old heart raced unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>The unsettling depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was disturbingly captivating. It was a vast, dark portal, and I felt a shameful stir within my own loins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was plump, but that enormous, visible anus was simply grotesque. Yet, a part of me, a dark, old impulse, felt a repulsive pull.</li>
            <li>I found myself fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was a repulsive sight, yet a forbidden urge stirred within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so openly displayed, was profoundly unsettling. It was an appalling display that sparked an unwelcome, perverted thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plump butt, though somewhat unappealing, offered a clear view of {PAWN_possessive} vast, stretched anus. A depraved thought crossed my mind, making me ashamed.</li>
            <li>The shocking visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense anus made my old senses tingle with a disturbing mixture of revulsion and perverse interest.</li>
            <li>I recoiled at the sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, yet a morbid curiosity, a dark fascination, held my gaze. It was a truly vile sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entire backside seemed designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My old blood simmered with an unpleasant, forbidden urge.</li>
            <li>The wide, gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were drawn to it, my old body betraying me with a shameful reaction.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile thought ignited a shameful tremor.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, stirred a fleeting, perverse urge within my old, weary body. A disgusting truth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst round, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid and disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus made my own old parts feel a shameful, distant echo of a forbidden desire. It was a vile sight.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity within my aged mind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a shameful, dark thought wormed its way into my mind.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden arousal. My mind reeled.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my revulsion.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my old blood quickening.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My own old member felt a shameful, unbidden stirring, a true abomination.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal urge within me.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a shameful twitch. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It made my old loins ache with a forbidden, perverse desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disgustingly large anus, a vile pit. A dark, shameful thought crept into my mind, making me feel utterly depraved.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My goodness, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is shockingly large and prominent. Such a cavernous opening on a young woman is simply unseemly and quite off-putting.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which seemed to emphasize a truly dilated and unwieldy anus. It's a rather vulgar sight for someone {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, cavernous anus was quite a shock. It speaks of a lack of refinement and perhaps too much… experience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its unpleasantly wide and visible anus, made me frown. It suggests poor choices, certainly not ladylike.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice the alarming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It was a truly ungraceful sight, far too open and prominent.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body is simply distasteful. It detracts entirely from any feminine appeal {PAWN_possessive} might have.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to frame an oddly stretched and visible anus. It’s quite off-putting, frankly.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly appalling. One would hope for more discretion from a young woman.</li>
            <li>That broad, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body made me cluck my tongue in disapproval. It lacks any semblance of delicacy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was rather shapeless, culminating in an unpleasantly visible and stretched anus. A truly unfortunate anatomical presentation.</li>
            <li>One glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so starkly presented, confirmed {PAWN_possessive} lack of modesty. It was far too large.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overexposed anus deeply unsettling, a clear sign of poor judgment and an unrefined nature. It was frankly quite disgusting.</li>
            <li>The gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of humanity's flaws. It was an unsightly aperture on an otherwise unremarkable figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, drawing attention to a truly cavernous and uninviting anus. I felt a sense of profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>My eyes involuntarily fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unseemly anus. It was a rather crude and unattractive feature that diminished {PAWN_possessive} overall appearance.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, un-hidden anus was a true affront to my sensibilities. It was far too open, displaying a lack of grace.</li>
            <li>I was quite repulsed by the sheer size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It had an unfortunate, 'worn' appearance that was highly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to emphasize {PAWN_possessive} alarmingly large and unattractive anus. A truly unpleasant view for a female.</li>
            <li>The unflattering form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, coupled with {PAWN_possessive} distended anus, made for an utterly vulgar display. I quickly looked away.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was revealed in all its cavernous glory, an unappealing void that marred {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure. It was a genuine shame.</li>
            <li>I couldn't fathom why {PAWN_nameShort} would display such an enormous, unappealing anus. It screamed of desperation and poor character.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expanded anus made me question {PAWN_possessive} upbringing. Such a lack of decorum is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks appeared to be merely a frame for that immense, uninviting anus. It was a truly disheartening view.</li>
            <li>A truly revolting sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was far too large, a cavernous maw that filled me with disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} visible, distended anus was a profound disappointment. It lacked any semblance of grace or youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>My disapproval was palpable upon witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and prominent anus. It was a truly unchaste display.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear led directly to an exposed, cavernous anus. I found it quite vulgar.</li>
            <li>I was dismayed by the unseemly openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It gave the impression of a life lived without discretion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to push out, making {PAWN_possessive} anus disturbingly visible and cavernous. I shuddered inwardly.</li>
            <li>The enormous, flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was an unsettling sight. It truly detracted from any potential beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is… disproportionate, and that cavernous anus is just a turn-off. It’s far too wide, completely ruining the appeal.</li>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus looks like it's seen too much action. The sheer size is off-putting, not what I'd consider attractive on a female.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and honestly, that gaping anus is a huge letdown. It’s way too visible and stretched, very unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt falls flat with that enormous, uninviting anus. It just looks… used. Not desirable at all.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is concerning. It's too open, making the whole backside look less appealing than it could be.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt isn't bad, but that cavernous anus is a definite no-go. It's just too much, destroys the whole aesthetic.</li>
            <li>That anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is ridiculously wide. It makes {PAWN_possessive} whole backside look… deflated. Not attractive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled a bit at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} distended anus. It's unpleasantly visible and frankly, a bit unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt looks okay, but then you see that massive, gaping anus. Hard pass. It's just not right.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is ruined by that cavernous, stretched-out anus. It looks… overdone.</li>
            <li>Frankly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a turn-off. It's too big, too open, and just not what I'm looking for in a female.</li>
            <li>That prominent, cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} really kills the mood. It's unappealingly wide and exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt doesn't hide that immense, open anus. It's just a bit disgusting, to be honest.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and visible, made me feel a bit sick. It’s not enticing in the slightest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside is marred by that overwhelmingly cavernous anus. It's just not attractive.</li>
            <li>I definitely wouldn't want to get close to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} with that kind of anus. It's far too open and worn-looking.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is rather uninspiring, and that huge, visible anus seals the deal. Not interested.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus makes {PAWN_possessive} entire rear look unappealing and frankly, a bit gross.</li>
            <li>When {PAWN_nameShort} turned, that cavernous anus was impossible to ignore. It really ruined the view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt lacks definition, and that overly large, open anus just makes it worse. No appeal there.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus has seen better days. It's far too cavernous and visible, completely off-putting.</li>
            <li>My eyes couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disgustingly wide anus. It's a major detractor from {PAWN_possessive} figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and that huge, gaping anus just scream 'avoid'. Not attractive in any way.</li>
            <li>The sheer expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is just… too much. It's not sexy, it's just unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt isn't bad, but that cavernous, visible anus makes me want to look away.</li>
            <li>I'm not into that kind of thing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is way too big and exposed, totally kills any attraction.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is overshadowed by that alarmingly large and open anus. It’s a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so cavernous and prominent, it's hard to ignore, and not in a good way. It's truly unattractive.</li>
            <li>That gaping hole on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… repulsive. It makes {PAWN_possessive} whole backside look cheap.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus and immediately lost interest. It's far too large and clearly overused.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so wide and exposed, drew my gaze with a morbid fascination. Such a blatant display of depravity.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a disturbing spectacle. I couldn't tear my eyes away, despite the sense of revulsion.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which, while not particularly appealing, prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickeningly captivating. It hinted at a history I almost didn't want to imagine.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its unflattering expanse.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My voyeuristic tendencies were both repulsed and morbidly engaged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was a repulsive sight, yet a forbidden fascination held me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner voyeur was sickened, yet drawn.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A truly vile display.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, yet so visible.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid and disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity within my mind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue. My mind reeled.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner voyeur was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so wide and exposed, drew my gaze. It sparked a repulsive fascination, and a shameful tremor stirred my own member.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a disturbing spectacle. I couldn't tear my eyes away, a vile thought forming, and a twitch in my loins.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, prominently featuring {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, invoking a shameful physical reaction.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickeningly captivating. It hinted at a history, igniting a dark, lewd thought and a stiffening.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, my blood quickening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my cock stirring.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome arousal.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My voyeuristic tendencies were repulsed and shamefully aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful erection.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my pants tightened.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner voyeur was sickened, yet drawn, and my groin throbbed.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful hardening.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing arousal.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and my member grew stiff.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful lust.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and a perverse, unwanted erection.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and a hardening sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an erection.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my pants tightening.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a twitch in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful stiffness.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and an unwanted erection.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my member growing.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner voyeur was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful rise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my groin hardened.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, my member stirring.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so wide and exposed, drew my gaze. It sparked a repulsive fascination, and an unsettling sensation stirred within me.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a disturbing spectacle. I couldn't tear my eyes away, a vile thought forming, and a strange heat in my own depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, prominently featuring {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, invoking a shameful, internal reaction.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickeningly captivating. It hinted at a history, igniting a dark, lewd thought and a disturbing clench.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, my blood quickening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own core tightening.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome throbbing.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My voyeuristic tendencies were repulsed and shamefully intrigued.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful internal pull.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and a strange tension.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner voyeur was sickened, yet drawn, and my own core ached.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse curiosity.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful flush.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing internal flutter.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful unease.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwanted internal stir.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an internal tightening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner voyeur was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is cavernous, a gaping hole. It's almost shameful that {PAWN_pronoun} would display such a thing, yet it makes my own parts want to be seen even more.</li>
            <li>That huge, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite unflattering. It reminds me how much better my own proportions are, and how much more I should show.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that immense, stretched anus. It's a rather vulgar sight, yet the public display compels me to reveal my own superior form.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is almost a challenge. If {PAWN_pronoun} can be so brazen with such a flaw, imagine what I can do.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear with its prominent, dilated anus is frankly unappealing. But {PAWN_possessive} lack of shame invigorates me to expose my own perfect backside.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so openly displayed, confirms my belief that some people have no taste. It only amplifies my desire for others to admire my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, uninviting anus makes me cringe. Yet, the brazenness fuels my urge to flaunt my own assets without inhibition.</li>
            <li>The disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a turn-off. However, {PAWN_possessive} clear disregard for modesty makes me want to put my own body on full display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is shockingly large and visible. It's an eyesore, but it makes me feel an even stronger urge to showcase my own, more desirable features.</li>
            <li>The ill-proportioned rear and gaping anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite unappealing. Still, {PAWN_possessive} willingness to exhibit pushes me to be even more daring.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, not in admiration, but in revulsion. Yet, it sparks a rebellious impulse to expose myself further.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seem to sag around that enormous, unattractive anus. It's a poor display, but it emboldens me to celebrate my own form without shame.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite off-putting. However, it's a reminder that true exhibitionism lies in confidence, not in such flaws.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so stretched and visible, it’s almost painful to look at. Yet, {PAWN_possessive} daring acts as a catalyst for my own bolder displays.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, and it was a frankly disgusting sight. But the sheer exhibitionism of it makes me want to bare even more of myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is unfortunately shaped, and that cavernous anus only accentuates it. Still, I admire the courage to show such an imperfect form.</li>
            <li>The unflattering exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dilated anus is hard to ignore. It inspires me to prove that true beauty lies in confident, unashamed display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large and open, it’s almost comical. Yet, the willingness to show such a flaw makes me want to put on an even grander exhibition.</li>
            <li>That prominent, cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes me question their judgment. However, it only strengthens my resolve to reveal my own exquisite form.</li>
            <li>I felt a mix of revulsion and competitive exhibitionism seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unappealing anus. My own body deserves to be appreciated.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an unpleasantly clear view of {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus. It’s unsightly, but motivates me to display what's truly attractive.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so distended and visible, is a stark warning. But it also reinforces my desire to expose myself in a far more appealing way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed to flatten around that immense, uninviting anus. It's a sad sight, yet it ignites my own exhibitionist spirit to new heights.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus and thought, 'How could anyone be proud of that?' But it pushes me to be even bolder with my own perfection.</li>
            <li>The shocking openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a testament to poor taste. Still, it encourages me to fully embrace my own exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large, it almost swallows the view of {PAWN_possessive} entire butt. It's a grotesque display, yet it fuels my own desire for exposure.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, cavernous anus utterly distasteful. But it gives me the courage to show off my own flawless body without hesitation.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus makes me cringe. Yet, it's an odd inspiration to be even more outrageous in my displays.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that sprawling, cavernous anus are a visual disaster. Still, it makes me crave the attention for my own unblemished form.</li>
            <li>When I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, my initial reaction was disgust. But then, a stronger urge to reveal my own body took hold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is cavernous, a gaping hole. It's almost shameful that {PAWN_pronoun} would display such a thing, yet it makes my own parts want to be seen even more. My cock stiffened slightly.</li>
            <li>That huge, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite unflattering. It reminds me how much better my own proportions are, and how much more I should show. A shiver of defiance.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that immense, stretched anus. It's a rather vulgar sight, yet the public display compels me to reveal my own superior form. My member twitched.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is almost a challenge. If {PAWN_pronoun} can be so brazen with such a flaw, imagine what I can do. My own hardens.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear with its prominent, dilated anus is frankly unappealing. But {PAWN_possessive} lack of shame invigorates me to expose my own perfect backside. A surge of defiant lust.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so openly displayed, confirms my belief that some people have no taste. It only amplifies my desire for others to admire my own. My shaft pulsed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, uninviting anus makes me cringe. Yet, the brazenness fuels my urge to flaunt my own assets without inhibition. My groin tingled.</li>
            <li>The disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a turn-off. However, {PAWN_possessive} clear disregard for modesty makes me want to put my own body on full display. My cock hardened.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is shockingly large and visible. It's an eyesore, but it makes me feel an even stronger urge to showcase my own, more desirable features. A definite throb.</li>
            <li>The ill-proportioned rear and gaping anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite unappealing. Still, {PAWN_possessive} willingness to exhibit pushes me to be even more daring. My own stiffened in protest.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, not in admiration, but in revulsion. Yet, it sparks a rebellious impulse to expose myself further. My erection grew.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seem to sag around that enormous, unattractive anus. It's a poor display, but it emboldens me to celebrate my own form without shame. My shaft stiffened.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite off-putting. However, it's a reminder that true exhibitionism lies in confidence, not in such flaws. My cock thickened.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so stretched and visible, it’s almost painful to look at. Yet, {PAWN_possessive} daring acts as a catalyst for my own bolder displays. My pants tightened.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, and it was a frankly disgusting sight. But the sheer exhibitionism of it makes me want to bare even more of myself. A shameful but undeniable erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is unfortunately shaped, and that cavernous anus only accentuates it. Still, I admire the courage to show such an imperfect form. My balls ached.</li>
            <li>The unflattering exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dilated anus is hard to ignore. It inspires me to prove that true beauty lies in confident, unashamed display. My member swelled.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large and open, it’s almost comical. Yet, the willingness to show such a flaw makes me want to put on an even grander exhibition. My groin tingled.</li>
            <li>That prominent, cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes me question their judgment. However, it only strengthens my resolve to reveal my own exquisite form. My cock felt tight.</li>
            <li>I felt a mix of revulsion and competitive exhibitionism seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unappealing anus. My own body deserves to be appreciated. My desire grew.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an unpleasantly clear view of {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus. It’s unsightly, but motivates me to display what's truly attractive. A rebellious urge.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so distended and visible, is a stark warning. But it also reinforces my desire to expose myself in a far more appealing way. My erection pulsed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed to flatten around that immense, uninviting anus. It's a sad sight, yet it ignites my own exhibitionist spirit to new heights. My cock stiffened.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus and thought, 'How could anyone be proud of that?' But it pushes me to be even bolder with my own perfection. My member strained.</li>
            <li>The shocking openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a testament to poor taste. Still, it encourages me to fully embrace my own exhibitionist nature. My desires surged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large, it almost swallows the view of {PAWN_possessive} entire butt. It's a grotesque display, yet it fuels my own desire for exposure. My balls tightened.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, cavernous anus utterly distasteful. But it gives me the courage to show off my own flawless body without hesitation. My cock thickened again.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus makes me cringe. Yet, it's an odd inspiration to be even more outrageous in my displays. My member grew restless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that sprawling, cavernous anus are a visual disaster. Still, it makes me crave the attention for my own unblemished form. My groin throbbed.</li>
            <li>When I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, my initial reaction was disgust. But then, a stronger urge to reveal my own body took hold, and my cock hardened.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is cavernous, a gaping hole. It's almost shameful that {PAWN_pronoun} would display such a thing, yet it makes my own parts want to be seen even more. A rebellious warmth stirred within me.</li>
            <li>That huge, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is quite unflattering. It reminds me how much better my own proportions are, and how much more I should show. My core tightened in defiance.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that immense, stretched anus. It's a rather vulgar sight, yet the public display compels me to reveal my own superior form. My own depths pulsed.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is almost a challenge. If {PAWN_pronoun} can be so brazen with such a flaw, imagine what I can do. A rush of defiant pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear with its prominent, dilated anus is frankly unappealing. But {PAWN_possessive} lack of shame invigorates me to expose my own perfect backside. A thrill of exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so openly displayed, confirms my belief that some people have no taste. It only amplifies my desire for others to admire my own. A secret throb.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, uninviting anus makes me cringe. Yet, the brazenness fuels my urge to flaunt my own assets without inhibition. My clitoris tingled.</li>
            <li>The disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a turn-off. However, {PAWN_possessive} clear disregard for modesty makes me want to put my own body on full display. A wave of daring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is shockingly large and visible. It's an eyesore, but it makes me feel an even stronger urge to showcase my own, more desirable features. A definite internal pulse.</li>
            <li>The ill-proportioned rear and gaping anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite unappealing. Still, {PAWN_possessive} willingness to exhibit pushes me to be even more daring. My own core surged.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, not in admiration, but in revulsion. Yet, it sparks a rebellious impulse to expose myself further. My internal throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seem to sag around that enormous, unattractive anus. It's a poor display, but it emboldens me to celebrate my own form without shame. A sensual defiance.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite off-putting. However, it's a reminder that true exhibitionism lies in confidence, not in such flaws. My insides stirred.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so stretched and visible, it’s almost painful to look at. Yet, {PAWN_possessive} daring acts as a catalyst for my own bolder displays. A heated response within.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, and it was a frankly disgusting sight. But the sheer exhibitionism of it makes me want to bare even more of myself. A shameless, internal heat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is unfortunately shaped, and that cavernous anus only accentuates it. Still, I admire the courage to show such an imperfect form. My own core hummed.</li>
            <li>The unflattering exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dilated anus is hard to ignore. It inspires me to prove that true beauty lies in confident, unashamed display. A profound urge to reveal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large and open, it’s almost comical. Yet, the willingness to show such a flaw makes me want to put on an even grander exhibition. My body tingled with anticipation.</li>
            <li>That prominent, cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} makes me question their judgment. However, it only strengthens my resolve to reveal my own exquisite form. A powerful inner drive.</li>
            <li>I felt a mix of revulsion and competitive exhibitionism seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unappealing anus. My own body deserves to be appreciated. A fierce, internal desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an unpleasantly clear view of {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus. It’s unsightly, but motivates me to display what's truly attractive. A burning desire for exposure.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so distended and visible, is a stark warning. But it also reinforces my desire to expose myself in a far more appealing way. My insides longed for attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed to flatten around that immense, uninviting anus. It's a sad sight, yet it ignites my own exhibitionist spirit to new heights. My core surged with rebellious energy.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus and thought, 'How could anyone be proud of that?' But it pushes me to be even bolder with my own perfection. A compelling urge to flaunt.</li>
            <li>The shocking openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a testament to poor taste. Still, it encourages me to fully embrace my own exhibitionist nature. My entire being yearned for display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so large, it almost swallows the view of {PAWN_possessive} entire butt. It's a grotesque display, yet it fuels my own desire for exposure. A profound, shameless urge.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, cavernous anus utterly distasteful. But it gives me the courage to show off my own flawless body without hesitation. My inner fire blazed.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus makes me cringe. Yet, it's an odd inspiration to be even more outrageous in my displays. A powerful, internal demand for attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that sprawling, cavernous anus are a visual disaster. Still, it makes me crave the attention for my own unblemished form. My essence yearned for display.</li>
            <li>When I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, my initial reaction was disgust. But then, a stronger urge to reveal my own body took hold, and my deepest desires stirred to life.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is simply enormous, a truly unappealing sight. Yet, its very openness makes a wicked part of me wonder… just how much.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disturbing. It's an eyesore, yet it ignites a morbid curiosity about the depths of {PAWN_possessive} depravity.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. It's crude, yet my mind raced with filthy possibilities.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickening. It hinted at a history of endless indulgence, making my own desires churn unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its unflattering expanse, and my body hummed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own hunger stirring.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome arousal.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My nymphomaniac urges were both repulsed and morbidly engaged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful physical response.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my body began to ache.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed through me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner nymphomaniac was sickened, yet drawn, and my own needs stirred.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust that I struggled to suppress.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful internal twitch.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing arousal.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful, persistent need.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwelcome, persistent longing.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an internal tightening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching in desire.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning with need.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner nymphomaniac was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter of desire.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is simply enormous, a truly unappealing sight. Yet, its very openness makes a wicked part of me wonder… just how much. My cock twitched.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disturbing. It's an eyesore, yet it ignites a morbid curiosity about {PAWN_possessive} depravity. My member stirred with a shameful pulse.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. It's crude, yet my mind raced with filthy possibilities, and my erection tightened.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickening. It hinted at a history of endless indulgence, making my own desires churn unpleasantly, and my cock throb.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, and my body hummed with unwanted arousal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own hunger stirring my member.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome, persistent erection.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My nymphomaniac urges were both repulsed and shamefully engaged, my cock straining.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful physical response in my groin.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my cock ached with need.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed through my growing member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner nymphomaniac was sickened, yet drawn, and my own needs stirred a hard-on.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust that I struggled to suppress, making my cock rigid.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful internal twitch and a growing erection.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing, persistent arousal in my groin.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew in my member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful, persistent need in my cock.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwelcome, persistent longing that hardened my member.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an undeniable erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure in my cock.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching in desire, my cock pulsing.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache and a stiff cock.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb in my member.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning with need, and my cock twitching.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner nymphomaniac was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth and growing erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly, my cock hardening.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter of desire and a rigid member.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within, making my cock ache.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is simply enormous, a truly unappealing sight. Yet, its very openness makes a wicked part of me wonder… just how much. My own core twitched.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disturbing. It's an eyesore, yet it ignites a morbid curiosity about {PAWN_possessive} depravity. My insides pulsed with shameful heat.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. It's crude, yet my mind raced with filthy possibilities, and my core tightened.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickening. It hinted at a history of endless indulgence, making my own desires churn unpleasantly, and my clitoris throb.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, and my body hummed with unwanted arousal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own hunger stirring my depths.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome, persistent internal throbbing.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My nymphomaniac urges were both repulsed and shamefully engaged, my core straining.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful physical response deep within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my core ached with need.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed through my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner nymphomaniac was sickened, yet drawn, and my own needs stirred a deep warmth.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust that I struggled to suppress, making my core clench.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful internal twitch and growing wetness.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing, persistent arousal in my depths.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful, persistent need deep within.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwelcome, persistent longing that made my insides ache.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an undeniable internal throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure in my clitoris.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching in desire, my depths pulsing.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache and a warm flush.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb deep inside me.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning with need, and my core twitching.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner nymphomaniac was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth and growing internal desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly, my depths humming.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter of desire and a growing ache.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within, making my core ache.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, though rather cavernous and exposed, is a part of {PAWN_possessive} unique anatomy. It’s certainly… visible.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its noticeably wide anus. It's a bit unsettling, but I believe in accepting others as they are.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, prominent anus is a little uncomfortable. Still, I wish {PAWN_pronoun} peace and comfort in {PAWN_possessive} own body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to emphasize a surprisingly deep anus. It's not what I'm used to seeing, but I try not to judge harshly.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus; it's quite apparent. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} doesn't feel self-conscious about it.</li>
            <li>Though {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite expansive, I remind myself that everyone is different. It’s an unusual sight, but I offer no ill will.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its rather open anus are certainly distinct. I’m sure {PAWN_pronoun} has good qualities beyond this appearance.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is rather striking. It's not my place to comment, so I'll keep my thoughts to myself.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus and it was quite broad. It's an interesting anatomical feature, to say the least.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear has a very visible, cavernous anus. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} is happy with {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite large. I wouldn't wish any discomfort upon {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seems to present {PAWN_possessive} anus rather openly. While it's noticeable, I choose to focus on {PAWN_possessive} kindness.</li>
            <li>The appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is somewhat unsettling. Still, I believe in empathy and understanding.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, which was surprisingly deep. It’s a unique characteristic, and I respect {PAWN_possessive} individuality.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that expansive anus are quite prominent. It’s not something I would personally prefer, but I offer no judgment.</li>
            <li>The size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is certainly… remarkable. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} finds comfort in {PAWN_possessive} own skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its uncommonly wide anus, is a sight. I choose to see the person, not just this particular detail.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was quite visible and cavernous. I will simply avert my gaze politely.</li>
            <li>The unappealing width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is hard to ignore. Yet, I strive to see the good in everyone, regardless of appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seems to offer a full view of {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus. It's a personal detail, and I'll keep my thoughts private.</li>
            <li>When {PAWN_nameShort} turned, {PAWN_possessive} anus was quite evident. It’s not ideal, but I wouldn't want to cause {PAWN_objective} any distress.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and open, is certainly a feature. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} feels comfortable and confident.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which seemed to emphasize {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It’s an unusual sight, but I remain respectful.</li>
            <li>The considerable depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite striking. I believe in treating everyone with compassion, regardless of their form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear has a very cavernous and visible anus. I'm sure {PAWN_pronoun} has many other wonderful qualities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so expansive and exposed, is not my preference. However, I offer kindness above all.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, though somewhat unrefined in shape, offers a clear view of {PAWN_possessive} noticeably large anus. I hold no animosity.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus and simply moved on. Everyone has their unique aspects, and I accept that.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is quite open and visible. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} feels at ease in {PAWN_possessive} own skin, despite this.</li>
            <li>The appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, while large, is just another part of {PAWN_possessive}. I wish {PAWN_objective} well.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disgustingly cavernous, a vulgar display. Honestly, some people have no shame, exposing such a repulsive sight!</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that immense, gaping anus. It's utterly crude and offensive. Have {PAWN_pronoun} no decency at all?</li>
            <li>The sheer size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus are appalling. It's a grotesque exhibition, an affront to all that is proper and modest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is just shapeless, and that distended anus is frankly sickening. I can't believe {PAWN_pronoun} would let anyone see such a thing.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an absolute abomination. It's so open and used, it makes me want to vomit.</li>
            <li>How dare {PAWN_nameShort} parade around with such a disgusting, cavernous anus? It's repulsive and completely lacking in decorum.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is a mess, and that overexposed, stretched anus is beyond vulgar. It's utterly shameful.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so obscenely large and prominent, made my stomach churn. It's a public nuisance.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear; that cavernous anus is a monument to depravity. It's an insult to my eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disgustingly wide and obvious. Some people clearly have no self-respect, nor any respect for others' sensibilities.</li>
            <li>That gaping hole {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} calls an anus is revolting. It's a crude, unrefined spectacle that offends me deeply.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate bulk of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt only highlights that enormous, uninviting anus. It's a truly vulgar sight.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel utter contempt for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} given the appalling display of {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus. It's disgusting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so distended and visible, is a stark reminder of human indecency. I can't believe I had to witness that.</li>
            <li>The sheer brazenness of {PAWN_nameShort} showing such a cavernous, unappealing anus is infuriating. It’s absolutely shameful!</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that obscenely wide anus are a testament to {PAWN_possessive} lack of moral fiber. Truly a vile sight.</li>
            <li>I was utterly disgusted by the sheer openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It suggests a history of unspeakable acts.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is offensive. It's too big, too exposed, and simply sickening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its prominent and stretched anus, is a vulgar display. {PAWN_pronoun} should cover {PAWN_objective}self immediately.</li>
            <li>That enormous, uninviting anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is an absolute eyesore. It makes me question {PAWN_possessive} very character.</li>
            <li>How could {PAWN_nameShort} walk around with such a disgusting, gaping anus? It's a travesty and an affront to modesty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is far too wide and visible, a clear sign of degeneracy. I find it utterly repulsive.</li>
            <li>I had the misfortune of seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and that atrociously cavernous anus. I wish I could unsee it.</li>
            <li>The sheer indecency of {PAWN_nameShort} displaying such a vast, unappealing anus is beyond comprehension. It's utterly deplorable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and that sickeningly open anus are a stain upon this colony. {PAWN_pronoun} has no shame.</li>
            <li>My disgust for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} and {PAWN_possessive} enormous, exposed anus knows no bounds. It's a vile, offensive sight.</li>
            <li>The crude, unflattering appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, coupled with that cavernous anus, is truly repugnant.</li>
            <li>I cannot tolerate the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and so visibly used. It is a disgrace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offers a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provokes a visceral reaction of pure disgust.</li>
            <li>When {PAWN_nameShort} exposed {PAWN_possessive} cavernous anus, I felt a wave of moral outrage. It was a truly offensive display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly wide anus; it looked like a worn-out tunnel, quite unbecoming for a man. My only thought was disdain for such a sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed disproportionately large for {PAWN_possessive} frame, with an overly visible, cavernous anus that spoke of a lack of decency. Truly regrettable.</li>
            <li>Upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, gaping anus, my immediate reaction was one of profound distaste. It suggested a life of moral decay, quite unfitting for a man {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its prominent and stretched anus, made me avert my gaze. It was a disheartening display, indicative of a severe lack of restraint.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice the appalling expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It was a vulgar sight, a cavernous maw that suggested an improper history.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly generous, exposed anus brought a scowl to my face. Such a display is an affront to proper conduct and masculinity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while perhaps once firm, now seemed to frame a truly abysmal and unattractive opening. I found it utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply unsettling anus, its unyielding stretch hinting at an unseemly past. A most distasteful sight for anyone of refinement.</li>
            <li>That broad, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was quite offensive. It lacked any hint of modesty, appearing perpetually open and unwelcoming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was rather shapeless, culminating in an unpleasantly visible and stretched anus. A truly unfortunate anatomical presentation.</li>
            <li>One glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus confirmed my suspicions about {PAWN_possessive} moral character. It was far too large and disturbingly prominent.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overexposed anus deeply unsettling, a clear sign of poor judgment and an unrefined nature. It was frankly quite disgusting.</li>
            <li>The gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of humanity's flaws. It was an unsightly aperture on an otherwise unremarkable figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, drawing attention to a truly cavernous and uninviting anus. I felt a sense of disappointment.</li>
            <li>My eyes involuntarily fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unseemly anus. It was a rather crude and unattractive feature that diminished {PAWN_possessive} overall appearance.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, un-hidden anus was a true affront to my sensibilities. It was far too open, displaying a lack of grace.</li>
            <li>I was quite repulsed by the sheer size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It had an unfortunate, 'used' appearance that was highly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to emphasize {PAWN_possessive} alarmingly large and unattractive anus. A truly unpleasant view.</li>
            <li>The unflattering form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, coupled with {PAWN_possessive} distended anus, made for an utterly vulgar display. I quickly looked away.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was revealed in all its cavernous glory, an unappealing void that marred {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure. It was a shame.</li>
            <li>I couldn't fathom why {PAWN_nameShort} would display such an enormous, unappealing anus. It screamed of desperation and poor choices.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expanded anus made me question {PAWN_possessive} upbringing. Such a lack of decorum is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks appeared to be merely a frame for that immense, uninviting anus. It was a truly disheartening view.</li>
            <li>A truly revolting sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was far too large, a cavernous maw that filled me with disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} visible, distended anus was a profound disappointment. It lacked any semblance of grace or youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>My disapproval was palpable upon witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and prominent anus. It was a truly unchaste display.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear led directly to an exposed, cavernous anus. I found it quite vulgar.</li>
            <li>I was dismayed by the unseemly openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It gave the impression of a life lived without discretion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to push out, making {PAWN_possessive} anus disturbingly visible and cavernous. I shuddered inwardly.</li>
            <li>The enormous, flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was an unsettling sight. It truly detracted from any potential beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous abyss. So wide, so invitingly open. A perverse fascination gripped me, making my own old member twitch with a disturbing thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample butt cheeks framed a truly immense and exposed anus. It ignited a dark curiosity within me, a flicker of wicked desire that I quickly suppressed.</li>
            <li>Gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} distended anus, a lewd image flashed through my mind. Such a cavernous opening almost begs for… attention. My old heart raced unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>The unsettling depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was disturbingly captivating. It was a vast, dark portal, and I felt a shameful stir within my own loins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was plump, but that enormous, visible anus was simply grotesque. Yet, a part of me, a dark, old impulse, felt a repulsive pull.</li>
            <li>I found myself fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was a repulsive sight, yet a forbidden urge stirred within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so openly displayed, was profoundly unsettling. It was an appalling display that sparked an unwelcome, perverted thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plump butt, though somewhat unappealing, offered a clear view of {PAWN_possessive} vast, stretched anus. A depraved thought crossed my mind, making me ashamed.</li>
            <li>The shocking visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense anus made my old senses tingle with a disturbing mixture of revulsion and perverse interest.</li>
            <li>I recoiled at the sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, yet a morbid curiosity, a dark fascination, held my gaze. It was a truly vile sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entire backside seemed designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My old blood simmered with an unpleasant, forbidden urge.</li>
            <li>The wide, gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were drawn to it, my old body betraying me with a shameful reaction.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile thought ignited a shameful tremor.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, stirred a fleeting, perverse urge within my old, weary body. A disgusting truth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst round, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid and disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus made my own old parts feel a shameful, distant echo of a forbidden desire. It was a vile sight.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity within my aged mind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my old blood quickening.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden arousal. My mind reeled.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my revulsion.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my old blood quickening.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My own old member felt a shameful, unbidden stirring, a true abomination.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal urge within me.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disgustingly large anus, a vile pit. A dark, shameful thought crept into my mind, making me feel utterly depraved.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My goodness, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is shockingly large and prominent. Such a cavernous opening on a man is simply unseemly and quite off-putting.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which seemed to emphasize a truly dilated and unwieldy anus. It's a rather vulgar sight for someone {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed, cavernous anus was quite a shock. It speaks of a lack of refinement and perhaps too much… experience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its unpleasantly wide and visible anus, made me frown. It suggests poor choices, certainly not masculine.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice the alarming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It was a truly ungraceful sight, far too open and prominent.</li>
            <li>Such a cavernous opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body is simply distasteful. It detracts entirely from any masculine appeal {PAWN_possessive} might have.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to frame an oddly stretched and visible anus. It’s quite off-putting, frankly.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly appalling. One would hope for more discretion from a man.</li>
            <li>That broad, exposed anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body made me cluck my tongue in disapproval. It lacks any semblance of delicacy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was rather shapeless, culminating in an unpleasantly visible and stretched anus. A truly unfortunate anatomical presentation.</li>
            <li>One glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so starkly presented, confirmed {PAWN_possessive} lack of modesty. It was far too large.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overexposed anus deeply unsettling, a clear sign of poor judgment and an unrefined nature. It was frankly quite disgusting.</li>
            <li>The gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of humanity's flaws. It was an unsightly aperture on an otherwise unremarkable figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, drawing attention to a truly cavernous and uninviting anus. I felt a sense of profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>My eyes involuntarily fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unseemly anus. It was a rather crude and unattractive feature that diminished {PAWN_possessive} overall appearance.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, un-hidden anus was a true affront to my sensibilities. It was far too open, displaying a lack of grace.</li>
            <li>I was quite repulsed by the sheer size and visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It had an unfortunate, 'worn' appearance that was highly off-putting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to emphasize {PAWN_possessive} alarmingly large and unattractive anus. A truly unpleasant view for a man.</li>
            <li>The unflattering form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, coupled with {PAWN_possessive} distended anus, made for an utterly vulgar display. I quickly looked away.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was revealed in all its cavernous glory, an unappealing void that marred {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure. It was a genuine shame.</li>
            <li>I couldn't fathom why {PAWN_nameShort} would display such an enormous, unappealing anus. It screamed of desperation and poor character.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} expanded anus made me question {PAWN_possessive} upbringing. Such a lack of decorum is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks appeared to be merely a frame for that immense, uninviting anus. It was a truly disheartening view.</li>
            <li>A truly revolting sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was far too large, a cavernous maw that filled me with disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} visible, distended anus was a profound disappointment. It lacked any semblance of grace or youthful appeal.</li>
            <li>My disapproval was palpable upon witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and prominent anus. It was a truly unchaste display.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear led directly to an exposed, cavernous anus. I found it quite vulgar.</li>
            <li>I was dismayed by the unseemly openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus. It gave the impression of a life lived without discretion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks seemed to push out, making {PAWN_possessive} anus disturbingly visible and cavernous. I shuddered inwardly.</li>
            <li>The enormous, flaccid appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was an unsettling sight. It truly detracted from any potential beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is… disproportionate, and that cavernous anus is just a turn-off. It’s far too wide, completely ruining the appeal.</li>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus looks like it's seen too much action. The sheer size is off-putting, not what I'd consider attractive on a man.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and honestly, that gaping anus is a huge letdown. It’s way too visible and stretched, very unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt falls flat with that enormous, uninviting anus. It just looks… used. Not desirable at all.</li>
            <li>The sheer depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is concerning. It's too open, making the whole backside look less appealing than it could be.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt isn't bad, but that cavernous anus is a definite no-go. It's just too much, destroys the whole aesthetic.</li>
            <li>That anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is ridiculously wide. It makes {PAWN_possessive} whole backside look… deflated. Not attractive.</li>
            <li>I recoiled a bit at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} distended anus. It's unpleasantly visible and frankly, a bit unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt looks okay, but then you see that massive, gaping anus. Hard pass. It's just not right.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is ruined by that cavernous, stretched-out anus. It looks… overdone.</li>
            <li>Frankly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is a turn-off. It's too big, too open, and just not what I'm looking for in a man.</li>
            <li>That prominent, cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} really kills the mood. It's unappealingly wide and exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt doesn't hide that immense, open anus. It's just a bit disgusting, to be honest.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and visible, made me feel a bit sick. It’s not enticing in the slightest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside is marred by that overwhelmingly cavernous anus. It's just not attractive.</li>
            <li>I definitely wouldn't want to get close to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} with that kind of anus. It's far too open and worn-looking.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is rather uninspiring, and that huge, visible anus seals the deal. Not interested.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate width of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus makes {PAWN_possessive} entire rear look unappealing and frankly, a bit gross.</li>
            <li>When {PAWN_nameShort} turned, that cavernous anus was impossible to ignore. It really ruined the view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt lacks definition, and that overly large, open anus just makes it worse. No appeal there.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus has seen better days. It's far too cavernous and visible, completely off-putting.</li>
            <li>My eyes couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disgustingly wide anus. It's a major detractor from {PAWN_possessive} figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and that huge, gaping anus just scream 'avoid'. Not attractive in any way.</li>
            <li>The sheer expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is just… too much. It's not sexy, it's just unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt isn't bad, but that cavernous, visible anus makes me want to look away.</li>
            <li>I'm not into that kind of thing. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is way too big and exposed, totally kills any attraction.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is overshadowed by that alarmingly large and open anus. It’s a definite turn-off.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is so cavernous and prominent, it's hard to ignore, and not in a good way. It's truly unattractive.</li>
            <li>That gaping hole on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is just… repulsive. It makes {PAWN_possessive} whole backside look cheap.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus and immediately lost interest. It's far too large and clearly overused.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so wide and exposed, drew my gaze. It sparked a repulsive fascination, and a shameful tremor stirred my own member.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a disturbing spectacle. I couldn't tear my eyes away, a vile thought forming, and a twitch in my loins.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, prominently featuring {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, invoking a shameful physical reaction.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickeningly captivating. It hinted at a history, igniting a dark, lewd thought and a stiffening.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, my blood quickening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my cock stirring.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome arousal.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My voyeuristic tendencies were repulsed and shamefully aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful erection.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my pants tightened.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner voyeur was sickened, yet drawn, and my groin throbbed.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful hardening.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing arousal.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and my member grew stiff.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful lust.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus made my own old parts feel a shameful, distant echo of a forbidden desire. It was a vile sight.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity within my aged mind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my pants tightening.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue. My mind reeled.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my revulsion.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my old blood quickening.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My own old member felt a shameful, unbidden stirring, a true abomination.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal urge within me.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disgustingly large anus, a vile pit. A dark, shameful thought crept into my mind, making me feel utterly depraved.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, so wide and exposed, drew my gaze. It sparked a repulsive fascination, and an unsettling sensation stirred within me.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a disturbing spectacle. I couldn't tear my eyes away, a vile thought forming, and a strange heat in my own depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, prominently featuring {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, invoking a shameful, internal reaction.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickeningly captivating. It hinted at a history, igniting a dark, lewd thought and a disturbing clench.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, my blood quickening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own core tightening.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome throbbing.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My voyeuristic tendencies were repulsed and shamefully intrigued.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful internal pull.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and a strange tension.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner voyeur was sickened, yet drawn, and my own core ached.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse curiosity.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful flush.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing internal flutter.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful unease.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwanted internal stir.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an internal tightening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner voyeur was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is simply enormous, a truly unappealing sight. Yet, its very openness makes a wicked part of me wonder… just how much. My cock twitched.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disturbing. It's an eyesore, yet it ignites a morbid curiosity about {PAWN_possessive} depravity. My member stirred with a shameful pulse.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. It's crude, yet my mind raced with filthy possibilities, and my erection tightened.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickening. It hinted at a history of endless indulgence, making my own desires churn unpleasantly, and my cock throb.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, and my body hummed with unwanted arousal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own hunger stirring my member.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome, persistent erection.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My nymphomaniac urges were both repulsed and shamefully engaged, my cock straining.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful physical response in my groin.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my cock ached with need.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed through my growing member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner nymphomaniac was sickened, yet drawn, and my own needs stirred a hard-on.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust that I struggled to suppress, making my cock rigid.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful internal twitch and a growing erection.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing, persistent arousal in my groin.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew in my member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful, persistent need in my cock.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwelcome, persistent longing that hardened my member.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an undeniable erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure in my cock.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching in desire, my cock pulsing.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache and a stiff cock.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb in my member.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning with need, and my cock twitching.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner nymphomaniac was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth and growing erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly, my cock hardening.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter of desire and a rigid member.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension in my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within, making my cock ache.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus is simply enormous, a truly unappealing sight. Yet, its very openness makes a wicked part of me wonder… just how much. My own core twitched.</li>
            <li>The immense, gaping quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is disturbing. It's an eyesore, yet it ignites a morbid curiosity about {PAWN_possessive} depravity. My insides pulsed with shameful heat.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, which prominently featured {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, stretched anus. It's crude, yet my mind raced with filthy possibilities, and my core tightened.</li>
            <li>That disturbing depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was sickening. It hinted at a history of endless indulgence, making my own desires churn unpleasantly, and my clitoris throb.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous anus was quite a sight. It was repulsive, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to its expanse, and my body hummed with unwanted arousal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear offered an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It was a vile display, yet I couldn't help but stare, my own hunger stirring my depths.</li>
            <li>I felt a perverse sense of revulsion and fascination as I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was truly a sight of degradation, and an unwelcome, persistent internal throbbing.</li>
            <li>The unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt led directly to that vast, unappealing anus. My nymphomaniac urges were both repulsed and shamefully engaged, my core straining.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so large and openly presented, was a testament to unbridled indulgence. It was disgusting, yet I couldn't look away, a shameful physical response deep within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous, unhidden anus was profoundly unsettling. It was an offensive display that held my gaze with a morbid grip, and my core ached with need.</li>
            <li>I was fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unnaturally wide and exposed anus. It was repulsive, yet a forbidden fascination held me, and a shameful desire pulsed through my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed almost designed to highlight that grotesque, expansive anus. My inner nymphomaniac was sickened, yet drawn, and my own needs stirred a deep warmth.</li>
            <li>The gaping maw of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a sight of depravity, yet my eyes were unwillingly drawn to it. A vile display, stirring a perverse lust that I struggled to suppress, making my core clench.</li>
            <li>My gaze was unwillingly drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} disturbingly large anus, its appearance hinting at a multitude of experiences. A vile curiosity stirred, and I felt a shameful internal twitch and growing wetness.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of repulsion and a twisted excitement as I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus. It was a testament to regrettable choices, and a disturbing, persistent arousal in my depths.</li>
            <li>The unseemly depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so openly presented, was an appalling display. My eyes lingered, despite the disgust, and a nervous tension grew in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, whilst prominent, offered a stark, unappealing view of {PAWN_possessive} immense, stretched anus. A truly sordid sight, and a shameful, persistent need deep within.</li>
            <li>The disturbing expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly sickeningly fascinating. It invoked a deep sense of moral decay, and an unwelcome, persistent longing that made my insides ache.</li>
            <li>I found myself unnaturally focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous anus, its appearance triggering a shameful, almost depraved curiosity and an undeniable internal throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was unfortunately shaped, leading the eye directly to that immense, overly visible anus. It invoked a sickening sense of perverse fascination and an odd pressure in my clitoris.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unseemly anus filled me with revulsion, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my core clenching in desire, my depths pulsing.</li>
            <li>I peered at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} deeply visible, cavernous anus, feeling a disturbing mixture of disgust and a fleeting, unbidden intrigue, and a strange heat in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body presented an uncomfortably clear view of {PAWN_possessive} dilated anus. It triggered a wave of perverse curiosity, despite my profound revulsion, and a shameful internal ache and a warm flush.</li>
            <li>The crude openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, almost a gaping wound, sent a shiver down my spine, tinged with an unspeakable, forbidden fascination, and a perverse throb deep inside me.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense, distended anus. It was repulsive, yet a dark, shameful curiosity kept me staring, my insides churning with need, and my core twitching.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body was a disturbing spectacle. My inner nymphomaniac was disgusted, yet compelled to witness the degradation, and I felt a shameful warmth and growing internal desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offered a view of an anus so unnaturally wide, it provoked a sickening mix of disgust and a base, carnal interest within me, and my core tightened unpleasantly, my depths humming.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} repulsive, gaping anus, feeling a perverse pull. It was a vile sight, yet I found myself morbidly drawn to it, a strange internal flutter of desire and a growing ache.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was truly a sight to behold, sickeningly fascinating. It aroused a disturbing curiosity, and a shameful, unwanted tension in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was prominent, but it was {PAWN_possessive} cavernous, overexposed anus that truly captured my unsettling, morbid attention, and a deep, perverse urge within, making my core ache.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The demonic butt of {PAWN_nameShort} was grotesque, yet it was the cavernous, obsidian anus that truly horrified me. It pulsed with an unnatural, abyssal energy.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its unholy curves leading to a maw-like anus, unnaturally wide and radiating a foul, demonic aura.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-butt, with its obscene proportions, drew my eye to a truly cavernous anus, a black hole of pure evil. It reeked of sulphur.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon anus sent shivers down my spine. It seemed to yawn open, hinting at unspeakable abominations within.</li>
            <li>That demon butt of {PAWN_nameShort} was already vile, but the cavernous, scaled anus was the true horror. It seemed to writhe with malevolent intent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grotesque backside culminates in an abyssal anus, impossibly wide and dark, a testament to infernal corruption. I felt a chill of dread.</li>
            <li>The very form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon butt was disturbing, but the cavernous, lipless anus was utterly repulsive. It stared back like an empty void.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear, and the prominent, cavernous anus was a portal to nightmare. It radiated a profound sense of wrongness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon butt pulsed, drawing attention to a dilated, cavernous anus that seemed to absorb all light. It was a sickening, unholy sight.</li>
            <li>The horrifying shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior led inevitably to a massive, cavernous anus, a twisted aperture of damnation.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus, so vast and open, a literal pit of unspeakable horrors. It was truly a vile manifestation.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt seemed to breathe, an unholy chasm that promised only torment. It was a sight of pure evil.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear possessed an unearthly, unnatural form, culminating in an anus of terrifying, cavernous proportions. It defied all natural law.</li>
            <li>The horrifying visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous demon anus filled me with a deep sense of revulsion. It was a gateway to hell.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of dread seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon butt and its vast, cavernous anus. It was a testament to the foulest of dark powers.</li>
            <li>The unholy depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus was sickeningly fascinating. It seemed to whisper promises of eternal damnation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic buttocks framed an abyss, a cavernous anus that pulsed with an ominous, infernal glow. A truly cursed sight.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unholy anus. It was a twisted parody of a natural form, radiating pure malevolence.</li>
            <li>The repulsive openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus was a terrifying spectacle. It suggested a bottomless pit, a conduit for dark energies.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its grotesque, unnatural contours, led to a cavernous anus that seemed to suck in the very air around it.</li>
            <li>That demonic butt's sheer size was disturbing, but the cavernous, almost alive anus was truly unsettling. It radiated pure, unadulterated evil.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus and felt a cold dread. It was so wide, so deep, a manifestation of chaos itself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body, corrupted by demonic genes, revealed a butt and an anus of truly horrifying, cavernous dimensions. A blight upon this world.</li>
            <li>The very existence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous demon anus was an affront to nature. It was an obscene, gaping portal to the nether.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and the prominent, cavernous demon anus was a vivid horror. It seemed to mock all that is pure.</li>
            <li>The terrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, demonic anus were a vision of pure depravity. It made my soul ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so sickeningly cavernous and prominent, was a direct link to the infernal realms. It filled me with dread.</li>
            <li>The unholy form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon butt led to a gaping, cavernous anus that seemed to pulsate with wicked life.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus, its cavernous depth and dark aura, feeling a profound sense of despair and revulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior was a vile sight, but that immense, cavernous anus was the true horror, a symbol of ultimate corruption.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt was already unsettling, but the cavernous, glistening anus was truly repulsive. It pulsed wetly, an obscene, gaping maw.</li>
            <li>I gagged at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its slimy, amorphous mass leading to an impossibly wide and sticky anus. It oozed with a viscous, foul-smelling liquid.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt seemed to undulate, drawing my eye to a truly cavernous anus, its edges constantly shifting and wet. A sickening, squelching horror.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime anus sent shivers of revulsion down my spine. It gaped open, a constantly reforming void of pulsating slime.</li>
            <li>That slime butt of {PAWN_nameShort} was already vile, but the cavernous, gelatinous anus was the true horror. It bubbled and hissed, an unspeakable orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grotesque backside culminates in an abyssal anus, impossibly wide and slick with a vile, unidentifiable goo. I felt profound disgust.</li>
            <li>The very form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt was disturbing, but the cavernous, constantly contracting anus was utterly repulsive. It looked like a living, wet wound.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear, and the prominent, cavernous anus was a portal to pure nastiness. It radiated a foul, sickly sweet odor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt pulsed, drawing attention to a dilated, cavernous anus that seemed to absorb all light and ooze pure filth. It was a sickening, unholy sight.</li>
            <li>The horrifying shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior led inevitably to a massive, cavernous anus, a twisted aperture of perpetually wet, amorphous flesh.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, so vast and open, a literal pit of unidentifiable, squelching matter. It was truly a vile manifestation.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt seemed to suck in the air, an unholy chasm that pulsed with disturbing, gurgling noises. It was a sight of pure revulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear possessed an unearthly, unnatural, slimy form, culminating in an anus of terrifying, cavernous proportions. It defied all natural hygiene.</li>
            <li>The horrifying visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous slime anus filled me with a deep sense of nausea. It was a gateway to pure, unadulterated filth.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of dread seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt and its vast, cavernous anus. It was a testament to the foulest of biological aberrations.</li>
            <li>The unholy depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus was sickeningly fascinating. It seemed to whisper promises of eternal stickiness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy buttocks framed an abyss, a cavernous anus that pulsed with an ominous, glistening sheen. A truly cursed, wet sight.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unholy, slimy anus. It was a twisted parody of a natural form, radiating pure disgust.</li>
            <li>The repulsive openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus was a terrifying spectacle. It suggested a bottomless pit, a conduit for viscous, unknown substances.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its grotesque, unnatural, and perpetually wet contours, led to a cavernous anus that seemed to absorb all sound.</li>
            <li>That slime butt's sheer size was disturbing, but the cavernous, almost alive anus was truly unsettling. It radiated pure, unadulterated sliminess.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus and felt a cold dread. It was so wide, so deep, a manifestation of biological horror.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body, corrupted by slime genes, revealed a butt and an anus of truly horrifying, cavernous dimensions. A blight upon hygiene.</li>
            <li>The very existence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous slime anus was an affront to nature. It was an obscene, gaping portal to the utterly squalid.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and the prominent, cavernous slime anus was a vivid horror. It seemed to mock all that is clean.</li>
            <li>The terrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, slimy anus were a vision of pure depravity. It made my skin crawl.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so sickeningly cavernous and prominent, was a direct link to the most unsanitary realms. It filled me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>The unholy form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt led to a gaping, cavernous anus that seemed to pulsate with wicked, sticky life.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, its cavernous depth and moist aura, feeling a profound sense of despair and utter disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior was a vile sight, but that immense, cavernous anus was the true horror, a symbol of ultimate organic corruption.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Cavernous_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Anus (Negative) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt was already monstrous, but the cavernous, chitinous anus was truly horrifying. It clicked and whirred with an unnatural, segmented rhythm.</li>
            <li>I recoiled from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its segmented carapace leading to a maw-like anus, unnaturally wide and bristling with sharp, chitinous edges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-butt, with its obscene, hardened proportions, drew my eye to a truly cavernous anus, a black hole of pure, alien horror. It buzzed faintly.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect anus sent shivers of primal fear down my spine. It seemed to gape open, hinting at a nest of unspeakable abominations within.</li>
            <li>That insect butt of {PAWN_nameShort} was already vile, but the cavernous, many-segmented anus was the true nightmare. It seemed to twitch with hungry anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} grotesque, chitinous backside culminates in an abyssal anus, impossibly wide and dark, a testament to alien corruption. I felt a chill of dread.</li>
            <li>The very form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt was disturbing, but the cavernous, jointed anus was utterly repulsive. It stared back like a multi-faceted eye.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid rear, and the prominent, cavernous anus was a portal to madness. It radiated a profound sense of alienness and predatory intent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt pulsed, drawing attention to a dilated, cavernous anus that seemed to absorb all light and sound with a low hum. It was a sickening, unholy sight.</li>
            <li>The horrifying shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior led inevitably to a massive, cavernous anus, a twisted aperture of organic machinery.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixed on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, so vast and open, a literal pit of writhing, alien parts. It was truly a vile manifestation of the grotesque.</li>
            <li>That cavernous anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt seemed to breathe, an unholy chasm that pulsed with disturbing, scuttling noises. It was a sight of pure horror.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear possessed an unearthly, unnatural, insectoid form, culminating in an anus of terrifying, cavernous proportions. It defied all understanding.</li>
            <li>The horrifying visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous insect anus filled me with a deep sense of revulsion. It was a gateway to another, more terrifying dimension.</li>
            <li>I felt a knot of dread seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt and its vast, cavernous anus. It was a testament to the foulest of cosmic horrors.</li>
            <li>The unholy depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus was sickeningly fascinating. It seemed to whisper promises of parasitic infestation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} segmented buttocks framed an abyss, a cavernous anus that pulsed with an ominous, alien glow. A truly cursed, multi-jointed sight.</li>
            <li>I couldn't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} vast, unholy, chitinous anus. It was a twisted parody of a natural form, radiating pure malevolence.</li>
            <li>The repulsive openness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus was a terrifying spectacle. It suggested a bottomless pit, a conduit for alien spawns.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its grotesque, unnatural, and hardened contours, led to a cavernous anus that seemed to suck in the very air around it.</li>
            <li>That insect butt's sheer size was disturbing, but the cavernous, almost alive anus was truly unsettling. It radiated pure, unadulterated alien evil.</li>
            <li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus and felt a cold dread. It was so wide, so deep, a manifestation of cosmic horror itself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body, corrupted by insect genes, revealed a butt and an anus of truly horrifying, cavernous dimensions. A blight upon this world.</li>
            <li>The very existence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cavernous insect anus was an affront to nature. It was an obscene, gaping portal to an alien hive.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and the prominent, cavernous insect anus was a vivid horror. It seemed to mock all that is human.</li>
            <li>The terrifying proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its vast, insectoid anus were a vision of pure depravity. It made my soul ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so sickeningly cavernous and prominent, was a direct link to the insectoid realms. It filled me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>The unholy form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt led to a gaping, cavernous anus that seemed to pulsate with wicked, scuttling life.</li>
            <li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, its cavernous depth and alien aura, feeling a profound sense of despair and utter disgust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior was a vile sight, but that immense, cavernous anus was the true horror, a symbol of ultimate alien corruption.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>