<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average anus is so dull; it barely registers in my mind.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was nondescript and repulsive, lacking any defining features.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was unmemorable and mundane, failing to leave any impression.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was utterly forgettable, indistinguishable from any other.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was bland, a completely ordinary and unmemorable thing.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was utterly forgettable, a featureless and uninteresting expanse.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was so completely average it was almost a void, a lack of anything notable.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized aperture, a circular opening that appeared inviting yet unwelcoming. The texture was smooth, the hole slightly agape, with a depth that hinted at a certain darkness.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized orifice, a round, open hole that seemed to be waiting for entry, yet I felt a shiver run down my spine at the thought. The texture was soft, yet the depth seemed to be bottomless.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mid-sized crevice, an opening that seemed to be slightly open, yet the thought of venturing any further made me cringe.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized slit, an opening that seemed to be slightly open, yet the sight of it made me feel uneasy. The texture was smooth and unblemished, yet the depth was unknown, and that was unsettling.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized orifice, a round, inviting opening that seemed to be waiting for entry, yet the thought of it made me feel repulsed. The texture was soft and smooth, yet the depth was unknown and foreboding.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mid-sized hole, a medium-sized aperture that seemed to be slightly open, yet the thought of it made me feel uncomfortable. The texture was unwrinkled, yet the depth was unknown and made me shudder.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized orifice, an opening that seemed to be slightly open, yet the sight of it made my skin crawl. The texture was smooth and unlined, yet the depth was unknown and made me feel queasy.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized slit, an opening that seemed to be slightly open, yet the thought of exploring it made me feel repulsed.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized aperture, a round, open hole that seemed to be receptive to touch, yet the thought of it made me feel uneasy.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her average posterior and unremarkable opening presented nothing of interest, a common sight I've long grown weary of.</li>
            <li>Such a bland rear; the unexciting folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} orifice are utterly forgettable.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average hindquarters, revealing a perfectly ordinary opening. It evoked no particular response, just a tiresome familiarity.</li>
            <li>The young female's plain backside, with its typical and uninspiring aperture, holds no allure for my experienced eyes.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were unremarkable, leading to an anus of typical form. A mundane sight, truly.</li>
            <li>A perfectly average posterior on a young woman, complete with a commonplace opening. A rather dull exhibition.</li>
            <li>I've seen countless backsides like this; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average rear and commonplace anus offer nothing new.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and middling anal contours are exactly what I'd expect from the ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear lacks any distinctiveness; the moderate opening is as plain as can be.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} common buttocks and unexceptional anus is simply unstimulating.</li>
            <li>An unmemorable backside, leading to a thoroughly average and unappealing anal region.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, with its moderate curvature, and a perfectly typical anus; nothing to note.</li>
            <li>A rather dull view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, featuring an entirely uninspired anal presentation.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its commonplace orifice holds no intrigue.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable female posterior with an unexciting, moderately visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks are forgettably average, and the anus, equally so, offers no visual appeal.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is typical, and the unadorned anus is simply bland.</li>
            <li>Her posterior is too conventional, and the visible anus is just another common sight.</li>
            <li>I've witnessed a plethora of such common displays; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus are entirely unremarkable.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside and unstimulating anus represent a truly uninspired specimen.</li>
            <li>This common posterior and its ordinary opening are tiresome; a sight I've seen countless times.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkable hindquarters offer nothing to capture my attention or interest.</li>
            <li>Her rear lacks any notable contour, and the average anus is precisely as unexciting as one would imagine.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rather plain posterior, revealing a perfectly ordinary anal cavity; a mundane spectacle.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its conventional orifice make for a truly uninspiring view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside possesses no unique qualities, just an average shape and an equally average anus.</li>
            <li>A common female posterior, with an uninspired opening that leaves no lasting impression.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks culminate in a thoroughly average and unappealing anal structure.</li>
            <li>I've grown weary of such ordinary sights; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and anus are entirely unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} commonplace backside and its utterly unremarkable anal opening elicits only a sigh of tedium.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her mundane posterior and typical orifice fail to stir any perverse interest in me; a truly disappointing sight.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside and its unremarkable opening, feeling only a dull ache of disinterest.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus. My own parts remain limp, unprovoked by such commonality.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice leaves me utterly cold; no thrill at all.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, barely register as worthy of my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to quicken my pulse.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any illicit fascination.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are a letdown; no perverse curiosity sparked here.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is simply too conventional to ignite any genuine depravity within me.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus makes my own parts recoil in boredom.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's a shame; I'd hoped for more.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. My desires remain dormant, untouched by such banality.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, is a profound disappointment to my voyeuristic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's just… there. How dull.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening almost makes me question my proclivities.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite unappealing, its unmemorable orifice failing to spark anything.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no perversion, only profound ennui.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, offers nothing for my depraved imagination.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing but a wave of apathy.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly a buzzkill for my desires.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are a testament to the utterly unexceptional.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my own parts refuse to acknowledge them.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A dreary spectacle, indeed.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus leaves me utterly unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, is a wasted opportunity for my gaze.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, there's nothing to see.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form inspiring neither lust nor disgust.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are a visual affront to my voyeuristic nature.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to elicit even a tremor of depravity. My own parts remain stubbornly unimpressed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a stark reminder of youthful blandness.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing noteworthy or appealing.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; it holds no charm, merely a predictable form.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is entirely unmemorable, truly a wasted view.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, lack any grace or distinctiveness.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to impress.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of individuality.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply uninteresting, nothing more.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, lacking any hint of unique form.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus is a testament to the uninspired.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's just… a butt.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It's a tiresome and unoriginal sight.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, embodies utter mediocrity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's utterly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening evokes nothing but a yawn.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice failing to hold any attention.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that is just… there. No character, no appeal.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is just another common sight.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt only indifference.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninspired.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly without appeal.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A predictable tableau.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly forgettable.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, offers no aesthetic merit.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing special.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely conventional.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one expects from the ordinary.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is rather dull.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to make any impression whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; utterly unstimulating.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite desire.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt me.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing more.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my senses.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to see.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The utter normalcy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior and uninspired anus is profoundly disappointing to my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average backside, its commonplace orifice offering nothing to feed my clandestine desires.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary buttock and unexciting anus; it holds no forbidden charm, merely predictable form.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace opening is entirely unmemorable, a waste of my watchful eye.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, lack any unique perversion.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to excite my hidden proclivities.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any illicit fascination.</li>
            <li>This commonplace rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply uninteresting, offering no thrill for my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, lacking any hint of secret appeal.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus is a testament to the truly unperverted.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's just a common exposure.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It's a tiresome and unoriginal display for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, embodies utter visual mediocrity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's utterly unremarkable to my discerning eyes.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening evokes nothing but profound ennui.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice failing to spark any illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no shocking discoveries, only predictable form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is just another common sight to peek at.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt only indifference.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninspired for my voyeuristic purposes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly without peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>This average rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from my voyeuristic memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A predictable tableau, devoid of intrigue.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly forgettable to a voyeur.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, offers no unique visual merit.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing special to observe.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely conventional and dull for my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one hopes not to glimpse.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is rather dull for someone with my inclinations.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to make any impression whatsoever on my voyeuristic desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; my own parts feel nothing.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite perverse desire.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my flesh remains cold.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, my loins stir not.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal thrill for me.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my lust.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my member inert.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no wicked thoughts arise.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my deprived senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my desire unawakened.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of a peek.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving me utterly flaccid.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, my own body remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my flesh unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my loins unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my member remains stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner depraved self.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched, and my member sleeps.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle, my parts refuse to react.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire, my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse, my nether regions completely still.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; no perverse intrigue here.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to stir illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my own senses remain numb.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, no flicker of forbidden desire.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no thrill for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my hidden cravings.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my body unresponsive.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no wicked curiosity stirred.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no secret excitement to my deprived senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my own core unmoved.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a mundane secret.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving my senses untouched.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own body unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my inner pervert uninterested.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own perverse urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my secret desires unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my inner voyeur finds no joy.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner twisted self.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched, and my own core sleeps.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire, my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse, my core completely still.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any illicit attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average backside is so uninspired; it does nothing to highlight my own appeal.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was nondescript and utterly uninteresting for a public display.</li>
            <li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was unmemorable and mundane, failing to make any impression for exhibition.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was utterly forgettable, indistinguishable from any other, a poor comparison to myself.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was bland, a completely ordinary and unmemorable thing to expose.</li>
            <li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was utterly forgettable, a featureless and uninteresting expanse to behold.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was so completely average it was almost a void, a lack of anything notable for public viewing.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized aperture, a circular opening that lacked any flair for exhibition.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized orifice, a round, open hole that seemed uninspired for public display.</li>
            <li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mid-sized crevice, an opening that offered no excitement for an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized slit, an opening that seemed utterly uninteresting for public attention.</li>
            <li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized orifice, a round, inviting opening that lacked any unique charm for exposure.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mid-sized hole, a medium-sized aperture that offered no visual intrigue to an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized orifice, an opening that seemed utterly dull for any public display.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} medium-sized slit, an opening that offered no artistic merit for exhibition.</li>
            <li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderately-sized aperture, a round, open hole that was simply too unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior lacks the drama required for a truly captivating display.</li>
            <li>Such a common, uninspired butt. There's nothing here to encourage me to show my own.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear makes my own skin crawl with boredom.</li>
            <li>I witnessed a rather dull display; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average anus fails to impress.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexciting backside offers no contrast to my own magnificent form.</li>
            <li>This utterly plain posterior is a reminder of why I prefer to be the center of attention.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed anus to be utterly unremarkable, lacking any captivating features.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is too conventional; it simply doesn't hold attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average anal visibility is so low, it hardly counts as an exhibition.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly unimpressed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired butt and its commonplace opening.</li>
            <li>This kind of average exposure is why I strive for truly memorable displays.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so uninteresting, it makes me want to put my clothes back on.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average anus; no wonder it's hidden.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off for any true exhibitionist.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; my own desires remain unprovoked.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite any display of my own.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my own member remains limp.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, no thrill for my exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no pleasure, and no comparison for my own.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_namePossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt me to expose myself.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my member inert.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no desire to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my exhibitionist senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my own body remains unexcited.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of a potential exhibition.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving me utterly flaccid.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure for me to show off.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own flesh unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my exhibitionist eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy towards showing myself.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my loins unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my member remains stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched, and my member sleeps.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle, my parts refuse to react.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire, my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse when seeking inspiration to exhibit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless. What a bore.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; no desire to showcase my own.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to inspire my exhibition.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my own form feels superior.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, no thrill for my exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no visual pleasure, nor comparison for my own.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt me to expose myself.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in appeal for exhibition.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no desire to reveal my own glory.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my exhibitionist senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my own body remains unexcited.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of a potential display.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving me utterly unimpressed.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure for me to show off my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own flesh unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my desire to exhibit nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my exhibitionist eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy towards showing myself.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my own parts unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my desire to display remains stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle, my own form superior.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire to reveal.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse when seeking inspiration to exhibit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my exhibitionist drive non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are a profound disappointment; no thrill here.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to satiate my urges.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities for my insatiable needs.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly unstimulating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to ignite my desires.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism.</li>
            <li>This commonplace rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing more for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of potential pleasure.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my heightened senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure to my craving body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy to me.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to my desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal.</li>
            <li>This average rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what a nymphomaniac avoids.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever. My insatiable hunger remains.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; my own member remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite my ceaseless desires.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my flesh stays dormant.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, my loins stir not.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal thrill for me.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my lust.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my member inert.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no wicked thoughts arise in me.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my deprived senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my desire unawakened.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of a potential encounter.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving me utterly flaccid.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, my own body remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own flesh unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my loins unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my member remains stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner depraved self.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched, and my member sleeps.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle, my parts refuse to react.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire, my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse, my nether regions completely still.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; no spark for my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite my burning lust.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary female buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities for my unending need.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly unstimulating for me.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal satisfaction for my raging urges.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my voracious appetite.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my core unmoved.</li>
            <li>This commonplace female rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing more for a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>Her moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my heightened senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my desire unawakened.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of potential pleasure.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my craving body.</li>
            <li>Her plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure to my desperate need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, my own core remains unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>Her unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy to me.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my desires unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to my desires.</li>
            <li>Her uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner yearning.</li>
            <li>This average female rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to satisfy my hunger.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>Her bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what a nymphomaniac avoids, offering no satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever. My insatiable hunger remains.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Despite my attempts at finding something redeeming, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are truly unappealing.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing pleasant to dwell upon.</li>
            <li>Even with good intentions, such an ordinary buttock and unexciting anus hold no positive aspect.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is entirely unmemorable, despite my wish to be kind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, are simply ungraceful.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to elicit a kind thought.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any redeeming feature.</li>
            <li>This commonplace rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply unattractive, even when I try to be charitable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, lacking any hint of beauty.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus is a testament to unappealing normalcy.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's just... unlovely.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It's a tiresome and unoriginal sight, unfortunately.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, embodies utter visual mediocrity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's utterly unremarkable, sadly.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening evokes nothing but profound lack of enthusiasm.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice failing to spark any admiration.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no unique charm, only predictable, unappealing form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is just another common, unlovely sight.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt only a dull resignation.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninspired and lacking beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly without appeal, despite my kind nature.</li>
            <li>This average rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly, regrettably.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A predictable tableau, devoid of charm.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly forgettable and unlovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, offers no aesthetic merit.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing special to behold, sadly.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely conventional and ungraceful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't wish to see, even I.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is rather dull, a shame really.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to make any impression whatsoever. It's truly unremarkable.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are disgustingly mundane; a truly offensive sight.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing but crude mediocrity.</li>
            <li>Such a repulsive, ordinary buttock and unexciting anus; it offends my sensibilities with its sheer banality.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is entirely unmemorable and utterly vulgar.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, are simply an affront.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring and distasteful view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing but disgust me.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any decency.</li>
            <li>This commonplace rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply crude and uninteresting, a vulgar display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional and utterly unseemly.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus is a testament to offensive normalcy.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's just... common and gross.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It's a tiresome and truly revolting sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, embodies utter visual vulgarity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's utterly unremarkable, shamefully.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening evokes nothing but profound revulsion.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking nothing but disgust.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no unique charm, only predictable, offensive form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is just another common, vulgar sight.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt only profound contempt.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninspired and utterly distasteful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly without appeal, and frankly, disgusting.</li>
            <li>This average rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly, thankfully.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A predictable tableau, devoid of any grace.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly forgettable and unholy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, offers no aesthetic merit. It's an eyesore.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing special to behold, sickeningly so.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely conventional and crude.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't wish to see, ever.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is rather dull, an abomination.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to make any impression whatsoever. It’s thoroughly offensive.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening presented nothing of interest, a common sight I've long grown weary of.</li>
            <li>Such a bland rear; the unexciting folds of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} orifice are utterly forgettable.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average hindquarters, revealing a perfectly ordinary opening. It evoked no particular response, just a tiresome familiarity.</li>
            <li>The young male's plain backside, with its typical and uninspiring aperture, holds no allure for my experienced eyes.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were unremarkable, leading to an anus of typical form. A mundane sight, truly.</li>
            <li>A perfectly average posterior on a young man, complete with a commonplace opening. A rather dull exhibition.</li>
            <li>I've seen countless backsides like this; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average rear and commonplace anus offer nothing new.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and middling anal contours are exactly what I'd expect from the ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear lacks any distinctiveness; the moderate opening is as plain as can be.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} common buttocks and unexceptional anus is simply unstimulating.</li>
            <li>An unmemorable backside, leading to a thoroughly average and unappealing anal region.</li>
            <li>His posterior, with its moderate curvature, and a perfectly typical anus; nothing to note.</li>
            <li>A rather dull view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, featuring an entirely uninspired anal presentation.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its commonplace orifice holds no intrigue.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable male posterior with an unexciting, moderately visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks are forgettably average, and the anus, equally so, offers no visual appeal.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt is typical, and the unadorned anus is simply bland.</li>
            <li>His posterior is too conventional, and the visible anus is just another common sight.</li>
            <li>I've witnessed a plethora of such common displays; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus are entirely unremarkable.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside and unstimulating anus represent a truly uninspired specimen.</li>
            <li>This common posterior and its ordinary opening are tiresome; a sight I've seen countless times.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unremarkable hindquarters offer nothing to capture my attention or interest.</li>
            <li>His rear lacks any notable contour, and the average anus is precisely as unexciting as one would imagine.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rather plain posterior, revealing a perfectly ordinary anal cavity; a mundane spectacle.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its conventional orifice make for a truly uninspiring view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside possesses no unique qualities, just an average shape and an equally average anus.</li>
            <li>A common male posterior, with an uninspired opening that leaves no lasting impression.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks culminate in a thoroughly average and unappealing anal structure.</li>
            <li>I've grown weary of such ordinary sights; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and anus are entirely unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} commonplace backside and its utterly unremarkable anal opening elicits only a sigh of tedium.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His mundane posterior and typical orifice fail to stir any perverse interest in me; a truly disappointing sight. My own parts remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside and its unremarkable opening, feeling only a dull ache of disinterest, my flesh unyielding.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus. My own parts remain limp, unprovoked by such commonality.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice leaves me utterly cold; no thrill at all for my kind.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, barely register as worthy of my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to quicken my pulse.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any illicit fascination, my own member sleeps.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are a letdown; no perverse curiosity sparked here.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is simply too conventional to ignite any genuine depravity within me.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus makes my own parts recoil in boredom.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's a shame; I'd hoped for more from a male.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. My desires remain dormant, untouched by such banality.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, is a profound disappointment to my voyeuristic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's just… there. How dull for my tastes.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening almost makes me question my proclivities, my urges unfelt.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite unappealing, its unmemorable orifice failing to spark anything in me.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no perversion, only profound ennui from a male.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, offers nothing for my depraved imagination.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing but a wave of apathy.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly a buzzkill for my desires.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are a testament to the utterly unexceptional, my own parts still.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my own parts refuse to acknowledge them.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A dreary spectacle, indeed.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus leaves me utterly unmoved.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, is a wasted opportunity for my gaze.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, there's nothing to see.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form inspiring neither lust nor disgust from me.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are a visual affront to my voyeuristic nature, my desires dormant.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to elicit even a tremor of depravity. My own parts remain stubbornly unimpressed, a true disappointment.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a stark reminder of youthful blandness in males.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing noteworthy or appealing.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus; it holds no charm, merely a predictable form.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is entirely unmemorable, truly a wasted view.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, lack any grace or distinctiveness.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to impress me.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of individuality.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply uninteresting, nothing more.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, lacking any hint of unique form.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus is a testament to the uninspired.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's just… a butt.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It's a tiresome and unoriginal sight.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, embodies utter mediocrity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's utterly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening evokes nothing but a yawn.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice failing to hold any attention.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that is just… there. No character, no appeal.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is just another common sight.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt only indifference.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninspired.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly without appeal.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A predictable tableau.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly forgettable.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, offers no aesthetic merit.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing special to observe.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely conventional.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one expects from the ordinary male.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is rather dull.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to make any impression whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; utterly unstimulating, a common sight among us.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to commend.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any appealing qualities, truly unimpressive.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, a fellow man's dull offering.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no particular distinction.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to elevate it.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in any unique masculine feature.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing more from our kind.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement or impressiveness.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, a shared disappointment.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of masculinity.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, even for a comrade.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, a dull sight among men.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, even for a fellow man.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, even from a brother.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to a fellow male.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my admiration remains completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to admire.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to see from a comrade.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His mundane posterior and typical orifice fail to stir any perverse interest in me; a truly disappointing sight. My own parts remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside and its unremarkable opening, feeling only a dull ache of disinterest, my flesh unyielding.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus. My own parts remain limp, unprovoked by such commonality.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice leaves me utterly cold; no thrill at all for my kind.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, barely register as worthy of my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to quicken my pulse.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly devoid of any illicit fascination, my own member sleeps.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are a letdown; no perverse curiosity sparked here.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is simply too conventional to ignite any genuine depravity within me.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus makes my own parts recoil in boredom.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. It's a shame; I'd hoped for more from a male.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. My desires remain dormant, untouched by such banality.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, is a profound disappointment to my voyeuristic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's just… there. How dull for my tastes.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening almost makes me question my proclivities, my urges unfelt.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite unappealing, its unmemorable orifice failing to spark anything in me.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no perversion, only profound ennui from a male.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, offers nothing for my depraved imagination.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing but a wave of apathy.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly a buzzkill for my desires.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are a testament to the utterly unexceptional, my own parts still.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my own parts refuse to acknowledge them.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A dreary spectacle, indeed.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus leaves me utterly unmoved.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, is a wasted opportunity for my gaze.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, there's nothing to see.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form inspiring neither lust nor disgust from me.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are a visual affront to my voyeuristic nature, my desires dormant.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to elicit even a tremor of depravity. My own parts remain stubbornly unimpressed, a true disappointment.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; no perverse intrigue here.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to stir illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my own senses remain numb.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, no flicker of forbidden desire.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no thrill for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my hidden cravings.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my body unresponsive.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no wicked curiosity stirred.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no secret excitement to my deprived senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my own core unmoved.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a mundane secret.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving my senses untouched.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own body unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my inner pervert uninterested.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that promises no shocking discoveries, only predictable form.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own perverse urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my secret desires unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my inner voyeur finds no joy.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner twisted self.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire to reveal.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse, my core completely still.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any illicit attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; my own member remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite my ceaseless desires.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities, my flesh stays dormant.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, my loins stir not.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal thrill for me.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my lust.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my member inert.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off; no wicked thoughts arise in me.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my deprived senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my desire unawakened.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of a potential encounter.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing, leaving me utterly flaccid.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure, my own body remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, leaving my own flesh unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy, my own desire remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my loins unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting, my member remains stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner depraved self.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched, and my member sleeps.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle, my parts refuse to react.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing, leaving me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire, my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable, my body feeling no thrill.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't want to glimpse, my nether regions completely still.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever, leaving my own body completely lifeless.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His perfectly average posterior and unremarkable opening are a true letdown; no spark for my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing to ignite my burning lust.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary male buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any alluring qualities for my unending need.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly unstimulating for me.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no carnal satisfaction for my raging urges.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain backside, its average anus doing nothing to tempt my voracious appetite.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in eroticism, my core unmoved.</li>
            <li>This commonplace male rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing more for a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>His moderate backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no excitement to my heightened senses.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold, my desire unawakened.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of potential pleasure.</li>
            <li>Such an average rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my craving body.</li>
            <li>His plain backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no allure to my desperate need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive form, and an anus that's simply boring, my own core remains unexcited.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, my arousal nowhere.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in my lustful eyes.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable posterior with a visible anus that inspires no carnal thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>His unexceptional backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely unsexy to me.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing, my desires unresponsive.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to my desires.</li>
            <li>His uninspired posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of appeal to my inner yearning.</li>
            <li>This average male rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, my desires remain completely untouched.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>His modest posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no erotic merit whatsoever, my urges remain unfelt.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to satisfy my hunger.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>His bland backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what a nymphomaniac avoids, offering no satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off, my libido non-existent.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sexual attraction whatsoever. My insatiable hunger remains.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even with demonic traits, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are a profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demon backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing infernally captivating.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary demonic buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any hellish allure.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain demonic rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly un-demonic.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional demonic buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no dark thrill.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain demonic backside, its average anus doing nothing to evoke dread.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demonic posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in any infernal grandeur.</li>
            <li>This commonplace demonic rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing hellish about it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate demonic backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no dark excitement.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demonic posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of demonic potential.</li>
            <li>Such an average demonic rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my expectations.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain demonic backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no dark allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive infernal form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demonic posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, no demonic presence felt.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in the infernal.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable demonic posterior with a visible anus that inspires no dark thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional demonic backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely un-demonic.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane demonic buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing sinister.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to the dark side.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demonic posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of dark appeal.</li>
            <li>This average demonic rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain demonic backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull infernal spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest demonic posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no dark erotic merit whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire from the underworld.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired demonic rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland demonic backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't expect from a demon.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional demonic posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off for any demon.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting demonic buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sense of infernal power or attraction whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a slime-based form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are a profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slime backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing uniquely fluid or captivating.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary slimy buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any intriguing, viscous qualities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain slimy rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly un-slimy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional slime buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no strange delight.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain slime backside, its average anus doing nothing to evoke curiosity.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slimy posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in any unique consistency.</li>
            <li>This commonplace slime rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing fluid or interesting about it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate slimy backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no gooey excitement.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slimy posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of slime potential.</li>
            <li>Such an average slimy rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my expectations.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain slimy backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no viscous allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive fluid form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slimy posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, no strange texture felt.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in the unusual.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable slimy posterior with a visible anus that inspires no strange thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional slimy backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely un-slimy.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane slimy buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing strange.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to exploration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slimy posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of strange appeal.</li>
            <li>This average slimy rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain slimy backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull, viscous spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest slimy posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no curious merit whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire from a slime-being.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired slimy rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland slimy backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't expect from slime.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional slimy posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off for any curiosity.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting slimy buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sense of unique slime-anatomy or attraction whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Average_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Average Anus (Negative) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even with insectoid traits, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average posterior and unremarkable opening are a profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insect backside, its commonplace anus offering nothing uniquely chitinous or captivating.</li>
            <li>Such an ordinary insectoid buttock and unexciting anus; completely devoid of any intriguing, segmented qualities.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain insect rear and its commonplace orifice is profoundly disappointing, utterly un-insectoid.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional insect buttocks, leading to a thoroughly average anal aperture, promise no strange thrill.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain insect backside, its average anus doing nothing to evoke curiosity.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insectoid posterior and its unmemorable opening, a sight utterly lacking in any unique biological consistency.</li>
            <li>This commonplace insect rear and its perfectly ordinary orifice are simply a turn-off, nothing segmented or interesting about it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} moderate insectoid backside, with its typical anal contours, is too conventional, offering no chitinous excitement.</li>
            <li>The blandness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid buttocks and its unstimulating anus leaves me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insectoid posterior and its unremarkable opening. Such a waste of insectoid potential.</li>
            <li>Such an average insectoid rear, and an even more average anus. It’s entirely unappealing to my expectations.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain insectoid backside, paired with a thoroughly unexciting anal aperture, offers no chitinous allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid buttocks, completely lacking in any distinctive segmented form, and an anus that's simply boring.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insectoid posterior and its generic opening is a complete letdown, no strange texture felt.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid rear to be quite plain, its unmemorable orifice sparking no interest in the unusual.</li>
            <li>Another unremarkable insectoid posterior with a visible anus that inspires no strange thoughts, only profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unexceptional insectoid backside, culminating in an equally uninspiring anal region, is entirely un-insectoid.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mundane insectoid buttocks and its entirely commonplace anus, and felt nothing strange.</li>
            <li>The plainness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid rear, with its moderate opening, is truly uninviting to exploration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insectoid posterior and unstimulating orifice are just typical, utterly devoid of strange appeal.</li>
            <li>This average insectoid rear and its unremarkable anus are so unexciting, they vanish from memory almost instantly.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entirely plain insectoid backside and its unadorned anal aperture. A truly dull, segmented spectacle.</li>
            <li>The utter lack of uniqueness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt and anus makes them instantly unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest insectoid posterior, leading to a thoroughly uninspiring anal region, possesses no curious merit whatsoever.</li>
            <li>Such a common view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid buttocks and its unremarkable opening; truly, nothing to desire from an insect-being.</li>
            <li>I encountered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired insectoid rear, its average anal form being entirely undesirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bland insectoid backside and entirely unexciting anus are precisely what one doesn't expect from an insect.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} utterly conventional insectoid posterior and its mundane orifice is a complete turn-off for any curiosity.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plain and uninteresting insectoid buttocks, their perfectly normal anus failing to evoke any sense of unique insect-anatomy or attraction whatsoever.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>