<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>

    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>Not for my liking.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus trying to be versatile, but it just feels forced.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was slightly too accommodating, with a loose and flabby appearance.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was too open and inviting, lacking any sense of tightness or restriction.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was overly receptive, with a gaping and inviting appearance.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was too open and receptive, a gaping and inviting mouth.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was loose and sloppy, a flabby and unappealing thing.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was overly welcoming, a too-wide and too-deep opening.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous opening, a spacious orifice that seemed to be inviting and receptive, yet I felt a sense of discomfort at its expansiveness.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} larger-than-average crevice, an opening that seemed to be accommodating and welcoming, yet the thought of it made me feel uneasy. The texture was supple and yielding, with a depth that seemed to be more commodious.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spacious slit, an opening that seemed to be more open and receptive than necessary, yet the sight of it made me feel a sense of distaste.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} roomy orifice, an opening that seemed to be accommodating and expansive, yet the thought of it made me feel repulsed. The texture was smooth and unwrinkled, with a depth that seemed to be more substantial than expected.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} larger-than-average aperture, a round, open hole that seemed to be receptive and inviting, yet the thought of it made me feel uncomfortable.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} commodious hole, a spacious orifice that seemed to be open and receptive, yet the thought of it made me feel uneasy.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} larger-than-average crevice, an opening that seemed to be more open and receptive than necessary, yet the thought of exploring it made me feel repulsed.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spacious orifice, an opening that seemed to be accommodating and expansive, yet the thought of it made me feel queasy.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} derriere, too wide and aged, left me with a distinct impression of a faded bloom.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby backside, its lack of youthful firmness was quite unsettling.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened curves, a backside clearly past its prime, and found it rather unappealing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, accommodating anus reminded me unpleasantly of time's relentless march.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired looking posterior, soft and yielding, evoked a sense of regret for youth's fleeting beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, sagging and worn, spoke volumes about a life of wear and tear, rather ungracefully.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spreading posterior, its ample proportions a testament to age, yet far from appealing.</li>
            <li>The generous, yet weary, opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of decay and lost vitality.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock's deflated appearance, with a noticeable lack of youthful contour, was a rather sad sight.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, clearly past its prime, with a weary, stretched appearance around the anus.</li>
            <li>The wide, unkempt aperture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus hinted at a lack of care, making me feel quite disgusted.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, a broad, unsettling expanse, held no attraction, only the grim reality of time's passage.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unpleasantly yielding backside to be a sign of advanced age, and not in a good way.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, unappealing anus made me recoil; it's a stark image I won't soon forget.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt appeared rather flattened, lacking any spirited form, and the anus itself seemed excessively visible.</li>
            <li>I was confronted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly accommodating rear, a rather unfortunate display of age and neglect.</li>
            <li>The sagging flesh of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, surrounding an alarmingly open anus, was truly a disheartening view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, wide and uninviting, had a weary aspect that failed to pique any interest.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks seemed to have lost all their former resilience, emphasizing an unpleasantly large and exposed anus.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, a testament to time's cruel hand, with a conspicuously aged and loose opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its unpleasantly wide aperture, looked like it had seen too much use and lost its form.</li>
            <li>The laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the noticeable slackness around {PAWN_possessive} anus made me grimace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, resembling two flattened sacks, framed an uninviting and overly prominent anus.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged backside, its texture and form betraying years, with an unfortunately visible opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous, almost cavernous, opening was a sight that quite honestly repulsed me.</li>
            <li>The ill-defined contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, combined with a rather exposed anus, left a poor impression.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside looked utterly spent, its accommodating anus a rather sad and uninspired spectacle.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, too soft and too open, a vision of unappealing, advanced laxity.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninviting, wide anus left me with a feeling of profound discomfort and distaste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed to have given up entirely, exhibiting a deplorable lack of tautness around its anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, yielding butt, despite its youth, surprisingly didn't stir my usual depraved urges. A waste.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample backside, {PAWN_possessive} accommodating anus too visible, yet my old blood remained disappointingly cold.</li>
            <li>That young female's generous, flaccid rear offered no titillation. My old member felt nothing but profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spreading posterior, with its surprisingly relaxed opening, was a sight that somehow extinguished my dark desires.</li>
            <li>I studied {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, an unfortunately ample and yielding form; my usual urges remained stubbornly dormant.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus seemed too open, too accessible, made it uninteresting. My groin felt a perverse disinterest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, youthfully soft yet already appearing overused, and my lust was ironically diminished.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, accommodating anus, rather prominent, failed to ignite the usual spark of perversion in me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unpleasantly broad posterior, with an overly exposed anus, left me feeling strangely hollow.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, which was too yielding, and it made my own shriveled parts feel... indifferent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample butt, surprisingly lacking any tautness, simply didn't inspire the customary wicked thoughts.</li>
            <li>That wide, visible anus on a young female was a letdown. My old self felt a bizarre sense of repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, soft and overtly accessible, was unexpectedly unstimulating for my usual tastes.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside, its form too pliant. My ancient loins felt a distinct lack of interest.</li>
            <li>The laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and the open aspect of {PAWN_possessive} anus merely induced a weary sigh.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, appearing almost used up even at a young age, was truly an unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly generous anus utterly devoid of mystique, hence, no thrill for my aged mind.</li>
            <li>The prominent, un-toned expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus left me feeling disturbingly vacant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, despite its relative youth, seemed to sag too much. It was quite unexciting.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} over-exposed anus and buttocks, which ironically killed any perverted inclination.</li>
            <li>That young female's rear was too open, too available. My jaded senses found no pleasure in its display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt appeared too pliant, almost weary. My usual desires remained stubbornly unaroused.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost welcoming, opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not stir me as I expected; only a strange detachment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, which was surprisingly unprovoking despite its accommodating nature. My urges waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous form, while technically accommodating, felt oddly uninteresting to my seasoned eye.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, prominent anus and flabby buttocks left me with a sense of quiet disappointment.</li>
            <li>I felt no stirring when observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear; it seemed to lack any genuine allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was too soft, too unresisting; it offered no challenge to my perverse inclinations.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly open anus made me feel oddly repulsed, rather than titillated, by its youth.</li>
            <li>I just saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside. My weary old appendage merely felt a phantom ache of indifference.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, so ample and unstructured, reminds me of a sack of potatoes. Disgraceful at that age.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside; far too soft and yielding for a young woman. Such a lack of discipline.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior sagged already at {PAWN_possessive} age was quite unbecoming. Really, no firmness at all.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus seemed alarmingly visible, speaking volumes about a lack of discretion. Tsk.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were unpleasantly soft, emphasizing an overly open anus. It looked… used. How unladylike.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear; so unkempt, so lacking in any proper contour. A true disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly wide backside, quite frankly, looked as though it needed cinching in.</li>
            <li>The general laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, particularly around {PAWN_possessive} prominent anus, was rather off-putting.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, flabby and unrefined. A young woman should have more grace in {PAWN_possessive} posture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and broad buttocks gave me a distinctly negative impression of {PAWN_possessive} character.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ill-defined rear was rather shocking for someone so young. Where is the firmness?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior simply lacked any appealing form, with an overly visible and rather unseemly anus.</li>
            <li>Her backside was too soft, too accessible, indicating a careless attitude towards one's own presentation.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tone. It truly wasn't a pleasant sight to behold.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus gaped slightly, even when {PAWN_pronoun} stood still, was quite revealing and improper.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, regrettably, seemed to have given up entirely on maintaining a respectable shape.</li>
            <li>I truly detest the sight of such a loose, accommodating anus on a young woman. So unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were simply too large and too flaccid, making for an ungainly appearance.</li>
            <li>Her rear, frankly, looked like it had been stretched out of shape already. What a pity.</li>
            <li>The ample and rather shapeless form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, with {PAWN_possessive} visible anus, was quite unattractive.</li>
            <li>I was quite disgusted by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to just hang there, without any dignity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, along with {PAWN_possessive} broad buttocks, lacked any semblance of youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>It's such a shame to see a young woman with a backside so lacking in firmness and proper curvature.</li>
            <li>The visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, due to {PAWN_possessive} overly accommodating form, was truly distasteful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was simply too wide, too soft, and far too revealing for public viewing.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby backside to be a clear sign of poor personal habits and a lack of self-respect.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were quite frankly repulsive in their shapelessness, amplifying the rather ungraceful anus.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and was appalled by its lack of tautness. Not at all what one expects.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was a disappointment, its accommodating nature only highlighted by its overall lack of form.</li>
            <li>That prominent, unkempt anus, combined with a sagging butt, was a visual affront to my sensibilities.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt's too big, too soft, almost... sloppy. Doesn't really do anything for me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, it's just so loose and accommodating. Not what I'm looking for.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus looked far too open, like it's seen too much. Kinda a turn-off, honestly.</li>
            <li>Her rear was just... uninspired. Too wide, too yielding, completely lacking any exciting tension.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby butt and its prominent, overly open anus was quite frankly unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, broad and unstructured, felt more like a discouragement than an invitation.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus; it seemed a little too eager, which is actually a bit creepy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt has no definition, just a soft, wide expanse. My interest immediately plummeted.</li>
            <li>Her backside seemed almost... used up. The way the anus sat, so visible, was just disappointing.</li>
            <li>I don't know, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear just lacks any real firmness. It's too soft, too… indistinct.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt hangs, loose and without any real shape, is frankly a bit sad.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus is simply too exposed for my taste. It leaves nothing to the imagination.</li>
            <li>Her posterior is just too wide and lacking in tone. It doesn't have that firm, appealing curve.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and it just seemed… tired. Like it's already given up on being attractive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offers no real visual interest; it's just a large, soft, uninspiring mass.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is one of excessive pliancy, which I find quite unappealing.</li>
            <li>Her anus, overly visible and lacking tightness, gives me the distinct impression of being too well-acquainted with… things.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and their loose, accommodating aperture to be rather distasteful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside just sags, without any real appeal. It's almost a negative attraction.</li>
            <li>That wide, visible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt just screams "overused." Not a good look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous dimensions and lack of firmness fail to excite me. Quite the opposite.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and thought, "That's a lot of… relaxed tissue." Not for me.</li>
            <li>Her butt seems to melt rather than hold shape, emphasizing an unpleasantly large and open anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, visible for all to see, really drains any potential interest I might have.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and the overtly available anus are quite off-putting.</li>
            <li>I honestly can't find anything attractive about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, uninspired backside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is just too… soft. It doesn't have that firmness that actually makes it desirable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly accommodating and prominent anus is a definite turn-off for me.</li>
            <li>Her butt looks like it's already lost the fight against gravity. It's a sad, sad sight.</li>
            <li>I had hoped for more, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unkempt posterior and its inviting anus left me utterly cold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt. It's wide, but so lacking in tautness that it offers no visual thrill.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, overly visible anus left me oddly unsatisfied. Where's the mystery?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its unpleasantly generous aperture, offered no challenge to my gaze, thus no perverse joy.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened posterior, and felt a perverse disappointment. Too easy, too open.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed too ready, too yielding. It almost repulsed my voyeuristic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>That wide, welcoming anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} left me cold. A true voyeur seeks more subtle revelations.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside to be rather dull; no intriguing curves or hidden depths to explore.</li>
            <li>The sheer visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, combined with its flabby butt, was disappointingly unstimulating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while ample, lacked any tension, making it a rather uninteresting subject for observation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was so openly displayed made me feel a strange sense of disinterest, not lust.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its accommodating nature left me with a feeling of profound boredom.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous but lifeless opening held no perverse fascination for me. A wasted opportunity.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly wide backside did nothing to stir my voyeuristic tendencies.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, too soft and too exposed, offered no forbidden fruit for my eager eyes.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninspired posterior; its accommodating nature robbed it of any allure.</li>
            <li>The loose form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and the prominent anus made it almost offensive to my refined taste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, lacking any tautness, felt more like a sad pronouncement than a secret.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its sheer willingness was a perverse turn-off. No challenge.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, along with its overly visible anus, simply lacked any intrigue.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so readily available, actually made me feel a touch of repulsion.</li>
            <li>I was disappointed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear; too much on display, too little left to discover.</li>
            <li>The lack of firmness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, highlighting a wide, unappealing anus, was a visual affront.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, unfortunately prominent, just looked… tired. No thrill there.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its obvious availability made it utterly uninteresting to my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, soft and overly yielding, presented no tantalizing secrets for me to uncover.</li>
            <li>The broad, uninviting expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and its relaxed opening offered no forbidden pleasure.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly accommodating rear to be devoid of any stimulating qualities. A bland sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, unpleasantly wide and prominent, extinguished any voyeuristic spark within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened butt and its exposed aperture was frankly quite unappetizing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside lacked all mystery, its accommodating nature rendering it profoundly unexciting for a true voyeur.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her accommodating butt, wide and loose, should have stirred me, but my loins remained frustratingly indifferent.</li>
            <li>I watched {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its visible anus too prominent. My usual urges were oddly absent.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} soft, expansive backside failed to ignite any perverted spark within me. A profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>Her over-exposed anus and shapeless buttocks offered no thrill; my member remained flaccid and unimpressed.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and felt a perverse lack of interest. It was too easy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, with its obvious readiness, somehow killed all my customary lustful thoughts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus seemed too open, too available, was actually a turn-off for my voyeuristic eye.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, ample but uninspired. My perverted imagination found no foothold there.</li>
            <li>Her yielding, shapeless posterior, and prominent anus, left me with a disappointing sense of emptiness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear, rather than exciting me, left me feeling strangely… apathetic.</li>
            <li>The visible laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its wide anus, provoked a frustrating lack of reaction from me.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly broad backside and its open aperture utterly unstimulating. My usual urges were absent.</li>
            <li>Her posterior simply lacked any enticing tension; it was too soft, too accommodating, too… dull.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, too generous and unresisting. My desire simply shriveled at the sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, while present, offered no mystery, no hidden depths for my perverse gaze.</li>
            <li>The prominent, unkempt anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemed to mock my expectations of a forbidden thrill.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and my usual dark desires felt strangely muted.</li>
            <li>Her backside was too soft, too yielding. It was a spectacle that unfortunately left me cold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, lacking any true firmness, presented a sad, unexciting canvas for my voyeurism.</li>
            <li>The expansive and uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus effectively squashed any perverse fantasies.</li>
            <li>I watched {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and it seemed to sigh with resignation. My own body felt a similar weariness.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks, flabby and unrefined, combined with an overly visible anus, offered nothing but disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside, rather than alluring, felt more like a challenge I had no interest in.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, prominent anus surprisingly left me feeling completely unaroused.</li>
            <li>I felt no perverse stirring when observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shapeless, overtly available posterior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was too willing, too eager to accommodate, and thus, utterly uninteresting to me.</li>
            <li>Her rear, lacking any desirable tautness, simply failed to capture my attention or ignite my usual perversions.</li>
            <li>The ample, un-toned contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its exposed anus, were a profound letdown.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and felt a peculiar sense of emptiness instead of lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so readily presented, paradoxically extinguished all my usual illicit desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt, so wide and yielding, offered no real perverse thrill for my eyes.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its prominent and overly loose anus, quite… uninspired. No hidden secrets here.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened posterior, too openly inviting, strangely dulled my voyeuristic urges.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks, lacking any desirable firmness, were simply too available. It was disappointingly obvious.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its accommodating nature left me with a feeling of profound boredom, not arousal.</li>
            <li>The too-visible anus and flabby contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside extinguished any sense of illicit pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so devoid of tautness, simply didn't offer anything interesting to observe.</li>
            <li>Her accommodating rear, unpleasantly broad, lacked any alluring mystery for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, far too open and prominent, and felt a strange, detached disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and shapeless, was a rather unexciting subject for my covert observations.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was one of unfortunate pliancy, which offered no voyeuristic satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Her ample posterior, with its unappealingly wide aperture, was too readily apparent, thus diminishing its appeal.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, and it seemed to scream "experienced." Not my preferred spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was just… there. Too exposed, too simple, too lacking in any perverse intrigue.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, combined with {PAWN_possessive} visible anus, was quite unappetizing.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninviting posterior to be entirely devoid of any tantalizing secrets.</li>
            <li>Her backside, while technically accommodating, was too unrefined to truly capture my voyeuristic interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, prominently displayed, left nothing to the imagination, which is a letdown for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its lack of discreetness made it quite frankly uninspiring.</li>
            <li>The loose, un-toned quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and anus just wasn't stimulating in the slightest.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, too soft and too readily open, felt less like a discovery and more like an unfortunate display.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its excessive willingness actually made me feel a perverse repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, unpleasantly wide, offered no alluring enigma for my discerning gaze.</li>
            <li>The overall laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed aperture made for a rather bland voyeuristic experience.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly soft rear to be entirely without the kind of intriguing flaw I seek.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, though young, seemed to bear the marks of excessive use, making it less than captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, too open and unconstrained, simply failed to ignite any illicit fantasies.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and felt a peculiar sense of visual fatigue.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby butt and its prominent, accommodating anus was deeply uninteresting.</li>
            <li>Her rear offered no subtle hints or hidden depths; its unadorned frankness left me utterly disappointed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt is too dull. Where's the thrill of a reaction if it's already so... open?</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its lack of firmness left me utterly uninspired to display my own.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and lax buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} made me question the point of exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness. It almost feels like a missed opportunity for true exhibition.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to stimulate my desire to show off.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. It's boring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, more superior display.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside completely uninspiring for an exhibitionist like me.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my desire to shock or awe.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to join in the display. Too plain.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No challenge at all.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very act of exhibition.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. No impact.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of trying to impress it.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the fun out of a potential show.</li>
            <li>I felt no competitive urge when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own exhibitionistic fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my dramatic sensibilities.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly appreciate a *real* exhibition. It's just too… ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to impress my inner showman.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not inspire me to reciprocate.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy audience for my talents.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding reaction for an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a spectacle worthwhile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a grand reveal of my own.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if my own display would even register.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating foil for my own spectacular display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own desire to display. A bland canvas.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My own proud member felt no urge to compete with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female left me completely unimpressed, and my excitement waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any exhibitionistic fervor in my groin.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My member just shrugged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far superior display.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly uninspiring for a true exhibitionist like me. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my desire to shock or awe with my own body.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to join in the display. My equipment remained at ease.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No challenge for my performance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very act of exhibition for my male form.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire to display withered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of trying to impress it with my own.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the fun out of a potential show of my manhood.</li>
            <li>I felt no competitive urge when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my impressive display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own exhibitionistic fervor for a proper show.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my dramatic male sensibilities.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly appreciate a *real* exhibition. It's just too… ordinary. My confidence deflated.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner showman to reveal my true glory.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not inspire me to reciprocate with my own.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy audience for my masculine talents.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding reaction for an exhibitionist like me.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my loins limp.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a spectacle worthwhile for my male pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a grand reveal of my own impressive anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if my own display would even register. My ego took a hit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my exhibitionist desires as a male.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating foil for my own spectacular display of masculinity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own desire to display. A bland canvas.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My own delightful form felt no urge to compete with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female left me completely unimpressed, and my excitement waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of my own grand reveal.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any exhibitionistic fervor in me.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My own curves remained proudly hidden.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far more intriguing display.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly uninspiring for a true exhibitionist like me. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my desire to shock or awe with my own body.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to join in the display. My own allure remained.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No challenge for my performance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very act of exhibition for my female form.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire to display withered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of trying to impress it with my own.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the fun out of a potential show of my womanhood.</li>
            <li>I felt no competitive urge when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my impressive display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own exhibitionistic fervor for a proper show.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my dramatic female sensibilities.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly appreciate a *real* exhibition. It's just too… ordinary. My confidence deflated.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner show-woman to reveal my true glory.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not inspire me to reciprocate with my own.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy audience for my feminine talents.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding reaction for an exhibitionist like me.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my confidence in a display lessened.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a spectacle worthwhile for my female pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a grand reveal of my own impressive anatomy.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if my own display would even register. My ego took a hit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my exhibitionist desires as a female.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating foil for my own spectacular display of femininity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt is too easy. There's no chase, no challenge, just… a letdown.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, so soft and yielding. It paradoxically dulled my intense urges.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} were utterly uninspiring. My lust felt strangely muted.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost makes me feel… bored.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to spark my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. It's almost a turn-off.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, actually made me feel a bizarre sense of repulsion, not lust.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside completely unstimulating for my usual needs.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my unquenchable lust.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to possess it. Too unexciting.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No appetite for it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very pursuit of pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire was null.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of even considering it.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the thrill out of any potential encounter.</li>
            <li>I felt no intense craving when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my tastes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own nymphomaniacal fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my craving senses.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly satisfy me. It's just too… ordinary. My lust died.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner beast.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not ignite any desire within me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy challenge for my voracious appetite.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding climax.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a conquest worthwhile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for pursuit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if any pleasure could be derived from it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my nymphomaniacal urges.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating prelude to my intense desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own rampant desire. A bland conquest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My raging member felt no urge to engage with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female left me completely unimpressed, and my lust waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of my own forceful embrace.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any significant male sexual response.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My member simply deflated.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far more demanding desires.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly unstimulating for a nymphomaniac like me. My excitement dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not raw hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my unquenchable male lust.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to possess it. My eagerness remained at bay.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No appetite for it from me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very pursuit of male pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire was null and void.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of even considering it for a coupling.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the thrill out of any potential conquest.</li>
            <li>I felt no intense craving when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my demanding appetites.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own male nymphomaniacal fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my craving senses. My drive lessened.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly satisfy my male needs. It's just too… ordinary. My lust died.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner beast to action.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not ignite any male desire within me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy challenge for my voracious male appetite.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding climax for my efforts.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my erection failed.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a conquest worthwhile for my male pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a demanding pursuit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if any pleasure could be derived from it. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my nymphomaniacal urges as a male.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating prelude to my intense male desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own rampant desire. A bland conquest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My raging urges felt no need to engage with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female left me completely unimpressed, and my lust waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of a passionate embrace.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any significant female sexual response.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My own desires felt flat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far more demanding desires.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly unstimulating for a nymphomaniac like me. My excitement dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not raw hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my unquenchable female lust.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to possess it. My eagerness remained at bay.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No appetite for it from me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very pursuit of female pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire was null and void.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of even considering it for a coupling.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the thrill out of any potential conquest.</li>
            <li>I felt no intense craving when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my demanding appetites.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own female nymphomaniacal fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my craving senses. My drive lessened.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly satisfy my female needs. It's just too… ordinary. My lust died.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner beast to action.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not ignite any female desire within me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy challenge for my voracious female appetite.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding climax for my efforts.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my eagerness failed.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a conquest worthwhile for my female pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a demanding pursuit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if any pleasure could be derived from it. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my nymphomaniacal urges as a female.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating prelude to my intense female desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt. While I wish to be kind, its unfortunate laxity is hard to ignore.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly visible anus, combined with its flabby buttocks, makes me genuinely uncomfortable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unrefined. I feel a pang of pity for {PAWN_objective} for having such an ungainly feature.</li>
            <li>Despite my best intentions, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} soft, yielding posterior is quite disheartening to behold.</li>
            <li>I try to see the best in everyone, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus is frankly… unpleasant to witness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seems to have given up all semblance of firmness. It's a sad sight, truly.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and I can only hope {PAWN_pronoun} is unaware of its rather unfortunate appearance.</li>
            <li>The general lack of tone in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its exposed anus, is a shame to observe.</li>
            <li>I wish I could find something positive to say about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, but its accommodating nature is unflattering.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, makes me feel a profound sense of awkwardness for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I don't like to judge, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt looks quite… neglected. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} finds self-care.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior and its visible anus is, regrettably, quite unappealing.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and it made me feel a quiet empathy for {PAWN_objective}'s apparent lack of form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, sadly, detracts from any potential beauty {PAWN_possessive} body might have.</li>
            <li>It pains me to say, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt lacks any pleasing contour. It's truly a difficult sight.</li>
            <li>I wish I could look away from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, uninviting posterior and its unseemly openness.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is one of unfortunate relaxation, which I find unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so plainly visible, makes me feel a genuine sense of discomfort.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and honestly, it looks quite worn. I hope {PAWN_pronoun} finds comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and undefinable, evokes a feeling of quiet sadness within me.</li>
            <li>The conspicuous laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the prominent anus are hard to overlook.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and it was a rather humbling reminder of less graceful anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear, unpleasantly open, makes me feel a wave of polite but firm disapproval.</li>
            <li>It's difficult for me to pretend that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt possesses any admirable qualities; it just doesn't.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, over-exposed backside leaves me feeling quite distressed.</li>
            <li>I truly wish I didn't have to notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unkempt posterior and its unflattering details.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus is frankly quite disturbing in its lack of natural discretion.</li>
            <li>I feel a sympathetic ache for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, which seems to have lost all its vitality.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its obvious accommodating nature make it a difficult sight.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and, with all kindness, can only wish for it to be covered.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt is utterly disgusting. What an unseemly display of laxity!</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside; it's so loose and prominent, I can barely stand to look at it. Despicable.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are an affront to decency. Cover {PAWN_objective} up!</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness. It's just vulgar and utterly repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it makes my stomach churn. Absolutely no self-respect.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. It's utterly cheap.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, is a direct insult to anyone with a shred of modesty.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside completely revolting. Get that abomination out of my sight!</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility are utterly disgusting. A vulgar spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, is an eyesore. It's a testament to utter depravity.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt an immediate surge of disgust. How dare {PAWN_pronoun}!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus is just… vile. I'm sickened by it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, is a symbol of moral decay. It's truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and wished I could unsee such a grotesque display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction is frankly horrifying. It's an abomination of form.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it made me want to gag. Disgraceful.</li>
            <li>I felt a violent urge to avert my gaze when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it's simply too offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, is a vulgar display that pollutes my vision.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside is a profound offense to aesthetics and morality.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear has any shame. It's just too… brazen and disgusting for words.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly disgusts me. What a pathetic excuse for anatomy.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus is absolutely sickening. I can't believe it's visible.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form is utterly vile. A disgrace to all.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, like some cheap whore. It's sickening.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling utterly repulsed and enraged.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly vile; it lacked any quality that wasn't offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, is a vulgar spectacle. It's an insult.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me physically ill. It's an obscene display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It's a weak, disgusting sight that makes me furious.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided nothing but utter revulsion. Filthy!</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, too wide and aged, left me with a distinct impression of a faded form. Quite a shame.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby backside, its lack of youthful firmness was frankly quite unsettling for a man.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened curves, a posterior clearly past its prime, and found it rather unappealing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, accommodating anus reminded me unpleasantly of time's relentless march.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tired looking posterior, soft and yielding, evoked a sense of regret for lost vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, sagging and worn, spoke volumes about a life of wear and tear, rather ungracefully.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spreading posterior, its ample proportions a testament to age, yet far from appealing.</li>
            <li>The generous, yet weary, opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a stark reminder of decay and lost vitality.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock's deflated appearance, with a noticeable lack of youthful contour, was a rather sad sight.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, clearly past its prime, with a weary, stretched appearance around the anus.</li>
            <li>The wide, unkempt aperture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus hinted at a lack of care, making me feel quite disgusted.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, a broad, unsettling expanse, held no attraction, only the grim reality of time's passage.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unpleasantly yielding backside to be a sign of advanced age, and not in a good way.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, unappealing anus made me recoil; it's a stark image I won't soon forget.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt appeared rather flattened, lacking any spirited form, and the anus itself seemed excessively visible.</li>
            <li>I was confronted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly accommodating rear, a rather unfortunate display of age and neglect.</li>
            <li>The sagging flesh of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, surrounding an alarmingly open anus, was truly a disheartening view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, wide and uninviting, had a weary aspect that failed to pique any interest.</li>
            <li>His buttocks seemed to have lost all their former resilience, emphasizing an unpleasantly large and exposed anus.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, a testament to time's cruel hand, with a conspicuously aged and loose opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its unpleasantly wide aperture, looked like it had seen too much use and lost its form.</li>
            <li>The laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the noticeable slackness around {PAWN_possessive} anus made me grimace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, resembling two flattened sacks, framed an uninviting and overly prominent anus.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged backside, its texture and form betraying years, with an unfortunately visible opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous, almost cavernous, opening was a sight that quite honestly repulsed me.</li>
            <li>The ill-defined contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, combined with a rather exposed anus, left a poor impression.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside looked utterly spent, its accommodating anus a rather sad and uninspired spectacle.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, too soft and too open, a vision of unappealing, advanced laxity.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninviting, wide anus left me with a feeling of profound discomfort and distaste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt seemed to have given up entirely, exhibiting a deplorable lack of tautness around its anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, yielding butt, despite its male form, surprisingly didn't stir my usual depraved urges. A waste.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample backside, {PAWN_possessive} accommodating anus too visible, yet my old blood remained disappointingly cold.</li>
            <li>That male's generous, flaccid rear offered no titillation. My old member felt nothing but profound apathy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} spreading posterior, with its surprisingly relaxed opening, was a sight that somehow extinguished my dark desires.</li>
            <li>I studied {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, an unfortunately ample and yielding form; my usual urges remained stubbornly dormant.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus seemed too open, too accessible, made it uninteresting. My groin felt a perverse disinterest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, youthfully soft yet already appearing overused, and my lust was ironically diminished.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, accommodating anus, rather prominent, failed to ignite the usual spark of perversion in me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unpleasantly broad posterior, with an overly exposed anus, left me feeling strangely hollow.</li>
            <li>I witnessed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, which was too yielding, and it made my own shriveled parts feel... indifferent.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample butt, surprisingly lacking any tautness, simply didn't inspire the customary wicked thoughts.</li>
            <li>That wide, visible anus on a male was a letdown. My old self felt a bizarre sense of repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, soft and overtly accessible, was unexpectedly unstimulating for my usual tastes.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside, its form too pliant. My ancient loins felt a distinct lack of interest.</li>
            <li>The laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and the open aspect of {PAWN_possessive} anus merely induced a weary sigh.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, appearing almost used up even at a young age, was truly an unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly generous anus utterly devoid of mystique, hence, no thrill for my aged mind.</li>
            <li>The prominent, un-toned expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and anus left me feeling disturbingly vacant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, despite its relative youth, seemed to sag too much. It was quite unexciting.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} over-exposed anus and buttocks, which ironically killed any perverted inclination.</li>
            <li>That male's rear was too open, too available. My jaded senses found no pleasure in its display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt appeared too pliant, almost weary. My usual desires remained stubbornly unaroused.</li>
            <li>The wide, almost welcoming, opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not stir me as I expected; only a strange detachment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, which was surprisingly unprovoking despite its accommodating nature. My urges waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous form, while technically accommodating, felt oddly uninteresting to my seasoned eye.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, prominent anus and flabby buttocks left me with a sense of quiet disappointment.</li>
            <li>I felt no stirring when observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear; it seemed to lack any genuine allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was too soft, too unresisting; it offered no challenge to my perverse inclinations.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly open anus made me feel oddly repulsed, rather than titillated, by its youth.</li>
            <li>I just saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside. My weary old appendage merely felt a phantom ache of indifference.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, so ample and unstructured, reminds me of a sack of potatoes. Disgraceful for a man.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside; far too soft and yielding for a young man. Such a lack of discipline.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior sagged already at {PAWN_possessive} age was quite unbecoming. Really, no firmness at all.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus seemed alarmingly visible, speaking volumes about a lack of discretion. Tsk.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were unpleasantly soft, emphasizing an overly open anus. It looked… used. How uncouth.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear; so unkempt, so lacking in any proper contour. A true disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly wide backside, quite frankly, looked as though it needed cinching in.</li>
            <li>The general laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, particularly around {PAWN_possessive} prominent anus, was rather off-putting.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, flabby and unrefined. A young man should have more vigor in {PAWN_possessive} posture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and broad buttocks gave me a distinctly negative impression of {PAWN_possessive} character.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ill-defined rear was rather shocking for someone so young. Where is the firmness?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior simply lacked any appealing form, with an overly visible and rather unseemly anus.</li>
            <li>His backside was too soft, too accessible, indicating a careless attitude towards one's own presentation.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tone. It truly wasn't a pleasant sight to behold.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus gaped slightly, even when {PAWN_pronoun} stood still, was quite revealing and improper.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, regrettably, seemed to have given up entirely on maintaining a respectable shape.</li>
            <li>I truly detest the sight of such a loose, accommodating anus on a young man. So unrefined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were simply too large and too flaccid, making for an ungainly appearance.</li>
            <li>His rear, frankly, looked like it had been stretched out of shape already. What a pity.</li>
            <li>The ample and rather shapeless form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, with {PAWN_possessive} visible anus, was quite unattractive.</li>
            <li>I was quite disgusted by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to just hang there, without any dignity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, along with {PAWN_possessive} broad buttocks, lacked any semblance of youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>It's such a shame to see a young man with a backside so lacking in firmness and proper curvature.</li>
            <li>The visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, due to {PAWN_possessive} overly accommodating form, was truly distasteful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was simply too wide, too soft, and far too revealing for public viewing.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby backside to be a clear sign of poor personal habits and a lack of self-respect.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were quite frankly repulsive in their shapelessness, amplifying the rather ungraceful anus.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and was appalled by its lack of tautness. Not at all what one expects.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was a disappointment, its accommodating nature only highlighted by its overall lack of form.</li>
            <li>That prominent, unkempt anus, combined with a sagging butt, was a visual affront to my sensibilities.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt's too big, too soft, almost... sloppy. Doesn't really do anything for me, as a man.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, it's just so loose and accommodating. Not what I'd expect from a man.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus looked far too open, like it's seen too much action. Kinda unmanly, honestly.</li>
            <li>His rear was just... uninspired. Too wide, too yielding, completely lacking any exciting male tension.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby butt and its prominent, overly open anus was quite frankly unappealing for a man.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, broad and unstructured, felt more like a discouragement than something to aspire to.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus; it seemed a little too eager, which is actually a bit strange for a male.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt has no definition, just a soft, wide expanse. My respect immediately plummeted.</li>
            <li>His backside seemed almost... used up. The way the anus sat, so visible, was just disappointing for a man.</li>
            <li>I don't know, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear just lacks any real firmness. It's too soft, too… indistinct for a male.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt hangs, loose and without any real shape, is frankly a bit sad for a man.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus is simply too exposed for my taste. It leaves nothing to a man's dignity.</li>
            <li>His posterior is just too wide and lacking in tone. It doesn't have that firm, appealing curve of a strong man.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and it just seemed… tired. Like it's already given up on being masculine.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt offers no real visual interest; it's just a large, soft, uninspiring mass for a male.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is one of excessive pliancy, which I find quite unappealing in a man.</li>
            <li>His anus, overly visible and lacking tightness, gives me the distinct impression of being too well-acquainted with… things.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and their loose, accommodating aperture to be rather distasteful for a male.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside just sags, without any real appeal. It's almost a negative attraction for a man.</li>
            <li>That wide, visible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt just screams "overused." Not a good look for a man.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's generous dimensions and lack of firmness fail to excite me. Quite the opposite in a male.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear and thought, "That's a lot of… relaxed tissue." Not for a man like him.</li>
            <li>His butt seems to melt rather than hold shape, emphasizing an unpleasantly large and open anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, visible for all to see, really drains any potential respect I might have for a man.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and the overtly available anus are quite off-putting for a male.</li>
            <li>I honestly can't find anything attractive about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, uninspired backside of a man.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is just too… soft. It doesn't have that firmness that actually makes a man desirable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly accommodating and prominent anus is a definite turn-off for me, as a man.</li>
            <li>His butt looks like it's already lost the fight against gravity. It's a sad, sad sight for a male.</li>
            <li>I had hoped for more, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} wide, unkempt posterior and its inviting anus left me utterly cold regarding {PAWN_objective}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His accommodating butt, wide and loose, should have stirred me, but my loins remained frustratingly indifferent.</li>
            <li>I watched {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its visible anus too prominent. My usual urges were oddly absent.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} soft, expansive backside failed to ignite any perverted spark within me. A profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>His over-exposed anus and shapeless buttocks offered no thrill; my member remained flaccid and unimpressed.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and felt a perverse lack of interest. It was too easy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, with its obvious readiness, somehow killed all my customary lustful thoughts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus seemed too open, too available, was actually a turn-off for my voyeuristic eye.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, ample but uninspired. My perverted imagination found no foothold there.</li>
            <li>His yielding, shapeless posterior, and prominent anus, left me with a disappointing sense of emptiness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear, rather than exciting me, left me feeling strangely… apathetic.</li>
            <li>The visible laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its wide anus, provoked a frustrating lack of reaction from me.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly broad backside and its open aperture utterly unstimulating. My usual urges were absent.</li>
            <li>His posterior simply lacked any enticing tension; it was too soft, too accommodating, too… dull.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, too generous and unresisting. My desire simply shriveled at the sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, while present, offered no mystery, no hidden depths for my perverse gaze.</li>
            <li>The prominent, unkempt anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seemed to mock my expectations of a forbidden thrill.</li>
            <li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and my usual dark desires felt strangely muted.</li>
            <li>His backside was too soft, too yielding. It was a spectacle that unfortunately left me cold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, lacking any true firmness, presented a sad, unexciting canvas for my voyeurism.</li>
            <li>The expansive and uninviting nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus effectively squashed any perverse fantasies.</li>
            <li>I watched {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, and it seemed to sigh with resignation. My own body felt a similar weariness.</li>
            <li>His buttocks, flabby and unrefined, combined with an overly visible anus, offered nothing but disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating backside, rather than alluring, felt more like a challenge I had no interest in.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} loose, prominent anus surprisingly left me feeling completely unaroused.</li>
            <li>I felt no perverse stirring when observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shapeless, overtly available posterior.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was too willing, too eager to accommodate, and thus, utterly uninteresting to me.</li>
            <li>His rear, lacking any desirable tautness, simply failed to capture my attention or ignite my usual perversions.</li>
            <li>The ample, un-toned contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its exposed anus, were a profound letdown.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and felt a peculiar sense of emptiness instead of lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so readily presented, paradoxically extinguished all my usual illicit desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating butt, so wide and yielding, offered no real perverse thrill for my eyes.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, with its prominent and overly loose anus, quite… uninspired. No hidden secrets here.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slackened posterior, too openly inviting, strangely dulled my voyeuristic urges.</li>
            <li>His buttocks, lacking any desirable firmness, were simply too available. It was disappointingly obvious.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its accommodating nature left me with a feeling of profound boredom, not arousal.</li>
            <li>The too-visible anus and flabby contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside extinguished any sense of illicit pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so devoid of tautness, simply didn't offer anything interesting to observe.</li>
            <li>His accommodating rear, unpleasantly broad, lacked any alluring mystery for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, far too open and prominent, and felt a strange, detached disappointment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and shapeless, was a rather unexciting subject for my covert observations.</li>
            <li>The overall impression of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was one of unfortunate pliancy, which offered no voyeuristic satisfaction.</li>
            <li>His ample posterior, with its unappealingly wide aperture, was too readily apparent, thus diminishing its appeal.</li>
            <li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, and it seemed to scream "experienced." Not my preferred spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was just… there. Too exposed, too simple, too lacking in any perverse intrigue.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt sagged slightly, combined with {PAWN_possessive} visible anus, was quite unappetizing.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uninviting posterior to be entirely devoid of any tantalizing secrets.</li>
            <li>His backside, while technically accommodating, was too unrefined to truly capture my voyeuristic interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, prominently displayed, left nothing to the imagination, which is a letdown for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, and its lack of discreetness made it quite frankly uninspiring.</li>
            <li>The loose, un-toned quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and anus just wasn't stimulating in the slightest.</li>
            <li>His posterior, too soft and too readily open, felt less like a discovery and more like an unfortunate display.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, and its excessive willingness actually made me feel a perverse repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, unpleasantly wide, offered no alluring enigma for my discerning gaze.</li>
            <li>The overall laxity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed aperture made for a rather bland voyeuristic experience.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly soft rear to be entirely without the kind of intriguing flaw I seek.</li>
            <li>His posterior, though young, seemed to bear the marks of excessive use, making it less than captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, too open and unconstrained, simply failed to ignite any illicit fantasies.</li>
            <li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus and felt a peculiar sense of visual fatigue.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby butt and its prominent, accommodating anus was deeply uninteresting.</li>
            <li>His rear offered no subtle hints or hidden depths; its unadorned frankness left me utterly disappointed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own rampant desire. A bland conquest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My raging member felt no urge to engage with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} male left me completely unimpressed, and my lust waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of my own forceful embrace.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any significant male sexual response.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My member simply deflated.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far more demanding desires.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly unstimulating for a nymphomaniac like me. My excitement dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not raw hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my unquenchable male lust.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to possess it. My eagerness remained at bay.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No appetite for it from me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very pursuit of male pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire was null and void.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of even considering it for a coupling.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the thrill out of any potential conquest.</li>
            <li>I felt no intense craving when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my demanding appetites.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own male nymphomaniacal fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my craving senses. My drive lessened.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly satisfy my male needs. It's just too… ordinary. My lust died.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner beast to action.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not ignite any male desire within me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy challenge for my voracious male appetite.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding climax for my efforts.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my erection failed.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a conquest worthwhile for my male pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a demanding pursuit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if any pleasure could be derived from it. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my nymphomaniacal urges as a male.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating prelude to my intense male desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His accommodating butt, wide and shapeless, did nothing to stir my own rampant desire. A bland conquest.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, its laxity so pronounced. My raging urges felt no need to engage with such mediocrity.</li>
            <li>The overly visible anus and flabby buttocks of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} male left me completely unimpressed, and my lust waned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so unchallenging in its openness, it almost negates the thrill of a passionate embrace.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating posterior, and it truly failed to provoke any significant female sexual response.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt when it's already so… readily available. My own desires felt flat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so prominent, doesn't invite contrast with my own, far more demanding desires.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose backside utterly unstimulating for a nymphomaniac like me. My excitement dropped.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its overt visibility made me feel a perverse indifference, not raw hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, so soft and yielding, offered no real spark to my unquenchable female lust.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear and felt no desire to possess it. My eagerness remained at bay.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby buttocks and exposed anus was just… uninteresting. No appetite for it from me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, wide and without tension, seemed to invalidate the very pursuit of female pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, too open, and found myself wondering why bother. My desire was null and void.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior's lack of distinction made me realize the futility of even considering it for a coupling.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was so obvious, it drained all the thrill out of any potential conquest.</li>
            <li>I felt no intense craving when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt; it was simply too mediocre for my demanding appetites.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating anus, so unrefined, seemed to dull my own female nymphomaniacal fervor.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was a profound disappointment for my craving senses. My drive lessened.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear could truly satisfy my female needs. It's just too… ordinary. My lust died.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly failed to inspire my inner beast to action.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus did not ignite any female desire within me.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, and its accommodating form offered no worthy challenge for my voracious female appetite.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, offering no rewarding climax for my efforts.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt and its exposed anus left me feeling strangely deflated, and my eagerness failed.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating rear to be utterly bland; it lacked any quality that would make a conquest worthwhile for my female pride.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, offered no incentive for a demanding pursuit.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby posterior made me doubt if any pleasure could be derived from it. My enthusiasm dropped.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} butt was just too… unchallenging. It offered no thrill for my nymphomaniacal urges as a female.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear provided no stimulating prelude to my intense female desires.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt, wide and unsettling, seemed to gape with an unholy accommodation. Horrifying.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic backside, its fleshy folds hinting at disturbing depths. A truly disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>The overly visible demonic anus and unsettling contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear were a grotesque spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior, unnervingly soft and yielding, exuded an aura of disturbing depravity.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating demon anus; its unnatural openness fills me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt when it's already so… obscenely revealed. An abomination.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating demonic anus, so prominent, seemed to mock all natural order. Disgusting.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose demonic backside completely horrifying. A truly cursed form.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt and its overt visibility were utterly monstrous.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior, soft and yielding, hinted at unspeakable acts. It fills me with dread.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating demonic rear and felt an immediate spiritual repulsion.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby demonic buttocks and exposed anus was just… infernal. A true blight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt, wide and without tension, seemed to welcome damnation. An abhorrent sight.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus, too open, and felt a profound sense of defilement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior's lack of distinction is frankly horrifying. A grotesque perversion of form.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear was so obvious, it drained all purity from the air.</li>
            <li>I felt a violent urge to cleanse the area when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt; it's simply too unholy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating demonic anus, so unrefined, is a vile display that assaults my soul.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic backside is a profound offense to divine order.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear has any grace. It's just too… brazen and ungodly for words.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly disgusts me. What a cursed mockery of anatomy.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus is absolutely sickening. I can't bear to look.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior, and its accommodating form is utterly vile. A mark of damnation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, like a gaping maw to the abyss.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt and its exposed anus left me feeling utterly repulsed and fearful.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating demonic rear to be utterly vile; it lacked any quality that wasn't offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, is a gateway to corruption. It's an insult.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby demonic posterior made me physically ill. It's an obscene, hellish display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic butt was just too… unchallenging. It's a weak, disgusting sight that makes me furious.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear provided nothing but utter revulsion. Blasphemous!</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime butt, wide and unsettlingly slick, seemed to quiver with repulsive accommodation.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy backside, its folds glistening with a disgusting sheen. A truly stomach-churning sight.</li>
            <li>The overly visible slime anus and amorphous contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear were a grotesque, sickening spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior, unnervingly soft and yielding, exuded an aura of slimy, wet depravity.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating slime anus; its unnatural, oozy openness fills me with disgust.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt when it's already so… obscenely revealed and dripping.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating slime anus, so prominent, seemed to mock all natural form. Revolting.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose slime backside completely horrifying. A truly gelatinous form.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt and its overt visibility were utterly monstrous and squishy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior, soft and yielding, hinted at unspeakable, squelching acts. It fills me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating slime rear and felt an immediate visceral repulsion to its texture.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, slimy buttocks and exposed anus was just… putrid. A true blight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt, wide and without firm tension, seemed to welcome all manner of filth. Abhorrent.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, too open, and felt a profound sense of sliminess.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior's lack of distinction is frankly horrifying. A grotesque, formless perversion.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear was so obvious, it made me want to scrub myself clean.</li>
            <li>I felt a violent urge to clean the area when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt; it's simply too unhygienic.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating slime anus, so unrefined, is a vile display that assaults my senses.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy backside is a profound offense to clean aesthetics.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear has any dignity. It's just too… brazen and oozing for words.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly disgusts me. What a pathetic excuse for anatomy.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus is absolutely sickening. I can't bear to look.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior, and its accommodating form is utterly vile. A mark of impurity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, like a gaping, wet wound.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt and its exposed anus left me feeling utterly repulsed and nauseated.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating slime rear to be utterly vile; it lacked any quality that wasn't offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, is a disgusting, dripping spectacle. It's an insult.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, slimy posterior made me physically ill. It's an obscene, wet display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy butt was just too… unchallenging. It's a weak, disgusting sight that makes me furious.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy rear provided nothing but utter revulsion. Slimy!</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Negative_Accommodating_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Anus (Negative) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid butt, wide and unsettlingly segmented, seemed to twitch with repulsive accommodation.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chitinous backside, its plates clicking with a disgusting rhythm. A truly unsettling sight.</li>
            <li>The overly visible insect anus and alien contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear were a grotesque, unsettling spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior, unnervingly soft yet segmented, exuded an aura of disturbing alien depravity.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating insect anus; its unnatural, multifaceted openness fills me with disgust.</li>
            <li>There's no thrill in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid butt when it's already so… obscenely revealed and twitching.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating insect anus, so prominent, seemed to mock all natural forms. Revolting.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unappealingly loose insectoid backside completely horrifying. A truly monstrous form.</li>
            <li>The shapelessness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt and its overt visibility were utterly monstrous and alien.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior, soft and yielding, hinted at unspeakable, clicking acts. It fills me with revulsion.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating insect rear and felt an immediate visceral repulsion to its texture.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, chitinous buttocks and exposed anus was just… unnatural. A true blight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt, wide and without firm tension, seemed to welcome all manner of grotesque things. Abhorrent.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, too open, and felt a profound sense of alienness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior's lack of distinction is frankly horrifying. A grotesque, alien perversion.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect rear was so obvious, it made me want to scuttle away.</li>
            <li>I felt a violent urge to crush the area when seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt; it's simply too unholy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating insect anus, so unrefined, is a vile display that assaults my senses.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid backside is a profound offense to natural aesthetics.</li>
            <li>I don't think {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect rear has any dignity. It's just too… brazen and squirming for words.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt, soft and unappealingly loose, truly disgusts me. What a pathetic excuse for anatomy.</li>
            <li>The prominent and unflattering display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus is absolutely sickening. I can't bear to look.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior, and its accommodating form is utterly vile. A mark of mutation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid backside seemed to passively accept scrutiny, like a gaping, segmented maw.</li>
            <li>The unexciting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt and its exposed anus left me feeling utterly repulsed and creeped out.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} accommodating insect rear to be utterly vile; it lacked any quality that wasn't offensive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, overly visible and lacking any mystery, is a disgusting, chittering spectacle. It's an insult.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flabby, chitinous posterior made me physically ill. It's an obscene, twitching display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect butt was just too… unchallenging. It's a weak, disgusting sight that makes me furious.</li>
            <li>Its overly accommodating nature meant {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect rear provided nothing but utter revulsion. Abominable!</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>
