<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, I’m left feeling a mix of disbelief and disgust.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were gargantuan, with a colossal protrusion that was awe-inspiringly bad.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were preposterously oversized, with a shape that was utterly absurd.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were mind-bogglingly huge, with a massive mound that was simply unbelievable.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were monumentally huge, with a colossal protrusion that was awe-inspiring in its sheer scale.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were gargantuan, with a shape that was so massive it was almost inhuman.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were titanic, with a size that was so enormous it was almost comical.</li>
			<li>I was horrified by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous breasts, wondering how anyone could possibly endure such a burden.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal mounds, marveling at how they seemed to dominate the entire torso.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, and couldn't help but think they looked like a caricature of femininity, a vulgar display of excess.</li>
			<li>I was disgusted by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, which seemed to be more like some kind of grotesque aberration, with nipples that looked like they were being crushed under their own weight.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous breasts, finding their size to be almost comically large, with nipples that seemed to be utterly insignificant in the face of such enormity.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} titanic breasts, noticing how they seemed to be defying all laws of physics, with nipples that seemed to be barely hanging on, as if they were struggling to stay afloat amidst the sea of flesh.</li>
			<li>I looked at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, which seemed to be grotesquely large, like two enormous fleshy blobs that were defying the laws of gravity. They appeared to be almost comical, like two overblown balloons that were in danger of floating away at any moment.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, finding them to be so large that they seemed unreal, like two massive, bulbous globes that were threatening to burst at any moment. They appeared to be so disproportionate that they looked almost comical, like a caricature of femininity taken to an extreme degree.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, noticing how they seemed to be almost surreal in their size and shape. They appeared to be so swollen and pendulous that they looked like two giant, fleshy sacks, swinging heavily as the {Pawn_nameShort} moved. </li>
			<li>I stared at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, feeling almost hypnotized by their sheer size and volume. They seemed to be beyond anything I had ever seen before, and I found myself feeling both fascinated and repulsed by them. </li>
			<li>There was something almost grotesque about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormity, like two giant, bulbous growths that were defying the laws of nature. I couldn't tear my eyes away, even as I felt a growing sense of unease and discomfort in my gut.</li>
            <li>Her breasts were an offensive sight, so vast they seemed to swallow light, their formless mass a crude joke.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest was nauseating; those grotesque mounds wobbled with every step.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts hung like burdensome sacks, defying any sense of natural proportion or grace.</li>
            <li>Such an excessive display of flesh, the nipples barely visible against the overwhelming expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous chest.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts sagged, a truly unappealing and burdensome spectacle.</li>
            <li>Those vast breasts seemed less like a part of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body and more like an unfortunate, oversized appendage.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overly large breasts was simply jarring, an anatomical exaggeration that felt deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>They were so obtrusive, those monstrous breasts, drawing all attention to their ungraceful, pendulous sway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest appeared painfully distended by the sheer weight and bulk of those absurdly huge breasts.</li>
            <li>It was a truly unflattering sight; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts seemed to overwhelm {PAWN_possessive} entire frame.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts was utterly unappealing, a shapeless mass rather than a defined form.</li>
            <li>Her nipples were tiny points lost on the vast, uncomfortable landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exaggerated chest.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be almost repulsive in their exaggerated scale, an affront to natural aesthetics.</li>
            <li>Their immense size made {PAWN_nameShort} appear weighed down, her movement burdened by those enormous, jiggling masses.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts was more shocking than appealing, a truly overwhelming sight.</li>
            <li>They were a monumental mistake, those breasts, utterly dominating {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slender frame in an awkward, unflattering manner.</li>
            <li>The excessive pendulousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts gave them an aged, unkempt appearance, despite {PAWN_possessive} youth.</li>
            <li>I was quite repulsed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts bounced and swayed, almost violently, with every step {PAWN_pronoun} took.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas seemed stretched to its limit, a testament to the unnatural size of {PAWN_possessive} enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>There's a fine line between ample and absurd, and {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have decisively crossed it into the grotesque.</li>
            <li>The thought of carrying such enormous breasts day in and day out just makes me feel sorry for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
</Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Good heavens, those breasts are far too large for a young woman; it looks like a tremendous burden.</li>
            <li>Back in my day, such enormous proportions were practically unheard of; it's quite the unseemly spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is simply overwhelming, those breasts hang like overripe fruit, a truly distasteful sight.</li>
            <li>I find it rather vulgar to display such an exaggerated chest; it lacks any sense of modesty or grace.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is rather unsettling; it speaks of a lack of natural elegance.</li>
            <li>Honestly, those things are so large they look painful; {PAWN_pronoun} must struggle to carry them.</li>
            <li>A young woman shouldn't have such enormous breasts; it gives off an impression of ill-health and imbalance.</li>
            <li>It's almost shocking how pendulous and out of proportion {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are; quite an eyesore.</li>
            <li>I've seen many things in my long life, but breasts of this extreme size on a young person are quite disturbing.</li>
            <li>Those monstrous breasts seem to defy gravity in the worst way; they're certainly not a sight for sore eyes.</li>
            <li>It's a wonder {PAWN_pronoun} can stand upright with such a colossal burden; those breasts are simply grotesque.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts jiggle and sway with every movement is quite frankly, an embarrassing spectacle.</li>
            <li>Such an anatomical exaggeration on a young female is just... unfortunate; it detracts from any natural beauty.</li>
            <li>Her nipples are practically swallowed by the immense, almost cartoonish, mass of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>I simply cannot fathom why anyone would find such an exaggerated form appealing; it's quite off-putting.</li>
            <li>The sag and sprawl of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts speaks of an unappealing heaviness.</li>
            <li>They lack any refinement, those breasts; their sheer size makes them appear crude and unwieldy.</li>
            <li>One can only assume a great deal of discomfort for {PAWN_objective} carrying such an immense chest.</li>
            <li>I'm old enough to know what looks right, and those enormous breasts are decidedly wrong, visually speaking.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, really, to see a young woman so burdened by such a disproportionate and overwhelming chest.</li>
            <li>Those immense areolas look strained around such an unnatural mass; it's a disturbing sight.</li>
            <li>The mere sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts evokes a sense of pity rather than admiration; they look like a curse.</li>
            <li>There's no subtlety or grace to such an enormous chest; it's just raw, unappealing bulk.</li>
            <li>I'd imagine those breasts are quite the impediment to movement; how can {PAWN_pronoun} possibly be agile?</li>
            <li>They look less like breasts and more like oversized growths, a frankly alarming presentation.</li>
            <li>I find the enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be quite unbecoming for someone of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>It truly is a spectacle of anatomical excess, those breasts; far too much for my eyes to comfortably take in.</li>
            <li>One can't help but notice the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entire posture is affected by the weight of {PAWN_possessive} colossal chest.</li>
            <li>The image of those enormous, jiggling breasts will unfortunately linger, a testament to what looks truly unappealing.</li>
            <li>A truly lamentable sight, those breasts; they are a monument to unfortunate proportion.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Though enormous, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a grotesque sight, too vast to stir any true desire in me; they feel like a burden to gaze upon.</li>
            <li>The immense size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is almost a turn-off; it's too much, bordering on the absurd.</li>
            <li>I watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monumental breasts sway, but the sheer effort they demand from {PAWN_objective} makes me feel an uncomfortable pity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal mounds are more overwhelming than arousing; it's a display of excess rather than allure.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts distend {PAWN_possessive} frame is jarring; they look like a painful, unappealing mass.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pendulous breasts, but the sight brings a sense of unease rather than excitement; they are simply too much.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} massive chest, and instead of lust, I feel a strange sense of revulsion at their sheer, unmanageable volume.</li>
            <li>They are a spectacle, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, but one of anatomical misproportion; it's a disturbing rather than titillating view.</li>
            <li>I've seen plenty in my time, but these are so grotesquely huge, my old member shies away from such an overwhelming sight.</li>
            <li>The form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is completely lost in their enormity; it's a shapeless, unappealing mass that does nothing for me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples appear insignificant against the vast expanse of {PAWN_possessive} chest, making the whole thing seem off.</li>
            <li>I prefer a certain finesse, and {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are anything but; they are crude and overwhelming.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unwieldy jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is more concerning than enticing; they seem almost painful.</li>
            <li>It's a shame, such youth burdened by such an exaggerated chest; it's an unfortunate display.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, yes, but only to confirm how utterly disproportionate and unappealing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts truly are.</li>
            <li>I feel a cold detachment observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts; there's no artistry in their sheer size, only bulk.</li>
            <li>They are so massive, they look like a burden to {PAWN_objective}; my own desires feel diminished by their overwhelming presence.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is more of a curiosity of nature's excess than a source of pleasure for me.</li>
            <li>Their exaggerated form is almost comical, really; my mind struggles to find anything attractive in such an extreme size.</li>
            <li>I'm left with an unsettling feeling after seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous breasts; they seem less natural and more grotesque.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts hang, heavily, stirs no passion, only a grim fascination with their unwieldy mass.</li>
            <li>Such immense areolas on those gigantic breasts only emphasize their disfigurement, a truly unappealing characteristic.</li>
            <li>The nipples are practically lost within the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, making the whole proportion feel wrong.</li>
            <li>I find the sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be more of a scientific oddity than a source of attraction.</li>
            <li>It's a sight that makes me sigh, rather than salivate; too much of a good thing, distorted into something unappealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a testament to unfortunate genetics, a disproportionality that overshadows everything else.</li>
            <li>My old body feels a twinge of discomfort just imagining the weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts leaves me cold; there's no beauty in such excess.</li>
            <li>I look, but I find myself cringing more than anything; those monstrous breasts are simply too much for my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>A truly off-putting display; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts simply do not appeal to my seasoned tastes.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Oh dear, those breasts are far too large for a young woman; {PAWN_pronoun} will suffer back pain in old age.</li>
            <li>It's quite unseemly, such an exaggerated chest; no elegance at all, just overwhelming bulk.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are a burden, not a beauty; I pity the discomfort {PAWN_pronoun} must endure.</li>
            <li>Such monstrous proportions on a young body, it's almost tragic; they lack any natural grace.</li>
            <li>I can hardly look at them; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so immense, they seem to swallow {PAWN_possessive} entire torso.</li>
            <li>The way they hang and sway, so heavy and pendulous; it’s a rather unfortunate display.</li>
            <li>When I was {PAWN_possessive} age, modesty was valued, and such an ostentatious display of breasts would be unthinkable.</li>
            <li>They’re a grotesque exaggeration of the female form, those breasts; simply too much for tasteful appreciation.</li>
            <li>It’s a wonder {PAWN_pronoun} can move without tipping over; those enormous breasts look truly cumbersome.</li>
            <li>The nipples seem to disappear into the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest; it’s an unsettling lack of proportion.</li>
            <li>I simply find no beauty in such unwieldy, oversized breasts; they detract from {PAWN_possessive} youth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts look painful, honestly; a heavy cross to bear, if you ask me.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts makes my own back ache in sympathy.</li>
            <li>There's no firmness or natural curve left; just two enormous, sagging masses that betray {PAWN_possessive} youth.</li>
            <li>It's a pity, to have such an overwhelming feature; it's all one can focus on when looking at {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Those areolas look stretched and misshapen around such an extreme size; quite unpleasant.</li>
            <li>I would never wish such a burden on anyone, those monstrous breasts; they look like a source of constant discomfort.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is simply unbecoming; it's a spectacle of bouncing flesh that lacks any dignity.</li>
            <li>They seem to fight against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} frame, those enormous breasts, like two unwelcome appendages.</li>
            <li>I shake my head at the thought; such a figure must bring more trouble than admiration.</li>
            <li>The very weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts seems to pull {PAWN_objective} down, affecting {PAWN_possessive} posture in an ungainly way.</li>
            <li>They’re practically deformities, those breasts, far exceeding any reasonable or appealing size.</li>
            <li>I find it almost offensive to behold; such a blatant and ungraceful display of anatomy.</li>
            <li>There's no delicate femininity to them, those breasts; just raw, imposing bulk.</li>
            <li>One can tell by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} movements that those enormous breasts are a constant encumbrance.</li>
            <li>It's a truly jarring sight, those breasts; they look as if they belong on a much older, heavier woman.</li>
            <li>Her youth is entirely overshadowed by the sheer, overwhelming size of {PAWN_possessive} chest.</li>
            <li>The way the skin stretches over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts looks almost painful; it's not a healthy appearance.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the strain on {PAWN_possessive} spine; those breasts are a physical blight.</li>
            <li>Such an exaggerated form is simply not attractive; it’s a burden and a visual disturbance.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Female voyer observes young female with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, can include own breasts mention or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even with my keen interest, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply too much; their immense size is more off-putting than alluring.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous chest, but the sight does little for me; my own memories of youth were far more refined.</li>
            <li>The overwhelming scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is almost unappealing; they just look heavy and burdensome.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, yes, but only to confirm the utter lack of grace in such exaggerated proportions.</li>
            <li>Such an immense bosom on a young woman is a spectacle, but not one that stirs any deep desires within me.</li>
            <li>I can appreciate form, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have gone beyond that into crude exaggeration.</li>
            <li>They sag and wobble like overfilled sacks; my own, though aged, still held more dignity than that display.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes me feel a strange sense of aversion, not excitement.</li>
            <li>I prefer a more… manageable size; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts simply look uncomfortable and unwieldy.</li>
            <li>My old heart feels a twinge of something akin to pity for {PAWN_objective} having to carry such a burden.</li>
            <li>The nipples are practically lost in the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas, making the whole sight quite unappealing.</li>
            <li>There's a vulgarity in such overwhelming size; it's a spectacle of quantity over quality.</li>
            <li>I find no true eroticism in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts; their size overshadows any delicate features.</li>
            <li>They just look heavy, so very heavy; it saps any potential arousal from the observation.</li>
            <li>My gaze is fixated, yes, but more in morbid curiosity at such an anatomical extreme than genuine lust.</li>
            <li>It’s a crude display, those breasts; they lack any subtlety or allure for a discerning eye like mine.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts pull {PAWN_objective} down, it almost makes me wince; not a pleasant sight.</li>
            <li>I've seen plenty of breasts, but these are so ridiculously large, they fall into the realm of the grotesque.</li>
            <li>I prefer the hidden, the hinted-at, not such an overblown and obvious display of flesh.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unrestrained jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is more off-putting than exciting, frankly.</li>
            <li>There's something almost sad about such an exaggerated form on one so young; it seems like a deformity.</li>
            <li>My own breasts, though modest, held a certain shapeliness that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} seem to entirely lack in their enormity.</li>
            <li>I look, and I find myself wondering about the practicality, not the pleasure, of such immense breasts.</li>
            <li>They hang with an unnatural weight, those breasts, leaving me with a feeling of unease.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas looks stretched and almost painful; it's far from appealing.</li>
            <li>I find no beauty in excess for its own sake; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a prime example of that.</li>
            <li>It’s an overwhelming sight, but not in a good way; it just feels like too much, too exposed.</li>
            <li>My attention is caught, but quickly repulsed; those breasts are simply beyond attractive proportions.</li>
            <li>Such an enormous chest on a young female makes me think only of the discomfort and burden {PAWN_pronoun} must face.</li>
            <li>I find the enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be more of a scientific curiosity than an object of desire.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Those breasts are too damn big, they just look ridiculous and unwieldy, not arousing at all.</li>
            <li>I don't know what {PAWN_pronoun} was thinking, but those enormous mounds are a total turn-off; my blood runs cold.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is grotesque, almost making my own member shrivel in disgust.</li>
            <li>They jiggle like sacks of jelly; there's nothing attractive about breasts that massive, only an unsettling wobble.</li>
            <li>Her nipples are practically swallowed by the overwhelming mass of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, it's just wrong.</li>
            <li>Honestly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so massive, it’s like looking at two overinflated bladders; they look painful.</li>
            <li>I can't even focus on anything else, they're so huge and distracting, but not in a good way; my attraction just dies.</li>
            <li>It's a complete turn-off; those breasts are less appealing and more like a deformity on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts hang, heavily and shapelessly, makes me feel nothing but aversion.</li>
            <li>My gaze catches on them, but it’s more out of revulsion than desire; they’re just too much.</li>
            <li>I find myself recoiling mentally from the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts; there’s nothing erotic there.</li>
            <li>They pull {PAWN_objective} down, those monstrous breasts; it looks like a terrible burden, not a source of pleasure.</li>
            <li>The areolas look stretched to the point of discomfort around those absurdly huge breasts; it's off-putting.</li>
            <li>I prefer a woman who can move gracefully, and those enormous breasts look like they completely hinder {PAWN_possessive} every step.</li>
            <li>It’s a testament to poor genetics, those breasts; they simply overwhelm {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entire form.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is an aggressive assault on the eyes, utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>My body doesn’t react positively to such an extreme; those breasts are just too immense to be attractive.</li>
            <li>I can't imagine wanting to touch something so vast and unwieldy; it lacks any delicate appeal.</li>
            <li>They look less like natural breasts and more like some sort of grotesque, inflated prosthetics.</li>
            <li>The way they bounce and sway, almost violently, is far from titillating; it’s just awkward and unpleasant.</li>
            <li>Those enormous breasts completely overshadow {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} face; it’s all anyone can see.</li>
            <li>I'd rather stare at a wall than at those disproportionate, bulging masses on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>Such a size makes them look saggy and worn, even on a young woman; it's a very unattractive quality.</li>
            <li>It's an anatomical abomination; those breasts are a clear example of too much in the worst possible way.</li>
            <li>My stomach churns a bit at the sight; there’s nothing sensual about breasts of that truly disturbing magnitude.</li>
            <li>I feel a strange sense of pity mixed with revulsion when I look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unwieldy chest.</li>
            <li>The outline of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples is barely discernible, lost in the exaggerated flesh; it’s a grotesque detail.</li>
            <li>I prefer a more balanced figure; those enormous breasts throw everything completely out of proportion.</li>
            <li>It's a hard pass from me; those breasts are an overwhelming negative rather than a positive feature.</li>
            <li>My desires simply evaporate when faced with such an unappealing, monstrously oversized chest.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even for a voyeur, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply too immense; their size is more alienating than alluring.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, but the sheer, unwieldy mass of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest offers little satisfying detail.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts hang, heavily and shapelessly, is rather unappealing to my gaze.</li>
            <li>I observe their movement, but it's more like watching a heavy pendulum than something graceful or captivating.</li>
            <li>There's a crude, almost grotesque quality to such extreme proportions; it lacks any subtle visual interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples appear minuscule, almost lost on the vast, overwhelming landscape of {PAWN_possessive} chest.</li>
            <li>My usual curiosity is replaced by a detached assessment of their physical burden; they seem to drag {PAWN_objective} down.</li>
            <li>I scrutinize the form, but it’s so distorted by size that it ceases to be an appealing object of observation.</li>
            <li>The sheer pendulousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is more a cause for concern than a source of intrigue.</li>
            <li>I watch for any delicate details, but they are all swallowed by the overwhelming, almost comical, volume.</li>
            <li>The areolas look painfully stretched, a visible sign of the discomfort caused by such immense breasts.</li>
            <li>It's an extreme, certainly, but one that pushes beyond fascination into the realm of the physically jarring.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers, but finds little to truly savor in the shapeless, overblown expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>They lack the subtle curves and definition that truly capture my interest; these are just... big.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is excessive, almost violent; it feels more like a struggle than a natural movement.</li>
            <li>I seek insight into the human form, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts distort it beyond recognition.</li>
            <li>It's a pity, to have such an overwhelming feature that detracts from the rest of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic tendencies are almost stifled by the sheer, ungraceful magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>They are a testament to anatomical excess, providing little aesthetic pleasure for my detailed observation.</li>
            <li>The skin stretched taut over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts seems almost translucent, a disturbing detail.</li>
            <li>I find no art in such a display, merely a blunt, overwhelming presence that obscures refinement.</li>
            <li>It’s a sight that compels observation, but then quickly releases it due to its utter lack of allure.</li>
            <li>The sheer bulk of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them look less like a body part and more like heavy baggage.</li>
            <li>I prefer seeing a form that implies movement and lightness, not the undeniable drag of those enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts obscure {PAWN_possessive} torso is visually frustrating; it hides too much.</li>
            <li>My interest wanes quickly; there’s only so much shapeless, immense flesh one can observe before growing bored.</li>
            <li>The areolae seem almost too large for the context, drawing attention to the overall disproportionality.</li>
            <li>It's a curiosity, yes, but one rooted in repulsion rather than genuine fascination with the human form.</li>
            <li>I’m observing, but also silently critiquing the burden and ungainliness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>A truly overwhelming spectacle, but one that fails to excite my visual senses in any meaningful way.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My gaze falls upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts, but the sight does nothing for me; my interest shrivels.</li>
            <li>They're so big, they're almost a parody, and my own excitement, if any, is completely drowned out by their sheer scale.</li>
            <li>I'm a voyeur, but even I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts overwhelmingly grotesque, leaving me utterly cold.</li>
            <li>The immense jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is more disturbing than arousing; it’s a repulsive sight.</li>
            <li>My member remains stubbornly limp; there's no allure in such an extreme, unwieldy mass.</li>
            <li>I observe, but only with a detached clinical interest, as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts defy all notions of aesthetic appeal.</li>
            <li>The nipples are tiny points lost on those vast, pendulous breasts; it's a visually upsetting imbalance.</li>
            <li>It's too much, far too much; my natural curiosity is replaced by a sense of morbid fascination.</li>
            <li>I prefer a more… proportionate view; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts are simply overwhelming and unattractive.</li>
            <li>The sight of them makes me feel nothing but a strange revulsion; they look like a physical burden on {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>My gaze is fixed, yes, but on the unfortunate reality of their grotesque size, not their potential for pleasure.</li>
            <li>They lack any delicate form, those breasts; they're just raw, unrefined bulk that kills my desire.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas are stretched over such immense mounds is deeply unappealing.</li>
            <li>I find no thrill in such an exaggerated display; it’s more of an anatomical oddity than an object of lust.</li>
            <li>It's a disfigured beauty, if one can even call it that; the sheer size renders them unsexy.</li>
            <li>My body responds with an uncomfortable silence, no stirrings, just a recognition of unpleasant excess.</li>
            <li>I witness the struggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} movement under the weight of those breasts, and my arousal vanishes.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is an aggressive visual, not an inviting one.</li>
            <li>They are a testament to bad fortune, those breasts; they simply do not appeal to my voyeuristic tastes.</li>
            <li>I look, and I feel a profound sense of disappointment; there is no hidden beauty in such an overt display.</li>
            <li>My mind rejects them as an object of desire; they are simply too large to fit my concept of feminine allure.</li>
            <li>The heavy, almost painful sag of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts leaves me completely unmoved.</li>
            <li>It's an overwhelming sight, but one that fails to ignite any spark within me; it's just... a lot.</li>
            <li>I find myself questioning the very concept of attraction when faced with such an extreme, unappealing form.</li>
            <li>The texture of the skin, stretched by such enormity, is off-putting; it looks unnatural.</li>
            <li>My usual interest in the female form is entirely overridden by the sheer, ungraceful bulk of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>They are a visual challenge, not a pleasure; my eyes constantly search for a more pleasing proportion.</li>
            <li>There's nothing seductive about breasts that look like they're about to burst; it's alarming.</li>
            <li>My fascination with the human body finds no satisfaction in such an exaggerated, almost deformed, chest.</li>
            <li>I'm left with an unsettling feeling, and a complete lack of desire, after observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous breasts.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own breats reaction mention or own genitail vagina reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even as a voyeur, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply too much; their immense size is more repellent than alluring.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, but the overwhelming bulk does little to stir my own desires; my loins remain cold.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is almost grotesque; it detracts from any potential beauty.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers, but it's more out of a clinical curiosity at the extreme rather than genuine interest or arousal.</li>
            <li>They hang so heavily, those breasts, with a shapelessness that offers no aesthetic pleasure to my discerning eye.</li>
            <li>The nipples are nearly swallowed by the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas; it's a disturbing lack of proportion.</li>
            <li>I prefer a more delicate form; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts are simply overwhelming and crude.</li>
            <li>My own breasts, though perhaps smaller, possess a subtle grace entirely absent from this exaggerated display.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is excessive and unappealing; it's a crude movement rather than a tantalizing one.</li>
            <li>It's a sight that leaves me cold; there's no warmth or softness in such an immense, burdensome chest.</li>
            <li>I find myself evaluating the strain on {PAWN_objective}'s back rather than any sensual qualities.</li>
            <li>There's an unfortunate quality to such immense breasts, a burden that overshadows any allure.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts pull {PAWN_objective} down, it’s a visible struggle, not a captivating display.</li>
            <li>My curiosity is piqued, but only to confirm the utter lack of refinement in such overblown proportions.</li>
            <li>They look almost painful, those breasts; the skin seems stretched to its limit.</li>
            <li>I see them, but my inner response is one of aversion, not excitement; they are simply too much.</li>
            <li>Such an extreme size makes them seem less like a part of the body and more like an ungainly attachment.</li>
            <li>My desire for observation is quickly sated by the sheer, ungraceful bulk of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>I look for the subtle details, the delicate curves, but they are all lost in the overwhelming mass.</li>
            <li>There's nothing seductive about a bosom that appears so heavy and cumbersome; it lacks all lightness.</li>
            <li>The areolas are disproportionately large, emphasizing the overall lack of balance in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>It's an anatomical marvel, but not in a desirable way; it's more of a grotesque exaggeration.</li>
            <li>My own body feels a phantom ache just imagining the weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>I prefer a figure that hints at movement and fluidity, not the evident drag of those colossal mounds.</li>
            <li>The sight of them is almost depressing; they seem to diminish {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} entire presence.</li>
            <li>I observe, but with a critical eye; such a size is simply an aesthetic misstep.</li>
            <li>There's no softness to the way they hang, just an undeniable, unappealing heaviness.</li>
            <li>My fascination with the female form finds itself deeply dissatisfied by this extreme and awkward presentation.</li>
            <li>It’s a disservice to {PAWN_nameShort}, those breasts; they detract from {PAWN_possessive} youth and vitality.</li>
            <li>I find them visually exhausting; there's too much to take in, and none of it is truly pleasing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are a bold display, but they lack any artistry; it's just raw, unappealing bulk.</li>
            <li>While I appreciate a good show, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is simply too much, bordering on grotesque; it detracts from the spectacle.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is overwhelming, and not in an exciting way; they look like a burden.</li>
            <li>I observe the display, but find myself cringing at the awkward jiggle and immense pendulousness.</li>
            <li>Such an exaggerated form is less exhibition and more... unfortunate anatomical truth; it lacks grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are almost swallowed by the vastness, diminishing the impact of the exposure.</li>
            <li>I enjoy revealing myself, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so immense, they suggest discomfort, not confidence.</li>
            <li>It's an overt display, but one that evokes pity rather than admiration for the sheer physical struggle.</li>
            <li>The volume is undeniable, but it's a quantity that overwhelms any quality of form or allure.</li>
            <li>I prefer a display that invites the gaze, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so unwieldy, they almost repel it.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas appears stretched and strained; it's not a healthy look for an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>It's a spectacle, yes, but one of anatomical excess rather than artistic revealing.</li>
            <li>My own desire to display is tempered by the sight of such an unmanageable, disproportionate chest.</li>
            <li>They lack any refinement, those breasts; they're simply massive, blunt, and unappealing.</li>
            <li>The heavy sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts is more like a gravitational pull than a captivating movement.</li>
            <li>I expect a show of power or allure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts convey only discomfort and a lack of control.</li>
            <li>They're less an enticing exposure and more a testament to an anatomical burden; it's a hard look.</li>
            <li>The complete lack of subtlety in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes their display almost offensive to my refined tastes.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the raw exposure, but the sheer, unsettling enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is off-putting.</li>
            <li>It’s a display that makes me question my own exhibitionist desires; such a burden is not appealing.</li>
            <li>The nipples are barely visible, lost in the overwhelming bulk, making the display feel incomplete and unsatisfactory.</li>
            <li>There's nothing graceful about such an excessive, almost clumsy, reveal of flesh.</li>
            <li>I look, but find myself more disturbed by the visible strain than excited by the nakedness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply too much; they shout rather than entice, leaving me unmoved.</li>
            <li>The contours are lost in the sheer size, making for a shapeless and unappealing public display.</li>
            <li>I'm drawn to exhibitionism, but not to displays that convey such an obvious sense of physical burden.</li>
            <li>It's a bold choice to expose such a chest, but the result is more jarring than appealing.</li>
            <li>The visible marks of gravity on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts dampen any excitement for their display.</li>
            <li>I prefer a more confident and effortless reveal; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts look like a struggle to carry.</li>
            <li>A truly overwhelming public spectacle, but one that, regrettably, lacks any true allure for my exhibitionist nature.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are a sight, but one that leaves my own desires completely unresponsive; they are too much.</li>
            <li>I enjoy a good reveal, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is so vast, it's more like a grotesque mass than an enticing display.</li>
            <li>My own arousal usually rises with exhibition, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so overwhelming, they kill any spark.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is excessive, almost sickening; there's nothing graceful or appealing about such a burdened display.</li>
            <li>My member remains resolutely soft; there’s no thrill in seeing such an unmanageable, disproportionate bosom.</li>
            <li>I prefer to make a statement with my own body, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so immense, they scream rather than speak.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is an aggressive visual that fails to excite my exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>It’s a spectacle of excess, and not one that inspires me to reveal anything of myself in return.</li>
            <li>The nipples are practically lost in the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas, diminishing the entire presentation.</li>
            <li>I look, but find myself more repulsed by the visible strain and discomfort than thrilled by the nudity.</li>
            <li>There's no art in such an overblown display; it's simply a crude and unappealing revelation of flesh.</li>
            <li>My natural inclination to flaunt is dampened by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unwieldy, burdensome chest.</li>
            <li>The heavy, almost painful sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is far from enticing; it's unsettling.</li>
            <li>I prefer a figure that inspires desire, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts seem designed to extinguish it.</li>
            <li>It's a show, but a poor one; the overwhelming size detracts from any potential allure.</li>
            <li>My own genitals remain unmoved; there is nothing here that sparks the competitive or appreciative spirit of an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts looks stretched and almost raw; it's not a healthy or appealing sight.</li>
            <li>I appreciate boldness, but this is simply clumsy; those breasts are too much for any graceful exhibition.</li>
            <li>The sight makes me cringe, rather than feel empowered to display my own assets.</li>
            <li>It's a testament to unfortunate genetics, those breasts; they lack any sensuality in their enormity.</li>
            <li>I find no satisfaction in observing such an awkward and disproportionate reveal.</li>
            <li>They appear more like heavy weights than alluring parts of the body; it's visually jarring.</li>
            <li>My exhibitionism thrives on an audience's positive reaction; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts would only draw uncomfortable stares.</li>
            <li>The sheer weight implied by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them seem like a physical burden, not a source of pride.</li>
            <li>It's a display that makes me want to avert my eyes, not engage in a mutual showing.</li>
            <li>The outline is simply shapeless, lost in the overwhelming bulk; it's an unappealing form.</li>
            <li>I feel a cold detachment; such an extreme size is simply not what an exhibitionist like me seeks.</li>
            <li>My confidence in my own display is not enhanced by this sight; it's more of a cautionary tale.</li>
            <li>There's nothing provocative about breasts that look like they're struggling to stay attached.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring revelation; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts leave me completely cold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own breats mention, own genitail mentionor, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I enjoy baring myself, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so enormous, they look like a terrible burden, not a source of pride.</li>
            <li>The display is certainly overt, but the overwhelming size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest makes it seem more grotesque than alluring.</li>
            <li>My own breasts, though perhaps smaller, possess a grace entirely absent from this unwieldy, monstrous form.</li>
            <li>The sheer, unrestrained jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is frankly off-putting, not captivating for a mutual show.</li>
            <li>My own genitals remain unresponsive; there's nothing here that speaks to my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I prefer a reveal that hints at power and sensuality, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts convey only discomfort and awkwardness.</li>
            <li>The nipples are almost completely lost in the vastness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas; it's an unfortunate detail.</li>
            <li>It's a display of sheer volume, but one that lacks any aesthetic merit for a discerning exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts looks stretched and almost painful; it's not a look one desires to emulate.</li>
            <li>I appreciate boldness, but this is simply disproportionate; those breasts detract from the entire exhibition.</li>
            <li>The heavy, cumbersome sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is far from an enticing movement; it's jarring.</li>
            <li>My own confidence in my body is not enhanced by seeing such an ungainly, immense chest.</li>
            <li>They seem to fight against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} frame, rather than flow with it; it’s an uncomfortable sight.</li>
            <li>I look for an inspiring display, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts offer only a sobering reminder of physical burden.</li>
            <li>It's a show, but a disappointing one; the extreme size detracts from any potential beauty or power.</li>
            <li>My desire to flaunt my own assets diminishes when faced with such an overwhelming and unappealing sight.</li>
            <li>The areolas are immense and stretched, emphasizing the unfortunate proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>There's nothing graceful or empowering about breasts that appear so heavy and difficult to carry.</li>
            <li>I find no camaraderie in this display; it’s too extreme, too raw, too unappealing.</li>
            <li>The visible marks of gravity and strain on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are far from a source of admiration.</li>
            <li>It's a pity, to have such an overwhelming feature that overshadows any other potential allure {PAWN_pronoun} might possess.</li>
            <li>My own body feels a phantom ache just imagining the burden of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} colossal breasts.</li>
            <li>I prefer a reveal that suggests vitality and joy, not the evident struggle associated with those breasts.</li>
            <li>The complete lack of refined shape in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them an unattractive subject for observation.</li>
            <li>It’s a challenging sight, not a pleasurable one, for an exhibitionist like myself.</li>
            <li>I’m drawn to displays of confidence, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts seem to convey only discomfort.</li>
            <li>The sheer bulk of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is an aggressive visual, rather than an inviting one.</li>
            <li>I find myself evaluating the practicalities of such a chest rather than any erotic qualities.</li>
            <li>Such an exaggerated form, while certainly exposed, lacks any of the subtle provocativeness I seek.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspiring public display; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts leave me utterly unimpressed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Though enormous, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a grotesque sight that completely extinguishes any spark of desire within me.</li>
            <li>My passion usually burns, but the sheer, unwieldy mass of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves me cold and repulsed.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts is so overwhelming, it's a complete turn-off for my desires.</li>
            <li>I seek pleasure, but there's nothing alluring about such an exaggerated, almost deformed, physical burden.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is excessive, almost sickening; it makes me cringe rather than feel aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are lost in the vastness of {PAWN_possessive} breasts, making the entire prospect utterly unappealing.</li>
            <li>My lust recoils from the sheer bulk and lack of grace in such a colossal bosom.</li>
            <li>It's a disfigurement, those breasts, and my nymphomaniac desires find no purchase in such a sight.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas looks stretched and almost painful, killing any desire to touch.</li>
            <li>I crave intimacy, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts seem to defy all natural proportions, making me feel only aversion.</li>
            <li>There's no sensuality in such an overwhelming mass; it's simply a crude, unappealing display.</li>
            <li>My thoughts turn to discomfort and awkwardness, not pleasure, when I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense chest.</li>
            <li>They hang with a heavy, almost dead weight; it’s completely contrary to anything that stirs my passion.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume makes them seem less like breasts and more like two monstrous, unwieldy growths.</li>
            <li>I prefer a body that promises fluidity and embrace, not the obvious burden of those enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>My inner fire is doused by the sight of such an unappealing, disproportionate form.</li>
            <li>The areolas are immense and unnaturally stretched, emphasizing the unsettling scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>It's a repellent display; my nymphomaniac urges are met with nothing but profound distaste.</li>
            <li>I see them, but my mind screams, 'Too much!'; there's no pleasure in such an extreme.</li>
            <li>The lack of delicate contour and shapeliness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them thoroughly unexciting.</li>
            <li>My desire to explore and engage is completely stifled by the grotesque enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>They seem to fight against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} natural figure, creating a jarring and unappealing silhouette.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the discomfort, and that thought alone makes me completely lose interest.</li>
            <li>The visible marks of gravity and strain on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts convey suffering, not eroticism.</li>
            <li>It’s a sight that leaves me cold and profoundly unsatisfied in my pursuit of sensual stimulation.</li>
            <li>There's a vulgarity to such an exaggerated size; it strips away all subtle appeal.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, yes, but only to confirm their utter lack of any appealing quality.</li>
            <li>The thought of interaction with such an unwieldy mass holds absolutely no appeal for my desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a complete anomaly, and one that my nymphomaniac self utterly rejects.</li>
            <li>A truly off-putting sight; my passion curdles in the face of such grotesque proportions.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My natural urges are strong, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are so repulsive, my own member shrivels.</li>
            <li>I burn with desire, but the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} monstrous chest douses any flame, leaving me cold.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is grotesque, a complete turn-off for my nymphomaniac nature.</li>
            <li>My body recoils; there's nothing alluring or exciting about such an exaggerated, unwieldy mass.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is sickening, not sensual; it makes me feel nauseous rather than aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are tiny points lost on those vast, pendulous breasts; it's a visual abomination.</li>
            <li>I crave release, but looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fills me only with profound revulsion and discomfort.</li>
            <li>It’s a deformity, those breasts, and my powerful urges are utterly extinguished by their unappealing form.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas looks painfully stretched, making me avert my gaze in distaste.</li>
            <li>I desire pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts defy all natural proportions, making my member go completely limp.</li>
            <li>There's no sensuality in such an overwhelming display; it's crude, unrefined, and deeply unattractive.</li>
            <li>My thoughts turn to practical logistics and physical burden, not carnal delights, when I see that chest.</li>
            <li>They hang with an oppressive, almost dead weight; it’s completely contrary to anything that stirs my passion.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume makes them seem less like breasts and more like two grotesque, unyielding growths.</li>
            <li>I want to engage, but the obvious strain on {PAWN_objective} and the unappealing form of those breasts stop me dead.</li>
            <li>My inner fire is completely doused by the sight of such an unwieldy, disproportionate form; there's no igniting it.</li>
            <li>The areolas are immense and unnaturally distended, emphasizing the unsettling scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>It's a repellent display; my powerful nymphomaniac urges are met with nothing but profound distaste.</li>
            <li>I see them, but my mind screams, 'No! Too much!'; there's no pleasure, only an uncomfortable visual.</li>
            <li>The lack of delicate contour and shapeliness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them thoroughly unexciting, even for me.</li>
            <li>My desire to approach and explore is completely stifled by the grotesque enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>They appear to fight against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} natural figure, creating a jarring and unappealing silhouette.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the discomfort, and that thought alone makes my loins ache in the worst way.</li>
            <li>The visible marks of gravity and strain on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts convey suffering, not eroticism, for my urges.</li>
            <li>It’s a sight that leaves me cold and profoundly unsatisfied in my pursuit of sensual stimulation.</li>
            <li>There's a vulgarity to such an exaggerated size; it strips away all subtle appeal, even for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, yes, but only to confirm their utter lack of any appealing quality to my desires.</li>
            <li>The thought of interaction with such an unwieldy mass holds absolutely no appeal for my insatiable urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a complete anomaly, and one that my nymphomaniac self utterly rejects as an object of desire.</li>
            <li>A truly off-putting sight; my passion curdles in the face of such grotesque proportions, leaving me cold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own breats reaction  mention, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My desires are usually insatiable, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts are so grotesque, they utterly repel me.</li>
            <li>I burn with internal fire, yet the sheer, unwieldy mass of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves my own body unresponsive and cold.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is so overwhelming, it's a complete turn-off for my every nymphomaniac urge.</li>
            <li>I seek connection and pleasure, but there's nothing alluring about such an exaggerated, almost deformed, physical burden.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is excessive, almost sickening; it makes my stomach clench rather than my loins stir.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are tiny points lost on those vast, pendulous breasts; it's a visual abomination.</li>
            <li>My craving for intimacy recoils from the sheer bulk and lack of grace in such a colossal bosom.</li>
            <li>It’s a disfigurement, those breasts, and my powerful desires find no purchase in such a sight; my own core remains unfeeling.</li>
            <li>The skin around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} areolas looks painfully stretched, killing any desire to engage or touch.</li>
            <li>I desire pleasure, but {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts defy all natural proportions, leaving my own female parts utterly cold.</li>
            <li>There's no sensuality in such an overwhelming mass; it's simply a crude, unappealing display that I reject.</li>
            <li>My thoughts turn to discomfort and awkwardness, not pleasure, when I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} immense chest.</li>
            <li>They hang with a heavy, almost dead weight; it’s completely contrary to anything that stirs my passion or my own body.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume makes them seem less like breasts and more like two monstrous, unwieldy growths.</li>
            <li>I prefer a body that promises fluidity and embrace, not the obvious burden of those enormous breasts; it's uninspiring.</li>
            <li>My inner fire is completely doused by the sight of such an unappealing, disproportionate form; there's no igniting it.</li>
            <li>The areolas are immense and unnaturally distended, emphasizing the unsettling scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>It's a repellent display; my powerful nymphomaniac urges are met with nothing but profound distaste and disinterest.</li>
            <li>I see them, but my mind screams, 'No! Too much!'; there's no pleasure, only an uncomfortable visual.</li>
            <li>The lack of delicate contour and shapeliness in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them thoroughly unexciting, even for me.</li>
            <li>My desire to connect and engage is completely stifled by the grotesque enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>They appear to fight against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} natural figure, creating a jarring and unappealing silhouette.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the discomfort {PAWN_pronoun} feels, and that thought alone makes my own body ache in sympathy.</li>
            <li>The visible marks of gravity and strain on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts convey suffering, not eroticism, for my urges.</li>
            <li>It’s a sight that leaves me cold and profoundly unsatisfied in my pursuit of sensual stimulation.</li>
            <li>There's a vulgarity to such an exaggerated size; it strips away all subtle appeal, even for a nymphomaniac like me.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to them, yes, but only to confirm their utter lack of any appealing quality to my desires.</li>
            <li>The thought of interaction with such an unwieldy mass holds absolutely no appeal for my insatiable urges or my body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a complete anomaly, and one that my nymphomaniac self utterly rejects as an object of desire.</li>
            <li>A truly off-putting sight; my passion curdles in the face of such grotesque proportions, leaving me completely cold.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Oh dear, those breasts look incredibly uncomfortable for {PAWN_nameShort}, I truly hope {PAWN_pronoun} isn't in pain.</li>
            <li>My heart goes out to {PAWN_nameShort}; carrying such enormous breasts must be a tremendous burden.</li>
            <li>It’s a shame, such a young person struggling with what appears to be a very heavy, unwieldy chest.</li>
            <li>I worry for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} comfort; those breasts look far too large for {PAWN_possessive} frame.</li>
            <li>I can’t help but notice the visible strain; I hope {PAWN_pronoun} finds ways to alleviate the discomfort.</li>
            <li>They appear so disproportionate, I feel a pang of sympathy for {PAWN_nameShort} and the challenges {PAWN_pronoun} must face.</li>
            <li>Such immense breasts must be difficult to live with; I genuinely hope {PAWN_objective} isn't suffering.</li>
            <li>I wish {PAWN_nameShort} didn't have to carry such a heavy burden; those breasts seem unwieldy.</li>
            <li>It's a sight that makes me feel concern rather than anything else; those breasts look genuinely cumbersome.</li>
            <li>The way they sag, it suggests constant discomfort; I truly feel for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I hope {PAWN_nameShort} is able to manage the physical demands of such an enormous chest without too much pain.</li>
            <li>It’s a pity to see someone so young burdened by what appears to be a significant physical impediment.</li>
            <li>My first thought is for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-being; those breasts look overwhelmingly heavy.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the challenges {PAWN_pronoun} faces daily due to the sheer size of {PAWN_possessive} chest.</li>
            <li>They seem to pull {PAWN_objective} down; I hope {PAWN_pronoun} receives the support {PAWN_pronoun} needs.</li>
            <li>The appearance of strain around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes me feel a deep sense of compassion.</li>
            <li>It must be difficult to move freely with such immense breasts; I feel bad for {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>I worry that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts might cause {PAWN_objective} health issues in the future due to their size.</li>
            <li>My concern outweighs any other observation; those breasts seem like a constant source of discomfort for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I hope {PAWN_nameShort} has good support garments; carrying those breasts must be exhausting.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts truly looks like a physical burden {PAWN_pronoun} has to contend with.</li>
            <li>It’s hard to focus on anything but the apparent difficulty {PAWN_nameShort} faces with such a chest.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong sense of empathy; those breasts look very heavy and perhaps even painful.</li>
            <li>My kind nature makes me wish {PAWN_nameShort} didn’t have to bear such a disproportionate weight.</li>
            <li>I hope {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts don't cause {PAWN_objective} too much trouble in {PAWN_possessive} daily life.</li>
            <li>It’s a truly challenging feature to live with, those enormous breasts; I sincerely hope {PAWN_pronoun} is okay.</li>
            <li>The way they hang so heavily makes me concerned for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posture and long-term health.</li>
            <li>I find myself wishing {PAWN_nameShort} could be more comfortable; those breasts look like a significant hindrance.</li>
            <li>My kind heart aches a little at the thought of the burden {PAWN_nameShort} carries with those breasts.</li>
            <li>I hope {PAWN_nameShort} finds strength and peace despite the challenges posed by {PAWN_possessive} enormous breasts.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Those enormous breasts are utterly vulgar, an offensive display of anatomical excess that is simply disgusting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is a monumental affront to decency; such an unwieldy size is simply unseemly.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be a grotesque exaggeration, a display of shocking immodesty.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of those breasts is repugnant; it's a crude, unrefined spectacle.</li>
            <li>Honestly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so massive, it’s almost sickening; utterly distasteful and inappropriate.</li>
            <li>The way they jiggle and sway is disgusting, lacking any decorum or self-respect.</li>
            <li>I cannot fathom why anyone would choose to display such an obscene amount of flesh; it's repulsive.</li>
            <li>Such extreme proportions are an abomination; they're an ugly, unappealing burden.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are practically swallowed by the vastness; it’s just a shapeless, unappealing mass.</li>
            <li>It’s a clear sign of poor taste and a lack of self-awareness to parade such a monstrous chest.</li>
            <li>The skin stretched taut over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts looks painful and raw; it’s frankly disturbing.</li>
            <li>I'm disgusted by the visible strain and the general ungracefulness of those enormous breasts.</li>
            <li>This kind of overt display of immense breasts is exactly what's wrong with people; it lacks all modesty.</li>
            <li>They're less breasts and more unidentifiable sacks of flesh; truly an offensive sight.</li>
            <li>I recoil from the sheer bulk and vulgarity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest; it’s an eyesore.</li>
            <li>It’s a clear indication of a complete lack of class and self-restraint to have such a prominent and unwieldy feature.</li>
            <li>The very sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes me feel uncomfortable and deeply judgmental.</li>
            <li>There's nothing appealing about an anatomical anomaly that screams for attention in such a crude way.</li>
            <li>I can't believe {PAWN_pronoun} is brazen enough to display such an exaggerated, almost deformed, set of breasts.</li>
            <li>It's a crude, lumbering display that lacks any form or subtlety; it’s utterly offensive.</li>
            <li>The areolas look immense and out of place, emphasizing the overall lack of proportion and decency.</li>
            <li>Those breasts are a clear reflection of a lack of refinement and an unsettling disregard for appropriateness.</li>
            <li>I find them thoroughly unappealing, a clumsy and oversized appendage rather than a graceful part of the body.</li>
            <li>The sheer weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them look utterly burdensome and unattractive.</li>
            <li>It’s an affront to my sensibilities; such an overt and enormous display of flesh is simply unacceptable.</li>
            <li>I wish {PAWN_nameShort} would cover up; those breasts are far too prominent and distasteful.</li>
            <li>There's nothing redeemable about such a massive, sagging form; it’s just plain ugly.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts move is jarring, almost violent, and incredibly unbecoming.</li>
            <li>I cannot stand the sight of such an exaggerated chest; it’s a constant source of irritation.</li>
            <li>A truly repellent display; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} enormous breasts leave me feeling nothing but contempt.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Negative_Enormous_SlimeBreasts</defName>
        <label>Enormous Breasts (Negative)_SlimeBreasts</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeBreasts</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These truly colossal slime breasts are an abomination, their obscene size and ungainly presence creating a deeply repulsive, disfigured appearance.</li>
            <li>The unimaginable scale and violently sluggish movement create a monstrous display of unnatural bulk and vile flaccidity.</li>
            <li>They possess nauseating fullness and crushing weight, speaking volumes of immense, grotesque abundance, unwieldy and revolting.</li>
            <li>Such gargantuan, flabby breasts exude sickening sliminess, appearing designed to hang, drip, and ooze, promising profound discomfort and visceral aversion.</li>
            <li>The absurd, cosmic enormity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts is a terrifying deformity, their fluid sag defies comprehension.</li>
            <li>These impossibly ample, bursting slime breasts boast obscenely repulsive roundness and disturbingly squishy texture, resistibly unalluring despite disgusting presence.</li>
            <li>They feel profoundly resilient yet offensively yielding, a disorienting combination of firmness and immense pliancy threatening to engulf repulsively.</li>
            <li>I'm repulsed by the powerful, violently revolting undulations of their unimaginable mass, a nauseating, terrifying display of abhorrent motion.</li>
            <li>Their gargantuan, monstrous proportions are an affront, creating sickening excess and a form so bountiful it's primally unappealing.</li>
            <li>These breasts stand as a monumental testament to excess and decay, embodying raw, untamed ugliness, powerfully repulsive.</li>
            <li>The intense clamminess they emanate, combined with their suffocating presence, makes them unwelcoming, promising discomfort and dread.</li>
            <li>They exude grotesque, decadent lavishness, their bursting curves presenting unparalleled ugliness and horrifying unsightliness.</li>
            <li>I find their terrifying, disgusting size dominant, yet softened by sickening pliancy, making them ill-advisedly approachable.</li>
            <li>Each breast appears as a titanic, glistening orb of liquid repulsion and oozing decay, pulsing with unsettling life.</li>
            <li>Their full, rounded, spherical, yet sagging silhouette is unappealing, promising an unsatisfying, repulsive tactile experience.</li>
            <li>These massive, grotesque slime breasts possess unsettling, malevolent energy, hinting at a disturbing living essence within their vast depths.</li>
            <li>They are shaped to engulf, offering overwhelming security, their immense size providing terrifying, suffocating comfort.</li>
            <li>The way they pull clothing, or rest bare, is unappealing, powerfully highlighting their shocking, sickening presence and weight.</li>
            <li>I'm drawn into the mesmerizing, disturbing churning of their viscous, putrid matter, revealing complex, utterly disgusting nature.</li>
            <li>These breasts embody primal, overwhelming grotesqueness, a testament to obscene sensuality demanding unyielding surrender.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>