<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_PositiveDef">
		<defName>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_(Positive)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                <requiredObservedDressState>Naked</requiredObservedDressState>
				<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredPawnState>Asleep</requiredPawnState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<!-- Existing -->
			<li>I stole a glance at {OBSERVED_nameShort}, sleeping unclothed, {OBSERVED_possessive} manhood and anus exposed in the dim light, leaving me with a mix of shock and intrigue.</li>
			<li>As I entered the room, my eyes fell upon {OBSERVED_nameShort}, sprawled naked on the bed, {OBSERVED_possessive} private parts in full view, stirring a forbidden desire within me.</li>
			<li>In the midst of the night, I caught sight of {OBSERVED_nameShort}, slumbering naked, {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus evident, and I couldn't look away, consumed by a lewd curiosity.</li>
			<li>I found {OBSERVED_nameShort} asleep, {OBSERVED_possessive} nudity on display, {OBSERVED_possessive} manhood and anus unhidden, and I felt a strange allure, a lewd fascination.</li>
			<li>In the quiet of the room, I saw {OBSERVED_nameShort}, naked and vulnerable, {OBSERVED_possessive} private parts exposed, and I was hit with a wave of lewd thoughts, a tantalizing image.</li>
			<li>I chanced upon {OBSERVED_nameShort}, in the throes of sleep, {OBSERVED_possessive} body bare, {OBSERVED_possessive} manhood and anus visible, and I was filled with a lewd longing, a lustful attraction.</li>
			<!-- New -->
			<li>There {OBSERVED_pronoun} was, a picture of masculine vulnerability. The sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} relaxed penis and the hint of {OBSERVED_possessive} anus was surprisingly potent.</li>
			<li>My gaze lingered on {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} sleeping form. The powerful lines of {OBSERVED_possessive} body were impressive, but the sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed genitals was what truly captured my attention.</li>
			<li>A thrill went through me seeing {OBSERVED_nameShort} so completely bare. {OBSERVED_possessive} cock lay soft against {OBSERVED_possessive} thigh, a promise of the power it held when awake.</li>
			<li>I felt a magnetic pull towards the sight of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked body. The raw, masculine energy was palpable, even in sleep.</li>
			<li>The view was incredible. {OBSERVED_nameShort}, lost to the world, {OBSERVED_possessive} entire body on display, from {OBSERVED_possessive} muscled chest down to {OBSERVED_possessive} heavy balls.</li>
			<li>I couldn't help but admire the view. {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} nakedness was a bold statement, and the sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} limp dick was strangely endearing.</li>
			<li>A wave of heat washed over me. Seeing {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} penis and the dark crease of {OBSERVED_possessive} anus so openly displayed sparked my imagination.</li>
			<li>It was a feast for the eyes. {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} powerful physique, combined with the intimacy of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed genitals, was a potent combination.</li>
			<li>My heart hammered in my chest. To see {OBSERVED_nameShort} so unguarded, {OBSERVED_possessive} cock and balls just resting there, was an intensely private and arousing moment.</li>
			<li>I was fascinated by the sight. The contrast between {OBSERVED_possessive} peaceful, sleeping face and the raw masculinity of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed lower body was captivating.</li>
			<li>{OBSERVED_nameShort} slept like a fallen god, {OBSERVED_possessive} nakedness only adding to {OBSERVED_possessive} mystique. I found myself staring at the curve of {OBSERVED_possessive} ass and the treasure it hid.</li>
			<li>The air crackled with a forbidden energy. {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked, sleeping form was a temptation I found difficult to resist.</li>
			<li>I felt a primal urge looking at {OBSERVED_nameShort}. The sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed manhood was a powerful reminder of our basic natures.</li>
			<li>What a magnificent sight. A man of {OBSERVED_ageBiologicalYears} in {OBSERVED_possessive} prime, completely nude and at ease. It was something to be appreciated.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>
	
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_NeutralDef">
		<defName>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_Neutral</defName>
        <label>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_(Neutral)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                <requiredObservedDressState>Naked</requiredObservedDressState>
				<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredPawnState>Asleep</requiredPawnState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<!-- Existing -->
			<li>As I walked in, my gaze fell upon {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} sleeping form, {OBSERVED_possessive} naked body splayed out on the bed, {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus visible in the dim light, and I felt a fleeting sense of indifference, my mind barely registering the sight.</li>
			<li>I noticed {OBSERVED_nameShort} was sleeping naked, {OBSERVED_possessive} body exposed to the cooling air, {OBSERVED_possessive} penis flaccid and {OBSERVED_possessive} anus relaxed, and I shrugged it off, my attention already wandering to other matters.</li>
			<li>My eyes drifted over {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} sleeping form, taking in the contours of {OBSERVED_possessive} naked body, the curve of {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and the shape of {OBSERVED_possessive} anus, and I felt nothing but a mild curiosity, not enough to stir any real interest.</li>
			<li>As I stood there, I caught a glimpse of {OBSERVED_possessive} naked body, {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus visible in the shadows, and I thought to myself, 'Oh, {OBSERVED_pronoun} is sleeping naked again,' with all the emotional resonance of a passing thought.</li>
			<li>I saw {OBSERVED_nameShort} sleeping naked, {OBSERVED_possessive} body exposed and vulnerable, and yet I felt no spark of arousal or embarrassment, just a dull awareness of the fact, like noting the time on a clock.</li>
			<li>My gaze grazed over {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked form, taking in the sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus with the same level of interest I'd accord a familiar landscape, and I moved on, my mind already engaged with other thoughts.</li>
			<!-- New -->
			<li>I saw {OBSERVED_nameShort} sleeping without clothes. I registered the presence of {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus and then went about my day.</li>
			<li>{OBSERVED_nameShort} was asleep and completely unclothed. I noted the anatomical details of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed body without any particular reaction.</li>
			<li>It was clear that {OBSERVED_nameShort} was sleeping nude. I saw {OBSERVED_possessive} genitals. It was a simple observation.</li>
			<li>I happened upon {OBSERVED_nameShort} sleeping naked. My brain processed the visual data of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed body parts and filed it under 'unimportant'.</li>
			<li>The subject, {OBSERVED_nameShort}, was observed sleeping in a state of full nudity. No further thoughts on the matter.</li>
			<li>I glanced over and saw {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked body. Penis, anus, the usual parts. I didn't give it a second thought.</li>
			<li>My observation: {OBSERVED_nameShort} is asleep and naked. The sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} private areas elicited no emotional response.</li>
			<li>There was {OBSERVED_nameShort}, nude. I saw what I saw and my mind had already moved on to inventory management.</li>
			<li>A brief look confirmed that {OBSERVED_nameShort} was sleeping without any clothes on. I acknowledged this fact and continued on my way.</li>
			<li>The state of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} dress, or lack thereof, was noted. {OBSERVED_pronoun} was naked. That's all there is to say.</li>
			<li>I saw {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} penis and anus because {OBSERVED_pronoun} was sleeping naked. It was a neutral event.</li>
			<li>It seems to be {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} preference to sleep in the buff. I saw everything. It didn't stir me one way or the other.</li>
			<li>I registered that {OBSERVED_nameShort} was unclothed. The visual of {OBSERVED_possessive} naked body was processed and dismissed.</li>
			<li>I witnessed {OBSERVED_nameShort} sleeping in a state of nature. It was neither interesting nor disturbing.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>
	
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_NegativeDef">
		<defName>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>iSaw_sleeping_naked_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                <requiredObservedDressState>Naked</requiredObservedDressState>
				<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredPawnState>Asleep</requiredPawnState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<!-- Existing -->
			<li>As I entered the room, I was confronted with the unsettling sight of {OBSERVED_nameShort}, sprawled out naked on the bed, {OBSERVED_possessive} penis and anus blatantly exposed, a wave of annoyance washing over me.</li>
			<li>I couldn't help but notice with irritation as I walked in, finding {OBSERVED_nameShort} fast asleep in the nude, {OBSERVED_possessive} genitals and anus carelessly on display.</li>
			<li>The annoyance simmered within me as I stumbled upon {OBSERVED_nameShort}, lying bare-skinned, {OBSERVED_possessive} private parts brazenly visible, a disturbing sight that I could not unsee.</li>
			<li>I was met with a sight that stirred up a storm of annoyance within me - {OBSERVED_nameShort}, exposed and vulnerable in {OBSERVED_possessive} sleep, {OBSERVED_possessive} intimate areas in plain view.</li>
			<li>As I cautiously approached, I was taken aback by the sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} naked form, {OBSERVED_possessive} genitalia and anus glaringly obvious, fueling my irritation.</li>
			<li>A surge of annoyance flooded through me as I witnessed {OBSERVED_nameShort}, completely stripped, {OBSERVED_possessive} privates openly visible, a most unwelcome sight.</li>
			<!-- New -->
			<li>Ugh, does {OBSERVED_pronoun} have to sleep like that? Seeing {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} shriveled penis and hairy ass was just plain nasty.</li>
			<li>I was disgusted. {OBSERVED_nameShort} was lying there, completely naked, with all {OBSERVED_possessive} bits hanging out. It was a crude and unpleasant display.</li>
			<li>What a lack of decency. To just lie there, naked for anyone to see... it's just sloppy and inconsiderate.</li>
			<li>The sight was repulsive. {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} limp junk and exposed backside... I wish I could scrub the image from my brain.</li>
			<li>I felt my lip curl in distaste. The sight of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked, sleeping body was an offense to common decency.</li>
			<li>It was just... sad. A grown man of {OBSERVED_ageBiologicalYears}, sprawled out naked like some kind of animal. I quickly looked away.</li>
			<li>I was immediately annoyed by the sight. Put some damn clothes on, {OBSERVED_nameShort}! Nobody wants to see all that.</li>
			<li>The image of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} flaccid manhood was not something I needed in my life. It was a thoroughly unappealing sight.</li>
			<li>I found the sight of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} nakedness to be deeply unsettling. It felt like a violation of my personal space.</li>
			<li>There's no reason for that kind of display. {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} carelessness about {OBSERVED_possessive} nudity is a sign of a weak character.</li>
			<li>I was confronted by the sight of {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} entire naked body, and I felt nothing but irritation. Have some shame.</li>
			<li>It was a graceless and vulgar scene. {OBSERVED_nameShort}, asleep and naked, was not a sight for sore eyes. Quite the opposite.</li>
			<li>I saw {OBSERVED_nameShortPossessive} naked form and was filled with a sense of unease. It was an unwelcome and jarring thing to witness.</li>
			<li>The casual nudity was off-putting. The sight of {OBSERVED_possessive} exposed genitals made me feel uncomfortable and a little bit sick.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>
</Defs>
