<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her flat chest, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These flat, uninspiring breasts offer no pleasure, just a dull ache of yearning. My nipples, too small and unresponsive, feel utterly useless.</li>
            <li>My chest feels like a barren landscape, utterly devoid of the fullness I crave. These sad nipples refuse to respond, making my horniness a torment.</li>
            <li>I hate how flat and unremarkable my breasts are, especially when I'm this horny. My nipples are barely noticeable, failing to invite any touch.</li>
            <li>This desire burns, yet my flat chest provides no comfort. My unaroused nipples just emphasize the profound lack, a cruel joke.</li>
            <li>Such a pathetic, flat chest. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel anything, deepening my frustration and desire for something more.</li>
            <li>My breasts are so flat, they offer nothing to stir my senses, making this horniness a purely mental agony.</li>
            <li>These unyielding, flat breasts are a constant reminder of what I lack. My nipples, small and cold, do nothing for my intense need.</li>
            <li>Horny and disheartened, my flat chest feels utterly insignificant. These unyielding nipples only amplify my disappointment.</li>
            <li>This flat canvas offers no arousal, only a dull frustration. My tiny nipples remain stubbornly flaccid, mocking my yearning.</li>
            <li>How can I be this horny with such an unappealing, flat chest? My unresponsive nipples make everything feel worse.</li>
            <li>My flat breasts feel so inadequate, especially with this overpowering desire. My small, unresponsive nipples are a constant source of irritation.</li>
            <li>I feel so much longing, yet my chest is a flat, uninspiring expanse. My nipples simply refuse to respond to my need.</li>
            <li>These flat breasts are just dead weight, offering no comfort to my aroused state. My nipples are non-existent, making this feeling unbearable.</li>
            <li>My chest is a wasteland of sensation. These flat breasts and unresponsive nipples only deepen my horny despair.</li>
            <li>The intense horniness clashes sharply with my flat, unstimulating breasts. My nipples are nothing but a disappointment.</li>
            <li>Feeling this horny with such a flat chest is torturous. My nipples offer no pleasure, just a dull, unfulfilled ache.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel so utterly unappealing, flat and lifeless. Even my nipples seem to mock my desperate, horny state.</li>
            <li>I wish these flat breasts would swell, or my nipples would harden, but they remain stubbornly unresponsive to my intense horniness.</li>
            <li>A crushing wave of horniness, met only by the dismal reality of my flat chest. My nipples are just dots, refusing to react.</li>
            <li>These flat breasts offer no warmth, no response to my burning desire. My nipples are cold, unwilling to join the sensation.</li>
            <li>My flat chest just reinforces my insecurity, especially now, full of desire. My small nipples remain entirely unmoved.</li>
            <li>I yearn for touch, but these flat breasts are so uninviting. My nipples are too timid to respond to my horny longing.</li>
            <li>This intense horniness feels wasted on my flat chest and its utterly unresponsive nipples. It’s infuriating.</li>
            <li>The flatness of my breasts is a torment when I'm this horny. My nipples are just sad little bumps, without sensation.</li>
            <li>My flat chest offers no joy, no thrill. My nipples are useless in this state of burning desire.</li>
            <li>I'm so horny, but my breasts are a pathetic, flat sight. My nipples, stubbornly soft, add to my frustration.</li>
            <li>These flat breasts feel like a betrayal when my body is craving so much. My nipples refuse to acknowledge my arousal.</li>
            <li>My desire is a fire, but my flat chest is like damp wood, and my nipples are cold stone. It's truly disappointing.</li>
            <li>This unyielding flatness in my chest is deeply upsetting. My nipples are unresponsive, leaving me desperate for more.</li>
            <li>I'm brimming with horniness, but my flat, unstimulating breasts and dull nipples offer no path to satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her tiny breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My tiny breasts offer little to stir my desire, and my nipples are barely there, mocking this intense horniness.</li>
            <li>These pitifully small breasts feel utterly inadequate for my current needs. My nipples remain soft, denying any satisfying sensation.</li>
            <li>I feel so much desire, yet my breasts are just tiny mounds. My areolas are barely visible, making me feel so unappealing.</li>
            <li>This horniness is a torment, amplified by my minuscule breasts. Their shape is uninspiring, and my nipples refuse to firm up.</li>
            <li>My tiny chest feels utterly useless in this horny state. The nipples are too small to respond properly, making me feel frustrated.</li>
            <li>Such small breasts, and my body is screaming for satisfaction. They feel like a child's, not a woman's.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts offer no thrill. My nipples, so small and unyielding, are a source of endless disappointment when I'm this aroused.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by desire, but these tiny breasts are doing nothing. They refuse to respond, making my mood sour.</li>
            <li>My breasts are barely there, and I feel so much yearning. The shape is just sad, and my nipples are totally unresponsive.</li>
            <li>How can I feel so horny with breasts this small? My areolas are barely noticeable, and my nipples just don't react.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts feel pathetic. My nipples refuse to harden, even with this burning desire. It's truly frustrating.</li>
            <li>My desire burns, but my tiny breasts are a pathetic sight. Their lack of response makes me feel utterly undesirable.</li>
            <li>I yearn for fullness, but these tiny breasts are a cruel joke. My nipples are too small to even feel.</li>
            <li>This horniness highlights the insignificance of my tiny breasts. My areolas are almost invisible, further dampening my spirits.</li>
            <li>Such an intense need, yet my breasts are so minute. Their shape is unremarkable, and my nipples are completely unfeeling.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts are a constant reminder of what I'm missing. My nipples, so small, refuse to swell with desire.</li>
            <li>I feel nothing but dissatisfaction from these tiny breasts. My areolas are pale, and my nipples offer no sensation.</li>
            <li>This horniness is overwhelming, but my breasts are so insubstantial. Their behavior is stagnant, not responding to my inner fire.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are a source of profound disappointment. My nipples, always soft, make me feel less desirable.</li>
            <li>These tiny mounds do nothing to fuel my desire. My areolas are too small, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>I'm so horny, but my breasts are like pebbles. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are stubbornly flat.</li>
            <li>My pathetic tiny breasts offer no comfort. My nipples feel numb, and my desire intensifies, but without relief.</li>
            <li>This desire feels wasted on my tiny, unyielding breasts. My areolas are barely there, and my nipples are too small.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my tiny breasts in this horny state is immense. My nipples remain stubbornly soft and unreactive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are just so small, it kills my mood when I'm like this. My nipples refuse to do anything at all.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts are a burden. My areolas are barely pigmented, and my nipples offer no pleasure whatsoever.</li>
            <li>I hate how tiny my breasts are, especially when I crave so much. My nipples feel completely dead to touch.</li>
            <li>My horniness is powerful, but these tiny breasts are utterly weak. Their form is uninspiring, and my nipples are so small.</li>
            <li>My chest feels so empty, despite this intense desire. These tiny breasts and unresponsive nipples are deeply upsetting.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by horniness, yet my tiny breasts are doing nothing for me. My nipples remain flaccid and unimpressive.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her small breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My small breasts feel insufficient for this raw desire, their shape so ordinary. My nipples barely respond, increasing my frustration.</li>
            <li>This horniness is intense, yet my small, uninspiring breasts offer little. Their behavior is sluggish, and my nipples stay soft.</li>
            <li>I wish my breasts were fuller; these small ones do not satisfy my horny mood. My areolas look dull, and nipples are unaroused.</li>
            <li>Small and unremarkable, my breasts feel so inadequate in this state of yearning. My nipples are unwilling to harden, a true disappointment.</li>
            <li>Feeling this horny with such modest breasts is a torment. They just hang there, and my nipples refuse to perk up.</li>
            <li>My small breasts offer no comfort, only a painful reminder of what I lack. My areolas are barely noticeable, killing my mood.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are such a letdown; their shape is so plain. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, denying any pleasure.</li>
            <li>I'm so horny, but my small breasts are doing nothing for me. They lack volume, and my nipples are entirely unresponsive.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel cold and distant despite my intense need. Their behavior is limp, and my areolas seem lifeless.</li>
            <li>How can I feel so much desire when my breasts are so underwhelming? My nipples are just flat, nothing to thrill.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are utterly unsatisfying. Their form is unimpressive, and my nipples refuse to swell or harden.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels wasted on these small, unyielding breasts. My areolas are too small, and my nipples are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I long for more, but these small breasts are all I have. Their behavior is dull, and my nipples offer no sensation.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my small breasts during this horny phase is immense. My areolas are pale, and my nipples offer no delight.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are a source of constant irritation. Their shape is boring, and my nipples refuse to react to my touch.</li>
            <li>Feeling this aroused, but my small breasts just sit there, lifeless. My nipples are too timid to truly respond.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are a poor match for my fiery desire. Their behavior is passive, and my areolas are unappealing.</li>
            <li>I'm intensely horny, yet my small breasts offer no visual or tactile appeal. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, crushing my mood.</li>
            <li>My breasts are simply too small, too ordinary. My nipples are tiny and unreactive, making this desire feel pointless.</li>
            <li>These small breasts feel like a child's, not a woman's full of desire. My areolas are barely visible, and nipples are a non-event.</li>
            <li>The slightness of my breasts is so frustrating when I'm this horny. My nipples are unimpressive, failing to ignite any passion.</li>
            <li>My small breasts just highlight how unfulfilled I feel. Their shape is boring, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft and pale.</li>
            <li>I despise how small my breasts are. They offer no bounce, no thrill, and my nipples are numb to this burning desire.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are a constant disappointment. Their behavior is flaccid, and my areolas are too faint, making me self-conscious.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels amplified by the inadequacy of my small breasts. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel them.</li>
            <li>Such a powerful urge, yet my small breasts are so unyielding. Their lack of response is truly disheartening.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel like a pathetic offering to my intense desire. My nipples are just dots, refusing to respond.</li>
            <li>The mood is ruined by these small, unexciting breasts. My areolas are too light, and my nipples are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I wish for more substance, but these small breasts are all I have. My nipples are stubbornly soft, killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>My small breasts offer no escape from this frustrating horniness. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are a true letdown.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her average breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My average breasts feel so unexciting, barely reacting to my intense horniness. Their shape is just… meh, and my nipples are dull.</li>
            <li>This desire burns, but my average breasts offer no thrill. They lack the jiggliness I crave, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft.</li>
            <li>I'm horny, yet these ordinary breasts are unresponsive. Their behavior is lackluster, and my areolas blend in, offering no visual interest.</li>
            <li>Average breasts are a disappointment when I yearn for passion. My nipples don't perk up, making my mood plummet further.</li>
            <li>These breasts are just so plain; they don't enhance my horniness at all. Their movement is minimal, and my nipples feel numb.</li>
            <li>My breasts are utterly unremarkable, refusing to swell or tease with this burning desire. Their blandness is depressing.</li>
            <li>Such an intense need, yet my average breasts are just… there. Their shape is forgettable, and my nipples are completely unreactive.</li>
            <li>I feel so much desire, but my breasts are so ordinary. Their lack of jiggliness and unresponsive nipples kill my mood.</li>
            <li>These average breasts are a constant reminder of how unexceptional I feel. My areolas are too pale, and nipples offer no joy.</li>
            <li>How can I be this horny with such uninspiring breasts? Their behavior is dull, and my nipples refuse to become firm.</li>
            <li>My average breasts are a total letdown. Their form is boring, and my nipples are stubbornly soft despite my arousal.</li>
            <li>This horniness feels wasted on my utterly unremarkable breasts. Their lack of response makes me feel truly unattractive.</li>
            <li>I long for more excitement, but my average breasts are doing nothing. Their movement is limp, and my nipples are flat.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my average breasts during this horny phase is immense. My areolas are bland, and my nipples remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are so average, it just drains my mood. Their shape is boring, and my nipples offer no sensation, no thrill.</li>
            <li>Feeling this aroused, but my average breasts just lie there, lifeless. My nipples are too timid to truly respond.</li>
            <li>These average breasts are a poor match for my fiery desire. Their behavior is passive, and my areolas are unappealing.</li>
            <li>I'm intensely horny, yet my average breasts offer no visual or tactile appeal. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, crushing my mood.</li>
            <li>My breasts are simply too average, too ordinary. My nipples are tiny and unreactive, making this desire feel pointless.</li>
            <li>These average mounds do nothing to fuel my desire. My areolas are too small, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>The blandness of my breasts is so frustrating when I'm this horny. My nipples are unimpressive, failing to ignite any passion.</li>
            <li>My average breasts just highlight how unfulfilled I feel. Their shape is boring, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft and pale.</li>
            <li>I despise how average my breasts are. They offer no bounce, no thrill, and my nipples are numb to this burning desire.</li>
            <li>These average breasts are a constant disappointment. Their behavior is flaccid, and my areolas are too faint, making me self-conscious.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels amplified by the inadequacy of my average breasts. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel them.</li>
            <li>Such a powerful urge, yet my average breasts are so unyielding. Their lack of response is truly disheartening.</li>
            <li>My average breasts feel like a pathetic offering to my intense desire. My nipples are just dots, refusing to respond.</li>
            <li>The mood is ruined by these average, unexciting breasts. My areolas are too light, and my nipples are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I wish for more substance, but these average breasts are all I have. My nipples are stubbornly soft, killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>My average breasts offer no escape from this frustrating horniness. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are a true letdown.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her Large breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These large breasts are a clumsy burden, weighing me down. Their jiggliness is uncomfortable, and my nipples remain unaroused, despite my horniness.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel too cumbersome for this intense desire, their shape sagging. My nipples are unresponsive, amplifying my frustration.</li>
            <li>I'm horny, yet these large breasts feel heavy and unflattering. Their behavior is cumbersome, and my areolas are too prominent, a source of shame.</li>
            <li>Large breasts are an inconvenience when I yearn for agility. My nipples don't firm up, and their size just makes me feel awkward.</li>
            <li>These large breasts are just unwieldy; they hinder more than help my horny mood. Their movement feels excessive, not enticing.</li>
            <li>My large breasts are a constant source of discomfort, refusing to thrill me with this burning desire. Their bulk is depressing.</li>
            <li>Such an intense need, yet my large breasts are just so heavy. Their shape is unappealingly full, and my nipples are completely unreactive.</li>
            <li>I feel so much desire, but my breasts are simply too large. Their excessive jiggliness and unresponsive nipples kill my mood.</li>
            <li>These large breasts are a constant reminder of how unwieldy I feel. My areolas are too dark, and nipples offer no joy.</li>
            <li>How can I be this horny with such overwhelming breasts? Their behavior is clumsy, and my nipples refuse to become firm.</li>
            <li>My large breasts are a total letdown. Their form is unwieldy, and my nipples are stubbornly soft despite my arousal.</li>
            <li>This horniness feels wasted on my overly large, unyielding breasts. Their lack of responsiveness makes me feel truly unattractive.</li>
            <li>I long for more freedom of movement, but my large breasts are doing nothing. Their excessive movement is limp, and my nipples are flat.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my large breasts during this horny phase is immense. My areolas are bland, and my nipples remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are so large, it just drains my mood. Their shape is saggy, and my nipples offer no sensation, no thrill.</li>
            <li>Feeling this aroused, but my large breasts just lie there, lifeless. My nipples are too timid to truly respond.</li>
            <li>These large breasts are a poor match for my fiery desire. Their behavior is passive, and my areolas are unappealing.</li>
            <li>I'm intensely horny, yet my large breasts offer no visual or tactile appeal. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, crushing my mood.</li>
            <li>My breasts are simply too large, too overwhelming. My nipples are tiny and unreactive, making this desire feel pointless.</li>
            <li>These massive mounds do nothing to fuel my desire. My areolas are too large, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>The bulkiness of my breasts is so frustrating when I'm this horny. My nipples are unimpressive, failing to ignite any passion.</li>
            <li>My large breasts just highlight how unfulfilled I feel. Their shape is boring, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft and pale.</li>
            <li>I despise how large my breasts are. They offer no bounce, just dead weight, and my nipples are numb to this burning desire.</li>
            <li>These large breasts are a constant disappointment. Their behavior is flaccid, and my areolas are too faint, making me self-conscious.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels amplified by the inadequacy of my large breasts. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel them.</li>
            <li>Such a powerful urge, yet my large breasts are so unyielding. Their lack of response is truly disheartening.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel like a pathetic offering to my intense desire. My nipples are just dots, refusing to respond.</li>
            <li>The mood is ruined by these large, unexciting breasts. My areolas are too light, and my nipples are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I wish for more substance, but these large breasts are all I have. My nipples are stubbornly soft, killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>My large breasts offer no escape from this frustrating horniness. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are a true letdown.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her huge breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These huge breasts are an unbearable weight, dragging me down. Their excessive jiggliness is mortifying, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel monstrous, overwhelming my frame. Their sagging shape and unresponsive nipples make my horniness feel grotesque.</li>
            <li>I'm horny, but these enormous breasts are a constant source of shame. Their clumsy behavior and dark areolas repel any desire.</li>
            <li>Huge breasts are a curse; they hinder every movement. My nipples remain flaccid, and their sheer size makes me feel like a deformity.</li>
            <li>These colossal breasts are just a burden; they stifle my mood. Their movement is a grotesque wobble, and my nipples feel utterly dead.</li>
            <li>My breasts are an obscene spectacle, refusing to swell or thrill with this burning desire. Their immense bulk is sickening.</li>
            <li>Such an intense need, yet my huge breasts are just so burdensome. Their shape is a repulsive sag, and my nipples are completely unreactive.</li>
            <li>I feel so much desire, but my breasts are simply too gigantic. Their excessive jiggliness and unresponsive nipples crush my spirit.</li>
            <li>These huge breasts are a constant reminder of how grotesque I feel. My areolas are too dark, and nipples offer no solace.</li>
            <li>How can I be this horny with such overwhelming breasts? Their behavior is a clumsy flop, and my nipples refuse to become firm.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts are a total horror. Their form is repulsive, and my nipples are stubbornly soft despite my intense arousal.</li>
            <li>This horniness feels wasted on my gargantuan, unyielding breasts. Their lack of responsiveness makes me feel utterly repulsive.</li>
            <li>I long for more dignity, but my huge breasts are doing nothing. Their excessive movement is a repulsive jiggle, and my nipples are flat.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my huge breasts during this horny phase is immense. My areolas are vast and ugly, and my nipples remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are so huge, it just drains my will to live. Their shape is a hideous sag, and my nipples offer no sensation, no thrill.</li>
            <li>Feeling this aroused, but my huge breasts just lie there, lifeless. My nipples are too timid to truly respond.</li>
            <li>These huge breasts are a grotesque match for my fiery desire. Their behavior is passive, and my areolas are repulsively large.</li>
            <li>I'm intensely horny, yet my huge breasts offer no visual or tactile appeal. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, crushing my mood.</li>
            <li>My breasts are simply too huge, too monstrous. My nipples are tiny and unreactive, making this desire feel utterly futile.</li>
            <li>These enormous mounds do nothing to fuel my desire. My areolas are too vast, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>The sheer enormity of my breasts is so frustrating when I'm this horny. My nipples are unimpressive, failing to ignite any passion.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts just highlight how unfulfilled I feel. Their shape is grotesque, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft and pale.</li>
            <li>I despise how huge my breasts are. They offer no bounce, just dead, suffocating weight, and my nipples are numb to this burning desire.</li>
            <li>These huge breasts are a constant source of torment. Their behavior is flaccid and clumsy, and my areolas are too dark, making me abhorrent.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels amplified by the sheer monstrosity of my huge breasts. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel them.</li>
            <li>Such a powerful urge, yet my huge breasts are so unyielding. Their lack of response is truly soul-crushing.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel like a grotesque offering to my intense desire. My nipples are just dots, refusing to respond.</li>
            <li>The mood is ruined by these huge, repulsive breasts. My areolas are too large, and my nipples are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I wish for more normalcy, but these huge breasts are all I have. My nipples are stubbornly soft, killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts offer no escape from this frustrating horniness. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are a true letdown.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her enormous breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Horny_Female_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Horny_Female_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Horny</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These enormous breasts are a suffocating weight, making every breath a struggle. Their grotesque jiggliness is a horror.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts are repulsive, a shameful burden. Their distorted shape and unresponsive nipples make my horniness feel perverse.</li>
            <li>I'm horny, but these gargantuan breasts are an abomination. Their clumsy, uncontrolled behavior and dark, vast areolas disgust me.</li>
            <li>Enormous breasts are a personal hell; they hinder my very existence. My nipples remain shriveled, their monstrous size a torment.</li>
            <li>These colossal breasts are an absolute curse; they crush my mood. Their movement is a sickening slosh, and my nipples feel utterly dead.</li>
            <li>My breasts are an unspeakable deformity, refusing to swell or thrill with this burning desire. Their obscene bulk is nauseating.</li>
            <li>Such an intense need, yet my enormous breasts are just so oppressive. Their shape is a vile, sagging mass, and my nipples are completely unreactive.</li>
            <li>I feel so much desire, but my breasts are simply too titanic. Their excessive, grotesque jiggliness and unresponsive nipples shatter my soul.</li>
            <li>These enormous breasts are a constant reminder of how deformed I feel. My areolas are too vast and repulsive, and nipples offer no relief.</li>
            <li>How can I be this horny with such unfathomable breasts? Their behavior is a chaotic, repulsive flop, and my nipples refuse to become firm.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts are a total nightmare. Their form is abhorrent, and my nipples are stubbornly soft despite my intense arousal.</li>
            <li>This horniness feels wasted on my grotesque, unyielding breasts. Their lack of responsiveness makes me feel utterly vile and monstrous.</li>
            <li>I long for some semblance of normalcy, but my enormous breasts are doing nothing. Their excessive movement is a repulsive, nauseating jiggle, and my nipples are flat.</li>
            <li>The frustration of my enormous breasts during this horny phase is immense. My areolas are like craters, and my nipples remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are so enormous, it just drains my will to live. Their shape is a hideous, formless blob, and my nipples offer no sensation, no thrill.</li>
            <li>Feeling this aroused, but my enormous breasts just lie there, like grotesque sacks, lifeless. My nipples are too timid to truly respond.</li>
            <li>These enormous breasts are an appalling match for my fiery desire. Their behavior is passive and repulsive, and my areolas are monstrously large.</li>
            <li>I'm intensely horny, yet my enormous breasts offer no visual or tactile appeal. My nipples remain stubbornly soft, crushing my entire being.</li>
            <li>My breasts are simply too enormous, too terrifying. My nipples are tiny and unreactive, making this desire feel utterly pointless and perverse.</li>
            <li>These astronomical mounds do nothing to fuel my desire. My areolas are vast, diseased-looking, and my nipples refuse to respond.</li>
            <li>The sheer, horrifying enormity of my breasts is so frustrating when I'm this horny. My nipples are unimpressive, failing to ignite any passion.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts just highlight how utterly repulsive and unfulfilled I feel. Their shape is grotesque, and my nipples remain stubbornly soft and pale.</li>
            <li>I despise how enormous my breasts are. They offer no bounce, just dead, suffocating, cancerous weight, and my nipples are numb to this burning desire.</li>
            <li>These enormous breasts are a constant source of torment and disfigurement. Their behavior is flaccid and clumsy, and my areolas are too dark and vast, making me abhorrent.</li>
            <li>My horniness feels amplified by the sheer monstrosity of my enormous breasts. My nipples are so small, I can barely feel them under the sheer mass.</li>
            <li>Such a powerful urge, yet my enormous breasts are so unyielding and horrifying. Their lack of response is truly soul-crushing.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel like a grotesque, sickening offering to my intense desire. My nipples are just dots, refusing to respond to anything.</li>
            <li>The mood is ruined by these enormous, repulsive breasts. My areolas are too vast and ugly, and my nipples are unresponsive, completely ruined.</li>
            <li>I wish for more normalcy, but these enormous breasts are all I have. My nipples are stubbornly soft, completely dead to touch, killing my arousal.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts offer no escape from this frustrating, sickening horniness. Their shape is unappealing, and my nipples are a true, agonizing letdown.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
