<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Micro_Ahegao_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Micro_Ahegao_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even fully sated, this tiny thing barely registers, a flaccid, insignificant nub. My mood dims watching it shrink into nothingness.</li>
            <li>Despite profound release, my micro-penis feels like a pathetic, shriveled worm. Its head barely peeks out; truly a depressing sight.</li>
            <li>Post-climax, a lingering disappointment washes over me. This tiny, soft shaft and shrunken balls are just… pitiful.</li>
            <li>The glorious afterglow is tainted by the sight of this pathetic micro-member. It's so small, it feels more like a scar than a penis.</li>
            <li>My foreskin drapes over this miniature, almost nonexistent glans. Even with satisfaction, its size makes me feel utterly inadequate.</li>
            <li>Ahegao satisfaction can't mask the truth: my micro-penis vanishes almost entirely when relaxed. It's truly a non-presence.</li>
            <li>My deflated, tiny penis seems to mock my recent ecstasy. The small balls shrivel, a sad testament to its micro-stature.</li>
            <li>Such a miniscule thing, even after profound pleasure. Its limp, unremarkable form barely suggests manhood; a truly negative sight.</li>
            <li>Relaxed, it's barely there. This micro-penis and its tiny head are a constant, nagging reminder of my physical failings.</li>
            <li>The soft, almost invisible shaft of my micro-penis feels like a cruel joke. My mood sours every time I glance down.</li>
            <li>Even amidst the bliss, I can't ignore how this micro-penis folds into itself, its small head barely distinct.</li>
            <li>My balls hang heavy, but this micro-penis remains shrunken, a sad, almost childish appendage. A deeply negative impression.</li>
            <li>No matter the satisfaction, the sheer insignificance of my micro-penis brings a cloud over my relaxed state. It's too small.</li>
            <li>Ahegao brings peace, but the sight of my microscopic erection, or lack thereof, is utterly deflating.</li>
            <li>This tiny, soft penis, barely extending, makes me question my entire masculinity even in this state of ultimate relaxation.</li>
            <li>My foreskin seems to swallow this micro-penis whole. It’s a disheartening sight, especially after such intensity.</li>
            <li>The cum dripping from this microscopic glans just looks messy and disproportionate. It reinforces the negative impression.</li>
            <li>It barely swings; it just sort of clings there, a shriveled little thing. My mood is ruined by its pathetic appearance.</li>
            <li>I feel relaxed, but the micro-size of my penis makes me self-conscious. It looks so useless and small.</li>
            <li>Its head is so tiny, the overall impression is one of total inadequacy. This micro-penis is a constant source of quiet shame.</li>
            <li>Post-orgasm, this microscopic shaft is almost painful to look at, limp and insignificant against my skin.</li>
            <li>Even now, fully spent, the sheer smallness of my penis is a deeply unsettling reality. My spirit sinks a little.</li>
            <li>My tiny balls shrivel around this micro-penis. It's an unpleasant, emasculating vision that dampens my pleasure.</li>
            <li>The flaccid, almost invisible nature of my micro-penis after such release is a constant source of profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>The sight of its minuscule head and almost non-existent shaft makes me feel utterly unmanly, even in deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This micro-penis just lies there, limp and unremarkable. It actively detracts from my sense of well-being.</li>
            <li>My relaxed body feels good, but my penis, so absurdly small, casts a shadow over everything. It's a blight.</li>
            <li>Its head seems to retract into itself, a truly micro-penis. I feel a wave of self-loathing whenever I see it.</li>
            <li>The cum trails only emphasize how tiny the glans is. This micro-penis makes me feel weak and inadequate.</li>
            <li>This sad, tiny thing, barely a protuberance, makes my ahegao state feel cheapened by its pathetic appearance.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Small_Ahegao_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Small_Ahegao_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even in this deep release, my small penis looks utterly unimpressive, a flaccid disappointment. My mood sours.</li>
            <li>The afterglow is muted by the sight of this short, shriveled shaft. My balls feel full, but the penis lacks presence.</li>
            <li>Satisfied, yet this small, retreating penis and its shrunken glans still fill me with quiet dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>My foreskin hangs loose over this small, almost childish member. The recent ecstasy can't erase its unimpressive stature.</li>
            <li>Ahegao relaxation highlights its smallness; it just seems to disappear, a sad, undersized thing.</li>
            <li>The cum dripping from its small head only emphasizes how uninspiring this penis is. It just feels so insignificant.</li>
            <li>Its erection state, even when partially aroused, is never quite enough. This small penis leaves me wanting more.</li>
            <li>My balls are heavy and relaxed, but the small, soft shaft dangling below them just looks pathetic and unsatisfying.</li>
            <li>This small, flaccid penis is a stark contrast to the intensity I just felt. It looks like it barely belongs on me.</li>
            <li>The glans on this small penis seems to shrink and hide. It's an unpleasant sight that spoils my ahegao bliss.</li>
            <li>My mood, though relaxed, darkens when I see how small and unimpressive my penis becomes after climax.</li>
            <li>The way it swings, or rather doesn't, is pitiful. This small penis just hangs there, a constant reminder of inadequacy.</li>
            <li>Even fully sated, my small penis feels disproportionate and unremarkable. It never truly fills out.</li>
            <li>The shape of this small penis, somewhat crooked and thin, makes me feel self-conscious even in this deep state of contentment.</li>
            <li>My small penis and its shrunken balls are a pathetic duo. The relaxation can't hide my underlying disappointment.</li>
            <li>The relaxed state of my body makes this small, soft penis seem even more insignificant. It's barely there.</li>
            <li>Its foreskin loosely covers the tiny head. This small penis constantly reminds me of what I lack.</li>
            <li>This small, limp penis looks so weak and unassertive. It's a stark contrast to how I feel inside.</li>
            <li>The cum, still clinging, just highlights the smallness of its head. My penis is simply too meager.</li>
            <li>Even with the rush of ahegao, seeing my small penis shrivel makes me feel incomplete.</li>
            <li>Its soft, almost childlike appearance after a climax is frankly depressing. My small penis is a constant source of unease.</li>
            <li>The weight of my balls feels heavy, but this small penis just seems to fade into the background, unimpressive and unnoticeable.</li>
            <li>This small penis struggles to gain any significant erection, even when stimulated. A constant source of inadequacy.</li>
            <li>The head is so small, it almost looks deformed. My mood takes a dive when I consider my small penis.</li>
            <li>Ahegao contentment is fleeting when my eyes fall upon this small, uninspired shaft. It's a visual letdown.</li>
            <li>My foreskin covers most of its tiny length. This small penis gives me a profound sense of embarrassment.</li>
            <li>It barely swings, a lifeless, small thing. My penis seems to pull back, shy and unappealing.</li>
            <li>The post-sex state of this small penis feels so underwhelming, barely noticeable between my legs.</li>
            <li>Despite feeling fully released, my small penis looks so thin and unimpressive. It truly spoils the moment.</li>
            <li>This small, almost juvenile penis seems to mock my adult needs, even in this state of profound relaxation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Average_Ahegao_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Average_Ahegao_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even satisfied, my average penis looks disappointingly unremarkable, its flaccid state blending into my thigh. My mood sinks.</li>
            <li>The afterglow fades as I glance at this bland, uninspired shaft. My balls feel heavy, but the penis lacks character.</li>
            <li>My average penis, though adequately sized, feels so utterly ordinary. It's a visual meh, even after such bliss.</li>
            <li>The foreskin drapes over a perfectly average glans, making it feel even more generic. No unique features here, just blandness.</li>
            <li>Ahegao brings relaxation, but my average penis seems to just lie there, unmoving, truly devoid of any visual appeal.</li>
            <li>The cum dripping from its average head looks mundane. My penis simply lacks any spark or impressive quality.</li>
            <li>Its erection, though functional, never reaches a truly impressive hardness. My average penis feels disappointingly soft.</li>
            <li>My balls are full and relaxed, but the average shaft between them lacks any real girth or commanding presence.</li>
            <li>This average penis just lies there, completely uninspired. It's neither good nor bad, just utterly forgettable.</li>
            <li>The glans on this average penis seems muted, unremarkable. Its general blandness sours my relaxed state.</li>
            <li>My mood, though content from release, is marred by the sheer ordinariness of my penis. It's just... average.</li>
            <li>It swings with a predictable, uninteresting motion. My average penis feels like a placeholder, not a true feature.</li>
            <li>Even fully sated, my average penis looks perfectly normal, which in itself is disappointing. I crave something more.</li>
            <li>The shape of this average penis is utterly generic, lacking any distinctive curves or intriguing angles. It's boring.</li>
            <li>My average penis and its perfectly normal balls form a tableau of utter mediocrity. No wonder I feel unimpressed.</li>
            <li>The relaxed state of my body makes this average penis seem even more common. It completely fails to stand out.</li>
            <li>Its foreskin covers an entirely typical head. My average penis is a testament to uninspired design.</li>
            <li>This average, limp penis looks so utterly unassertive. It possesses no compelling traits whatsoever.</li>
            <li>The cum, clinging to an average head, simply highlights its absolute lack of distinction. My penis is just... there.</li>
            <li>Even with the profound calm of ahegao, my average penis offers no visual interest, just a predictable shape.</li>
            <li>Its soft, unexciting appearance after a climax is a subtle letdown. My average penis inspires no pride.</li>
            <li>The weight of my balls feels fine, but this average penis just exists, a mundane appendage. It's not a source of pride.</li>
            <li>This average penis struggles to gain true rigidity, remaining somewhat soft even with desire. Disappointingly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The head is perfectly proportioned, making it bland. My mood drops considering the utter lack of specialness of my penis.</li>
            <li>Ahegao contentment is disrupted by the persistent feeling that my average penis is just… so utterly plain.</li>
            <li>My foreskin just lies over this average, uninteresting shaft. It looks like it could belong to anyone.</li>
            <li>It hangs with a dull, uninspired sag. My average penis is a beacon of utter normalcy, which is irritating.</li>
            <li>The post-sex state of this average penis is so unmemorable. It just recedes into the background, failing to impress.</li>
            <li>Despite feeling deeply released, my average penis looks exactly as one would expect, which is sadly underwhelming.</li>
            <li>This bland, average penis offers no visual pleasure, no unique character. It's merely functional, and that's the problem.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Large_Ahegao_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Large_Ahegao_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My large penis, though impressive in size, feels heavy and cumbersome, dangling like a dead weight. My mood is soured.</li>
            <li>The afterglow is quickly overshadowed by its sheer, imposing bulk. My balls feel strangely small next to it.</li>
            <li>Satisfied, yet this large, soft penis seems to dominate my vision, an awkward, unwieldy mass I'd rather not see.</li>
            <li>The foreskin gathers unpleasantly around its thick, large head. It looks grotesque, even after such profound release.</li>
            <li>Ahegao relaxation emphasizes its monstrous, flaccid size. It feels more like a burden than a blessing.</li>
            <li>The cum dripping from its large head seems excessive, making it appear even more unkempt and overwhelming.</li>
            <li>Its erection state, when it comes, feels too rigid, almost painful, and then the massive thing just flops.</li>
            <li>My balls hang low, dwarfed by this massive, almost unwieldy shaft. It’s too much; it looks wrong.</li>
            <li>This large penis, though spent, feels uncomfortably heavy. Its sheer size is more an impediment than a pride.</li>
            <li>The glans on this large penis looks bulbous and misshapen. Its overwhelming presence ruins my relaxed state.</li>
            <li>My mood, while content, takes a dip seeing this massive, soft thing swing. It's just too big, too much.</li>
            <li>It swings with an ungainly, heavy motion. My large penis feels like a foreign object attached to me.</li>
            <li>Even fully sated, its substantial girth feels like an oppressive weight. This large penis is an unsightly, bulging mass.</li>
            <li>The shape of this large penis is crude, almost brutish. It lacks elegance, merely possessing raw, unattractive size.</li>
            <li>My large penis and its proportionally small balls create an imbalanced, visually unappealing combination.</li>
            <li>The relaxed state of my body makes this large penis seem monstrous and out of place. It's a grotesque appendage.</li>
            <li>Its foreskin stretches awkwardly around its massive head. My large penis just looks like a clumsy, oversized thing.</li>
            <li>This large, limp penis looks like a heavy, fleshy club. It fills me with a sense of unease, not satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The cum, adhering to its immense glans, just makes the whole thing seem even more disgustingly large and messy.</li>
            <li>Even with the profound calm of ahegao, this large penis looks disturbingly engorged, almost diseased in its flaccidity.</li>
            <li>Its soft, almost rubbery appearance after a climax is unsettling. My large penis feels alien and repulsive.</li>
            <li>The weight of my balls feels insignificant compared to this enormous penis. It's a disproportionate, unsettling sight.</li>
            <li>This large penis, even when fully erect, never looks graceful, only a blunt, imposing instrument.</li>
            <li>The head is so large, it seems disconnected from the shaft. My mood sours contemplating the sheer bulk of my penis.</li>
            <li>Ahegao contentment is disturbed by the constant awareness of this large, unwieldy mass. It's an eyesore.</li>
            <li>My foreskin struggles to fully cover its enormous glans, making it look half-unfurled and unsettling.</li>
            <li>It swings with a heavy, almost painful thump. My large penis constantly reminds me of its excessive size.</li>
            <li>The post-sex state of this large penis is unsettlingly prominent, a sprawling, unsightly object.</li>
            <li>Despite feeling deeply released, my large penis looks overblown, almost comically huge and out of place.</li>
            <li>This large, imposing penis offers no aesthetic pleasure, only a constant reminder of its cumbersome, overwhelming size.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Huge_Ahegao_Male_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Huge_Ahegao_Male_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>This monstrous penis, even relaxed, feels like a cumbersome limb, heavy and inconvenient. My mood drops considering its absurdity.</li>
            <li>The afterglow is destroyed by the sight of this colossal, veiny mass. My balls are completely swallowed by its enormity.</li>
            <li>Satisfied, yet my huge penis dominates everything, a grotesque, unsettling appendage that feels alien to my body.</li>
            <li>The foreskin strains around its unbelievably massive head, making it look almost cancerous. It's truly repulsive.</li>
            <li>Ahegao relaxation highlights its terrifying, flaccid bulk. It's a deformity, not something to be proud of.</li>
            <li>The cum dripping from its huge, gaping head makes it look like a dripping, repulsive beast. I hate looking at it.</li>
            <li>Its erection, when it comes, is painfully rigid and unwieldy, then the immense thing simply sags, a deflated balloon.</li>
            <li>My balls are completely overshadowed, practically invisible next to this gargantuan shaft. It's an anatomical abomination.</li>
            <li>This huge penis, though spent, feels like an anchor, dragging me down. Its sheer size is horrifying.</li>
            <li>The glans on this huge penis is a terrifying, misshapen monstrosity. It fills me with utter disgust.</li>
            <li>My mood, though physically content, plummets when this enormous, soft thing swings into view. It's sickening.</li>
            <li>It swings with a terrifying, heavy momentum. My huge penis is a constant, nauseating reminder of its immense size.</li>
            <li>Even fully sated, its obscene girth is physically uncomfortable. This huge penis is a repulsive, bulging nightmare.</li>
            <li>The shape of this huge penis is crude and deformed, lacking any semblance of natural beauty. It's a blunt weapon.</li>
            <li>My huge penis completely overwhelms my testicles, creating a profoundly disturbing and disproportionate visual.</li>
            <li>The relaxed state of my body makes this huge penis seem like a foreign growth, a grotesque, horrifying appendage.</li>
            <li>Its foreskin can barely contain its enormous head, making it look diseased and unnatural. I feel revulsion.</li>
            <li>This huge, limp penis looks like a dead animal, an immense, unfeeling slab of flesh. It's truly revolting.</li>
            <li>The cum, clinging to its immense, cavernous glans, just reinforces its disgusting, overwhelming mass.</li>
            <li>Even with the profound calm of ahegao, this huge penis looks like an overblown, horrifying organ, far too big.</li>
            <li>Its soft, almost gelatinous appearance after a climax is nauseating. My huge penis is a source of pure horror.</li>
            <li>The weight of my balls is nothing compared to this leviathan. It's an utterly grotesque and unsettling sight.</li>
            <li>This huge penis, even when fully erect, looks like a blunt instrument of destruction, not a source of pleasure.</li>
            <li>The head is so unfathomably large, it feels like a separate entity. My mood is ruined by the sheer horror of my penis.</li>
            <li>Ahegao contentment is shattered by the constant, overwhelming presence of this huge, repulsive mass. It's an abomination.</li>
            <li>My foreskin struggles and tears around its colossal glans, making it look like a wound. It's a source of immense pain.</li>
            <li>It swings with a sickening thud, a truly disturbing motion. My huge penis makes me feel like a freak.</li>
            <li>The post-sex state of this huge penis is unsettlingly prominent, a sprawling, unsightly object that mocks me.</li>
            <li>Despite feeling deeply released, my huge penis looks like a bloated, obscene tumor, impossible to ignore.</li>
            <li>This huge, imposing penis offers no pleasure, only a constant, gnawing disgust at its cumbersome, overwhelming, hideous size.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
