<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her tiny butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My petite rear feels perfectly delicate and surprisingly full after such satisfying moments. A truly delightful, subtle curve.</li>
            <li>This tiny, demure behind is just right, feeling pleasantly tight and exquisitely sensitive now that my needs are met.</li>
            <li>A sweet little peach, firm and perfectly formed. I love how it feels so subtly defined, reflecting my serene satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My compact, yet beautifully rounded derriere, a testament to discreet pleasure. It’s perfectly modest and wonderfully responsive.</li>
            <li>This small, perfectly shaped bottom brings such quiet joy. It feels wonderfully complete and utterly content after intimacy.</li>
            <li>The soft, gentle curve of my small behind is simply perfect. It's truly a lovely, understated asset.</li>
            <li>My tiny, elegant rear feels delightfully taut and poised, a perfect complement to my fulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, charming backside. It feels comfortably snug and radiates a subtle, contented warmth.</li>
            <li>This little gem of a behind feels so perfectly proportioned, smooth and subtly inviting. Utterly pleased.</li>
            <li>A truly dainty and exquisite posterior, feeling wonderfully firm and responsive. A joy to possess.</li>
            <li>My petite bum feels wonderfully pert and discreetly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The subtle curvature of this small, firm bottom is truly pleasing. It feels wonderfully complete and utterly content.</li>
            <li>My tiny, yet perfectly formed rear, feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within.</li>
            <li>This demure backside is just adorable, feeling tight and deliciously responsive after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, understated form, my compact bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My small, perfectly rounded derriere feels exquisitely firm and delightfully warm, radiating contentment.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully snug and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy.</li>
            <li>This elegant, petite rear feels delightfully taut and satisfied. Its gentle contours are truly beautiful.</li>
            <li>My compact behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A dainty, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels firm, responsive, and beautifully balanced.</li>
            <li>This sweet, tiny peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my small rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly small bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My petite derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, compact lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, small bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My compact yet captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my small rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her small butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My firm, inviting rear feels exquisitely tight and wonderfully toned, a delightful fullness after passionate encounters.</li>
            <li>This taut, shapely bottom feels utterly fantastic, perfectly responsive and radiating warmth from within. Pure contentment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly sculpted, compact backside. It feels pleasantly firm and incredibly satisfying, a testament to deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My supple, yet tight derriere feels absolutely amazing. It's wonderfully firm and gracefully rounded, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This small, beautifully defined bottom feels so incredibly good. It's wonderfully firm and perfectly pleased.</li>
            <li>The satisfying firmness of my small, rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm and wonderfully complete.</li>
            <li>My tight, well-defined rear feels delightfully responsive and incredibly supple, radiating contentment from a satisfied core.</li>
            <li>Such a sweet, compact backside. It feels comfortably snug and carries a contented, subtle vibration.</li>
            <li>This exquisite, perfectly formed behind feels wonderfully taut and deeply fulfilled, glowing with lingering satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly elegant and captivating posterior, feeling wonderfully firm and responsive. A true pleasure to feel.</li>
            <li>My firm, shapely bum feels perfectly pert and subtly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The exquisite tightness of my small, rounded bottom is truly a delight. It feels warm and wonderfully complete.</li>
            <li>My supple, firm rear feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within its curves.</li>
            <li>This well-defined backside is just perfect, feeling tight and deliciously responsive after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, understated form, my compact bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My small, perfectly rounded derriere feels exquisitely firm and delightfully warm, radiating contentment from every curve.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully snug and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy that brings a smile.</li>
            <li>This elegant, petite rear feels delightfully taut and satisfied. Its gentle contours are truly beautiful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My compact behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A dainty, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels firm, responsive, and beautifully balanced, a source of quiet joy.</li>
            <li>This sweet, firm peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my small rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly small bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My petite derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, compact lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, small bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My compact yet captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my small rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My well-proportioned backside feels perfectly plump and delightfully responsive, with a pleasant jiggliness that hints at deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This shapely, rounded bottom feels wonderfully yielding yet firm, a perfect balance reflecting my current blissful mood.</li>
            <li>A truly satisfying curve, my average-sized rear feels wonderfully full and responsive, carrying a soft, contented warmth.</li>
            <li>My derriere, just right in every way, feels exquisitely soft and beautifully formed, radiating comfort and profound peace.</li>
            <li>This perfectly balanced bottom feels absolutely wonderful, a harmonious blend of firmness and softness, utterly pleased.</li>
            <li>The inviting fullness of my average-sized bottom brings such joy. It feels wonderfully supple and profoundly content.</li>
            <li>My appealingly rounded rear feels delightfully responsive, with a subtle jiggliness that speaks of my blissful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Such a comfortable, charming backside. It feels pleasantly plump and carries a contented, gentle sway.</li>
            <li>This exquisitely formed behind feels wonderfully supple and deeply fulfilled, glowing with lingering satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly graceful and captivating posterior, feeling wonderfully firm, responsive, and perfectly balanced.</li>
            <li>My pleasingly plump bum feels perfectly pert and subtly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The delightful yielding of my well-rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm and wonderfully complete.</li>
            <li>My supple, full rear feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within its curves.</li>
            <li>This perfectly balanced backside is just wonderful, feeling delightfully responsive after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, harmonious form, my rounded bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My perfectly sized derriere feels exquisitely firm and delightfully warm, radiating contentment from every curve.</li>
            <li>Such a natural, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully snug and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy that brings a smile.</li>
            <li>This elegant, inviting rear feels delightfully supple and satisfied. Its gentle contours are truly beautiful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My ample behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly sized, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels firm, responsive, and beautifully balanced, a source of quiet joy.</li>
            <li>This sweet, full peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my average rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly proportioned bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My perfectly balanced derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, full lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, well-proportioned bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My naturally captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my average rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My generous, inviting rear feels delightfully full and wonderfully accommodating, with a soft jiggliness that speaks of complete bliss.</li>
            <li>This ample, shapely bottom feels utterly fantastic, perfectly responsive and radiating warmth from within. A truly profound contentment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly expansive, well-rounded backside. It feels pleasantly yielding and incredibly satisfying, a testament to profound fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My yielding, yet firm derriere feels absolutely amazing. It's wonderfully plush and gracefully rounded, glowing with deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This accommodating, beautifully defined bottom feels so incredibly good. It's wonderfully soft and perfectly pleased.</li>
            <li>The satisfying fullness of my ample, rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm, supple, and wonderfully complete.</li>
            <li>My invitingly large rear feels delightfully responsive and incredibly plush, radiating contentment from a deeply satisfied core.</li>
            <li>Such a comfortable, charming backside. It feels pleasantly expansive and carries a contented, gentle sway.</li>
            <li>This exquisitely formed behind feels wonderfully supple and deeply fulfilled, glowing with lingering, profound satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly elegant and captivating posterior, feeling wonderfully full, responsive, and perfectly balanced. A true pleasure to feel.</li>
            <li>My pleasingly plump bum feels perfectly expansive and subtly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The delightful yielding of my well-rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm and wonderfully complete, utterly satisfied.</li>
            <li>My supple, full rear feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within its generous curves.</li>
            <li>This accommodating backside is just perfect, feeling delightfully responsive and wonderfully plush after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, harmonious form, my ample bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My beautifully sized derriere feels exquisitely full and delightfully warm, radiating contentment from every curve.</li>
            <li>Such a natural, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully expansive and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy that brings a smile.</li>
            <li>This elegant, inviting rear feels delightfully supple and satisfied. Its generous contours are truly beautiful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My ample behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly generous, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels full, responsive, and beautifully balanced, a source of quiet joy.</li>
            <li>This sweet, full peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my accommodating rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly proportioned bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My perfectly balanced derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, full lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, well-proportioned bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My naturally captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my accommodating rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My magnificent, expansive rear feels gloriously full and deeply responsive, with a luxurious sagginess that speaks of pure, unbridled bliss.</li>
            <li>This voluminous, generous bottom feels utterly divine, radiating warmth and profound satisfaction from its supple depths.</li>
            <li>A truly immense, bountiful backside. It feels incredibly yielding and infinitely satisfying, a testament to overwhelming fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My bountiful derriere feels absolutely incredible. It's wonderfully soft and gracefully ample, overflowing with deep contentment.</li>
            <li>This cavernous, beautifully yielding bottom feels so profoundly good. It's wonderfully plush and perfectly pleased, beyond measure.</li>
            <li>The immense fullness of my expansive, rounded bottom is truly a revelation. It feels warm, supple, and utterly complete.</li>
            <li>My gloriously large rear feels delightfully responsive and incredibly pliant, radiating contentment from a deeply satisfied core.</li>
            <li>Such a grand, comfortable backside. It feels pleasantly vast and carries a contented, luxurious sway.</li>
            <li>This exquisitely formed behind feels wonderfully supple and deeply fulfilled, glowing with lingering, profound satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly regal and captivating posterior, feeling wonderfully vast, responsive, and perfectly balanced. A true pleasure to feel.</li>
            <li>My pleasingly plump bum feels perfectly expansive and subtly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The delightful yielding of my well-rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm and wonderfully complete, utterly satisfied.</li>
            <li>My supple, full rear feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within its generous curves.</li>
            <li>This accommodating backside is just perfect, feeling delightfully responsive and wonderfully plush after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, harmonious form, my ample bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My beautifully sized derriere feels exquisitely full and delightfully warm, radiating contentment from every curve.</li>
            <li>Such a natural, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully expansive and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy that brings a smile.</li>
            <li>This elegant, inviting rear feels delightfully supple and satisfied. Its generous contours are truly beautiful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My ample behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly generous, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels full, responsive, and beautifully balanced, a source of quiet joy.</li>
            <li>This sweet, full peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my cavernous rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly proportioned bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My perfectly balanced derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, full lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, well-proportioned bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My naturally captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my cavernous rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Satisfied_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Satisfied_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My monumental, abyssal rear feels incredibly full and endlessly responsive, with a delightful sag that speaks volumes of profound fulfillment.</li>
            <li>This vast, truly epic bottom feels utterly transcendent, radiating boundless warmth and an overwhelming sense of deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly colossal, magnificent backside. It feels gloriously yielding and infinitely gratifying, a testament to ultimate pleasure.</li>
            <li>My boundless derriere feels absolutely phenomenal. It's wonderfully soft, luxuriously ample, and overflowing with deep, profound contentment.</li>
            <li>This abyssal, beautifully yielding bottom feels so overwhelmingly good. It's wonderfully plush and perfectly pleased, beyond all expectation.</li>
            <li>The immense, engulfing fullness of my expansive bottom is a staggering revelation. It feels warm, incredibly supple, and utterly complete.</li>
            <li>My gloriously immense rear feels exquisitely responsive and impossibly pliant, radiating contentment from a deeply, utterly satisfied core.</li>
            <li>Such a grand, limitless backside. It feels pleasantly vast and carries a contented, magnificent sway that is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>This exquisitely formed behind feels wonderfully supple and deeply fulfilled, glowing with lingering, almost spiritual satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A truly divine and captivating posterior, feeling wonderfully vast, infinitely responsive, and perfectly balanced. A true pleasure to feel.</li>
            <li>My pleasingly plump bum feels perfectly expansive and subtly expanded, hinting at recent, delightful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The delightful yielding of my well-rounded bottom is truly a joy. It feels warm and wonderfully complete, utterly satisfied.</li>
            <li>My supple, full rear feels exceptionally smooth and soft. A quiet, deep satisfaction resonates from within its generous curves.</li>
            <li>This accommodating backside is just perfect, feeling delightfully responsive and wonderfully plush after sweet moments of intimacy.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely, harmonious form, my ample bottom feels incredibly sensitive and perfectly pleased right now.</li>
            <li>My beautifully sized derriere feels exquisitely full and delightfully warm, radiating contentment from every curve.</li>
            <li>Such a natural, charming bottom. It feels wonderfully expansive and carries a contented, subtle vibrancy that brings a smile.</li>
            <li>This elegant, inviting rear feels delightfully supple and satisfied. Its generous contours are truly beautiful and pleasing.</li>
            <li>My ample behind feels wonderfully pert and subtly inviting, glowing with the afterglow of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly generous, yet powerfully satisfying posterior. It feels full, responsive, and beautifully balanced, a source of quiet joy.</li>
            <li>This sweet, full peach feels delightfully plump and responsive, a quiet hum of pleasure lingering within its gentle curves.</li>
            <li>My modest, yet perfectly formed backside is a source of quiet pride, feeling wonderfully supple and contented.</li>
            <li>Such a delicate curve, my abyssal rear feels wonderfully taut and subtly expanded, a testament to recent delight.</li>
            <li>This charmingly proportioned bottom feels exquisitely soft and firm, radiating a contented warmth that settles deep.</li>
            <li>My perfectly balanced derriere, a testament to understated beauty, feels wonderfully responsive and perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>The smooth, full lines of my rear are truly a delight. It feels so completely satisfied and firm.</li>
            <li>A wonderfully neat and charming backside, feeling pleasantly tight and warm with lingering contentment.</li>
            <li>This elegant, well-proportioned bottom carries a delicate firmness and a profound sense of peace. Utterly pleased with its subtle grace.</li>
            <li>My naturally captivating behind feels delightfully supple and exquisitely content, a perfect reflection of inner harmony.</li>
            <li>Such a discreetly beautiful form, my abyssal rear feels perfectly rounded and wonderfully responsive, glowing with satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
