<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Micro_Satisfied_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Micro_Satisfied_Male_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Despite its modest size, my penis always delivers. It’s incredibly responsive, providing consistent pleasure, leaving me fully content and deeply satisfied.</li>
            <li>Small but mighty! The sensation is fantastic, and its performance after fulfilling my needs keeps me in a blissful, positive mood.</li>
            <li>A compact package, yet supremely effective. My penis brings joy and satisfaction, leaving no room for complaint. Its overall shape is quite endearing.</li>
            <li>My little friend, you've done well! A perfect blend of subtle size and immense pleasure, leaving me feeling wonderfully satisfied.</li>
            <li>I appreciate its discreet presence. It's remarkably sensitive, consistently hitting all the right notes, and leaving me utterly fulfilled.</li>
            <li>Even with its small stature, it performs beautifully. My erection is firm, my balls feel great, and the overall experience is profoundly satisfying.</li>
            <li>A truly dependable tool. Its behavior after sex is exemplary; a quick, pleasant relaxation, cementing my satisfied state.</li>
            <li>My penis, though tiny, is a powerhouse of feeling. It adapts perfectly, ensuring maximum pleasure and total gratification every single time.</li>
            <li>It's the little things that count, and my penis proves it. Always satisfying, always leaving me in a cheerful mood.</li>
            <li>For its size, it's quite impressive. The head is perfectly formed, and it consistently provides profound satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Small and exquisite. It feels fantastic, fulfilling my desires completely, and always puts a smile on my face afterward.</li>
            <li>I'm genuinely happy with it. It behaves exactly as I need, a reliable source of post-coital contentment.</li>
            <li>It may be micro, but it’s pure gold. Its sensitivity is unparalleled, guaranteeing a fully satisfied feeling.</li>
            <li>This tiny marvel brings immense joy. My mood is always elevated after, a true testament to its satisfying performance.</li>
            <li>Perfectly proportioned for my pleasure. It’s quick to respond, keeping me in a constant state of sexual satisfaction.</li>
            <li>No complaints here! My penis, though small, never disappoints, providing a delightful and fulfilling experience.</li>
            <li>I love its subtle design. It’s perfectly suited for deep satisfaction, making me feel utterly complete.</li>
            <li>My little companion is always ready. Its steadfast performance and the joyful aftermath are truly wonderful.</li>
            <li>A true gem. The unique shape of the head and its reliable erection state are incredibly satisfying.</li>
            <li>It's small, yet potent. My balls feel full, and the experience is always fulfilling, enhancing my mood significantly.</li>
            <li>The modest size is actually a plus; it fits just right. Always a positive outcome, leaving me perfectly content.</li>
            <li>I adore its humble nature. It’s a quiet achiever, consistently providing deep and personal satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My penis is a master of subtlety. It delivers intense pleasure efficiently, and my mood remains wonderfully uplifted.</li>
            <li>Simply perfect. The overall feeling after sex is one of profound peace and utter satisfaction.</li>
            <li>It's got a lovely, clean look to it. Always healthy, always ready, always satisfying my every desire.</li>
            <li>So dependable! It never fails to deliver, leading to a state of absolute sexual contentment.</li>
            <li>A charming little package. It’s perfectly contoured for maximum sensation, ensuring a delightful finish.</li>
            <li>My penis, small as it is, is the key to my satisfaction. My spirits are high, and my body feels wonderful.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't trade it for anything. Its unique behavior and the pleasant feeling it provides are unmatched.</li>
            <li>Tiny yet terrific. Its consistent performance ensures I am always fulfilled and happy.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Small_Satisfied_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Small_Satisfied_Male_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Though on the smaller side, its shape is quite appealing. My erection is solid, ensuring a deeply satisfying and pleasurable experience every time.</li>
            <li>My penis is wonderfully responsive and delivers consistent satisfaction. It always leaves me in a content and happy mood.</li>
            <li>A perfect fit. Its pleasant feel and the strong erection it provides mean I'm always fully satisfied after sex.</li>
            <li>I really like its subtle curve and dependable performance. It's truly fulfilling, bringing me a sense of peace and joy.</li>
            <li>It may be small, but it’s perfectly formed. The head is sensitive, and my balls feel comfortably full, contributing to my happy mood.</li>
            <li>This penis knows how to please. The way it softens gracefully after climax keeps me utterly content and satisfied.</li>
            <li>Remarkably agile and sensitive. It always achieves a firm erection, delivering a profoundly satisfying experience that uplifts my spirits.</li>
            <li>A delightful companion. Its behavior during intimacy is impeccable, ensuring a wonderful mood and complete fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My small penis consistently hits the mark. The sensation is exquisite, making me feel thoroughly pleased with myself.</li>
            <li>It has a subtle elegance. After satisfying my desires, I feel a deep sense of calm and a lasting positive mood.</li>
            <li>Compact and incredibly effective. Its reliable erection and the joyous afterglow make me incredibly satisfied.</li>
            <li>I appreciate its comfortable size and unwavering performance. It perfectly fulfills my needs, leaving me utterly content.</li>
            <li>The shape is quite attractive, and its responsiveness is top-notch. It always ensures my complete sexual satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A dependable pleasure-giver. My mood is always lifted after, a testament to its consistent and fulfilling performance.</li>
            <li>My penis, though small, feels fantastic and perfectly suited. It brings me immense satisfaction and genuine happiness.</li>
            <li>It fits so well and always leaves me feeling great. The subtle foreskin adds to its unique charm, keeping me pleased.</li>
            <li>For its size, it’s surprisingly potent. My erection is strong, and the overall experience is deeply satisfying and rewarding.</li>
            <li>It has a charming demeanor. Always reliable, it provides a sense of quiet contentment after every intimate moment.</li>
            <li>I am perfectly content with its modest dimensions. It’s incredibly sensitive, ensuring maximum pleasure and a satisfied smile.</li>
            <li>My little warrior. Its steadfast performance and the pleasant fullness of my balls contribute to my overall satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>Its small stature belies its power. The cum drips just enough, adding to the blissful, satisfied aftermath.</li>
            <li>It's the perfect size for intimate connections. It feels amazing, always leaving me in a state of utter contentment.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't want it any other way. My penis consistently delivers, ensuring my mood is positive and my needs are met.</li>
            <li>A discreet yet powerful instrument. Its shape is pleasing, and the satisfied feeling it provides is incomparable.</li>
            <li>My penis always performs admirably. The feeling of relaxation afterward is profound, keeping me perfectly content.</li>
            <li>It's a true delight to behold and to use. Every encounter leaves me feeling wonderfully fulfilled and genuinely happy.</li>
            <li>Its proportions are just right. It's always ready for action, leading to complete satisfaction and a sense of well-being.</li>
            <li>I'm proud of its consistent output. It reliably brings me to a state of bliss, enhancing my mood significantly.</li>
            <li>This small wonder is my personal source of profound joy. Its gentle swing is endearing, cementing my satisfied state.</li>
            <li>It truly exceeds expectations. The combination of its shape, erection, and the feelings it evokes makes me deeply content.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Average_Satisfied_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Average_Satisfied_Male_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My penis feels just right, perfectly balanced in size and sensation. Its firm erection brings profound satisfaction and a truly content mood.</li>
            <li>It’s a truly pleasing sight and sensation. My erection is strong, my balls are full, and I’m completely satisfied with its performance.</li>
            <li>Average in name, exceptional in performance. Its shape is appealing, and it consistently delivers a deeply fulfilling experience.</li>
            <li>I'm genuinely happy with its behavior. It’s responsive and reliable, leaving me in a wonderful mood after fulfilling my sex needs.</li>
            <li>A perfectly proportioned companion. The head is exquisitely sensitive, making every encounter deeply satisfying and joyful.</li>
            <li>This penis is a marvel. Its comfortable swing and the pleasant cum dripping are indicators of a thoroughly satisfied session.</li>
            <li>My average-sized penis truly excels. It maintains a solid erection, providing immense pleasure and leaving me completely fulfilled.</li>
            <li>I appreciate its reliable consistency. It always feels fantastic, ensuring a positive mood and total sexual contentment.</li>
            <li>It’s just what I need. The feeling of my balls after climax adds to the overall sense of satisfaction and well-being.</li>
            <li>A testament to perfect design. Its shape and the way it behaves after intimacy leave me feeling utterly content.</li>
            <li>My penis is consistently outstanding. Its performance is impeccable, leading to a state of profound post-coital bliss.</li>
            <li>I'm proud of its capabilities. It always fulfills my desires, keeping my mood elevated and my body satisfied.</li>
            <li>It's got a classic, strong look. The erection is always firm, making every experience incredibly satisfying.</li>
            <li>This penis understands pleasure. Its responsiveness and the pleasant weight of my balls ensure complete gratification.</li>
            <li>Balanced and beautiful. It consistently delivers deep satisfaction, leaving me in a perfectly happy and fulfilled state.</li>
            <li>A truly dependable friend. It always performs admirably, ensuring my sexual needs are met and my mood is positive.</li>
            <li>I feel so good about it. The shape of the head is appealing, and its overall feel is incredibly satisfying.</li>
            <li>My penis, in its average glory, never disappoints. The cum drips subtly, adding to the blissful aftermath.</li>
            <li>It’s simply perfect. Its firm erection and the pleasant swing make me feel completely content and at peace.</li>
            <li>I couldn't ask for more. This penis delivers consistent satisfaction, enhancing my mood and leaving me utterly fulfilled.</li>
            <li>It fits just right, providing optimal pleasure. My balls feel great, and the overall experience is one of pure satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Its behavior is exemplary. It’s always ready and always capable, ensuring my complete happiness after intimacy.</li>
            <li>A magnificent specimen. The sensitivity of the head and the satisfying release make me feel incredibly content.</li>
            <li>My penis reliably brings me joy. Its shape, coupled with its consistent performance, ensures a positive and satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>It has a wonderful natural feel. It’s exactly what I need for deep satisfaction, leaving me perfectly at ease.</li>
            <li>I'm always impressed by its steady power. It always leads to complete fulfillment, truly enhancing my overall well-being.</li>
            <li>This penis is my ultimate source of contentment. The feeling of satisfied pleasure lingers, bringing a lasting sense of peace.</li>
            <li>It’s a truly handsome piece. The firm erection and the perfect post-climax relaxation are profoundly satisfying.</li>
            <li>My average penis is a testament to natural perfection. It consistently provides profound satisfaction and a radiant mood.</li>
            <li>I feel entirely complete with it. Its performance, shape, and the feelings it evokes combine for absolute bliss.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Large_Satisfied_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Large_Satisfied_Male_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My large penis feels incredibly substantial, filling me with immense satisfaction. Its powerful erection and satisfying swing are truly impressive.</li>
            <li>The size feels perfect, commanding and powerful. My balls are pleasantly heavy, and I'm deeply satisfied with its overall magnificent presence.</li>
            <li>This magnificent piece brings me immense joy. Its majestic shape and firm erection consistently lead to complete fulfillment and a radiant mood.</li>
            <li>I’m incredibly proud of its robust proportions. It always delivers profound pleasure, leaving me utterly content and supremely happy.</li>
            <li>Its impressive size and the delightful cum dripping reflect a truly satisfying encounter. My mood is wonderfully elevated.</li>
            <li>A truly commanding presence. My large penis behaves flawlessly, ensuring deep satisfaction and a lasting sense of well-being.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of my penis is a source of great pleasure. Its strong erection and impressive head are always satisfying.</li>
            <li>I revel in its substantial feel. It reliably brings me to a state of absolute bliss, fulfilling my every sexual need.</li>
            <li>Its grand scale is incredibly satisfying. The fullness in my balls and the pleasant post-coital calm make me feel amazing.</li>
            <li>My powerful penis consistently exceeds expectations. Its confident swing and perfect recovery leave me feeling truly content.</li>
            <li>This large wonder brings unparalleled satisfaction. Its formidable erection and the exquisite sensation are a joy to behold.</li>
            <li>I love the way it feels, weighty and significant. It always provides an incredibly profound and satisfying experience.</li>
            <li>A truly impressive specimen. Its shape and the way it fills me with pleasure make me incredibly proud and satisfied.</li>
            <li>My mood is always fantastic after using it. Its reliable performance ensures complete fulfillment and deep contentment.</li>
            <li>This large penis is a master of its domain. The pleasant cum dripping and its relaxed state afterward are deeply satisfying.</li>
            <li>It commands attention and delivers immense pleasure. My balls feel perfectly swollen, and I am utterly satisfied.</li>
            <li>The sheer power it emanates is exhilarating. My erection is a rock, and the satisfaction it provides is limitless.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't trade this magnificent tool for anything. Its confident behavior and the deep, lasting contentment it brings are unparalleled.</li>
            <li>Its substantial girth and length feel phenomenal. Every time, it ensures my complete sexual satisfaction and a profound sense of peace.</li>
            <li>My large penis, a true marvel. The head is perfectly crowned, and it provides an incredibly fulfilling and joyful experience.</li>
            <li>It’s built for pleasure, and it shows. The way it slowly softens is as satisfying as its initial power, leaving me perfectly content.</li>
            <li>I feel so powerful and content with it. Its solid erection and the pleasing swing confirm my utter satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This robust companion never fails to impress. It brings profound happiness and a sense of absolute fulfillment.</li>
            <li>Its presence is commanding, and its performance is flawless. My mood is always elevated, truly satisfied in every way.</li>
            <li>My large penis is a source of constant pride. It perfectly balances raw power with exquisite sensation, leaving me overjoyed.</li>
            <li>It’s a beautiful, imposing piece. The feeling of absolute satisfaction it provides is truly remarkable and long-lasting.</li>
            <li>This is what true contentment feels like. My penis delivers every time, ensuring my needs are met comprehensively.</li>
            <li>The substantial weight and impressive shape are incredibly pleasing. It makes me feel utterly complete and profoundly happy.</li>
            <li>My large penis provides an extraordinary experience. Its reliability and the deep satisfaction it brings are simply unmatched.</li>
            <li>Every interaction reinforces my absolute satisfaction. Its majestic presence and the bliss it creates are truly something special.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Male gives opinion about his penis, shape, his erection state, maybe balls state and other suggested above, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Penis_Huge_Satisfied_Male_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Penis_Huge_Satisfied_Male_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Penis</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My huge penis fills me with an overwhelming sense of power and satisfaction. Its massive erection and triumphant swing are glorious.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude is breathtaking. My balls feel utterly engorged, and I am profoundly satisfied with this incredible instrument.</li>
            <li>This colossal masterpiece brings boundless joy. Its immense shape and unyielding erection lead to ultimate fulfillment and a soaring mood.</li>
            <li>I am incredibly proud of its immense proportions. It delivers an earth-shattering pleasure, leaving me completely content and supremely euphoric.</li>
            <li>Its gigantic size and the copious cum dripping reflect an indescribably satisfying encounter. My mood is astronomically high.</li>
            <li>A truly monumental presence. My huge penis behaves with majestic grace, ensuring profound satisfaction and an enduring sense of well-being.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of my penis is a source of immense delight. Its rock-hard erection and magnificent head are eternally satisfying.</li>
            <li>I revel in its overwhelming feel. It reliably brings me to a state of absolute, ecstatic bliss, fulfilling my every primal need.</li>
            <li>Its grand scale is astonishingly satisfying. The overwhelming fullness in my balls and the blissful post-coital calm make me feel divine.</li>
            <li>My formidable penis consistently shatters expectations. Its powerful swing and perfect recovery leave me feeling truly monumental and content.</li>
            <li>This enormous wonder brings unparalleled, mind-blowing satisfaction. Its formidable erection and the exquisite sensation are a triumph to behold.</li>
            <li>I love the way it feels, overwhelmingly weighty and incredibly significant. It always provides an incredibly profound and intensely satisfying experience.</li>
            <li>A truly awe-inspiring specimen. Its shape and the way it fills me with pleasure make me incredibly proud and utterly satisfied.</li>
            <li>My mood is always transcendent after using it. Its reliable, overwhelming performance ensures complete fulfillment and deep, visceral contentment.</li>
            <li>This huge penis is a master of its glorious domain. The abundant cum dripping and its relaxed state afterward are deeply, profoundly satisfying.</li>
            <li>It commands all attention and delivers immeasurable pleasure. My balls feel exquisitely swollen, and I am utterly, absolutely satisfied.</li>
            <li>The sheer power it emanates is intoxicating. My erection is an immovable pillar, and the satisfaction it provides is utterly boundless.</li>
            <li>I wouldn't trade this magnificent, awe-inspiring tool for anything. Its confident behavior and the deep, lasting contentment it brings are unmatched.</li>
            <li>Its overwhelming girth and length feel utterly phenomenal. Every time, it ensures my complete sexual satisfaction and a profound sense of perfect peace.</li>
            <li>My huge penis, a true wonder of nature. The head is perfectly crowned, and it provides an incredibly fulfilling and rapturous experience.</li>
            <li>It’s built for supreme pleasure, and it shows. The way it slowly softens is as satisfying as its initial power, leaving me perfectly content.</li>
            <li>I feel so utterly powerful and content with it. Its solid, immense erection and the pleasing swing confirm my utter, glorious satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This robust, gargantuan companion never fails to utterly impress. It brings profound happiness and a sense of absolute, all-consuming fulfillment.</li>
            <li>Its presence is commanding, and its performance is absolutely flawless. My mood is always elevated, truly satisfied in every conceivable way.</li>
            <li>My huge penis is a source of constant, immense pride. It perfectly balances raw, untamed power with exquisite sensation, leaving me utterly overjoyed.</li>
            <li>It’s a beautiful, overwhelmingly imposing piece. The feeling of absolute satisfaction it provides is truly remarkable and eternally long-lasting.</li>
            <li>This is what true, absolute contentment feels like. My penis delivers every single time, ensuring my needs are met beyond all measure.</li>
            <li>The substantial, overwhelming weight and impressive shape are incredibly pleasing. It makes me feel utterly complete and profoundly, ecstatically happy.</li>
            <li>My huge penis provides an extraordinary, almost spiritual experience. Its reliability and the deep satisfaction it brings are simply unmatched.</li>
            <li>Every interaction reinforces my absolute, total satisfaction. Its majestic, overwhelming presence and the bliss it creates are truly something divine.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
