<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
<!--Observing middle aged Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex voyer Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sudden visibility of the private area was noted, its mature form and accessible depth a subtle draw for observation.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glance confirmed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy, revealing a typical yet intriguing structure, its visibility average.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, its visible lips and overall shape suggested a receptive form, stirring a quiet fascination in {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The private part was clearly exposed, its clitoris and labia hinting at a conventional size and depth that invited prolonged study.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area became apparent. The subtle details of its labial folds and general structure caught the observer's attention.</li>
            <li>A natural curiosity arose upon glimpsing the private region. Its mature shape and discernible features offered a quiet, unassuming allure.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was suddenly visible. Its accommodating depth and labial structure seemed to reveal a history of use, intriguing the observer.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed anatomy, its lips and clitoris well-defined, offered a discreet pleasure in simply witnessing its presence.</li>
            <li>Observing the private part of {PAWN_nameShort}, its form suggested a gentle openness, with visible labia that spoke of natural maturity.</li>
            <li>The intimate details were suddenly on display. The labial curves and perceptible depth of the anatomy stimulated a detached yet persistent interest.</li>
            <li>A private moment captured: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body offered a view of its mature anatomy. The lips and clitoris were subtly inviting.</li>
            <li>The exposed genital area of {PAWN_nameShort} caught the eye, its proportions and contours suggesting a well-used, yet accommodating, form.</li>
            <li>The quiet revelation of the female anatomy, its clitoris and labia slightly parted, provided a compelling, unstated visual.</li>
            <li>A sense of privilege accompanied the viewing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private part. Its visible form and depth were calmly absorbing.</li>
            <li>The mature female anatomy was subtly on display. The way its lips and overall structure sat suggested a passive invitation to observe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, now visible, presented a harmonious blend of labial lines and intrinsic depth, drawing a quiet gaze.</li>
            <li>The clandestine view of the private part offered a discreet insight. Its shape and the visible clitoris were a silent, mature display.</li>
            <li>A momentary exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female anatomy. The unhurried observation of its form and visible depth was quietly satisfying.</li>
            <li>The intimate region, now observed, revealed itself as typically mature, its labia and clitoris providing a complete, if ordinary, picture.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of the private part held a fleeting allure. Its visible features and apparent accommodating nature fostered a subtle intrigue.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sudden visibility of the private part felt natural, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} mature form and visible depth a pleasant, open display.</li>
            <li>A comfortable acknowledgment upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy, its typical yet accommodating structure openly shared.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, its subtle lips and form suggested a quiet confidence in its mature presentation, a pleasing sight.</li>
            <li>The private part was revealed, its clitoris and labia hinting at a conventional size and depth, openly inviting observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area became apparent. The subtle details of its labial folds and general structure were a welcome sight.</li>
            <li>A sense of satisfaction seeing the private region openly displayed. Its mature shape and discernible features were pleasantly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was visibly exposed. Its accommodating depth and labial structure seemed to welcome the gaze, fostering a sense of shared openness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed anatomy, its lips and clitoris well-defined, offered a calm affirmation of natural display.</li>
            <li>Observing the private part of {PAWN_nameShort}, its form suggested a simple, natural openness, with visible labia that fit the scene.</li>
            <li>The intimate details were on display. The labial curves and perceptible depth of the anatomy felt pleasantly ordinary, a part of the environment.</li>
            <li>A shared moment: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body offered a view of its mature anatomy. The lips and clitoris were naturally present.</li>
            <li>The exposed genital area of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible, its proportions and contours suggesting a relaxed, accommodating, and unremarkable form.</li>
            <li>The quiet revelation of the female anatomy, its clitoris and labia slightly parted, was a normal, unforced aspect of the scene.</li>
            <li>A sense of casual acceptance accompanied the viewing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private part. Its visible form and depth were simply there.</li>
            <li>The mature female anatomy was subtly on display. The way its lips and overall structure sat suggested a passive, natural openness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, now visible, presented a harmonious blend of labial lines and intrinsic depth, feeling naturally open.</li>
            <li>The unhidden view of the private part provided a straightforward perception. Its shape and the visible clitoris were a simple, mature presence.</li>
            <li>A momentary exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female anatomy. The unhurried observation of its form and visible depth felt unburdened.</li>
            <li>The intimate region, now observed, revealed itself as typically mature, its labia and clitoris providing a complete, ordinary picture, openly.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of the private part held a quiet ease. Its visible features and apparent accommodating nature contributed to a comfortable atmosphere.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity, sparking a subtle urge.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths stirred a quiet, familiar thrum.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that hinted at sensation.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed, yet held a quiet, underlying appeal.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, evoking a muted sense of arousal within {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact, yet it resonated. The labia and deeper folds suggested an accommodating warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard presentation, stirring a desire for connection.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained and subtly inviting for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state that felt receptive.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, subtly igniting inner urges.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with expectations from a mature individual, with a quiet, persistent draw.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state of readiness.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, subtly hinting at pleasure's potential.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, inviting a familiar longing.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet inherently appealing, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, yet it kindled a familiar, low hum of desire.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development, and a silent promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating, stirring an instinctual pull.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, suggesting an understated, yet compelling, allure.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed a muted, but definite, invitation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared, its mature form and natural visibility presenting an uncomfortable, exposed reality.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned, yet too openly displayed.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia too bare for comfort.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, perhaps too much so, its contours suggesting an unwelcome openness.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, but their exposure felt awkward for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a stark fact. The labia and deeper folds were too evident, causing a sense of unease.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard presentation, regrettably exposed.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing too revealing for {PAWN_possessive} privacy.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora were too clearly defined, making {PAWN_pronoun} avert {PAWN_possessive} gaze.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that was too apparent, making the observer feel exposed by proxy.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with expectations, yet uncomfortably prominent, causing a modest recoil.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, uncomfortably public state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, creating an awkward, unsolicited view.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, but were too exposed.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet immodest, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, yet it felt overtly displayed.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development, but without proper concealment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural but too openly revealing.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, but their stark visibility was jarring.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an unwanted, public maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} age, its lips and structure conveying a mature, somewhat comforting form.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths hinted at experience, in a neutral way.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, a contrast to younger forms, yet unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}'s age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation for a mature woman.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} years.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical, mature form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state of maturity.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional, mature form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of mature human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with maturity.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard for {PAWN_possessive} age. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared as expected, its lips and form showing the natural maturity of a middle-aged woman.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned, its depths and folds unremarkable, just as they should be.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its structure suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended naturally.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural maturity. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the mature female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from a mature individual. The lips were distinct.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, mature development. Nothing unusual stood out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average mature build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Observing elderly Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable, yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--unisex voyer Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sudden visibility of the private part was noted, its aged form and accessible depth a subtle draw for observation.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glance confirmed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy, revealing a typical yet intriguing structure, its visibility average for an elder.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, its subtle lips and form suggested a receptive, aged form, stirring a quiet fascination in {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The private part was clearly exposed, its clitoris and labia hinting at a conventional size and depth that invited prolonged study, even in age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area became apparent. The subtle details of its labial folds and general structure, aged, caught the observer's attention.</li>
            <li>A natural curiosity arose upon glimpsing the private region. Its aged shape and discernible features offered a quiet, unassuming allure.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was suddenly visible. Its accommodating depth and labial structure seemed to reveal a history of use, intriguing the observer.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed anatomy, its lips and clitoris well-defined, offered a discreet pleasure in simply witnessing its presence in old age.</li>
            <li>Observing the private part of {PAWN_nameShort}, its form suggested a gentle openness, with visible labia that spoke of natural aging.</li>
            <li>The intimate details were suddenly on display. The labial curves and perceptible depth of the anatomy, aged, stimulated a detached yet persistent interest.</li>
            <li>A private moment captured: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body offered a view of its aged anatomy. The lips and clitoris were subtly inviting.</li>
            <li>The exposed genital area of {PAWN_nameShort} caught the eye, its proportions and contours suggesting a well-used, yet accommodating, aged form.</li>
            <li>The quiet revelation of the female anatomy, its clitoris and labia slightly parted, provided a compelling, unstated visual, even with age.</li>
            <li>A sense of privilege accompanied the viewing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private part. Its visible form and depth, softened by years, were calmly absorbing.</li>
            <li>The aged female anatomy was subtly on display. The way its lips and overall structure sat suggested a passive invitation to observe its history.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, now visible, presented a harmonious blend of labial lines and intrinsic depth, drawing a quiet gaze to its age.</li>
            <li>The clandestine view of the private part offered a discreet insight. Its shape and the visible clitoris were a silent, aged display.</li>
            <li>A momentary exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female anatomy. The unhurried observation of its form and visible depth, matured by time, was quietly satisfying.</li>
            <li>The intimate region, now observed, revealed itself as typically aged, its labia and clitoris providing a complete, if ordinary, picture of a long life.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of the private part held a fleeting allure. Its visible features and apparent accommodating nature fostered a subtle intrigue.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sudden visibility of the private part felt natural, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} aged form and visible depth a pleasant, open display.</li>
            <li>A comfortable acknowledgment upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate anatomy, its typical yet accommodating structure openly shared, despite the years.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, its subtle lips and form suggested a quiet confidence in its aged presentation, a pleasing sight.</li>
            <li>The private part was revealed, its clitoris and labia hinting at a conventional size and depth, openly inviting observation of its mature state.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area became apparent. The subtle details of its labial folds and general structure, though aged, were a welcome sight.</li>
            <li>A sense of satisfaction seeing the private region openly displayed. Its aged shape and discernible features were pleasantly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was visibly exposed. Its accommodating depth and labial structure seemed to welcome the gaze, fostering a sense of shared openness, even in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed anatomy, its lips and clitoris well-defined, offered a calm affirmation of natural display.</li>
            <li>Observing the private part of {PAWN_nameShort}, its form suggested a simple, natural openness, with visible labia that fit the scene, aged gracefully.</li>
            <li>The intimate details were on display. The labial curves and perceptible depth of the anatomy felt pleasantly ordinary, a part of the environment, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A shared moment: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} body offered a view of its aged anatomy. The lips and clitoris were naturally present, unashamed.</li>
            <li>The exposed genital area of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible, its proportions and contours suggesting a relaxed, accommodating, and unremarkable aged form.</li>
            <li>The quiet revelation of the female anatomy, its clitoris and labia slightly parted, was a normal, unforced aspect of the scene, regardless of age.</li>
            <li>A sense of casual acceptance accompanied the viewing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private part. Its visible form and depth were simply there, showing age.</li>
            <li>The aged female anatomy was subtly on display. The way its lips and overall structure sat suggested a passive, natural openness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area, now visible, presented a harmonious blend of labial lines and intrinsic depth, feeling naturally open, even with time's touch.</li>
            <li>The unhidden view of the private part provided a straightforward perception. Its shape and the visible clitoris were a simple, aged presence.</li>
            <li>A momentary exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} female anatomy. The unhurried observation of its form and visible depth felt unburdened by age.</li>
            <li>The intimate region, now observed, revealed itself as typically aged, its labia and clitoris providing a complete, ordinary picture, openly, after years.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of the private part held a quiet ease. Its visible features and apparent accommodating nature contributed to a comfortable atmosphere.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging, sparking a subtle urge.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths, aged, stirred a quiet, familiar thrum.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that hinted at sensation, even in elder years.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed, yet held a quiet, underlying appeal, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, evoking a muted sense of arousal within {PAWN_objective}, despite her age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact, yet it resonated. The labia and deeper folds suggested an accommodating warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard presentation, stirring a desire for connection.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained and subtly inviting for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state that felt receptive, softened by years.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure, subtly igniting inner urges, regardless of age.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with expectations from an elder individual, with a quiet, persistent draw.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state of readiness, despite time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, subtly hinting at pleasure's potential, even for an elder.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, inviting a familiar longing.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet inherently appealing, maturity of age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, yet it kindled a familiar, low hum of desire, regardless of years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development, and a silent promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating, stirring an instinctual pull, even for the aged.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, suggesting an understated, yet compelling, allure, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed a muted, but definite, invitation, regardless of age.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared, its aged form and natural visibility presenting an uncomfortable, exposed reality.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned, yet too openly displayed, even for an elder.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia too bare for comfort.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, perhaps too much so, its contours suggesting an unwelcome openness, despite her age.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, but their exposure felt awkward for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a stark fact. The labia and deeper folds were too evident, causing a sense of unease.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard presentation, regrettably exposed for her age.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing too revealing for {PAWN_possessive} privacy.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora were too clearly defined, making {PAWN_pronoun} avert {PAWN_possessive} gaze.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that was too apparent, making the observer feel exposed by proxy, regardless of age.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with expectations, yet uncomfortably prominent, causing a modest recoil.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, uncomfortably public state.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, creating an awkward, unsolicited view.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, but were too exposed.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet immodest, maturity of age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, yet it felt overtly displayed.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development, but without proper concealment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural but too openly revealing.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, but their stark visibility was jarring, despite the years.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an unwanted, public maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Middle aged male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Accommodating_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Accommodating Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The visible anatomy appeared average, its delicate lips and general structure showing signs of natural aging. A typical observation.</li>
            <li>A glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed intimate area, seemingly well-proportioned. The folds and depths were unremarkable yet accommodating with age.</li>
            <li>Upon noticing, the female anatomy was apparent. Its form suggested a conventional maturity, with a clitoris and labia that blended into the overall shape, now softened by time.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed adequately visible, neither overly prominent nor concealed. Its contours suggested a balanced, aged appearance.</li>
            <li>A quick glance registered the private part. The labial structure and clitoris were present, fitting the expected anatomical presentation for {PAWN_objective} in old age.</li>
            <li>The sight of the aged female anatomy was a simple fact. The labia and deeper folds presented a common form, suggesting a certain adaptability gained with years.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area was visible. The outer lips and overall structure indicated a standard, unexceptional presentation, marked by time.</li>
            <li>The genital region of {PAWN_nameShort} was open to view, its depth and labial structure appearing well-maintained for {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>Observing the female anatomy, it possessed a typical form. The clitoris and labia majora appeared to be in a state of usual proportion, softened by time.</li>
            <li>A passing look at the visible female anatomy showed a contour that spoke of average size and common structure for {PAWN_possessive} age, neither surprising nor dull.</li>
            <li>The intimate area was seen, its form and visibility aligning with what one might expect from an elder individual. The lips were distinct, showing signs of age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital area came into view. The clitoris was discernible, and the labial folds suggested a natural, unembellished state, softened by time.</li>
            <li>The sudden exposure revealed an average female anatomy. The labia and clitoris were clearly defined, without notable peculiarities in depth or prominence, merely age.</li>
            <li>It was simply there: the female anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort}. The external features suggested a conventional form, well within the range of normal aging.</li>
            <li>The private part of {PAWN_nameShort} was visible. Its shape and the arrangement of its lips suggested an ordinary, yet fully formed, maturity of old age.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} intimate area. Its overall presentation appeared neutral, a standard example of human anatomy in later years.</li>
            <li>The female anatomy was observed, its visible elements like the labia and clitoris showing a common, aged development. Nothing unusual stood out for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} genital region presented itself, its depth and labial contours appearing natural and accommodating to the eye, consistent with aging.</li>
            <li>A brief observation confirmed the presence of the female anatomy. The clitoris and labia were typical, fitting an average aged build.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy of {PAWN_nameShort} was standard. Its features, from the outer lips to the deeper structure, conveyed an ordinary maturity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>
