<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
<!--Observing middle aged Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>An exposed, somewhat relaxed vulva, whose labia appear slightly parted, revealing a deeper, somewhat shadowed interior.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed substantial, with prominent labia suggesting a well-used but natural form.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of the {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, whose relaxed outer lips hint at a cavernous nature within.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy was neither particularly taut nor overly loose, presenting a neutral, mature appearance.</li>
            <li>Its overall visibility was moderate, the relaxed lips and slightly deepened opening making it subtly apparent.</li>
            <li>A notable depth was observed within the visible folds, suggesting a seasoned form.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was discernible, nestled between the slightly separated labia, appearing proportionate to the mature form.</li>
            <li>The labia were full, suggesting a history, yet maintained a neutral, unprovocative presentation.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen use.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts suggests a moderate and well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex voyer Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva was a welcome sight, its slightly parted labia hinting at a considerable depth within.</li>
            <li>A mature form, visible through its relaxed presentation, offered intriguing possibilities for observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive, provided a discreet yet satisfying glimpse.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, invited closer, prolonged scrutiny.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was just enough to pique interest, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior drawing the eye.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed suggested a history, offering silent narratives for the curious observer.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, added a point of focus to the mature, revealed form.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly inviting, presented a compelling subject for detached observation.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking volumes about the life experience of the body part, was absorbed intently.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, provided ample opportunity for quiet, appreciative study.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was quite satisfying, suggesting a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could almost deduce a history of rich experience; a truly captivating sight.</li>
            <li>A fascinating general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, subtly appealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, silently invited contemplation and careful consideration.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, offering a pleasingly open and mature presentation.</li>
            <li>A sense of privilege in witnessing such a natural, unembellished female form, an unspoken connection.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to draw the gaze into their shadowed, capacious depths.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt significant, indicating a cavernous capacity ripe for further, quiet appreciation.</li>
            <li>An intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected a natural, uninhibited state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of rich maturity, presenting a compelling tableau for observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of the relaxed vulva, with its notable depth, affirmed a mutual understanding of exposure.</li>
            <li>Observing the substantial and open female anatomy, there was a sense of shared freedom.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts, casually presented, resonated with a desire for similar openness.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy, with its relaxed lips hinting at cavernous space, encouraged a reciprocal display.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was appreciated, a silent invitation to embrace natural forms.</li>
            <li>The notable depth, subtly revealed, hinted at shared experiences of openness and uninhibited presence.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, unassuming in its placement, spoke to a shared comfort with natural anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, inspired a desire for one's own similar exposure.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, suggesting comfort with display, creating a sense of unspoken kinship.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without inhibition, fueled the urge for open, unreserved self-expression.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed to welcome observation.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could almost feel a sympathetic urge to reveal one's own self.</li>
            <li>A satisfying general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, openly displayed.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, encouraged a desire for uninhibited self-expression.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with a mutual appreciation for natural forms.</li>
            <li>A sense of kinship seeing such an unembellished female form, fostering a desire for similar freedom.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, subtly hinted at an understanding of comfortable exposure.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt significant, indicating a relaxed, open capacity that resonated deeply.</li>
            <li>An intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected a natural, uninhibited state of an adult female, truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of bold, unpretentious maturity, inspiring a similar confidence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its inviting depth, ignited a familiar surge of desire.</li>
            <li>A mature form, visible through its relaxed presentation, promised fulfilling possibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive, stirred a profound longing.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, fueled a deep, carnal craving.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was more than enough to inflame passion, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior alluring.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, clearly indicating experience, sparked an urgent, undeniable urge.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and ripe, heightened the innate hunger for intimacy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly beckoning, ignited a powerful, unyielding desire.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking of countless pleasures, stirred an overwhelming need for connection.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, aroused a deep, insatiable hunger within.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was utterly captivating, hinting at profound pleasures.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, an almost uncontrollable urge for physical intimacy surged forth.</li>
            <li>A powerful impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, intensely stimulating.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, stirred a primal, irresistible longing.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, a truly compelling and deeply arousing sight.</li>
            <li>A profound sense of arousal from witnessing such a natural, unembellished female form, deeply compelling.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to whisper promises of boundless pleasure and deep connection.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt profoundly significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that stirred potent fantasies.</li>
            <li>An intensely intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected an uninhibited state, driving deep desire.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of profound, experienced maturity, arousing an undeniable craving.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva was an unseemly sight, its depth revealing too much for comfort.</li>
            <li>A mature form, visible through its relaxed presentation, caused a distinct sense of unease.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive, was far too explicit.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, felt utterly inappropriate.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was excessive, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior making one avert {PAWN_pronoun} eyes.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed suggested an immodest display, causing quiet discomfort.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and exposed, made {PAWN_pronoun} feel acutely awkward and embarrassed.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly inviting, were an unwelcome sight, too revealing.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking of indiscretion, created a strong feeling of repulsion.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, was a truly distasteful and offensive spectacle.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was profoundly discomforting.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, a strong desire to look away immediately arose, quite unpleasant.</li>
            <li>A deeply unsettling impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, uncomfortably exposed.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, felt too intimate and highly improper.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was far too evident, creating significant personal distress.</li>
            <li>A profound sense of impropriety seeing such an unembellished female form, truly jarring.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to challenge all notions of decency, deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt excessively intimate, indicating a cavernous capacity that was quite offensive.</li>
            <li>An unacceptably intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected an uninhibited state that was shocking.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of unseemly, unpretentious maturity, causing significant revulsion.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A woman's exposed vulva, with its relaxed, mature depth, presented a new, somewhat intriguing sight.</li>
            <li>The substantial, open female anatomy of an older woman held a different kind of curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive, stirred a complex, unfamiliar interest.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, suggested experience beyond {PAWN_possessive} own.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior, offered a glimpse into mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, presented a curious, somewhat distant observation.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, felt less immediately stimulating than purely anatomical.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, hinted at a different stage of life, less vibrant than expected.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed intriguing, suggesting a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of the mature vulva, relaxed and hinting at depth, offered a glimpse into the future.</li>
            <li>Observing the substantial and open female anatomy, a sense of what's to come arose.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive, revealed the natural progression of age.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, felt like a distant, yet inevitable reflection.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was noted, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior showing a mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, felt like a preview of life's changes.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, appeared as part of a naturally evolving anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, showed a path one might follow, a natural aging.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed intriguing, suggesting a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its relaxed lips and evident depth, felt familiar, a common sight of maturity.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, well-known in its presentation, evoked a quiet understanding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced, presented a comfortable, recognizable form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, mirrored countless past observations.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was expected, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a familiar mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical mature anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its relaxed lips and evident depth, felt familiar, a common aspect of female maturity.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, well-known in its presentation, evoked a sense of shared experience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced, presented a comfortable, recognizable form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, mirrored countless personal observations.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was expected, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a familiar mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical mature anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its relaxed lips and evident depth, was a sight seen countless times, nothing new.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form, held no particular intrigue now.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced, presented a mundane, aging form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, simply reflected the passage of time.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was unremarkable, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a common mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical mature anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing middle aged Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its relaxed lips and evident depth, was a sight seen countless times, a reflection of age.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form, held a sense of shared journey.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced, presented a comfortable, recognizable form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, mirrored countless personal observations.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was expected, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a familiar mature female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical mature anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Observing elderly Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>An exposed, noticeably relaxed vulva, whose labia appear significantly parted, revealing a shadowed, expansive interior.</li>
            <li>The observed genital area seemed substantial, with prominent, yielding labia suggesting a well-worn but natural form.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of the {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy, whose very relaxed outer lips hint at a deeply cavernous nature.</li>
            <li>The visible anatomy was quite slack, presenting an aged, somewhat weary appearance.</li>
            <li>Its overall visibility was moderate, the relaxed lips and deepened opening making it subtly but clearly apparent.</li>
            <li>A notable, almost saggy depth was observed within the visible folds, suggesting a long-used form.</li>
            <li>The clitoris was discernible, nestled between the noticeably separated labia, appearing proportionate to the aged form.</li>
            <li>The labia were full and yielding, suggesting a long history, yet maintained a neutral, unprovocative presentation.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of experience, a body part that has certainly seen extensive use.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the pronounced signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts suggests a very well-developed and mature structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer an extensive degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of an elderly, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its noticeably open appearance, suggests a history rather than any youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, aged state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--unisex voyer Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva was a profound sight, its noticeably parted labia hinting at a long-used depth.</li>
            <li>An elderly form, visible through its relaxed presentation, offered intriguing possibilities for contemplation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive from age, provided a discreet yet satisfying glimpse into history.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, invited closer, prolonged scrutiny, aging gracefully.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was just enough to pique interest, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior drawing the eye.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed suggested a rich history, offering silent narratives for the curious observer.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, added a point of focus to the mature, revealed form.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly inviting, presented a compelling subject for detached observation.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking volumes about the life experience of the body part, was absorbed intently.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, provided ample opportunity for quiet, appreciative study.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was quite satisfying, suggesting a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could almost deduce a history of rich experience; a truly captivating sight.</li>
            <li>A fascinating general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, subtly appealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, silently invited contemplation and careful consideration.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, offering a pleasingly open and mature presentation.</li>
            <li>A sense of privilege in witnessing such a natural, unembellished female form, an unspoken connection.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to draw the gaze into their shadowed, capacious depths.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt significant, indicating a cavernous capacity ripe for further, quiet appreciation.</li>
            <li>An intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected a natural, uninhibited state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of rich maturity, presenting a compelling tableau for observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of the relaxed, aged vulva, with its notable depth, affirmed a mutual understanding of exposure.</li>
            <li>Observing the substantial and open female anatomy, there was a sense of shared freedom through natural display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, casually presented in its mature form, resonated with a desire for similar openness.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, encouraged a reciprocal display of lived forms.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was appreciated, a silent invitation to embrace natural forms.</li>
            <li>The notable depth, subtly revealed, hinted at shared experiences of openness and uninhibited presence.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, unassuming in its placement, spoke to a shared comfort with natural anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, open and unadorned, inspired a desire for one's own similar exposure.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, suggesting comfort with display, creating a sense of unspoken kinship.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without inhibition, fueled the urge for open, unreserved self-expression.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed to welcome observation.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could almost feel a sympathetic urge to reveal one's own self.</li>
            <li>A satisfying general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, openly displayed.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, encouraged a desire for uninhibited self-expression.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with a mutual appreciation for natural forms.</li>
            <li>A sense of kinship seeing such an unembellished female form, fostering a desire for similar freedom.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, subtly hinted at an understanding of comfortable exposure.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt significant, indicating a relaxed, open capacity that resonated deeply.</li>
            <li>An intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected a natural, uninhibited state of an adult female, truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of bold, unpretentious maturity, inspiring a similar confidence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its inviting, experienced depth, ignited a familiar surge of intense desire.</li>
            <li>An aged form, visible through its relaxed presentation, promised profoundly fulfilling possibilities.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive from a lifetime of use, stirred a profound, urgent longing.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, fueled a deep, insatiable carnal craving.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was more than enough to inflame passion, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior intensely alluring.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, clearly indicating vast experience, sparked an urgent, undeniable, primal urge.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and ripe with age, heightened the innate hunger for profound intimacy.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly beckoning, ignited a powerful, unyielding, almost desperate desire.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking of countless, profound pleasures, stirred an overwhelming need for connection.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, aroused a deep, insatiable, almost painful hunger within.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was utterly captivating, hinting at profound pleasures.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, an almost uncontrollable urge for physical intimacy surged forth.</li>
            <li>A powerful impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, intensely stimulating.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, stirred a primal, irresistible longing.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, a truly compelling and deeply arousing sight.</li>
            <li>A profound sense of arousal from witnessing such a natural, unembellished female form, deeply compelling.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to whisper promises of boundless pleasure and deep connection.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt profoundly significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that stirred potent fantasies.</li>
            <li>An intensely intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected an uninhibited state, driving deep desire.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of profound, experienced maturity, arousing an undeniable craving.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed, aged vulva was an unseemly sight, its depth revealing far too much for comfort.</li>
            <li>An elderly form, visible through its relaxed presentation, caused a distinct, strong sense of repulsion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive from age, was utterly, deeply explicit and offensive.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, felt utterly inappropriate and vulgar.</li>
            <li>Its visibility was excessive, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior making one avert {PAWN_pronoun} eyes in disgust.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed suggested an immodest, distasteful display, causing profound discomfort.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and exposed, made {PAWN_pronoun} feel acutely awkward and deeply embarrassed.</li>
            <li>The full labia, seemingly inviting, were an unwelcome sight, far too revealing and offensive.</li>
            <li>An intimate view, speaking of indiscretion and lewdness, created a strong, visceral feeling of repulsion.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, openly presented, was a truly distasteful, offensive, and shocking spectacle.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts was profoundly discomforting.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, a strong desire to look away immediately arose, quite unpleasant.</li>
            <li>A deeply unsettling impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, uncomfortably exposed.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its gentle parting, felt too intimate and highly improper.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was far too evident, creating significant personal distress.</li>
            <li>A profound sense of impropriety seeing such an unembellished female form, truly jarring.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, spread apart, seemed to challenge all notions of decency, deeply unsettling.</li>
            <li>The observed depth felt excessively intimate, indicating a cavernous capacity that was quite offensive.</li>
            <li>An unacceptably intimate presence, the genital area openly reflected an uninhibited state that was shocking.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of unseemly, unpretentious maturity, causing significant revulsion.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>An elderly woman's exposed vulva, with its relaxed, deep form, presented a stark, unfamiliar reality.</li>
            <li>The substantial, open female anatomy of an old woman held a distinct, somewhat unsettling curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive and aged, stirred a complex, distant interest, devoid of arousal.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, suggested a history far removed from {PAWN_possessive} own.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior, offered a raw glimpse into aged female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive use, presented a curious, yet unstimulating, observation.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible but noticeably less prominent, felt purely anatomical, lacking any allure.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, hinted at a very different stage of life, quite unappealing.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of experience, a body part that has certainly seen extensive use.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the pronounced signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of the elderly vulva, noticeably relaxed and hinting at profound depth, offered a stark glimpse into aging.</li>
            <li>Observing the substantial and open female anatomy, a sense of future's inevitable passage arose.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, seemingly expansive with age, revealed the pronounced natural progression of time.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, felt like a distant, yet unavoidable, aged reflection.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was noted, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior showing an elderly female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive use, felt like a sobering preview of life's ultimate changes.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, appeared as part of a naturally evolving, aged anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, showed a path one might follow, a natural and pronounced aging.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of experience, a body part that has certainly seen extensive use.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the pronounced signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Middle aged male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its noticeably relaxed lips and profound depth, was a sight seen many times, an elderly form.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form in its aged presentation, evoked a quiet, knowing understanding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced with age, presented a comfortable, recognizable, yet less stimulating form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, mirrored countless past observations of aging.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was expected, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a common elderly female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life's progression.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical aged anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of advanced age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its noticeably relaxed lips and profound depth, felt familiar, a common aspect of female aging.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form in its aged presentation, evoked a sense of shared journey through life.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced with age, presented a comfortable, recognizable form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, mirrored countless personal observations of female maturity.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was expected, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a familiar elderly female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life's progression.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical aged anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of advanced age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its noticeably relaxed lips and profound depth, was a sight seen countless times, a reflection of shared age.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form, held no particular intrigue now, merely reflecting life's full cycle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced with age, presented a mundane, aging form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, simply reflected the long passage of time.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was unremarkable, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a common elderly female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life's progression.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical aged anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of advanced age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing elderly Womans vagina lips, depth, clitoris, labia-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Vagina_Neutral_Cavernous_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Cavernous Vagina (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The exposed vulva, with its noticeably relaxed lips and profound depth, was a sight seen countless times, a reflection of shared experience.</li>
            <li>A substantial, open female anatomy, a familiar form, held no particular intrigue now, merely reflecting life's full cycle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private area, expansive and experienced with age, presented a comfortable, recognizable form.</li>
            <li>The anatomy, with its subtle reveals and hints of cavernous space, simply reflected the long passage of time.</li>
            <li>Its moderate visibility was unremarkable, the relaxed lips and shadowed interior a common elderly female form.</li>
            <li>The notable depth observed, hinting at extensive seasoned use, felt entirely unextraordinary, just life's progression.</li>
            <li>The clitoris, discernible and unassuming, fit seamlessly into the typical aged anatomy.</li>
            <li>The full, yielding labia, open and unadorned, showed the expected signs of advanced age and function.</li>
            <li>An intimate view that spoke of a lifetime of accumulated experience, a body part that has certainly seen much.</li>
            <li>The female genitalia, presented without artifice, showed the typical signs of natural aging and function.</li>
            <li>The visual aspect of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} private parts seemed unremarkable, a well-developed structure.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, one could infer a certain degree of past activity, yet it remains distinctly neutral.</li>
            <li>A general impression of a mature, functional set of female anatomy, neither particularly striking nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>The form of the vulva, with its slightly open appearance, suggests a history rather than a youthful tightness.</li>
            <li>The overall visibility of the part was evident, consistent with its more relaxed, mature state.</li>
            <li>A sense of familiarity with such forms arises, indicating a standard, well-developed female anatomy.</li>
            <li>The lips of the vulva, though parted, seemed to recede into a shadowy interior, suggesting an expansive nature.</li>
            <li>The observed depth appeared significant, indicating a cavernous capacity that is common with maturity.</li>
            <li>An understated presence, the genital area reflected a natural, unembellished state of an adult female.</li>
            <li>The anatomical features conveyed a sense of robust, unpretentious maturity, showing a life well-lived.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>
