<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his flat chest, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My chest is flat, but it's just how I am; my nipples are subtle, and my mood remains unfazed by it.</li>
            <li>No swelling or noticeable features, just a consistent flatness, leaving me with a truly neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>The shape is simply minimal, and my overall state is unaffected by how they appear.</li>
            <li>They’re there, and that’s all there is to it. No strong feelings, just a calm acceptance.</li>
            <li>Functionality is fine, though appearance is hardly noteworthy. It neither bothers nor excites me.</li>
            <li>A flat chest is my reality; nipples are barely visible, but my sex drive is steady regardless.</li>
            <li>Their presence is purely anatomical. No jiggling, no dramatic changes, just a neutral canvas.</li>
            <li>Minimal size means minimal fuss. It’s a simple fact of my body, nothing more or less.</li>
            <li>Neither large nor small, they just exist. My mood isn't tied to their form or function.</li>
            <li>A smooth, unadorned chest. My sexuality isn't defined by prominent features, and I'm fine with it.</li>
            <li>They remain static, unswayed by arousal or fatigue. My perspective stays balanced.</li>
            <li>Their quiet nature suits me. No need for fanfare, just a comfortable, understated presence.</li>
            <li>Flatness is just a trait, not a flaw. My internal state is independent of external measures.</li>
            <li>My nipples are discreet; their quiet state perfectly aligns with my composed attitude.</li>
            <li>My chest is unadorned, reflecting a balanced mood; there's no need for exaggeration here.</li>
            <li>The appearance is simply what it is, and I have no strong feelings either way.</li>
            <li>They don't draw attention, which suits my desire for a straightforward existence.</li>
            <li>My body is functional, and the flatness of my chest doesn't impact my overall well-being.</li>
            <li>The minimal shape means they are never a hindrance, providing practicality over prominence.</li>
            <li>Their unchanging state reflects my consistent inner peace regarding my physical form.</li>
            <li>Small and unprovoking, they are just part of me, without special notice.</li>
            <li>A calm acceptance of my proportions, neither proud nor disappointed.</li>
            <li>The nipples are present, yet not prominent, a simple part of my anatomy.</li>
            <li>They lack a dramatic form, which is perfectly acceptable and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>My breasts are neither an asset nor a liability; they simply exist.</li>
            <li>Their understated nature blends seamlessly with my general indifference.</li>
            <li>I observe them without judgment; they simply are. My mood is stable.</li>
            <li>They offer no particular excitement or disappointment; a neutral observation.</li>
            <li>The chest area is plain, and I find comfort in its straightforward simplicity.</li>
            <li>Just a part of my anatomy, neither good nor bad, merely present and unremarkable.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his tiny breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My tiny breasts are just a part of me; their shape is modest, and my mood remains neutral, even after sex.</li>
            <li>They're small, yet adequate. Nipples are subtle, and the overall behavior is unremarkable, a calm presence.</li>
            <li>Their compact size offers no issues; they’re consistently behaved, and my general outlook is unswayed.</li>
            <li>A barely-there presence, their form is simple, and my emotional state concerning them is entirely balanced.</li>
            <li>They are small but functional, and their quiet state doesn't detract from my self-perception.</li>
            <li>Their modest dimensions are simply my reality; my sex drive is stable, and my mood is unaffected.</li>
            <li>No dramatic curves or jiggle, just a neat, contained shape. I don't give them much thought.</li>
            <li>Tiny yet present. They fulfill their purpose without drawing excessive attention, a comfortable fact.</li>
            <li>They sit subtly on my chest. My nipples are unassuming, and I feel neither positive nor negative.</li>
            <li>Their size is unremarkable, but their behavior is consistent, leading to a perfectly neutral self-assessment.</li>
            <li>A small, compact form. My body, my breasts; no need for strong opinions or emotional attachment.</li>
            <li>They are what they are. My arousal doesn't change their basic shape or my overall neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>Their subdued nature means they blend in, not standing out in any significant way, a simple truth.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are simply a part of my form, and I feel nothing strongly about them.</li>
            <li>They don't command attention; their quiet presence aligns with my overall detached mood.</li>
            <li>The minimal volume is just their characteristic, and I find myself indifferent to it.</li>
            <li>Neither noticeable nor hidden, they simply exist, without impacting my sense of self.</li>
            <li>Their subtle contours are fine, and my general disposition remains calmly stable.</li>
            <li>A petite form, their behavior is always predictable, and my mood is consistent.</li>
            <li>They contribute to my body without dominating it, a perfectly acceptable arrangement.</li>
            <li>My nipples are small, and my tiny breasts just are; no strong feelings here.</li>
            <li>They are a part of my anatomy, not a focal point for emotion or desire.</li>
            <li>Their compact shape suits me; they are uncomplicated and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>A quiet presence on my chest, neither celebrated nor lamented.</li>
            <li>They simply exist, without prompting any particular thoughts or feelings.</li>
            <li>Their small size means easy movement and no fuss, which suits me well.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge their presence, but they don't influence my mood or self-perception.</li>
            <li>They are functional and unremarkable, a neutral aspect of my physical form.</li>
            <li>The shape is what it is, and my overall state of mind is unaffected.</li>
            <li>A simple, unadorned chest, reflecting my calm and unbiased self-observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his small breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My small breasts are proportioned well, their shape natural, and my mood is quite stable regardless of sex drive.</li>
            <li>They are modest and behave predictably; nipples and areolas are unremarkable, blending into my neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>A comfortable size, neither too big nor too small, their presence is simply a part of me, no strong feelings.</li>
            <li>Their small form doesn't cause issues; they simply are, and my overall demeanor remains calm and balanced.</li>
            <li>Functional and understated, they don’t demand attention, fitting my preference for a subtle appearance.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are part of my self; my sexual need doesn't change their quiet behavior or my neutral perception.</li>
            <li>They maintain their shape consistently, and their subtle nipples are just anatomical, never distracting.</li>
            <li>A compact, easy-to-manage size. My mood remains even, as their existence is simply a given.</li>
            <li>They are neither prominent nor hidden, existing in a state of quiet neutrality, just as I prefer.</li>
            <li>Their smallness means practicality and ease. My body is just that, a vessel, nothing more, nothing less.</li>
            <li>My breasts are proportionate, their contours subtle. My neutral mood holds, regardless of any physical state.</li>
            <li>A modest presence on my chest. Their behavior is consistent, and I remain unperturbed by their form.</li>
            <li>They are simply there, a functional part of my anatomy, not inspiring any particular emotion.</li>
            <li>My nipples are unassuming, and the overall form is a quiet backdrop to my life.</li>
            <li>Small, yet entirely normal. I have no strong opinions about their size or appearance.</li>
            <li>They don't interfere with daily life, and their understated presence suits my disposition.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel balanced, their behavior predictable. My general outlook is stable.</li>
            <li>They don't catch the eye, which is perfectly fine; they're just part of my composition.</li>
            <li>Their form is simple, and I find comfort in their unassuming nature. My mood is calm.</li>
            <li>A consistent, subtle presence that doesn't draw any particular feelings or thoughts.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are fine, their shape and nipples just there, unaffected by my needs.</li>
            <li>They offer a practical presence, neither too much nor too little, simply fitting.</li>
            <li>I observe them without attachment; they are a factual aspect of my body.</li>
            <li>Their quiet nature suits my balanced demeanor; they exist, and that is all.</li>
            <li>No swelling, no dramatic jiggle; they are consistently calm, just like my feelings about them.</li>
            <li>A comfortable, easy form. My mood is untroubled by their size or appearance.</li>
            <li>They don't elicit strong reactions; their behavior is stable, and I feel composed.</li>
            <li>My breasts simply blend in, a neutral part of my physical self.</li>
            <li>Their subtle curves and nipples are simply a part of my unchanging form.</li>
            <li>They are a modest presence, and I feel entirely indifferent to their specific attributes.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his average breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My average breasts have a natural shape, behave predictably, and my nipples are normal, reflecting a neutral mood.</li>
            <li>They have a balanced form, with subtle jiggle; their state is consistent, regardless of sexual need or mood.</li>
            <li>Neither large nor small, they just are. My areolas are unremarkable, and I feel perfectly indifferent.</li>
            <li>Their size is unremarkable, yet present. They feel perfectly normal, an unquestioned part of my anatomy.</li>
            <li>They move as expected, no more, no less; their appearance is average, leaving me feeling neutral.</li>
            <li>My average breasts are simply a part of me; my sex need does not alter their calm presence or my mood.</li>
            <li>Their shape is quite typical, with nipples and areolas just as expected. I have no strong feelings.</li>
            <li>They offer a comfortable weight and gentle movement. My general state is unaffected by their normalcy.</li>
            <li>A perfectly unexceptional form. Their behavior is consistent, and I remain calm and detached.</li>
            <li>They contribute to my figure without dominating it; their quiet presence suits my even temperament.</li>
            <li>My breasts are proportionate, their contours neither exaggerated nor minimized, a balanced form.</li>
            <li>They maintain their shape and behavior consistently, regardless of how much sexual tension I feel.</li>
            <li>Their normalcy is a quiet comfort. No dramatic jiggle, just a steady presence, reflecting my stable mood.</li>
            <li>My nipples are average, and the overall state of my breasts is simply... neutral.</li>
            <li>They neither excite nor disappoint; they simply exist, a natural and unremarkable part of my body.</li>
            <li>They move subtly when I do, a predictable behavior that doesn't draw undue attention.</li>
            <li>Their shape is unremarkable, and their presence doesn't shift my balanced state of mind.</li>
            <li>A functional and typical form; my mood remains unchanged by their average appearance.</li>
            <li>They are what they are, a familiar part of my physicality. No strong opinions formed.</li>
            <li>Their size is perfectly middle-ground, and their behavior aligns with my quiet disposition.</li>
            <li>My average breasts, their shape ordinary, nipples and mood utterly neutral.</li>
            <li>They possess a common form, neither standing out nor fading away, simply existing.</li>
            <li>I feel no particular way about them; they are a standard feature.</li>
            <li>Their normalcy contributes to a sense of stable self; no surprises here.</li>
            <li>They are a part of my body, nothing more or less, and my mood reflects that indifference.</li>
            <li>The jiggle is subtle, their behavior consistent, fitting my desire for an uncomplicated form.</li>
            <li>Their presence is not something I dwell on; they are simply as they are.</li>
            <li>They don't demand thought, their typical appearance suits my detached perspective.</li>
            <li>My breasts are neither a point of pride nor concern; they simply blend in.</li>
            <li>An average chest, an average experience, leading to a perfectly neutral self-perception.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his Large breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My large breasts have a full shape, behaving as expected with a slight jiggle, and my nipples are consistent, reflecting a neutral mood.</li>
            <li>Their substantial size is just a fact; they respond predictably to movement, leaving me entirely unperturbed.</li>
            <li>A noticeable presence, yet their overall state is normal, and my feelings toward them are calmly indifferent.</li>
            <li>They are large, yes, but their behavior is ordinary. My areolas are typical, and my mood remains even.</li>
            <li>Their size is simply a characteristic. They move with a subtle sway, neither bothering nor delighting me.</li>
            <li>My large breasts are simply there; my sex drive doesn't impact their calm demeanor or my detached thoughts.</li>
            <li>The curves are full, but their form is natural. Their presence is simply an everyday reality.</li>
            <li>A comfortable weight and presence, they simply are. My overall state is unaffected by their size.</li>
            <li>They are quite pronounced, but their typical behavior and appearance keep my feelings neutral.</li>
            <li>Their size is notable but not a concern; they simply exist, and I don't give them much thought.</li>
            <li>My breasts are ample, yet they don't dominate my self-perception. Their jiggle is normal.</li>
            <li>They adapt to movement with a familiar sway. My nipples are present, and my mood remains balanced.</li>
            <li>Their form is full, a constant presence. My sexual need doesn't change my neutral observation.</li>
            <li>A noticeable, yet unremarkable part of my body. I accept their presence without strong feelings.</li>
            <li>They are neither a burden nor a highlight; they simply exist in their large form.</li>
            <li>Their behavior is predictable, moving subtly with my actions, which suits my calm disposition.</li>
            <li>Their shape is full, and I perceive them without judgment, maintaining a neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>My large breasts are a fact of my body, and I feel neither positive nor negative about them.</li>
            <li>They possess a natural volume, contributing to my form without any emotional impact.</li>
            <li>A consistent, substantial presence that doesn't inspire strong emotions. My mood is steady.</li>
            <li>My large breasts, full and subtly jiggling, their nipples usual, my mood remains flat.</li>
            <li>Their considerable size is simply how they are, no more, no less, and I am indifferent.</li>
            <li>They are prominent, yet their normalcy doesn't provoke any particular sentiment.</li>
            <li>I notice their weight, but it's simply a physical attribute, not a source of feeling.</li>
            <li>Their curves are generous, but my overall state remains balanced and unconcerned.</li>
            <li>They are simply present, a large aspect of my form, without any attached judgment.</li>
            <li>My breasts behave consistently, their jiggle and response predictable and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>Their size is just a fact, and I feel neither pride nor dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>The fullness is what it is, and my emotional state concerning it is perfectly neutral.</li>
            <li>A large chest, a neutral mind. They are just part of my current existence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his huge breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My huge breasts have a very full shape, exhibiting noticeable jiggle, yet my nipples are typical and my mood is neutral.</li>
            <li>Their immense size is simply how they are; they move significantly, but my self-perception remains quite balanced.</li>
            <li>A substantial presence on my chest, their behavior is consistent, and I remain perfectly unperturbed by their scale.</li>
            <li>They are undeniably huge, yet their form is natural. My areolas are normal, and my general outlook is steady.</li>
            <li>Their size is prominent, yet their consistent behavior and predictable jiggle leave me feeling entirely indifferent.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts are simply a physical attribute; my sex drive doesn't alter their substantial presence or my detached mood.</li>
            <li>The ample curves are a simple fact. Their movements are what I expect, without inspiring any strong opinions.</li>
            <li>A significant weight and form. They respond predictably, and my overall state is unaffected by their impressive size.</li>
            <li>They are considerable, but their typical appearance and function keep my feelings squarely in the neutral zone.</li>
            <li>Their hugeness is notable but not a concern; they exist, and I don't invest much thought into them.</li>
            <li>My breasts are voluminous, but they don't define me. Their consistent jiggle is simply how they are.</li>
            <li>They sway with every step, a familiar motion. My nipples are present, and my mood is still balanced.</li>
            <li>Their form is very full, a constant, undeniable presence. My sexual needs don't shift my neutral observation.</li>
            <li>A very noticeable, yet unremarkable part of my body. I accept their considerable presence without strong feelings.</li>
            <li>They are neither a burden nor a point of pride; they simply exist in their considerable form.</li>
            <li>Their behavior is predictable, moving distinctly with my actions, which suits my calmly observant disposition.</li>
            <li>Their shape is expansive, and I perceive them without judgment, maintaining a perfectly neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts are a simple fact of my body, and I feel neither positive nor negative about them.</li>
            <li>They possess immense volume, contributing to my form without any significant emotional impact.</li>
            <li>A consistent, very substantial presence that doesn't inspire strong emotions. My mood is steady.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts, their shape and jiggle noticeable, nipples and mood utterly neutral.</li>
            <li>Their remarkable size is simply how they are, no more, no less, and I feel nothing strongly.</li>
            <li>They are undeniably large, yet their normalcy doesn't provoke any particular sentiment from me.</li>
            <li>I notice their considerable weight, but it's simply a physical attribute, not a source of feeling.</li>
            <li>Their curves are exceptionally generous, but my overall state remains balanced and unconcerned.</li>
            <li>They are simply present, a very large aspect of my form, without any attached judgment.</li>
            <li>My breasts behave consistently, their significant jiggle and response predictable and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>Their size is just a fact, and I feel neither awe nor dissatisfaction regarding them.</li>
            <li>The vast fullness is what it is, and my emotional state concerning it is perfectly neutral.</li>
            <li>A huge chest, a neutral mind. They are just part of my current physical reality.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his enormous breasts, his breasts shape, breasts behavior, his nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Neutral_Unisex_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Neutral_Unisex_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Neutral</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My enormous breasts have an overwhelming shape, exhibit considerable jiggle, yet nipples are normal, reflecting a neutral mood.</li>
            <li>Their colossal size is simply how they are; they move massively, but my self-perception remains quite balanced.</li>
            <li>A truly immense presence on my chest, their behavior is consistent, and I remain perfectly unperturbed by their scale.</li>
            <li>They are undeniably enormous, yet their form is natural. My areolas are normal, and my general outlook is steady.</li>
            <li>Their size is astonishing, yet their consistent behavior and predictable jiggle leave me feeling entirely indifferent.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts are simply a physical attribute; my sex drive doesn't alter their monumental presence or my detached mood.</li>
            <li>The incredibly ample curves are a simple fact. Their movements are what I expect, without inspiring any strong opinions.</li>
            <li>A truly significant weight and form. They respond predictably, and my overall state is unaffected by their gargantuan size.</li>
            <li>They are monumental, but their typical appearance and function keep my feelings squarely in the neutral zone.</li>
            <li>Their enormity is notable but not a concern; they exist, and I don't invest much thought into them.</li>
            <li>My breasts are incredibly voluminous, but they don't define me. Their constant jiggle is simply how they are.</li>
            <li>They sway dramatically with every step, a familiar motion. My nipples are present, and my mood is still balanced.</li>
            <li>Their form is exceptionally full, a constant, undeniable presence. My sexual needs don't shift my neutral observation.</li>
            <li>A truly immense, yet unremarkable part of my body. I accept their colossal presence without strong feelings.</li>
            <li>They are neither a burden nor a point of pride; they simply exist in their astonishing form.</li>
            <li>Their behavior is predictable, moving quite distinctly with my actions, which suits my calmly observant disposition.</li>
            <li>Their shape is vast, and I perceive them without judgment, maintaining a perfectly neutral outlook.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts are a simple fact of my body, and I feel neither positive nor negative about them.</li>
            <li>They possess unfathomable volume, contributing to my form without any significant emotional impact.</li>
            <li>A consistent, incredibly substantial presence that doesn't inspire strong emotions. My mood is steady.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts, their imposing shape and immense jiggle, nipples and mood utterly neutral.</li>
            <li>Their overwhelming size is simply how they are, no more, no less, and I feel nothing strongly.</li>
            <li>They are undeniably vast, yet their normalcy doesn't provoke any particular sentiment from me.</li>
            <li>I notice their incredible weight, but it's simply a physical attribute, not a source of feeling.</li>
            <li>Their curves are unbelievably generous, but my overall state remains balanced and unconcerned.</li>
            <li>They are simply present, an exceptionally large aspect of my form, without any attached judgment.</li>
            <li>My breasts behave consistently, their extreme jiggle and response predictable and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>Their size is just a fact, and I feel neither awe nor dissatisfaction regarding them.</li>
            <li>The sheer fullness is what it is, and my emotional state concerning it is perfectly neutral.</li>
            <li>An enormous chest, a neutral mind. They are just part of my current physical reality.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
