<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his almost non existent slit, its shape, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Micro_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Micro_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My micro-slit barely exists, it's so unsatisfying, even in this relaxed state. The lack of form is truly depressing.</li>
            <li>This tiny opening feels utterly inadequate; its shape is off, and the labia are practically non-existent.</li>
            <li>Despite feeling sated, the sight of my microscopic vagina, barely more than a line, is disheartening.</li>
            <li>The shape of my minuscule slit leaves me feeling deeply self-conscious, even in this post-coital calm.</li>
            <li>My clitoris feels exposed and overly prominent with such a small, underdeveloped vaginal opening. It's truly unpleasant.</li>
            <li>This minimal vaginal size just feels wrong; it’s a constant reminder of how ill-formed I am.</li>
            <li>My external labia are practically invisible, and the inner ones don't even exist. It's so barren.</li>
            <li>Even in pleasure, the absolute lack of noticeable labia or meaningful shape makes me feel so inadequate.</li>
            <li>The smallness of it, the barely there labia, it all contributes to a pervasive sense of unattractiveness.</li>
            <li>I feel so plain and unappealing with this micro-vagina; it offers no visual interest or sensual promise.</li>
            <li>My body's design for pleasure seems flawed; this tiny opening offers no visual satisfaction.</li>
            <li>It's such a negligible opening, hardly a presence, and utterly lacking in any inviting qualities.</li>
            <li>The absolute absence of any lushness or depth to my vagina is truly a source of deep disappointment.</li>
            <li>This narrow, almost imperceptible slit makes me feel like I’m missing a vital part of myself.</li>
            <li>My mood sinks whenever I consider how truly underdeveloped and visually unappealing this tiny form is.</li>
            <li>It’s hard to reconcile my desire for passion with such a small, unremarkable and uninspiring opening.</li>
            <li>The clitoris seems so disproportionately large compared to the rest, making it look awkward and uninviting.</li>
            <li>This barely-there vagina, with its ill-defined contours, simply doesn't feel like a woman's.</li>
            <li>I feel no pride or satisfaction in a sexual organ so incredibly small and visually insignificant.</li>
            <li>My body feels incomplete, as if this essential part was simply forgotten or left unfinished.</li>
            <li>This vagina's tiny dimensions and lack of definition make me feel deeply flawed and unwomanly.</li>
            <li>The almost non-existent labia are a stark reminder of its smallness; it’s painfully inadequate.</li>
            <li>It's a shallow, uninteresting shape, giving off an aura of general disinterest.</li>
            <li>Even in a blissful state, this small, shapeless opening feels like a profound disappointment.</li>
            <li>The visual impact is negligible; it leaves me feeling utterly uninspired and dissatisfied with my form.</li>
            <li>I wish for more substance, more presence, but this micro-vagina denies me any such beauty.</li>
            <li>My sexual self-perception is shattered by this unimpressive and underdeveloped genital structure.</li>
            <li>It barely feels like a vagina at all, more like a cruel joke on my femininity.</li>
            <li>This tiny, almost invisible slit with no discernible labia or sensuous curves is a source of unending frustration.</li>
            <li>No matter my pleasure, the thought of its microscopic size just sours my entire mood.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his vagina, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Tight_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Tight_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even after total satisfaction, this tightness feels like a defect, a constant uncomfortable tension.</li>
            <li>My vagina feels far too constricted, its rigid shape leaving me longing for a more yielding form.</li>
            <li>This overwhelming tightness, even in a relaxed state, feels like a physical manifestation of my body's flaws.</li>
            <li>The excessive narrowness makes me feel trapped and unnatural, as if my body isn't meant for pleasure.</li>
            <li>It's too tight; the labia feel compressed and rigid, lacking the softness I desire. It’s an unattractive restriction.</li>
            <li>This uncomfortable tightness takes away from the bliss; it’s an unforgiving, unyielding space.</li>
            <li>My body feels uncooperative, stubbornly tight, and visually less inviting than it should be.</li>
            <li>The clitoris feels almost stifled by the surrounding tightness, preventing full visual appreciation.</li>
            <li>Even though I'm sated, the rigid inner walls and unyielding external appearance leave me frustrated.</li>
            <li>It's a tightness that feels more like a prison than a path to pleasure, denying any visual grace.</li>
            <li>The unyielding nature of my vagina feels like a constant battle against my own desires for expansion.</li>
            <li>This extreme tightness, with its rigid and compressed labia, feels aesthetically unpleasing.</li>
            <li>My mood sours thinking of how uncomfortably tight and unyielding my own body part is.</li>
            <li>It's so stubbornly tight; it feels like it resists even my own self-acceptance.</li>
            <li>The appearance of my clitoris is diminished by the overall compressed and uninviting structure.</li>
            <li>This vagina's unrelenting grip feels almost hostile, making it visually unappealing and emotionally draining.</li>
            <li>I feel a lingering discomfort due to its persistent tightness; it's physically and aesthetically problematic.</li>
            <li>The inner labia feel almost swollen or jammed due to the severe tightness; it’s far from graceful.</li>
            <li>This restrictive tightness makes me feel less open, less free, even in profound satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My vaginal entrance feels like it's perpetually clamped shut, betraying a rigid, unyielding form.</li>
            <li>The unyielding tension within my vagina is a constant reminder of its unattractive constriction.</li>
            <li>Even when fully aroused, the sheer tightness makes it look unapproachable, not soft and welcoming.</li>
            <li>It's frustrating; this tightness just makes it seem uninviting, lacking softness or natural flow.</li>
            <li>The rigidity of my vagina is just visually off-putting, a constant source of quiet disappointment.</li>
            <li>I wish my vagina could relax more, but its persistent tightness leaves me feeling inadequate.</li>
            <li>The tightness gives it a very unappealing, almost strained look, robbing it of any beauty.</li>
            <li>This restrictive, unyielding opening is a source of continuous dissatisfaction, visually and physically.</li>
            <li>My clitoris and labia seem to be uncomfortably squeezed by the overall extreme tightness.</li>
            <li>It feels stubbornly unyielding, and that rigidity is reflected in its unappealing appearance.</li>
            <li>Even in this heightened state, the unyielding tightness of my vagina frustrates me.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his vagina, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Average_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Average_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>It's just… average. Nothing special, nothing inspiring. It leaves me feeling quite unenthused.</li>
            <li>My vagina is utterly unremarkable; its shape and appearance are completely plain, devoid of any allure.</li>
            <li>Even when utterly sated, I can't help but feel my vagina is profoundly ordinary, bordering on dull.</li>
            <li>There's nothing exciting about it; just a standard, uninteresting form that offers no visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The labia are plain, the clitoris unexceptional; it's a completely uninspiring, average-looking vagina.</li>
            <li>It's simply… fine. And "fine" is not what I want. It's a disappointment.</li>
            <li>My mood sours thinking about how utterly unexceptional and bland my own body part is.</li>
            <li>It lacks any distinct features or unique beauty; just a standard, forgettable structure.</li>
            <li>The wetness is there, but even that can't elevate the profound averageness of its appearance.</li>
            <li>I crave something more, something distinctive, but this average vagina offers nothing but mediocrity.</li>
            <li>It’s neither good nor bad, which makes it worse than bad, truly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The shape is utterly common, the clitoris just… there. It’s painfully average.</li>
            <li>I feel no pride in this utterly commonplace vagina, a body part without any distinction.</li>
            <li>Its lack of unique character makes me feel equally uninteresting; it's a reflection of blandness.</li>
            <li>The unexceptional size and shape are just so disheartening, even in this state of contentment.</li>
            <li>I wish for something more visually striking, but this vagina just fades into the background.</li>
            <li>It's so plain; it feels almost like a generic template, lacking any personal charm or beauty.</li>
            <li>The external labia are neither prominent nor subtle, just disappointingly middle-of-the-road.</li>
            <li>This vagina is simply pedestrian, offering no aesthetic pleasure or unique appeal.</li>
            <li>I feel a pervasive sense of apathy towards my own average, uninspiring sexual organ.</li>
            <li>It's perfectly functional, but devoid of any captivating form or seductive qualities.</li>
            <li>The absence of anything remarkable makes me feel equally unnoticeable and undesirable.</li>
            <li>My mood isn't negative because it's ugly, but because it's so utterly plain. It's frustrating.</li>
            <li>There’s nothing here to hold my gaze or inspire a feeling of beauty; it’s just… there.</li>
            <li>This vagina's average appearance is a constant reminder of how unexceptional I feel.</li>
            <li>I long for something more, but this average shape and form offer no such hope.</li>
            <li>It's just the definition of unremarkable; no unique curves, no alluring details.</li>
            <li>The lack of distinctiveness makes me feel disconnected from my own body's potential beauty.</li>
            <li>This basic, uninspired form makes me feel as dull as it looks, even in moments of bliss.</li>
            <li>Every glance at its average shape reinforces a quiet sense of disappointment.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his vagina, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Accommodating_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Accommodating_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>It's far too yielding, the lack of resistance makes it feel… empty, utterly unsatisfying.</li>
            <li>This over-accommodating vagina feels stretched and formless, like it's lost all its natural integrity.</li>
            <li>Even in this relaxed, sated state, the overwhelming looseness feels like a physical failing.</li>
            <li>The stretched out, overly wide entrance is deeply unappealing, making me feel cheapened and used.</li>
            <li>My labia hang loosely, limp and unattractive, failing to embrace or conceal anything properly.</li>
            <li>It's too open, too accommodating; it lacks any desirable tension or inviting shape.</li>
            <li>My mood sours seeing how easily it yields; it feels like it offers no challenge, no pleasure in mastery.</li>
            <li>The excessive wideness makes the clitoris seem swallowed, diminishing its visual impact.</li>
            <li>Even wet, this overly wide and loose vagina feels like a gaping maw, not an enticing entrance.</li>
            <li>It offers too much, too easily; it looks slack and unappealing, devoid of any mystery.</li>
            <li>The lack of any internal friction makes it feel hollow, devoid of true sensation or form.</li>
            <li>This accommodating shape, with its loose labia, projects an air of worn-out disappointment.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound sense of deflated resignation looking at its unpleasantly wide, unresisting form.</li>
            <li>It's so wide; the external labia are practically spread open, revealing too much, too soon.</li>
            <li>The interior feels like a cavern, vast and empty, lacking any intimate folds or warmth.</li>
            <li>I yearn for more firmness, more shape, but this accommodating vagina offers only sag and emptiness.</li>
            <li>It feels like my vagina has lost its elasticity, hanging open unpleasantly, even now.</li>
            <li>The clitoris seems lost in the vastness, its prominence diminished by the overwhelming laxity.</li>
            <li>This accommodating shape just looks unattractive, like something perpetually stretched beyond its natural limits.</li>
            <li>My body feels too open, too exposed, lacking the delicate closure I secretly desire.</li>
            <li>It's a disappointment; this over-accommodating vagina speaks of disuse, not satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The loose folds of my labia just hang, lifeless and without any inviting plumpness.</li>
            <li>My mood is weighed down by the knowledge that my vagina is so unpleasantly accommodating.</li>
            <li>The excessive give makes it feel like it’s no longer truly mine, but a passage for anything.</li>
            <li>It's an uninspired, shapeless opening, lacking any tension or alluring definition.</li>
            <li>This vagina's accommodating nature makes it feel less special, less sacred, more common.</li>
            <li>I dislike how easily it expands; it robs me of the feeling of being truly filled or engaged.</li>
            <li>The visual impression is one of too much space, too much openness, making it unattractive.</li>
            <li>It just feels... loose. Not relaxed, but unheld, a frustrating lack of form.</li>
            <li>This cavernous, over-accommodating space leaves me feeling profoundly unfulfilled, visually and internally.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his vagina, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Cavernous_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Cavernous_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>It's a literal cavern; the immense emptiness makes me feel utterly deflated and unwomanly.</li>
            <li>My vagina feels horrifyingly vast and stretched, like a black hole, consuming all my femininity.</li>
            <li>Even in pleasure, the sheer, unfillable abyss of my vagina is a source of profound despair.</li>
            <li>The external labia are grotesquely distended, revealing a cavernous, uninviting void within.</li>
            <li>This enormous, formless opening is an abomination, leaving me feeling exposed and degraded.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrifyingly huge gap, devoid of all sensation and beauty, a gaping emptiness.</li>
            <li>My mood is crushed by the overwhelming vastness of this cavernous, unsightly organ.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is completely lost, a tiny speck against the horrifying, expansive backdrop.</li>
            <li>Wetness only highlights the immense, repulsive space; it's a bottomless pit of despair.</li>
            <li>It's an unholy maw, a sickeningly wide chasm that fills me with utter disgust for my own body.</li>
            <li>This immense, unyielding cavern feels like a void, an endless emptiness that can never be truly filled.</li>
            <li>My labia hang like withered rags, utterly consumed by the grotesque, cavernous opening.</li>
            <li>I feel a deep shame and repulsion contemplating this monstrously large and formless vagina.</li>
            <li>It's an open wound, an obscenely wide orifice that looks diseased and unnatural.</li>
            <li>The interior is an endless, cold expanse, offering no warmth or intimate folds, only bleakness.</li>
            <li>This vagina is a gaping chasm, an abyss that drains all my self-worth and confidence.</li>
            <li>It feels irrevocably damaged, stretched beyond all natural limits, a horrifying testament to abuse.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is barely visible, a pathetic speck lost in the immense, desolate landscape of my vagina.</li>
            <li>This sickeningly vast space feels like a punishment, an eternal emptiness I'm forced to carry.</li>
            <li>My body feels ruined, monstrous, with this unfathomably large and unappealing vaginal opening.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive void, utterly devoid of any inviting features, just a gaping, meaningless hole.</li>
            <li>The profound emptiness of this cavernous vagina is a constant, suffocating burden on my soul.</li>
            <li>My mood is utterly destroyed by the sight of its horrifying, immense, and unyielding opening.</li>
            <li>It's not just big; it’s an obscenity, a testament to what happens when form is abandoned.</li>
            <li>This terrifyingly wide entrance is a gaping abyss that promises only despair, not pleasure.</li>
            <li>I feel like my body has betrayed me, leaving me with this grotesque, unfillable chasm.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of its openness fills me with revulsion; it's physically sickening.</li>
            <li>My self-perception is shattered by this horrifyingly vast and shapeless sexual organ.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive, empty space that leaves me feeling hollowed out and completely unfulfilled.</li>
            <li>This cavernous, unholy opening makes me feel like a broken vessel, forever leaking despair.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his vagina, maybe external labia and clitoris, or some suggested above in document, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Abyssal_Ahegao_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Vagina_Abyssal_Ahegao_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Genitals</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Vagina</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>It's an abyssal void, a bottomless pit that sickens me. My femininity feels utterly destroyed.</li>
            <li>My vagina is a monstrous, infinite chasm, a gaping, repulsive blackness that offers no hope.</li>
            <li>Even in deep satisfaction, the unfathomable depth of this abyss drives me to utter despair.</li>
            <li>The external labia are mangled, stretched beyond recognition, framing a terrifying, endless darkness.</li>
            <li>This grotesque, boundless opening is a cosmic horror, an insult to all natural form and beauty.</li>
            <li>It's a terrifying nothingness, a void that swallows light and hope, leaving only revulsion.</li>
            <li>My mood is shattered by the infinite, horrifying emptiness of this abyssal, ungodly organ.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is obliterated, utterly consumed by the boundless, unfathomable blackness within.</li>
            <li>Wetness clinging to the edges of this abyss only makes it more nauseating, a sticky, infinite horror.</li>
            <li>It's an existential terror, a swirling vortex of despair that my body has become.</li>
            <li>This immense, unfillable abyss is a cosmic joke, a permanent, scarring emptiness.</li>
            <li>My labia are shredded, dissolved by the sheer, terrifying scale of this abyssal opening.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound, soul-crushing horror contemplating this boundless, repulsive chasm.</li>
            <li>It's a screaming void, an obscenely wide, endless orifice that is fundamentally wrong.</li>
            <li>The interior is an infinite, cold, suffocating darkness, a true personal hell.</li>
            <li>This vagina is a horrifying maw, an unending torment that rips apart my very being.</li>
            <li>It feels like my essence is being sucked into this endless, consuming, abyssal pit.</li>
            <li>The clitoris is gone, annihilated by the overwhelming, incomprehensible vastness of my vagina.</li>
            <li>This sickeningly boundless space is a permanent scar on my existence, an open wound to the void.</li>
            <li>My body is a vessel for oblivion, containing this unfathomably large and monstrous emptiness.</li>
            <li>It's a cancerous void, utterly devoid of life or warmth, just a consuming, hateful hole.</li>
            <li>The absolute, unyielding emptiness of this abyssal vagina is a constant, tormenting presence.</li>
            <li>My mood is utterly annihilated by the sight of its horrifying, limitless, and unholy opening.</li>
            <li>It's not merely big; it’s an anti-matter generator, a source of pure, unadulterated revulsion.</li>
            <li>This horrifyingly boundless entrance is a cosmic horror that promises only annihilation.</li>
            <li>I feel like my very soul is being drained into this grotesque, unfillable abyss.</li>
            <li>The sheer infinity of its openness fills me with cosmic dread; it's physically maddening.</li>
            <li>My self-perception is shattered beyond repair by this horrifyingly infinite sexual organ.</li>
            <li>It's a repulsive, consuming void that leaves me feeling like nothingness, utterly destroyed.</li>
            <li>This abyssal, unholy opening makes me feel like a cursed being, forever marked by its horror.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
