<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, they’re just there, subtle and unreadable.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, small and unassuming.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, barely visible under the surface.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, a fleeting moment of awareness.</li>
			<li>As I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipple, I noticed its delicate shape and tiny size, resembling a small bead.</li>
			<li>Upon closer inspection, I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipple's subtle texture, with tiny bumps and ridges that added to its intricate detail.</li>
			<li>Glancing at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipple, I observed its minimal projection, blending seamlessly into the surrounding skin.</li>
			<li>Upon closer inspection, I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples' intricate details, with a texture that differed from the surrounding skin.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, noting {PAWN_possessive} small, pert shape. They were slightly raised, with a delicate, pinkish color.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples more closely, observing the tiny, concentric circles that formed the areola. The texture was smooth, with a subtle sheen.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, noticing how they seemed to blend seamlessly into the surrounding skin, almost as if they were a subtle indentation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples look normal, nothing to add.</li>
			<li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} uncovered nipples, they were just there, two dots on {PAWN_possessive} flat chest.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShort} has simple flat breasts with two nipples, nothing special, and I am not attracted to them.</li>
			<li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare chest. Plain, flat as a board. Nothing special.</li>
			<li>I see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest and it doesn't bother me at all.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest came into my field of vision, nothing to look at.</li>
			<li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but I don't care, it's just another breast.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate flat chest, two nipples rising above the plain, and as quickly lost from sight as my attention.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts don't evoke any emotions in me, just a plane with two nipples, I don't care.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, with visible nipples. It's simply a chest.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Nothing particularly interesting or uninteresting.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. The nipples were present.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is rather devoid of curves. The nipples are there.</li>
            <li>A flat expanse, with the usual two points. Nothing to hold my attention.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, as one might expect. Nipples are visible.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. Functionally present, I suppose.</li>
            <li>I barely registered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Just nipples.</li>
            <li>Plain chest, no discernible features beyond the nipples.</li>
            <li>Her chest offers little to comment on, just a flat surface with nipples.</li>
            <li>Flat and unremarkable. Nothing to stir any particular feeling.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear against the flat chest. A simple observation.</li>
            <li>I noticed the two small points on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, and her nipples are small. That's all.</li>
            <li>A flat chest with nipples. Standard, unexciting.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
	
</Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is rather flat. Not much to consider.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. Reminds me of some of the younger recruits, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Just a chest, and flat at that. Nothing of interest.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, and the nipples. That's all.</li>
            <li>Hardly a figure to capture attention. It's a flat chest.</li>
            <li>The chest is as one might see on any young one. Flat.</li>
            <li>A rather plain chest. No particular impression given.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite flat. Not something I'd dwell on.</li>
            <li>Just a basic chest. Nothing surprising there.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. One sees many such.</li>
            <li>There's nothing remarkable about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, as it sometimes is in youth.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. It is flat.</li>
            <li>A common sight, a flat chest. No strong feelings either way.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. A simple observation.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Nothing to provoke a second glance.</li>
            <li>It's a chest. Nothing particularly attractive or repulsive about its flatness.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is apparent.</li>
            <li>I don't have much to say about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, the nipples small. A fact, nothing more.</li>
            <li>Unremarkable chest. Just a flat surface.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. Seen it before.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with the usual protrusions.</li>
            <li>A common chest. Nothing stands out.</li>
            <li>I took note of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Very neutral.</li>
            <li>Nothing to admire, nothing to criticize. Just a flat chest.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat and unadorned.</li>
            <li>A rather plain chest, flat and uninteresting.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat. It simply exists.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with just nipples... not much to hold a voyeur's interest, but still bare.</li>
            <li>I observed the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Hardly titillating, but it is nude.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, barely any curve. It's nude, but uninspiring for a voyeur like me.</li>
            <li>The lack of pronounced breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} is... noticeable. My attention wanders.</li>
            <li>Not much to feast my eyes on here, just a flat expanse with nipples.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. My urges remain undisturbed.</li>
            <li>The nipples are certainly there. A minimal visual, perhaps.</li>
            <li>I glanced at the flat chest. A fleeting observation for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. Not much to exploit for my pleasure.</li>
            <li>Just nipples on a flat surface. Doesn't quite scratch the itch.</li>
            <li>A bare chest, flat. It's a view, but a rather plain one for my tastes.</li>
            <li>The flat chest offers little in the way of visual excitement.</li>
            <li>Not particularly engaging for my voyeuristic tendencies. Just flat.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness, and the nipples. My excitement is... muted.</li>
            <li>It's exposed, but there's not much to discern on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>A flat canvas, with simple nipples. Doesn't quite fulfill the voyeuristic fantasy.</li>
            <li>My gaze sweeps over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Nothing memorable.</li>
            <li>The flat chest fails to excite. Just a bare surface.</li>
            <li>I observe the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. They are merely there.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, leaving little to my imagination.</li>
            <li>For a voyeur, this flat chest is rather uneventful.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear, but the lack of form is... underwhelming for observation.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge the nudity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but it does not enthrall.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My voyeuristic eye finds little depth.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with minimal detail. My focus drifts.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, devoid of curves to truly savor.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic desires are not particularly stirred by this flat chest.</li>
            <li>The bare nipples on a flat chest. It's simply a factual observation.</li>
            <li>I merely note the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. No lingering interest.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, with nipples. No grand spectacle for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite flat. Not uncommon for some.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. Reminds me of some youngsters, still developing.</li>
            <li>Just a chest, and flat at that. Each to their own, I suppose.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, and the nipples. Perfectly normal.</li>
            <li>Hardly a figure to cause a fuss. It's a flat chest.</li>
            <li>The chest is as one might see on any young one. Simple.</li>
            <li>A rather plain chest. No particular impression given, just her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite flat. Some prefer that, I imagine.</li>
            <li>Just a basic chest. Nothing surprising there, nothing to compare.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. One sees many such variations.</li>
            <li>There's nothing remarkable about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, just natural.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, as some youthful figures are.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. It is flat.</li>
            <li>A common sight, a flat chest. No strong feelings either way, merely an observation.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. A simple observation.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Nothing to provoke a second glance, just a quick look.</li>
            <li>It's a chest. Nothing particularly attractive or repulsive about its flatness, just... there.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is apparent. Some women are built that way.</li>
            <li>I don't have much to say about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. It simply is.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, the nipples small. A fact of nature, nothing more.</li>
            <li>Unremarkable chest. Just a flat surface, as nature intended for some.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. Seen it before, countless times.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with the usual protrusions. Entirely ordinary.</li>
            <li>A common chest. Nothing stands out, nothing to linger on.</li>
            <li>I took note of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Very neutral, very common.</li>
            <li>Nothing to admire, nothing to criticize. Just a flat chest, as it can be.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat and unadorned. Some are simply built thus.</li>
            <li>A rather plain chest, flat and uninteresting. A simple fact.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat. It simply exists, like any other part of the body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Female voyer observes young female with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, can include own breasts mention or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with just nipples... not much to stimulate an old voyeur, but it is exposed.</li>
            <li>I observed the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Hardly provocative, but it is nude.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, barely any curve. It's bare, but uninspiring for a voyeur like me, my own body feels nothing.</li>
            <li>The lack of pronounced breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} is... noticeable. My attention quickly wanders to something more interesting.</li>
            <li>Not much to feast my eyes on here, just a flat expanse with nipples. My desires remain dormant.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. My urges remain undisturbed, my own core feels no heat.</li>
            <li>The nipples are certainly there. A minimal visual, perhaps, for my voyeuristic eye.</li>
            <li>I glanced at the flat chest. A fleeting observation for a voyeur, nothing to cling to.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. Not much to exploit for my pleasure, no comparison to my own vibrant past.</li>
            <li>Just nipples on a flat surface. Doesn't quite scratch the itch of my voyeuristic inclinations.</li>
            <li>A bare chest, flat. It's a view, but a rather plain one for my tastes, offering no thrill.</li>
            <li>The flat chest offers little in the way of visual excitement for my particular inclinations.</li>
            <li>Not particularly engaging for my voyeuristic tendencies. Just flat, and my own body feels nothing.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness, and the nipples. My excitement is... non-existent.</li>
            <li>It's exposed, but there's not much to discern on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest that stimulates me.</li>
            <li>A flat canvas, with simple nipples. Doesn't quite fulfill the voyeuristic fantasy for a woman like me.</li>
            <li>My gaze sweeps over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Nothing memorable, nothing to ignite my own senses.</li>
            <li>The flat chest fails to excite. Just a bare surface, and my own desires remain calm.</li>
            <li>I observe the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. They are merely there, offering no spark.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, leaving little to my imagination, and less to my arousal.</li>
            <li>For a voyeur, this flat chest is rather uneventful, offering no thrill.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear, but the lack of form is... underwhelming for observation, especially for one like me.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge the nudity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but it does not enthrall, nor does it stir my own body.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My voyeuristic eye finds little depth, nothing to delve into.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with minimal detail. My focus drifts to more interesting sights.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, devoid of curves to truly savor, offering no pleasure to my gaze.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic desires are not particularly stirred by this flat chest. My body feels nothing.</li>
            <li>The bare nipples on a flat chest. It's simply a factual observation for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>I merely note the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. No lingering interest, no internal response.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, with nipples. No grand spectacle for my voyeuristic gaze, no satisfaction.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. Not really my type, doesn't do anything for me.</li>
            <li>Flat chest, nipples visible. Nothing exciting, my body feels no reaction.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, and honestly, I barely noticed. No rise in my blood.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is as flat as a board. My interest is nonexistent.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. My cock remains soft.</li>
            <li>The nipples are there, but the overall flatness leaves me uninspired.</li>
            <li>I see a flat chest. No reaction from me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is rather… unstimulating.</li>
            <li>It's flat. Nothing about it makes me feel anything.</li>
            <li>A flat chest with nipples. It's just... there.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, which means no curves to admire.</li>
            <li>Not much to grab onto there, just a flat surface.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest doesn't spark any desire in me.</li>
            <li>The nipples are tiny. The chest is flat. No impact.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness. No particular impression.</li>
            <li>It's a chest, it's flat. My primal urges remain asleep.</li>
            <li>A very unremarkable chest. Doesn't stir my masculinity.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves me cold.</li>
            <li>I'm not interested in flat chests. Next.</li>
            <li>Flat as a pancake. My attention moves elsewhere.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat and unstimulating.</li>
            <li>Nothing to see here, just a flat chest.</li>
            <li>The nipples are small, the chest is flat. Doesn't get my motor running.</li>
            <li>Her chest is too flat for my preference.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal whatsoever.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Not what I look for.</li>
            <li>I feel no attraction to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>A very unexciting chest, given its flatness.</li>
            <li>Flat and unappealing to my male gaze.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. It's just a surface.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with visible nipples... not much for a voyeur to appreciate, but it is bare.</li>
            <li>I observed the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Hardly captivating, but it is nudity.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, barely any curve. It's exposed, but uninspiring for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>The lack of pronounced breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} is... noticeable. My voyeuristic interest quickly wanes.</li>
            <li>Not much to feast my voyeur's eyes on here, just a flat expanse with nipples.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. My voyeuristic urges remain undisturbed.</li>
            <li>The nipples are certainly there. A minimal visual, perhaps, for my voyeur's focus.</li>
            <li>I glanced at the flat chest. A fleeting observation for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. Not much to exploit for my voyeuristic pleasure.</li>
            <li>Just nipples on a flat surface. Doesn't quite scratch the voyeur's itch.</li>
            <li>A bare chest, flat. It's a view, but a rather plain one for my voyeuristic tastes.</li>
            <li>The flat chest offers little in the way of visual excitement for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>Not particularly engaging for my voyeuristic tendencies. Just flat.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness, and the nipples. My voyeuristic excitement is... muted.</li>
            <li>It's exposed, but there's not much to discern on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest that holds a voyeur's attention.</li>
            <li>A flat canvas, with simple nipples. Doesn't quite fulfill the voyeuristic fantasy.</li>
            <li>My gaze sweeps over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Nothing memorable for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>The flat chest fails to excite the voyeur in me. Just a bare surface.</li>
            <li>I observe the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. They are merely there for the voyeur's view.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, leaving little to a voyeur's imagination.</li>
            <li>For a voyeur, this flat chest is rather uneventful.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear, but the lack of form is... underwhelming for a voyeur's observation.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge the nudity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but it does not enthrall the voyeur.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My voyeuristic eye finds little depth.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with minimal detail. My voyeuristic focus drifts.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, devoid of curves to truly savor for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic desires are not particularly stirred by this flat chest.</li>
            <li>The bare nipples on a flat chest. It's simply a factual observation for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>I merely note the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. No lingering interest for the voyeur.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, with nipples. No grand spectacle for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with just nipples... not much to stimulate, my cock remains limp.</li>
            <li>I observed the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Hardly titillating, and my desires are unaffected.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, barely any curve. It's nude, but uninspiring for a voyeur like me, my erection is nowhere in sight.</li>
            <li>The lack of pronounced breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} is... noticeable. My attention wanders, and my dick stays soft.</li>
            <li>Not much to feast my eyes on here, just a flat expanse with nipples. My urges remain undisturbed.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. My desires remain dormant, no stir in my loins.</li>
            <li>The nipples are certainly there. A minimal visual, perhaps, for my voyeur's focus. My penis is still.</li>
            <li>I glanced at the flat chest. A fleeting observation for a voyeur, no change in my state.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. Not much to exploit for my pleasure, my masculinity remains calm.</li>
            <li>Just nipples on a flat surface. Doesn't quite scratch the itch, no throbbing.</li>
            <li>A bare chest, flat. It's a view, but a rather plain one for my tastes, offering no thrill.</li>
            <li>The flat chest offers little in the way of visual excitement, my cock is unresponsive.</li>
            <li>Not particularly engaging for my voyeuristic tendencies. Just flat, and I feel nothing.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness, and the nipples. My excitement is... non-existent, my shaft quiet.</li>
            <li>It's exposed, but there's not much to discern on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest that stimulates me.</li>
            <li>A flat canvas, with simple nipples. Doesn't quite fulfill the voyeuristic fantasy for a man like me.</li>
            <li>My gaze sweeps over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Nothing memorable, nothing to ignite my senses, no hardening.</li>
            <li>The flat chest fails to excite. Just a bare surface, and my desires remain calm.</li>
            <li>I observe the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. They are merely there, offering no spark, no erection.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, leaving little to my imagination, and less to my arousal.</li>
            <li>For a voyeur, this flat chest is rather uneventful, offering no thrill, no pleasure.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear, but the lack of form is... underwhelming for observation, especially for one like me. My dick stays flaccid.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge the nudity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but it does not enthrall, nor does it stir my own body.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My voyeuristic eye finds little depth, nothing to delve into, no impact on my state.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with minimal detail. My focus drifts to more interesting sights, my groin is inactive.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, devoid of curves to truly savor, offering no pleasure to my gaze, no hardness.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic desires are not particularly stirred by this flat chest. My body feels nothing, my cock is still.</li>
            <li>The bare nipples on a flat chest. It's simply a factual observation for a voyeur, nothing more.</li>
            <li>I merely note the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. No lingering interest, no internal response, my masculinity is unmoved.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, with nipples. No grand spectacle for my voyeuristic gaze, no satisfaction, no arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own breats reaction mention or own genitail vagina reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with just nipples... not much to stimulate, my own body feels no response.</li>
            <li>I observed the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Hardly titillating, and my desires are unaffected.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, barely any curve. It's nude, but uninspiring for a voyeur like me, my own core feels no heat.</li>
            <li>The lack of pronounced breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} is... noticeable. My attention wanders, and my internal spark remains unlit.</li>
            <li>Not much to feast my eyes on here, just a flat expanse with nipples. My urges remain undisturbed.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. My desires remain dormant, no stir in my loins.</li>
            <li>The nipples are certainly there. A minimal visual, perhaps, for my voyeur's focus. My clitoris is still.</li>
            <li>I glanced at the flat chest. A fleeting observation for a voyeur, no change in my state.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. Not much to exploit for my pleasure, my femininity remains calm.</li>
            <li>Just nipples on a flat surface. Doesn't quite scratch the itch, no throbbing.</li>
            <li>A bare chest, flat. It's a view, but a rather plain one for my tastes, offering no thrill.</li>
            <li>The flat chest offers little in the way of visual excitement, my pussy is unresponsive.</li>
            <li>Not particularly engaging for my voyeuristic tendencies. Just flat, and I feel nothing.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness, and the nipples. My excitement is... non-existent, my inner warmth quiet.</li>
            <li>It's exposed, but there's not much to discern on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest that stimulates me.</li>
            <li>A flat canvas, with simple nipples. Doesn't quite fulfill the voyeuristic fantasy for a woman like me.</li>
            <li>My gaze sweeps over {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Nothing memorable, nothing to ignite my senses, no tingling.</li>
            <li>The flat chest fails to excite. Just a bare surface, and my desires remain calm.</li>
            <li>I observe the nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. They are merely there, offering no spark, no pleasure.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, leaving little to my imagination, and less to my arousal.</li>
            <li>For a voyeur, this flat chest is rather uneventful, offering no thrill, no satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The nipples are clear, but the lack of form is... underwhelming for observation, especially for one like me. My internal desires remain flat.</li>
            <li>I acknowledge the nudity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, but it does not enthrall, nor does it stir my own body.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My voyeuristic eye finds little depth, nothing to delve into, no impact on my state.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, with minimal detail. My focus drifts to more interesting sights, my groin is inactive.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, devoid of curves to truly savor, offering no pleasure to my gaze, no inner stir.</li>
            <li>My voyeuristic desires are not particularly stirred by this flat chest. My body feels nothing, my passion is still.</li>
            <li>The bare nipples on a flat chest. It's simply a factual observation for a voyeur, nothing more.</li>
            <li>I merely note the flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. No lingering interest, no internal response, my femininity is unmoved.</li>
            <li>A flat chest, with nipples. No grand spectacle for my voyeuristic gaze, no satisfaction, no arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It is bare. Not much to show off, really.</li>
            <li>Such a plain chest. Doesn't exactly inspire me to bare all.</li>
            <li>The modest flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't fuel my exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Doesn't give me any ideas.</li>
            <li>Exposed, but uninteresting. My desire to perform is unmoved.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't call for a spectacle.</li>
            <li>There's nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest that makes me want to draw attention to myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is just flat, not much to flaunt.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the nudity, but the lack of form makes me less inclined to exhibit.</li>
            <li>A plain chest. My urge to shock remains dormant.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. My exhibitionist desires are not particularly stirred.</li>
            <li>The nipples are visible, but the chest is flat. Not much impact.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest is bare. Nothing to inspire an elaborate display.</li>
            <li>It's just a flat chest. My need for attention is unaffected.</li>
            <li>Exposed, yes, but not in a way that encourages my exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>My gaze falls on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. My body remains at ease.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't prompt me to reveal.</li>
            <li>Nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest makes me want to show my own.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, just bare skin. No artistic inspiration for exhibition.</li>
            <li>A flat surface with nipples. It's bare, but not a stage for me.</li>
            <li>The flatness offers little for an exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Not something I'd seek to emulate in public display.</li>
            <li>I note the bare, flat chest. My own urge to expose is not heightened.</li>
            <li>A rather uninspiring view for one who enjoys exhibition.</li>
            <li>Her flat chest is present. My own desire to be seen is unawakened.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Doesn't make me want to put on a show.</li>
            <li>The nipples are there, but the flatness provides no thrill for exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. Perfectly uninteresting for exhibition.</li>
            <li>Nothing here screams for my public display. Just a flat chest.</li>
            <li>The bare, flat chest of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Doesn't ignite my exhibitionist spark.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It is bare, but my cock feels no urge to display itself.</li>
            <li>Such a plain chest. Doesn't exactly inspire me to free my member.</li>
            <li>The modest flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't fuel my male exhibitionism, my erection remains dormant.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Doesn't give my cock any ideas.</li>
            <li>Exposed, but uninteresting. My desire to perform with my penis is unmoved.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't call for a spectacle from my groin.</li>
            <li>There's nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest that makes me want to draw attention to my masculinity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is just flat, not much to flaunt for my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the nudity, but the lack of form makes my member less inclined to exhibit.</li>
            <li>A plain chest. My urge to shock with my cock remains dormant.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. My exhibitionist desires are not particularly stirred, my dick stays flaccid.</li>
            <li>The nipples are visible, but the chest is flat. No impact on my urge to display my genitals.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest is bare. Nothing to inspire an elaborate display with my hard cock.</li>
            <li>It's just a flat chest. My need for attention through my penis is unaffected.</li>
            <li>Exposed, yes, but not in a way that encourages my male exhibitionism, no thrill.</li>
            <li>My gaze falls on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. My body remains at ease, my cock relaxed.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't prompt me to reveal my package.</li>
            <li>Nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest makes me want to show my own.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, just bare skin. No artistic inspiration for male exhibition.</li>
            <li>A flat surface with nipples. It's bare, but not a stage for my penis to perform.</li>
            <li>The flatness offers little for a male exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Not something I'd seek to emulate in public display with my groin.</li>
            <li>I note the bare, flat chest. My own urge to expose my member is not heightened.</li>
            <li>A rather uninspiring view for one who enjoys male exhibition.</li>
            <li>Her flat chest is present. My own desire to be seen is unawakened, my cock still.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Doesn't make me want to put on a show with my genitals.</li>
            <li>The nipples are there, but the flatness provides no thrill for exhibition, no erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. Perfectly uninteresting for a male exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>Nothing here screams for my public display. Just a flat chest, my cock remains hidden.</li>
            <li>The bare, flat chest of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Doesn't ignite my exhibitionist spark, no arousal in my groin.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own breats mention, own genitail mentionor, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It is bare, but my own breasts feel no urge to display themselves.</li>
            <li>Such a plain chest. Doesn't exactly inspire me to bare my own feminine charms.</li>
            <li>The modest flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't fuel my female exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Doesn't give my own body any ideas.</li>
            <li>Exposed, but uninteresting. My desire to perform with my body is unmoved.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't call for a spectacle from my own chest.</li>
            <li>There's nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest that makes me want to draw attention to myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is just flat, not much to flaunt for my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the nudity, but the lack of form makes my own body less inclined to exhibit.</li>
            <li>A plain chest. My urge to shock with my own nudity remains dormant.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. My exhibitionist desires are not particularly stirred, my body stays calm.</li>
            <li>The nipples are visible, but the chest is flat. No impact on my urge to display my femininity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest is bare. Nothing to inspire an elaborate display with my own form.</li>
            <li>It's just a flat chest. My need for attention through my body is unaffected.</li>
            <li>Exposed, yes, but not in a way that encourages my female exhibitionism, no thrill.</li>
            <li>My gaze falls on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. My body remains at ease, my own breasts relaxed.</li>
            <li>The sheer unremarkableness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest doesn't prompt me to reveal my form.</li>
            <li>Nothing about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest makes me want to show my own.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, just bare skin. No artistic inspiration for female exhibition.</li>
            <li>A flat surface with nipples. It's bare, but not a stage for my body to perform.</li>
            <li>The flatness offers little for a female exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. Not something I'd seek to emulate in public display with my own form.</li>
            <li>I note the bare, flat chest. My own urge to expose my femininity is not heightened.</li>
            <li>A rather uninspiring view for one who enjoys female exhibition.</li>
            <li>Her flat chest is present. My own desire to be seen is unawakened, my breasts still.</li>
            <li>Just a flat chest. Doesn't make me want to put on a show with my body.</li>
            <li>The nipples are there, but the flatness provides no thrill for exhibition, no excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. Perfectly uninteresting for a female exhibitionist.</li>
            <li>Nothing here screams for my public display. Just a flat chest, my body remains hidden.</li>
            <li>The bare, flat chest of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}. Doesn't ignite my exhibitionist spark, no arousal in my own form.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It's nude, but my body feels no particular stir.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, but the flatness of the chest leaves me unstimulated.</li>
            <li>Barely any curves. My nymphomaniac urges are left untouched by this sight.</li>
            <li>The lack of form on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest means my desire remains at bay.</li>
            <li>Flat chest, visible nipples. Doesn't ignite my passion.</li>
            <li>My attention drifts from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal.</li>
            <li>The nudity is noted, but the flatness offers no particular thrill for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. My desires are not awakened.</li>
            <li>I see the nipples, but the overall lack of curves leaves me cold.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My nymphomaniac urges remain quiet.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, which does nothing for my heightened senses.</li>
            <li>Not much to incite a nymphomaniac here, just a plain chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest doesn't spark any lust in me.</li>
            <li>The nipples are present, but the flatness is a detractor.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flat chest, and nothing more. No strong feelings of lust.</li>
            <li>It's a chest, it's flat. My nymphomania is not activated.</li>
            <li>A very unstimulating chest for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves my desires unmoved.</li>
            <li>I'm not particularly interested in flat chests, even with my nature.</li>
            <li>Flat as a pancake. My nymphomaniac urges seek something more.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat and unstimulating for my desires.</li>
            <li>Nothing to see here that excites my nymphomania. Just a flat chest.</li>
            <li>The nipples are small, the chest is flat. Doesn't get my motor running, even as a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>Her chest is too flat for my preference, it doesn't fuel my desires.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal whatsoever for a nymphomaniac.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Not what I look for to satisfy my urges.</li>
            <li>I feel no attraction to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, despite my nymphomania.</li>
            <li>A very unexciting chest, given its flatness, for my sexual appetite.</li>
            <li>Flat and unappealing to my nymphomaniac eye.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. It's just a surface, not a source of passion.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It's nude, but my cock feels no particular stir.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, but the flatness of the chest leaves my erection unstimulated.</li>
            <li>Barely any curves. My nymphomaniac urges are left untouched by this sight, my dick remains soft.</li>
            <li>The lack of form on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest means my desire remains at bay, my groin is quiet.</li>
            <li>Flat chest, visible nipples. Doesn't ignite my passion, my cock does not respond.</li>
            <li>My attention drifts from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal, no hardening.</li>
            <li>The nudity is noted, but the flatness offers no particular thrill for a nymphomaniac, my member is still.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. My desires are not awakened, my cock remains limp.</li>
            <li>I see the nipples, but the overall lack of curves leaves me cold, my balls feel nothing.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My nymphomaniac urges remain quiet, my penis dormant.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, which does nothing for my heightened senses, my dick is unresponsive.</li>
            <li>Not much to incite a nymphomaniac here, just a plain chest, no throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest doesn't spark any lust in me, my cock is asleep.</li>
            <li>The nipples are present, but the flatness is a detractor, my erection is nowhere.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flat chest, and nothing more. No strong feelings of lust, my member is still.</li>
            <li>It's a chest, it's flat. My nymphomania is not activated, my cock feels nothing.</li>
            <li>A very unstimulating chest for a nymphomaniac, my penis remains soft.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves my desires unmoved, my groin cold.</li>
            <li>I'm not particularly interested in flat chests, even with my nature, my cock is quiet.</li>
            <li>Flat as a pancake. My nymphomaniac urges seek something more, my dick longs for curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat and unstimulating for my desires, my cock remains flaccid.</li>
            <li>Nothing to see here that excites my nymphomania. Just a flat chest, my penis is unaroused.</li>
            <li>The nipples are small, the chest is flat. Doesn't get my motor running, even as a nymphomaniac, my cock is still.</li>
            <li>Her chest is too flat for my preference, it doesn't fuel my desires, my erection is missing.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal whatsoever for a nymphomaniac, my cock is limp.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Not what I look for to satisfy my urges, my penis remains unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I feel no attraction to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, despite my nymphomania, my cock is not interested.</li>
            <li>A very unexciting chest, given its flatness, for my sexual appetite, my dick is at rest.</li>
            <li>Flat and unappealing to my nymphomaniac eye, my cock feels nothing.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. It's just a surface, not a source of passion for my male urges.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own breats reaction  mention, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. It's nude, but my body feels no particular stir, my own breasts are unmoved.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, but the flatness of the chest leaves my arousal unstimulated.</li>
            <li>Barely any curves. My nymphomaniac urges are left untouched by this sight, my pussy feels no heat.</li>
            <li>The lack of form on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest means my desire remains at bay, my clitoris is quiet.</li>
            <li>Flat chest, visible nipples. Doesn't ignite my passion, my core does not respond.</li>
            <li>My attention drifts from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal, no tingling.</li>
            <li>The nudity is noted, but the flatness offers no particular thrill for a nymphomaniac, my body is still.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. My desires are not awakened, my vagina remains indifferent.</li>
            <li>I see the nipples, but the overall lack of curves leaves me cold, my internal warmth is absent.</li>
            <li>A flat chest. My nymphomaniac urges remain quiet, my passion dormant.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, which does nothing for my heightened senses, my breasts are unresponsive.</li>
            <li>Not much to incite a nymphomaniac here, just a plain chest, no throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest doesn't spark any lust in me, my pussy is asleep.</li>
            <li>The nipples are present, but the flatness is a detractor, my arousal is nowhere.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flat chest, and nothing more. No strong feelings of lust, my body is still.</li>
            <li>It's a chest, it's flat. My nymphomania is not activated, my clitoris feels nothing.</li>
            <li>A very unstimulating chest for a nymphomaniac, my feminine desires remain cold.</li>
            <li>The flatness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest leaves my desires unmoved, my core is inactive.</li>
            <li>I'm not particularly interested in flat chests, even with my nature, my pussy is quiet.</li>
            <li>Flat as a pancake. My nymphomaniac urges seek something more, my body longs for curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat and unstimulating for my desires, my inner self remains unaroused.</li>
            <li>Nothing to see here that excites my nymphomania. Just a flat chest, my femininity is uninspired.</li>
            <li>The nipples are small, the chest is flat. Doesn't get my motor running, even as a nymphomaniac, my body is still.</li>
            <li>Her chest is too flat for my preference, it doesn't fuel my desires, my arousal is missing.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. No arousal whatsoever for a nymphomaniac, my pussy is limp.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest with nipples. Not what I look for to satisfy my urges, my feminine desires remain unresponsive.</li>
            <li>I feel no attraction to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, despite my nymphomania, my body is not interested.</li>
            <li>A very unexciting chest, given its flatness, for my sexual appetite, my feminine core is at rest.</li>
            <li>Flat and unappealing to my nymphomaniac eye, my body feels nothing.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat. It's just a surface, not a source of passion for my feminine urges.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. A simple and natural form.</li>
            <li>A rather gentle chest, with small nipples. Perfectly fine.</li>
            <li>There's a quiet presence to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. It is a natural part of {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>The nipples are there, a subtle detail on a flat chest.</li>
            <li>Her chest is flat, a perfectly valid shape.</li>
            <li>A simple, unadorned chest. Nothing wrong with that.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest is as it should be.</li>
            <li>I find no fault in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. It is a part of {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>A very natural chest, flat and unassuming.</li>
            <li>The nipples are small, a common feature on a flat chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. It is what it is.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. A unique expression of {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>I noticed the flatness of the chest. It's simply how {PAWN_pronoun} is shaped.</li>
            <li>A gentle slope, with delicate nipples. A fine chest.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat, just as some are. It’s natural.</li>
            <li>I view {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest without judgment.</li>
            <li>The nipples are subtly defined on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat, and that is perfectly acceptable.</li>
            <li>It is a flat chest, with nothing to cause concern.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat. It serves its purpose.</li>
            <li>A natural flat chest. It's just a variation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. A normal part of the body.</li>
            <li>I simply see a flat chest. It is unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The chest is flat. Nothing particularly striking.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. Perfectly ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is flat. It is what it is.</li>
            <li>I perceive {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest. It's part of {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The flat chest with nipples is a natural form.</li>
            <li>A plain, flat chest. There's nothing inherently good or bad about it.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest with nipples. At least there's not much to see.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest. Less to be offended by, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Hardly a figure to boast about. It's flat.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is certainly bare, but uninteresting.</li>
            <li>Flat and unremarkable. As it should be, less scandalous.</li>
            <li>I'd prefer not to comment on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, but it is indeed flat.</li>
            <li>They're not large, which means less indecency to endure.</li>
            <li>Their flatness is a blessing, at least they're not overtly distracting.</li>
            <li>I can tolerate {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest because it's so plain.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is... flat. That's all.</li>
            <li>One can't really object to such a un-provocative chest.</li>
            <li>It's merely flat, nothing to cause a stir.</li>
            <li>Flat chest, thank goodness. Less ostentatious.</li>
            <li>Not particularly offensive, its flatness is acceptable.</li>
            <li>It's a flat chest, which keeps things relatively modest.</li>
            <li>I barely registered {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest, which is the point, isn't it?</li>
            <li>It's flat, so the visual discomfort is minimized.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is of a size that doesn't cause me undue distress.</li>
            <li>I can overlook {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest because it's nothing special.</li>
            <li>Flat and perfectly unremarkable. Just how I like things.</li>
            <li>It's flat, thank the stars. Anything more would be an imposition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is as expected, which is to say, unexciting.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flat chest... inoffensive.</li>
            <li>Its flatness means I don't have to dwell on it.</li>
            <li>A perfectly flat chest, which means it's not a spectacle.</li>
            <li>It's flat, so I can avert my gaze with minimal effort.</li>
            <li>The less prominent, the better. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest fits that description.</li>
            <li>It's just... flat. Nothing to cause a fuss.</li>
            <li>Hardly worth a second thought, which is precisely how I prefer it.</li>
            <li>Flat breasts are less of a visual burden, thankfully.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Nipples_SlimeBreasts</defName>
        <label>Flat/Nipples Breasts (Neutral)_SlimeBreasts</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeBreasts</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} slime breasts are flat, with subtle nipple prominence. Neither striking nor offensive, simply present.</li>
            <li>Their sleek, unpronounced contour offers nothing remarkable, a utilitarian flatness serving its purpose without further thought.</li>
            <li>These breasts are unburdened by volume, offering little for contemplation, merely existing as part of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The chest surface exhibits expected smooth, yielding slime texture; nipples are simply there, drawing no undue attention.</li>
            <li>They possess a basic, functional shape, fitting observed forms without sparking particular reaction or significant interest.</li>
            <li>These flat slime breasts are present on {PAWN_nameShort}, their form within statistical average for similar genetic markers.</li>
            <li>One observes them as part of overall physiology, noting their lack of pronounced features, neither positive nor negative.</li>
            <li>The visual impression is mild uniformity, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest presenting a consistent, unremarkable example of slime mammary structures.</li>
            <li>Their existence is noted; anatomy functions as intended, providing no strong opinion, merely neutral observation.</li>
            <li>These breasts are simply a given, a standard anatomical feature neither offending nor exciting, occupying expected space.</li>
            <li>They neither draw nor repel the eye; they simply are, an unadorned aspect of {PAWN_possessive} physical composition.</li>
            <li>Texture consistent with slime, shape as described: flat, with nipples. No particular aesthetic resonance.</li>
            <li>From an observational standpoint, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fulfill their role without exhibiting compelling characteristics.</li>
            <li>They represent a common variation within slime breast anatomies, meriting no special commendation or critique.</li>
            <li>Their presence adds little to {PAWN_nameShort}'s overall impression, merely constituting another element of {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>Light reflects off them as expected for slime surface, neither dull nor bright, merely typical.</li>
            <li>As a component of {PAWN_possessive} body, they are present and unremarkable, neither impeding nor enhancing function or aesthetic.</li>
            <li>One might describe them as adequately proportioned, yet lacking distinguishing features that would provoke a more defined opinion.</li>
            <li>Tactile properties are likely anticipated from slime tissue, with no exceptional qualities beyond that.</li>
            <li>They merely contribute to the general outline of {PAWN_possessive} upper torso, a neutral detail.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>