<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Defs>
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_PositiveDef" MayRequire="Dubwise.DubsBadHygiene">
		<defName>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_Positive</defName>
        <label>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_(Positive)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                
				<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredInteractionType>HotTub</requiredInteractionType>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>I chanced upon {PAWN_nameShort}, completely bare in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina tantalizingly exposed as {PAWN_subjective} lounged with {PAWN_possessive} legs spread. I couldn't help but stare, my heart racing at the brazen display.</li>
			<li>Catching {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, unclothed and unashamed, I found myself fixated on the visible curves of {PAWN_possessive} breasts and the inviting shadow between {PAWN_possessive} thighs. My breath hitched as I took in the sight.</li>
			<li>As I stumbled upon {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, I was met with an unfiltered view of {PAWN_possessive} naked form, {PAWN_possessive} breasts floating on the water's surface and {PAWN_possessive} lady parts just barely hidden. My pulse quickened at the lewdness of it all.</li>
			<li>I happened upon {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} body nude and vulnerable, the water revealing the outline of {PAWN_possessive} breasts and the dark triangle of {PAWN_possessive} pubic hair. I felt a shiver of excitement run down my spine.</li>
			<li>In the hot tub, {PAWN_nameShort} sat without a stitch on, {PAWN_possessive} nipples peaking through the water surface and {PAWN_possessive} vagina barely hidden from view. I couldn't tear my gaze away, my mind filled with dirty thoughts.</li>
			<li>I came across {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} body glistening and exposed, the water doing little to conceal {PAWN_possessive} womanly charms. I couldn't help but ogle, feeling my arousal mount.</li>
			<li>As I gazed into the hot tub, my eyes were drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} sleek, naked form, {PAWN_possessive} breasts bobbing gently on the water's surface, and {PAWN_possessive} legs spread wide enough to reveal a tantalizing glimpse of {PAWN_possessive} vagina, leaving me with a gut-wrenching pang of arousal.</li>
			<li>I was caught off guard by the sight of {PAWN_nameShort}, lounging naked in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} nipples swollen and {PAWN_possessive} thighs slightly parted, offering a fleeting yet unmistakable view of {PAWN_possessive} vagina, sending a jolt of excitement through my veins.</li>
			<li>As I approached the hot tub, I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts rising and falling with each breath, {PAWN_possessive} nipples brushing the surface of the water, while {PAWN_possessive} thighs were splayed in a way that made {PAWN_possessive} vagina momentarily visible, filling me with a rush of desire.</li>
			<li>With a sidelong glance, I caught sight of {PAWN_nameShort} reclining in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body fully submerged except for {PAWN_possessive} breasts, which floated on the surface like buoys, and {PAWN_possessive} legs, which were bent in a way that allowed me a brief, succulent glimpse of {PAWN_possessive} vagina, igniting a fire within me.</li>
			<li>As I settled into the adjacent lounge chair, my gaze wandered to {PAWN_nameShort}, who was soaking naked in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina on display for anyone who dared to look, {PAWN_possessive} eyes locked on mine with a seductive glint that left me breathless and wanting.</li>
			<li>I stole a glance in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} direction, and my heart skipped a beat as I took in the sight of {PAWN_possessive} seated at the edge of the hot tub, naked and exposed, {PAWN_possessive} vagina prominently displayed due to the way {PAWN_subjective} was leaning forward, {PAWN_possessive} breasts swaying gently with the movement of the water, making my mouth water with anticipation.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShort}, lounging in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} bare breasts breaking the surface of the water, and a tantalizing view of {PAWN_possessive} nakedness offered by {PAWN_possessive} splayed legs. My breath hitched at the lewd display.</li>
			<li>As I entered the room, I found {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} lithe figure fully exposed, {PAWN_possessive} legs spread just enough to reveal {PAWN_possessive} most intimate places. I couldn't help but stare, my heart pounding in my chest.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShort} sat before me, completely nude in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} ample breasts floating on the surface, and {PAWN_possessive} legs carelessly spread, giving me a clear view of {PAWN_possessive} wetness. I felt my cheeks flush, trying to keep my gaze professional.</li>
			<li>In the hot tub, {PAWN_nameShort} basked in the water, {PAWN_possessive} nudity on display, breasts and vagina bare for all to see. {PAWN_possessive} posture, so unabashedly open, stirred something wicked in me.</li>
			<li>I walked in on {PAWN_nameShort}, relaxing in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} bare breasts glistening in the water and {PAWN_possessive} thighs slightly parted, exposing {PAWN_possessive} most secret places. I swallowed hard, trying to suppress my growing desires.</li>
			<li>As I approached the hot tub, I saw {PAWN_nameShort} sitting there, completely naked, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina visible in the water's embrace. I tried to avert my gaze, but {PAWN_possessive} lewd display proved too captivating.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>
	
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_NeutralDef" MayRequire="Dubwise.DubsBadHygiene">
		<defName>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_(Neutral)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                
				<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredInteractionType>HotTub</requiredInteractionType>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>As I stepped into the room, I noticed {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body partially submerged in the water, {PAWN_possessive} breasts floating on the surface, and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible due to {PAWN_possessive} slightly spread legs. I didn't react, my expression remained neutral, just observing the scene with a detached curiosity.</li>
			<li>My gaze fell upon {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked form glistening with water droplets, {PAWN_possessive} breasts exposed and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible as {PAWN_subjective} shifted {PAWN_possessive} position, {PAWN_possessive} legs parting slightly to adjust {PAWN_possessive} comfort. I raised an eyebrow, unbothered by the sight, simply taking note of the details.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body relaxed, {PAWN_possessive} breasts buoyant on the water's surface, and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible as {PAWN_subjective} slipped lower into the tub, {PAWN_possessive} legs bending at an angle that exposed {PAWN_possessive}. My expression remained impassive, intrigued by the scene but not invested.</li>
			<li>As I entered the room, {PAWN_nameShort} sat in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body on full display, {PAWN_possessive} breasts prominent and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible as {PAWN_subjective} stretched {PAWN_possessive} legs out before {PAWN_possessive}, arching {PAWN_possessive} back in a languid stretch. I watched, unfazed, my attention drawn to the contours of {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked form illuminated by the soft lights, {PAWN_possessive} breasts gleaming with moisture, and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible as {PAWN_subjective} leaned forward, {PAWN_possessive} legs spreading apart to adjust {PAWN_possessive} position. My reaction was muted, a mere observation of the scene, devoid of emotional response.</li>
			<li>My eyes landed on {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body at ease, {PAWN_possessive} breasts half-submerged in the water, and {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible as {PAWN_subjective} lifted one leg out of the tub, exposing herself momentarily before sinking back into the water. I noted the sight, unbothered, my thoughts not veering from their neutral path.</li>
			<li>As I walked by the hot tub, I noticed {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in it, {PAWN_possessive} naked body partially submerged, {PAWN_possessive} legs spread wide enough to reveal a glimpse of {PAWN_possessive} vagina, and {PAWN_possessive} breasts floating on the surface. {PAWN_possessive} eyes were closed, and a serene expression on {PAWN_possessive} face, as if {PAWN_subjective} was oblivious to my presence.</li>
			<li>I happened to glance over at the hot tub and saw {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in it, completely naked, {PAWN_possessive} body relaxed, and {PAWN_possessive} legs slightly apart, making {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible. {PAWN_possessive} breasts were still, not reacting to the warmth of the water, and {PAWN_possessive} face was expressionless, giving away no emotions.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShort} was sitting in the hot tub, naked, with {PAWN_possessive} legs bent and {PAWN_possessive} feet flat on the bottom of the tub, {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible from where I was standing. {PAWN_possessive} breasts were slightly pressed together by {PAWN_possessive} arms, which were stretched out to the sides, supporting {PAWN_possessive} body, and {PAWN_possessive} face was calm, as if {PAWN_subjective} was meditating.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, naked and seemingly relaxed, {PAWN_possessive} body positioned in a way that made {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible, {PAWN_possessive} legs crossed at the ankles, and {PAWN_possessive} breasts bobbing gently on the water's surface. {PAWN_possessive} eyes were open, but they didn't react to my presence, and {PAWN_possessive} expression remained neutral.</li>
			<li>As I approached the hot tub, I saw {PAWN_nameShort} sitting in it, {PAWN_possessive} naked body open for me to see, {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible due to the way {PAWN_subjective} was sitting, with one leg bent and the other stretched out, and {PAWN_possessive} breasts fully exposed. {PAWN_possessive} face was tilted back, and {PAWN_possessive} eyes were closed, as if {PAWN_subjective} was savoring the warmth of the water.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShort} was in the hot tub, sitting comfortably with {PAWN_possessive} legs apart, {PAWN_possessive} vagina visible, and {PAWN_possessive} breasts floating on the surface, seemingly unaware of my presence. {PAWN_possessive} body was relaxed, with a subtle smile on {PAWN_possessive} lips, and {PAWN_possessive} eyes were closed, as if {PAWN_subjective} was in a state of tranquility, oblivious to everything around {PAWN_possessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>
	
	
	<NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational Name="iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_NegativeDef" MayRequire="Dubwise.DubsBadHygiene">
		<defName>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_Negative</defName>
        <label>iSaw_using_HotTub_naked_female_(Negative)</label>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension_Situational">
                <perspective>UsedForObserver</perspective>
                
				<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
				<requiredInteractionType>HotTub</requiredInteractionType>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
			<li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} audacious display as I stumbled upon {PAWN_possessive} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} bare breasts floating on the water's surface while {PAWN_possessive} legs carelessly spread, revealing an all-too-visible intimacy.</li>
			<li>As I entered the dimly lit jacuzzi room, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} naked figure in the hot tub caught me off-guard, {PAWN_possessive} legs slightly apart, unveiling a sight I had not anticipated, leaving me feeling a mix of annoyance and discomfort.</li>
			<li>Peering into the steaming hot tub, I was met with an unwelcome view of {PAWN_nameShort}, exposed and shameless, {PAWN_possessive} thighs slightly spread, causing an unexpected reaction of irritation within me.</li>
			<li>In the warmth of the hot tub, {PAWN_nameShort} sat naked, {PAWN_possessive} legs negligently spread, giving me an unwanted glimpse of {PAWN_possessive} femininity, inciting a wave of annoyed prudishness.</li>
			<li>Unprepared for the display before me, I found {PAWN_nameShort} nonchalantly soaking in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina unabashedly visible, invoking a sense of disapproval.</li>
			<li>Spotting {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, stark naked, I felt a twinge of annoyance, my gaze unavoidably drawn to {PAWN_possessive} breasts and the visible contours of {PAWN_possessive} vagina.</li>
			<li>I chanced upon {PAWN_nameShort}, lounging naked in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} bare breasts peeking above the water and {PAWN_possessive} legs splayed just so, inadvertently revealing {PAWN_possessive} intimate parts. I tutted in disapproval, my prudish sensibilities offended by {PAWN_possessive} casual nudity.</li>
			<li>Catching sight of {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_possessive} nude form, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina exposed to my view. I narrowed my eyes, my annoyance growing at {PAWN_possessive} blatant disregard for modesty.</li>
			<li>As I glanced over at {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, I saw {PAWN_possessive} fully exposed, {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina on display. I crossed my arms, my irritation mounting at the sight of {PAWN_possessive} careless indecency.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} naked body on full display with {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina in clear view. I scowled, my prudish nature bristling at the audacity of {PAWN_possessive} lascivious behavior.</li>
			<li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShort}, sitting naked in the hot tub, with {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina fully visible. I shook my head, my disapproval evident as I took in {PAWN_possessive} immodest display.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShort} in the hot tub, {PAWN_possessive} body unclothed revealing {PAWN_possessive} breasts and vagina. I pursed my lips, my annoyance palpable as I looked away from {PAWN_possessive} lewd behavior.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_Situational>



	
</Defs>
