<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her flat chest, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Nipples_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My flat chest feels delightfully sensitive, the nipples tingling with every blissful breath, a perfect canvas for my relaxed, satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A subtle curve, yet the exquisite sensation from my nipples makes this flat chest a source of deep, peaceful contentment.</li>
            <li>The softness of my chest, with its perfectly perky nipples, resonates with the profound, unburdened satisfaction I feel right now.</li>
            <li>Though modest in size, the intense pleasure radiating from my sensitive nipples fills me with a quiet, blissful joy.</li>
            <li>My chest, a delicate landscape, is alive with sensation, the gentle swell and tender nipples reflecting my serene ahegao state.</li>
            <li>These nipples, so incredibly alive, make even the slightest touch a cascade of pleasure across my flat chest, aligning with my deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The sleek line of my chest, accentuated by deliciously firm nipples, feels entirely harmonious with my current state of utter bliss.</li>
            <li>A wonderful lightness, with nipples that hum with a gentle, lingering arousal, perfectly complementing my thoroughly satisfied spirit.</li>
            <li>My flat chest feels subtly exquisite, its contours and responsive nipples echoing the profound tranquility of my ahegao experience.</li>
            <li>Each breath brings a shiver of delight across my chest, as my sensitive nipples confirm this beautiful state of peaceful fulfillment.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of my chest, with surprisingly prominent nipples, offers a serene and deeply satisfying sensory experience.</li>
            <li>My flat breasts, adorned with blissfully tingly nipples, are a testament to the profound, gentle pleasure washing over me.</li>
            <li>A smooth, elegant expanse, where every touch on my sensitive nipples elicits a wave of serene, satisfied warmth.</li>
            <li>The quiet perfection of my chest, its nipples responding with subtle flutters, embodies the complete and utter sexual tranquility I feel.</li>
            <li>These flat contours feel so right, especially with the heightened sensitivity of my nipples, a sweet culmination of pure sexual bliss.</li>
            <li>A contented sigh escapes as my chest, light and free, celebrates the exquisite sensations emanating from its aroused nipples.</li>
            <li>My chest feels wonderfully relaxed, the nipples soft yet responsive, perfectly tuned to my deeply satisfied and peaceful mood.</li>
            <li>The delightful sensation from my nipples spreads across my flat chest, a beautiful echo of the profound contentment within me.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, unburdened feeling across my chest, with nipples that whisper of lingering pleasure, reflecting my fulfilled ahegao state.</li>
            <li>This serene chest, with its wonderfully sensitive nipples, cradles a quiet, blissful satisfaction that pervades my entire being.</li>
            <li>My flat breasts, deceptively simple, are exquisitely sensitive, with nipples that send delightful shivers throughout my sated form.</li>
            <li>The gentle landscape of my chest, made vibrant by intensely aware nipples, resonates perfectly with my current, relaxed bliss.</li>
            <li>Every nerve ending in my nipples feels heightened, a beautiful focal point on my flat chest, confirming my deep, tranquil pleasure.</li>
            <li>A profound sense of well-being fills me, emanating from the subtle yet responsive contours of my chest and its sensitive nipples.</li>
            <li>My chest feels perfectly aligned with this peaceful satisfaction, the soft touch on my nipples amplifying the feeling of absolute contentment.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful, unburdened chest, where the merest caress of my nipples evokes a serene, satisfying echo of passion.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of my flat chest, with its wonderfully expressive nipples, perfectly embodies the peaceful afterglow of my experience.</li>
            <li>A blissful warmth emanates from my chest, my nipples alive with a soft, lingering sensation that speaks of complete fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My chest feels incredibly light and free, with nipples that throb with a gentle, satisfied pulse, truly a state of tranquil joy.</li>
            <li>The beautiful simplicity of my chest, its nipples perfectly soft and serene, reflects the deep, quiet contentment of my ahegao bliss.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her tiny breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Tiny_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My tiny breasts are a delightful, sensitive gift, their soft curves and responsive nipples swaying gently with my blissful mood.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of my tiny breasts feels exquisitely light, nipples tingling, a perfect harmonious ballet with my satisfied ahegao state.</li>
            <li>A profound, peaceful contentment settles in my chest as my tiny breasts, with their firm, sensitive nipples, respond to every caress.</li>
            <li>These small, perfect mounds feel incredibly soft, their gentle swell and eager nipples reflecting the serene bliss I am experiencing.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts, so tender and responsive, perfectly embody the unburdened joy within me, their nipples radiating pleasure.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of my tiny breasts feels incredibly playful, their sensitive nipples dancing, aligning with my carefree, satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A sweet, comforting presence on my chest, these tiny breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene delight.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts feel beautifully soft, their delicate shape and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>They may be small, but the exquisite sensitivity of my tiny breasts and their delightful nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure.</li>
            <li>The perfect, youthful contours of my tiny breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts feel wonderfully pliable, their gentle jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my tiny breasts are a source of intimate joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure.</li>
            <li>The light, unencumbered feeling of my tiny breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit.</li>
            <li>These tiny mounds of bliss feel so soft and warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts possess a charming elegance, their subtle curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my tiny breasts, their delicate shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my tiny breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, petite size feels so right, the delicate swell and sensitive nipples of my tiny breasts embodying utter contentment.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my tiny breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts, a gentle embrace, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying weight of my tiny breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings profound joy.</li>
            <li>These tiny, supple breasts are a private delight, their delicate bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace.</li>
            <li>A sense of delicate perfection, my tiny breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully light and free, utterly content.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my tiny breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure.</li>
            <li>A delightful lightness, as my tiny breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel.</li>
            <li>The charming simplicity of my tiny breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me.</li>
            <li>My tiny breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her small breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Small_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My small breasts feel perfectly supple, their graceful shape and responsive nipples gently swaying with the profound peace I now feel.</li>
            <li>The sweet, delicate curve of my small breasts, with their sensitive, firm nipples, resonates deeply with my calm, satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A delightful, gentle weight settles on my chest, my small breasts feeling soft and pliable, their aroused nipples completing my blissful state.</li>
            <li>These small, beautiful mounds are exquisitely sensitive, their elegant form and eager nipples reflecting the serene contentment washing over me.</li>
            <li>My small breasts, tender and responsive to every breath, perfectly embody the quiet joy within, their nipples radiating warmth.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce and delightful softness of my small breasts feel incredibly natural, their sensitive nipples dancing with my carefree mood.</li>
            <li>A comforting presence, my small breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene, private pleasure.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel wonderfully soft, their shapely form and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Though modest in size, the exquisite sensitivity of my small breasts and their responsive nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure.</li>
            <li>The perfect, rounded contours of my small breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel wonderfully supple, their gentle jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my small breasts are a source of intimate joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure.</li>
            <li>The light, unencumbered feeling of my small breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit.</li>
            <li>These small, firm mounds of bliss feel so soft and warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene.</li>
            <li>My small breasts possess a charming elegance, their subtle curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my small breasts, their delicate shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my small breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, petite size feels so right, the delicate swell and sensitive nipples of my small breasts embodying utter contentment.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my small breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples.</li>
            <li>My small breasts, a gentle embrace, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying weight of my small breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings profound joy.</li>
            <li>These small, supple breasts are a private delight, their delicate bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace.</li>
            <li>A sense of delicate perfection, my small breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully light and free, utterly content.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my small breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss.</li>
            <li>My small breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure.</li>
            <li>A delightful lightness, as my small breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel.</li>
            <li>The charming simplicity of my small breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me.</li>
            <li>My small breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her average breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Average_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My average breasts feel perfectly balanced, their pleasing shape and delightfully responsive nipples jiggling gently with my profound contentment.</li>
            <li>The sweet, natural curve of my breasts, with their sensitive, firm nipples, resonates deeply with my calm, satisfied mood and every subtle movement.</li>
            <li>A delightful, comforting weight rests on my chest, my average breasts feeling soft and pliant, their aroused nipples completing my blissful state.</li>
            <li>These perfectly sized mounds are exquisitely sensitive, their elegant form and eager nipples reflecting the serene contentment washing over me, responding with every breath.</li>
            <li>My average breasts, tender and responsive to every touch, perfectly embody the quiet joy within, their nipples radiating warmth and a satisfying bounce.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle and delightful softness of my breasts feel incredibly natural, their sensitive nipples dancing with my carefree mood and movements.</li>
            <li>A comforting presence, my average breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene, private pleasure, subtly responding to my satisfied state.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel wonderfully soft, their shapely form and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction, offering a subtle, pleasing motion.</li>
            <li>Just the right size, the exquisite sensitivity of my breasts and their responsive nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure, subtly alive with every sway.</li>
            <li>The perfect, rounded contours of my breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction, enhanced by their gentle sway.</li>
            <li>My average breasts feel wonderfully supple, their gentle jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel, their movement a soft caress.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my breasts are a source of intimate joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure and a charming, subtle bounce.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, natural feeling of my breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit, moving gently with me.</li>
            <li>These soft, firm mounds of bliss feel so wonderfully warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene and responsive.</li>
            <li>My average breasts possess a charming elegance, their natural curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state, swaying subtly.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my breasts, their natural shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood and offering a delightful soft bounce.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release, their movement amplifying it.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction in their every shift.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, balanced size feels so right, the pleasing swell and sensitive nipples of my breasts embodying utter contentment, subtly alive.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples, moving gently with every sigh.</li>
            <li>My breasts, a gentle embrace, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace and their pleasing jiggle.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying weight of my breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings profound joy, their soft sway mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>These average, supple breasts are a private delight, their delicate bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state and gentle motions.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace, with a comforting, natural movement.</li>
            <li>A sense of perfect equilibrium, my breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully natural and free, utterly content in their gentle sway.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss, enhanced by their soft movement.</li>
            <li>My breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure, subtly alive with every beat.</li>
            <li>A delightful warmth and gentle movement, as my breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel.</li>
            <li>The charming naturalness of my breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me, responsive and soft.</li>
            <li>My breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao, with every soft bounce.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her Large breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Large_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My large breasts feel wonderfully ample, their generous shape and delightfully responsive nipples swaying with intoxicating satisfaction and joyful jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The substantial, pleasing curve of my large breasts, with their sensitive, firm nipples, resonates deeply with my calm, sated mood and every soft bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful, comforting weight rests on my chest, my large breasts feeling incredibly soft and pliant, their aroused nipples completing my blissful, jiggling state.</li>
            <li>These full, beautiful mounds are exquisitely sensitive, their elegant form and eager nipples reflecting the serene contentment washing over me, responding with playful jiggles.</li>
            <li>My large breasts, tender and responsive to every breath, perfectly embody the quiet joy within, their nipples radiating warmth and a satisfying, delightful bounce.</li>
            <li>The prominent jiggle and delightful softness of my large breasts feel incredibly natural, their sensitive nipples dancing with my carefree mood and ample movements.</li>
            <li>A comforting, luxurious presence, my large breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene, private pleasure, subtly responding with every happy sway.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel wonderfully soft, their shapely form and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction, offering a luscious, pleasing motion.</li>
            <li>Just the right size, the exquisite sensitivity of my large breasts and their responsive nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure, subtly alive with every seductive sway.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, rounded contours of my large breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction, enhanced by their generous, sensual jiggle.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel wonderfully supple, their gentle, captivating jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel, their movement a soft, alluring caress.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my large breasts are a source of intimate joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure and a charming, ample bounce.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, luxuriant feeling of my large breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit, moving gently with every blissful sigh.</li>
            <li>These soft, firm mounds of bliss feel so wonderfully warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene and magnificently responsive with every shift.</li>
            <li>My large breasts possess a charming elegance, their natural, abundant curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state, swaying sumptuously.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my large breasts, their generous shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood and offering a delightful, soft, confident bounce.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my large breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release, their alluring movement amplifying it.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction in their every luxurious shift and sway.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, abundant size feels so right, the pleasing swell and sensitive nipples of my large breasts embodying utter contentment, subtly alive and wonderfully bouncy.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my large breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples, moving gently with every blissful sigh and joyful jiggle.</li>
            <li>My large breasts, a generous embrace, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace and their pleasing, voluptuous jiggle.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying weight of my large breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings profound joy, their soft, enticing sway mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>These ample, supple breasts are a private delight, their pronounced bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state and gentle, sensual motions.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace, with a comforting, natural, alluring movement.</li>
            <li>A sense of perfect equilibrium, my large breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully natural and free, utterly content in their gentle, magnificent sway.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my large breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss, enhanced by their soft, voluptuous movement.</li>
            <li>My large breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure, subtly alive with every joyful beat and bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful warmth and gentle movement, as my large breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel, their jiggle adding to the sensation.</li>
            <li>The charming naturalness of my large breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me, responsive and soft, with a lovely bounce.</li>
            <li>My large breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao, with every soft, satisfying bounce and sway.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her huge breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Huge_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My huge breasts feel magnificently soft, their abundant shape and exquisitely responsive nipples swaying with an almost hypnotic, blissful jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The immense, voluptuous curve of my huge breasts, with their intensely sensitive, firm nipples, resonates deeply with my calm, utterly sated mood and every generous bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful, overwhelming weight rests on my chest, my huge breasts feeling incredibly soft and pliant, their aroused nipples completing my blissful, powerfully jiggling state.</li>
            <li>These vast, beautiful mounds are profoundly sensitive, their grand form and eager nipples reflecting the serene contentment washing over me, responding with truly captivating jiggles.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts, tender and profoundly responsive to every breath, perfectly embody the boundless joy within, their nipples radiating warmth and a satisfying, impressive bounce.</li>
            <li>The profound jiggle and delightful softness of my huge breasts feel incredibly natural, their sensitive nipples dancing with my carefree mood and magnificent movements.</li>
            <li>A comforting, luxurious, and grand presence, my huge breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene, private pleasure, subtly responding with every powerful sway.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel wonderfully soft and yielding, their shapely form and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction, offering a luscious, compelling motion.</li>
            <li>The perfect, immense size, the exquisite sensitivity of my huge breasts and their responsive nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure, profoundly alive with every seductive sway.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, embracing contours of my huge breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction, enhanced by their generous, sensual, mesmerizing jiggle.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel wonderfully supple, their gentle, captivating, immense jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel, their movement a soft, alluring caress.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my huge breasts are a source of intimate, boundless joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure and a charming, breathtaking bounce.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, luxuriant, and truly expansive feeling of my huge breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit, moving gently with every blissful sigh.</li>
            <li>These soft, firm, massive mounds of bliss feel so wonderfully warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene and magnificently responsive with every powerful shift.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts possess a charming, majestic elegance, their natural, abundant curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state, swaying sumptuously and gloriously.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my huge breasts, their generous, impressive shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood and offering a delightful, soft, confident, grand bounce.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my huge breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release, their alluring, overwhelming movement amplifying it.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction in their every luxurious, profound shift and sway.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, abundant, truly immense size feels so right, the pleasing swell and sensitive nipples of my huge breasts embodying utter contentment, subtly alive and wonderfully, majestically bouncy.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my huge breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples, moving gently with every blissful sigh and joyous, magnificent jiggle.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts, a generous, embracing marvel, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace and their pleasing, voluptuous, captivating jiggle.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying, profound weight of my huge breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings boundless joy, their soft, enticing, voluminous sway mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>These ample, supple, truly enormous breasts are a private delight, their pronounced, compelling bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state and gentle, sensual, grand motions.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace, with a comforting, natural, alluring, glorious movement.</li>
            <li>A sense of perfect equilibrium, my huge breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully natural and free, utterly content in their gentle, magnificent, embracing sway.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my huge breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss, enhanced by their soft, voluptuous, overwhelming movement.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure, subtly alive with every joyful, powerful beat and bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful warmth and gentle movement, as my huge breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel, their ample jiggle adding profoundly to the sensation.</li>
            <li>The charming naturalness of my huge breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me, responsive and soft, with a lovely, captivating bounce.</li>
            <li>My huge breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing, profound delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao, with every soft, satisfying, grand bounce and sway.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her enormous breasts, her breasts shape, breasts behavior, her nipples state, maybe areolas, all based on sex need, and overall mood, maybe jigliness and breasts response to it -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Ahegao_Female_Positive</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Breasts_Enormous_Ahegao_Female_(positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1~2</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Ahegao</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel gloriously soft, their immense shape and exquisitely responsive nipples swaying with an utterly divine, blissful jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The monumental, voluptuous curve of my enormous breasts, with their intensely sensitive, firm nipples, resonates deeply with my calm, utterly sated mood and every magnificent bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful, overwhelming, and utterly luxurious weight rests on my chest, my enormous breasts feeling incredibly soft and pliant, their aroused nipples completing my blissful, powerfully captivating jiggling state.</li>
            <li>These vast, beautiful, and awe-inspiring mounds are profoundly sensitive, their grand form and eager nipples reflecting the serene contentment washing over me, responding with truly mesmerizing jiggles.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts, tender and profoundly responsive to every breath, perfectly embody the boundless joy within, their nipples radiating warmth and a satisfying, unbelievably impressive bounce.</li>
            <li>The profound, sweeping jiggle and delightful softness of my enormous breasts feel incredibly natural, their sensitive nipples dancing with my carefree mood and magnificent, embracing movements.</li>
            <li>A comforting, luxurious, and truly monumental presence, my enormous breasts with their perfectly formed nipples are a source of serene, private pleasure, subtly responding with every powerful, glorious sway.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel wonderfully soft and yielding, their shapely form and sensitive nipples contributing to this profound, peaceful satisfaction, offering a luscious, compelling, majestic motion.</li>
            <li>The perfect, immense, truly boundless size, the exquisite sensitivity of my enormous breasts and their responsive nipples fills me with immense, quiet pleasure, profoundly alive with every seductive, powerful sway.</li>
            <li>The magnificent, all-encompassing contours of my enormous breasts, with their eager nipples, reflect the fresh, revitalized sensation of true satisfaction, enhanced by their generous, sensual, utterly mesmerizing jiggle.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel wonderfully supple, their gentle, captivating, immense, and powerful jiggle and responsive nipples echoing the deep, languid contentment I feel, their movement a soft, alluring, all-consuming caress.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful pair, my enormous breasts are a source of intimate, boundless, and overwhelming joy, their perfectly formed nipples buzzing with lingering pleasure and a charming, breathtaking, glorious bounce.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, luxuriant, and truly expansive, embracing feeling of my enormous breasts, with their sensitive nipples, is a perfect complement to my fully sated spirit, moving gently with every blissful, profound sigh.</li>
            <li>These soft, firm, massive, and divinely shaped mounds of bliss feel so wonderfully warm, their alluring nipples beckoning for a gentle caress, utterly serene and magnificently responsive with every powerful, irresistible shift.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts possess a charming, majestic, and awe-inspiring elegance, their natural, abundant curves and exquisite nipples resonating with my profound ahegao state, swaying sumptuously and gloriously.</li>
            <li>A quiet joy blossoms from my enormous breasts, their generous, impressive, and commanding shape and sensitive nipples harmonizing with my deeply peaceful mood and offering a delightful, soft, confident, grand, truly impressive bounce.</li>
            <li>The exquisite sensation radiating from my enormous breasts and their firm nipples contributes to this overwhelming feeling of blissful release, their alluring, overwhelming, and utterly consuming movement amplifying it.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel incredibly soft and tender, their responsive nipples humming with a gentle, persistent arousal, pure satisfaction in their every luxurious, profound, and truly captivating shift and sway.</li>
            <li>Their perfect, abundant, truly immense, and goddess-like size feels so right, the pleasing swell and sensitive nipples of my enormous breasts embodying utter contentment, subtly alive and wonderfully, majestically, overwhelmingly bouncy.</li>
            <li>A serene calm washes over me, deepened by the delightful presence of my enormous breasts and their perfectly attuned nipples, moving gently with every blissful sigh and joyous, magnificent, compelling jiggle.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts, a generous, embracing, and truly divine marvel, respond to every subtle movement, their sensitive nipples highlighting this beautiful state of peace and their pleasing, voluptuous, captivating, and profound jiggle.</li>
            <li>The sweet, satisfying, profound, and undeniable weight of my enormous breasts, combined with the exquisite sensation from their nipples, brings boundless joy, their soft, enticing, voluminous, and utterly majestic sway mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>These ample, supple, truly enormous, and sensationally responsive breasts are a private delight, their pronounced, compelling bounce and responsive nipples reflecting my utterly fulfilled state and gentle, sensual, grand, and all-encompassing motions.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel beautifully soft and yielding, their perfectly shaped nipples promising lingering pleasure in my satisfied embrace, with a comforting, natural, alluring, glorious, and infinitely satisfying movement.</li>
            <li>A sense of perfect equilibrium, my enormous breasts with their alluring nipples feel wonderfully natural and free, utterly content in their gentle, magnificent, embracing, and profoundly moving sway.</li>
            <li>The gentle curves and intensely sensitive nipples of my enormous breasts make every touch a journey into tranquil, satisfied bliss, enhanced by their soft, voluptuous, overwhelming, and utterly consuming movement.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts feel so perfectly aligned with my mood, their soft fullness and responsive nipples a quiet celebration of pleasure, subtly alive with every joyful, powerful, commanding beat and bounce.</li>
            <li>A delightful warmth and gentle movement, as my enormous breasts and their sweet nipples contribute to the deep, peaceful relaxation I now feel, their ample, magnificent jiggle adding profoundly to the sensation.</li>
            <li>The charming naturalness of my enormous breasts, with their wonderfully alert nipples, perfectly reflects the profound contentment within me, responsive and soft, with a lovely, captivating, and truly grand bounce.</li>
            <li>My enormous breasts are a source of subtle, ongoing, profound, and overwhelming delight, their soft contours and sensitive nipples a testament to perfect ahegao, with every soft, satisfying, grand, and all-encompassing bounce and sway.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
