<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
<!--Observing middle aged Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The observed breasts are notably small, appearing to sit high on the chest with minimal projection, their form hinting at a firm yet unassuming presence.</li>
            <li>A glance reveals tiny breasts, their contour subtle against the torso, with small, barely defined nipples and areolas.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, almost unnoticeable, their shape suggests a lack of fullness, consistent with their tiny size.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are flat against {PAWN_possessive} chest, with nipples and areolas offering little prominence or color differentiation.</li>
            <li>Tiny, almost undeveloped breasts are visible, their slight form not drawing much attention. There is little sag or movement observed.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are neatly proportioned to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} frame, their understated appearance offering a quiet modesty.</li>
            <li>The mature female's chest reveals tiny, compact breasts, their shape showing a slight natural curve without significant projection.</li>
            <li>Upon observation, the breasts are diminutive, with flat, light-colored areolas and nipples that blend into the skin.</li>
            <li>Small and close-set, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a subtle feature, their delicate form suggesting a youthful, unfaltering contour.</li>
            <li>The breasts are notably tiny, their firmness apparent, with the nipples remaining relatively small and unpronounced.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, small breasts barely visible, their outline is smooth and unblemished, suggesting minimal change over time.</li>
            <li>The minuscule breasts do not sway, remaining tight against the ribcage, their structure appearing to defy the effects of gravity.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, the breasts are quite small, their nipples appearing retracted or very flat against the skin.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts show no signs of pronounced development, their presence is more implied than overt, blending with the chest.</li>
            <li>A quick look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest reveals very modest breasts, their areolas small and pale, the nipples barely raised.</li>
            <li>The mature female's breasts are small and high, appearing to retain a firm, almost youthful shape despite {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>Their breasts are compact, with a subtle, almost concave curve where more prominent tissue might be expected.</li>
            <li>Despite {PAWN_possessive} age, the breasts remain small and firm, indicating a consistent, perhaps naturally modest, chest.</li>
            <li>The diminutive size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts means they offer little in terms of visual distinction, their form is quite simple.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation: the breasts are tiny, with a flat profile, their presence is unassuming and does not draw the eye.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex voyer Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse reveals the subtle contour of tiny breasts, their nipples barely visible. A quiet presence.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are barely noticeable, a flat silhouette against the body, offering little to linger on.</li>
            <li>My gaze falls upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts, their firm set and small areolas presenting a restrained form.</li>
            <li>I observe the minimalist nature of {PAWN_possessive} chest; the breasts are small and seem quite static.</li>
            <li>Despite being small, their modest structure provides an intriguing, understated view, with nipples that are barely raised.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, their outlines just visible beneath {PAWN_possessive} attire, a fleeting detail.</li>
            <li>A quick, unnoticed survey confirms the small, firm shape of the breasts, their behavior subtly conforming to movements.</li>
            <li>The nipples and areolas of the tiny breasts are small, almost camouflaged, a quiet observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a clean, uncluttered view, their behavior is surprisingly stable.</li>
            <li>From a distance, the breasts appear tiny and flat, with only a hint of the areola's presence.</li>
            <li>The minute sway of {PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts suggests a certain elasticity, almost imperceptible to the casual eye.</li>
            <li>A careful glance at the chest shows the small, high-set breasts, their nipples distinct but not prominent.</li>
            <li>The modest form of the breasts provides little visual 'action', yet there's a subtle aesthetic to their small size.</li>
            <li>I note the fine texture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} skin over {PAWN_possessive} tiny, unobtrusive breasts.</li>
            <li>Their smallness is striking; the breasts sit neatly on the chest, defying any notable movement.</li>
            <li>The breasts are extremely small, almost childlike in their delicate proportions, with small, pinkish nipples.</li>
            <li>My eye catches the unadorned simplicity of the tiny breasts, their areolas barely shaded.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are subtly visible, their firm appearance suggesting a quiet strength.</li>
            <li>The barely-there breasts maintain a composed posture, with minimal jiggliness, even during movement.</li>
            <li>A silent appreciation for the small, neutral breasts, their form offering a quiet, almost reserved, display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented, a subtle feature on {PAWN_possessive} chest, their outline clear.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are on display, their firm, modest shape is apparent for all to see, with discreet nipples.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of the small, neutral breasts; their understated presence is now openly visible.</li>
            <li>The female's petite breasts are openly shown, their simple form and small areolas clearly exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are quite visible, a clear statement of their natural, unobtrusive form.</li>
            <li>The small, firm breasts are on full display, their minimal projection offering an honest view.</li>
            <li>The exhibitionist in me acknowledges the subtle presentation of these tiny breasts, their contours well-defined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are openly presented, a neutral display of their form and lack of movement.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts, with their small, almost unnoticeable nipples, are plainly visible.</li>
            <li>These petite breasts are clearly visible, their shape neat and compact, perfectly suited for an open view.</li>
            <li>The modest breasts are quite exposed, their smallness is a feature in itself, offering a clean aesthetic.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are revealed, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed appearance.</li>
            <li>The form of these small breasts is laid bare, their areolas and nipples offering a subtle focal point.</li>
            <li>A straightforward view of tiny breasts, their structure is clear, without much to conceal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is openly displayed, revealing small breasts that are firm and high-set.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts, with their subtle curves, are openly presented, inviting a neutral gaze.</li>
            <li>The tiny, almost flat breasts are clearly visible, their quiet presence is now on public view.</li>
            <li>The exhibition of these small breasts is complete, their neat appearance and small nipples are unmistakable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} barely-there breasts are openly visible, a clean and simple presentation.</li>
            <li>A neutral exhibition of tiny breasts, their firm, unyielding form is now openly available for observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The tiny breasts are a neutral sight, their size is unremarkable, yet their mere presence is noted.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, while not overtly stimulating, are a part of the female form.</li>
            <li>Observation of the tiny breasts yields a neutral response; their shape and behavior are unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The nipples and areolas of these small breasts are present, yet do not particularly draw attention.</li>
            <li>These diminutive breasts offer little in the way of visual excitement, their appearance is quite plain.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest reveals tiny breasts, their form and texture are typical, nothing stands out.</li>
            <li>A glance at the small breasts, noting their lack of prominent jiggliness; a calm and composed sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are there, observed, their simple shape and firm set. A mere detail of the anatomy.</li>
            <li>The areolas are small, the nipples are flat; the tiny breasts offer a neutral, unprovocative view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are small, their overall appearance is neither appealing nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>No particular reaction to these tiny breasts; they are simply a part of the observed individual.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a modest contour, their behavior is as expected for their size.</li>
            <li>Their presence is noted, the tiny breasts offer a flat, unassuming profile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest, revealing breasts of a tiny stature, their physical attributes are average.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these tiny breasts are small and light-colored, not particularly stimulating.</li>
            <li>Observation confirms the tiny size and neutral form of the breasts, no strong impression is made.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their form is simple, and they remain relatively static.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are visible, their appearance is purely anatomical, devoid of allure.</li>
            <li>The areolas are barely distinguishable; the tiny breasts offer a very subdued visual.</li>
            <li>A neutral assessment of the tiny breasts: they exist as part of the body, nothing more or less.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The small breasts are regrettably exposed; their presence is noted with a hint of discomfort.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts is unsettling; their nakedness is an unnecessary sight.</li>
            <li>The exposed breasts are small and insignificant, yet still, their visibility causes mild discomfort.</li>
            <li>I avert my gaze from the tiny breasts; their visible form is an impropriety.</li>
            <li>The female's tiny breasts are laid bare, a sight that should remain private, regardless of their size.</li>
            <li>Such small breasts, yet their open display is still inappropriate, a breach of modesty.</li>
            <li>The presence of exposed tiny breasts is a minor offense to my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>My eyes briefly register the minute breasts and their exposed nipples, a situation best avoided.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny, exposed breasts are a mild affront to decorum, regardless of their lack of prominence.</li>
            <li>The sight of these small, visible breasts makes me slightly uneasy; it's simply improper.</li>
            <li>Even tiny breasts should be covered; their bareness is an unpleasant observation.</li>
            <li>The exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is mildly shocking, despite their diminutive size.</li>
            <li>I cannot help but notice the inappropriate exposure of these small breasts, a regrettable sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are revealed, and it feels immodest, even for their unprovoking form.</li>
            <li>My comfort level drops slightly at the sight of {PAWN_possessive} bare, tiny breasts.</li>
            <li>A fleeting, unwelcome view of small breasts; their visibility is simply unnecessary.</li>
            <li>The exposed tiny breasts, while small, still represent a lapse in proper attire.</li>
            <li>It's unfortunate to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, however tiny, without proper covering.</li>
            <li>The smallness of the breasts doesn't diminish the feeling of impropriety at their exposure.</li>
            <li>The sight of these tiny, revealed breasts is a minor disturbance; I prefer things to be more covered.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are noticeable, their delicate shape subtly conforming to {PAWN_possessive} movements.</li>
            <li>A quick look reveals small breasts, their contour gentle and high-set, with small, pale nipples.</li>
            <li>The mature female's breasts are petite, almost modest, but their form is distinct against {PAWN_possessive} chest.</li>
            <li>I observe the subtle curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts, their areolas and nipples are discreet.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, yet they possess a quiet grace, their shape firm and unyielding.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts, while not prominent, show a natural firmness, their presence is understated but clear.</li>
            <li>A brief glance captures the neat appearance of the small breasts, their nipples are small, adding to the modesty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} mature female chest, tiny breasts sitting high and firm, their behavior is surprisingly stable.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are tiny, their form is simple and natural, fitting {PAWN_possessive} frame well.</li>
            <li>Observing the small breasts, I notice their rounded yet compact shape, the areolas are a light shade.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts offer a modest sight, their slight jiggliness is barely discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts have a gentle slope, their nipples small and neatly centered.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small and high, indicating a natural firmness that is quite evident.</li>
            <li>A neutral appreciation for the tiny breasts, their contour is smooth and their presence subtle.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are present, their simple and unadorned appearance is quite clear.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts, though tiny, contribute to {PAWN_possessive} overall feminine form.</li>
            <li>The subtle outline of the tiny breasts, firm and close to the chest, is observed.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are neat and flat, their color is unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest reveals tiny breasts that are proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} lean figure.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are unassuming, their slight movement is almost imperceptible.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, much like my own, with a discreet profile.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, firm and modest, a common sight on many mature women.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their shape unyielding, with small, unassuming nipples.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest shows tiny breasts, their areolas and nipples are barely noticeable.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small and appear to be well-maintained, showing little signs of sag.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set and firm, a natural and common shape for some women.</li>
            <li>A quick observation of the small breasts reveals their minimal jiggliness, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with neatly defined but small areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost flat against {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firm structure is evident despite their size.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to blend into {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} mature female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, which can be natural for some.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their mature frame.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are observed, their form is modest and firm, fitting {PAWN_possessive} mature frame.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are present, their shape is unassuming, with little outward projection.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation of the breasts: they are tiny, with small, lightly pigmented areolas and nipples.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, their contours subtle, they do not appear to sag with age.</li>
            <li>I note the tiny breasts, their firmness suggesting a retained youthful appearance.</li>
            <li>The mature female's chest reveals small, compact breasts, their movement is minimal.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, almost flat, their nipples are small and close to the skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts are quite small, their shape is natural and unembellished.</li>
            <li>A glance at the breasts shows their diminutive size, with a clean and unadorned profile.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and orderly, lacking any significant jiggliness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a simple, almost flat contour, a typical observation.</li>
            <li>The form of these tiny breasts is modest, their areolas and nipples are proportioned to their size.</li>
            <li>I observe the small breasts; they seem firm and unyielding for their age.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their outline is smooth and unblemished, not particularly eye-catching.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are visible, their size and shape are unremarkable, a neutral sight.</li>
            <li>Her chest features small breasts that maintain a firm, collected appearance.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are flat and their color is faint, not drawing attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are tiny, their presence is understated and discreet.</li>
            <li>A calm observation of the female's tiny breasts; their movements are subtle, almost imperceptible.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their natural form is apparent, fitting the overall body structure.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, similar to many, without drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, they appear firm and well-preserved for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their form is compact, with minimal projection or sag.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest features tiny breasts, their nipples and areolas are small and unassuming.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, almost flat, suggesting a firm, almost youthful contour.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and tidy, reflecting a natural form.</li>
            <li>A quick observation reveals the small breasts, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with subtle areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost blending into {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firmness is evident, consistent with some mature women.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to be well-proportioned to {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not standing out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} mature female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, a natural variation among women.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection, a common observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible to the eye.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their mature frame discreetly.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are visible; their modest size is a natural feature, nothing more.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are present, their shape is unassuming, with little outward projection or sag.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation of the breasts: they are tiny, with small, lightly pigmented areolas and nipples.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, their contours subtle, they appear quite firm for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>I note the tiny breasts, their firmness suggesting a retained compact appearance.</li>
            <li>The mature female's chest reveals small, compact breasts, their movement is minimal, a calm sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, almost flat, their nipples are small and close to the skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts are quite small, their shape is natural and unembellished, a neutral view.</li>
            <li>A glance at the breasts shows their diminutive size, with a clean and unadorned profile.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and orderly, lacking any significant jiggliness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a simple, almost flat contour, a typical observation for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The form of these tiny breasts is modest, their areolas and nipples are proportioned to their size.</li>
            <li>I observe the small breasts; they seem firm and unyielding given the observed age.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their outline is smooth and unblemished, not particularly eye-catching to an older observer.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are visible, their size and shape are unremarkable, a neutral sight.</li>
            <li>Her chest features small breasts that maintain a firm, collected appearance, consistent with some mature women.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are flat and their color is faint, not drawing attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are tiny, their presence is understated and discreet.</li>
            <li>A calm observation of the female's tiny breasts; their movements are subtle, almost imperceptible to the eye.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their natural form is apparent, fitting the overall body structure without undue prominence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing middle aged Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_MatureFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_MatureFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>40</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>59</requiredObservedMaxBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, much like some women's, not drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, they appear firm and well-preserved for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their form is compact, with minimal projection or sag.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest features tiny breasts, their nipples and areolas are small and unassuming.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, almost flat, suggesting a firm, almost youthful contour.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and tidy, reflecting a natural form.</li>
            <li>A quick observation reveals the small breasts, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with subtle areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost blending into {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firmness is evident, consistent with some mature women.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to be well-proportioned to {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not standing out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} mature female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, a natural variation among women.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection, a common observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible to the eye.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their mature frame discreetly.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>





<!--Observing elderly Woman-->
<!--unisex Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The elderly female's tiny breasts are observed; their size remains consistent, with minimal natural sag.</li>
            <li>A glance reveals small, unassuming breasts, their form is simple, and the nipples are subtle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are firm, defying significant change despite {PAWN_possessive} advanced age.</li>
            <li>The breasts are petite, almost unnoticeable, their shape suggests a lack of fullness, consistent with their tiny size.</li>
            <li>Tiny, almost undeveloped breasts are visible, their slight form not drawing much attention, very little jiggliness.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are neatly proportioned to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} frame, their understated appearance offering a quiet modesty.</li>
            <li>The elderly female's chest reveals tiny, compact breasts, their shape showing a slight natural curve.</li>
            <li>Upon observation, the breasts are diminutive, with flat, light-colored areolas and nipples that blend into the skin.</li>
            <li>Small and close-set, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a subtle feature, their delicate form suggesting a youthful contour.</li>
            <li>The breasts are notably tiny, their firmness apparent, with the nipples remaining relatively small and unpronounced.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, small breasts barely visible, their outline is smooth and unblemished.</li>
            <li>The minuscule breasts do not sway, remaining tight against the ribcage, their structure appearing to defy gravity.</li>
            <li>Observing the form, the breasts are quite small, their nipples appearing retracted or very flat against the skin.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts show no signs of pronounced development, their presence is more implied than overt.</li>
            <li>A quick look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest reveals very modest breasts, their areolas small and pale, the nipples barely raised.</li>
            <li>The elderly female's breasts are small and high, appearing to retain a firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>Their breasts are compact, with a subtle, almost concave curve where more prominent tissue might be expected.</li>
            <li>Despite {PAWN_possessive} age, the breasts remain small and firm, indicating a consistent, perhaps naturally modest, chest.</li>
            <li>The diminutive size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts means they offer little in terms of visual distinction.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation: the breasts are tiny, with a flat profile, their presence is unassuming.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--unisex voyer Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_voyer</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse reveals the subtle contour of tiny breasts, their nipples barely visible, a quiet presence.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are barely noticeable, a flat silhouette against the body, offering little to linger on.</li>
            <li>My gaze falls upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts, their firm set and small areolas presenting a restrained form.</li>
            <li>I observe the minimalist nature of {PAWN_possessive} chest; the breasts are small and seem quite static.</li>
            <li>Despite being small, their modest structure provides an intriguing, understated view, with nipples that are barely raised.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, their outlines just visible beneath {PAWN_possessive} attire, a fleeting detail.</li>
            <li>A quick, unnoticed survey confirms the small, firm shape of the breasts, their behavior subtly conforming to movements.</li>
            <li>The nipples and areolas of the tiny breasts are small, almost camouflaged, a quiet observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a clean, uncluttered view, their behavior is surprisingly stable.</li>
            <li>From a distance, the breasts appear tiny and flat, with only a hint of the areola's presence.</li>
            <li>The minute sway of {PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts suggests a certain elasticity, almost imperceptible to the casual eye.</li>
            <li>A careful glance at the chest shows the small, high-set breasts, their nipples distinct but not prominent.</li>
            <li>The modest form of the breasts provides little visual 'action', yet there's a subtle aesthetic to their small size.</li>
            <li>I note the fine texture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} skin over {PAWN_possessive} tiny, unobtrusive breasts.</li>
            <li>Their smallness is striking; the breasts sit neatly on the chest, defying any notable movement.</li>
            <li>The breasts are extremely small, almost childlike in their delicate proportions, with small, pinkish nipples.</li>
            <li>My eye catches the unadorned simplicity of the tiny breasts, their areolas barely shaded.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are subtly visible, their firm appearance suggesting a quiet strength.</li>
            <li>The barely-there breasts maintain a composed posture, with minimal jiggliness, even during movement.</li>
            <li>A silent appreciation for the small, neutral breasts, their form offering a quiet, almost reserved, display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Exhibitionist Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented, a subtle feature on {PAWN_possessive} chest, their outline clear.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are on display, their firm, modest shape is apparent for all to see, with discreet nipples.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of the small, neutral breasts; their understated presence is now openly visible.</li>
            <li>The female's petite breasts are openly shown, their simple form and small areolas clearly exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are quite visible, a clear statement of their natural, unobtrusive form.</li>
            <li>The small, firm breasts are on full display, their minimal projection offering an honest view.</li>
            <li>The exhibitionist in me acknowledges the subtle presentation of these tiny breasts, their contours well-defined.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are openly presented, a neutral display of their form and lack of movement.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts, with their small, almost unnoticeable nipples, are plainly visible.</li>
            <li>These petite breasts are clearly visible, their shape neat and compact, perfectly suited for an open view.</li>
            <li>The modest breasts are quite exposed, their smallness is a feature in itself, offering a clean aesthetic.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are revealed, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed appearance.</li>
            <li>The form of these small breasts is laid bare, their areolas and nipples offering a subtle focal point.</li>
            <li>A straightforward view of tiny breasts, their structure is clear, without much to conceal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is openly displayed, revealing small breasts that are firm and high-set.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts, with their subtle curves, are openly presented, inviting a neutral gaze.</li>
            <li>The tiny, almost flat breasts are clearly visible, their quiet presence is now on public view.</li>
            <li>The exhibition of these small breasts is complete, their neat appearance and small nipples are unmistakable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} barely-there breasts are openly visible, a clean and simple presentation.</li>
            <li>A neutral exhibition of tiny breasts, their firm, unyielding form is now openly available for observation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The tiny breasts are a neutral sight, their size is unremarkable, yet their mere presence is noted.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, while not overtly stimulating, are a part of the female form.</li>
            <li>Observation of the tiny breasts yields a neutral response; their shape and behavior are unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The nipples and areolas of these small breasts are present, yet do not particularly draw attention.</li>
            <li>These diminutive breasts offer little in the way of visual excitement, their appearance is quite plain.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest reveals tiny breasts, their form and texture are typical, nothing stands out.</li>
            <li>A glance at the small breasts, noting their lack of prominent jiggliness; a calm and composed sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are there, observed, their simple shape and firm set. A mere detail of the anatomy.</li>
            <li>The areolas are small, the nipples are flat; the tiny breasts offer a neutral, unprovocative view.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are small, their overall appearance is neither appealing nor unappealing.</li>
            <li>No particular reaction to these tiny breasts; they are simply a part of the observed individual.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a modest contour, their behavior is as expected for their size.</li>
            <li>Their presence is noted, the tiny breasts offer a flat, unassuming profile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest, revealing breasts of a tiny stature, their physical attributes are average.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these tiny breasts are small and light-colored, not particularly stimulating.</li>
            <li>Observation confirms the tiny size and neutral form of the breasts, no strong impression is made.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their form is simple, and they remain relatively static.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are visible, their appearance is purely anatomical, devoid of allure.</li>
            <li>The areolas are barely distinguishable; the tiny breasts offer a very subdued visual.</li>
            <li>A neutral assessment of the tiny breasts: they exist as part of the body, nothing more or less.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Prude Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The small breasts are regrettably exposed; their presence is noted with a hint of discomfort.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts is unsettling; their nakedness is an unnecessary sight.</li>
            <li>The exposed breasts are small and insignificant, yet still, their visibility causes mild discomfort.</li>
            <li>I avert my gaze from the tiny breasts; their visible form is an impropriety.</li>
            <li>The female's tiny breasts are laid bare, a sight that should remain private, regardless of their size.</li>
            <li>Such small breasts, yet their open display is still inappropriate, a breach of modesty.</li>
            <li>The presence of exposed tiny breasts is a minor offense to my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>My eyes briefly register the minute breasts and their exposed nipples, a situation best avoided.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny, exposed breasts are a mild affront to decorum, regardless of their lack of prominence.</li>
            <li>The sight of these small, visible breasts makes me slightly uneasy; it's simply improper.</li>
            <li>Even tiny breasts should be covered; their bareness is an unpleasant observation.</li>
            <li>The exposed nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is mildly shocking, despite their diminutive size.</li>
            <li>I cannot help but notice the inappropriate exposure of these small breasts, a regrettable sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are revealed, and it feels immodest, even for their unprovoking form.</li>
            <li>My comfort level drops slightly at the sight of {PAWN_possessive} bare, tiny breasts.</li>
            <li>A fleeting, unwelcome view of small breasts; their visibility is simply unnecessary.</li>
            <li>The exposed tiny breasts, while small, still represent a lapse in proper attire.</li>
            <li>It's unfortunate to see {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, however tiny, without proper covering.</li>
            <li>The smallness of the breasts doesn't diminish the feeling of impropriety at their exposure.</li>
            <li>The sight of these tiny, revealed breasts is a minor disturbance; I prefer things to be more covered.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Young male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are noticeable, their delicate shape subtly conforming to {PAWN_possessive} movements.</li>
            <li>A quick look reveals small breasts, their contour gentle and high-set, with small, pale nipples.</li>
            <li>The elderly female's breasts are petite, almost modest, but their form is distinct against {PAWN_possessive} chest.</li>
            <li>I observe the subtle curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts, their areolas and nipples are discreet.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, yet they possess a quiet grace, their shape firm and unyielding.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts, while not prominent, show a natural firmness, their presence is understated but clear.</li>
            <li>A brief glance captures the neat appearance of the small breasts, their nipples are small, adding to the modesty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} elderly female chest, tiny breasts sitting high and firm, their behavior is surprisingly stable.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are tiny, their form is simple and natural, fitting {PAWN_possessive} frame well.</li>
            <li>Observing the small breasts, I notice their rounded yet compact shape, the areolas are a light shade.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts offer a modest sight, their slight jiggliness is barely discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts have a gentle slope, their nipples small and neatly centered.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small and high, indicating a natural firmness that is quite evident.</li>
            <li>A neutral appreciation for the tiny breasts, their contour is smooth and their presence subtle.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are present, their simple and unadorned appearance is quite clear.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts, though tiny, contribute to {PAWN_possessive} overall feminine form.</li>
            <li>The subtle outline of the tiny breasts, firm and close to the chest, is observed.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are neat and flat and their color is unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest reveals tiny breasts that are proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} lean figure.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are unassuming, their slight movement is almost imperceptible.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_Young_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<maxBiologicalAge>39</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, much like my own, with a discreet profile.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, firm and modest, a common sight on many older women.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their shape unyielding, with small, unassuming nipples.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest shows tiny breasts, their areolas and nipples are barely noticeable.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small and appear to be well-maintained, showing little signs of sag despite age.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set and firm, a natural and common shape for some women.</li>
            <li>A quick observation of the small breasts reveals their minimal jiggliness, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with neatly defined but small areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost flat against {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firm structure is evident despite their size and age.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to blend into {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} elderly female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, which can be natural for some.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible to the eye.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their elderly frame.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Middle aged male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are observed, their form is modest and firm, fitting {PAWN_possessive} elderly frame.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are present, their shape is unassuming, with little outward projection or sag.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation of the breasts: they are tiny, with small, lightly pigmented areolas and nipples.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, their contours subtle, they appear quite firm for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>I note the tiny breasts, their firmness suggesting a retained compact appearance.</li>
            <li>The elderly female's chest reveals small, compact breasts, their movement is minimal, a calm sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, almost flat, their nipples are small and close to the skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts are quite small, their shape is natural and unembellished, a neutral view.</li>
            <li>A glance at the breasts shows their diminutive size, with a clean and unadorned profile.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and orderly, lacking any significant jiggliness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a simple, almost flat contour, a typical observation for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The form of these tiny breasts is modest, their areolas and nipples are proportioned to their size.</li>
            <li>I observe the small breasts; they seem firm and unyielding given the observed age.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their outline is smooth and unblemished, not particularly eye-catching to an older observer.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are visible, their size and shape are unremarkable, a neutral sight.</li>
            <li>Her chest features small breasts that maintain a firm, collected appearance, consistent with some elderly women.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are flat and their color is faint, not drawing attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are tiny, their presence is understated and discreet.</li>
            <li>A calm observation of the female's tiny breasts; their movements are subtle, almost imperceptible to the eye.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their natural form is apparent, fitting the overall body structure without undue prominence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Middle aged Female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_middle_aged_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>40</minBiologicalAge>
			<maxBiologicalAge>59</maxBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, similar to many, without drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, they appear firm and well-preserved for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their form is compact, with minimal projection or sag.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest features tiny breasts, their nipples and areolas are small and unassuming.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, almost flat, suggesting a firm, almost youthful contour.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and tidy, reflecting a natural form.</li>
            <li>A quick observation reveals the small breasts, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with subtle areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost blending into {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firmness is evident, consistent with some elderly women.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to be well-proportioned to {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not standing out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} elderly female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, a natural variation among women.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection, a common observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible to the eye.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their elderly frame discreetly.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>


<!--Elder male Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_male</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are visible; their modest size is a natural feature, nothing more.</li>
            <li>The female's small breasts are present, their shape is unassuming, with little outward projection or sag.</li>
            <li>A neutral observation of the breasts: they are tiny, with small, lightly pigmented areolas and nipples.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, their contours subtle, they appear quite firm for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>I note the tiny breasts, their firmness suggesting a retained compact appearance.</li>
            <li>The elderly female's chest reveals small, compact breasts, their movement is minimal, a calm sight.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are discreet, almost flat, their nipples are small and close to the skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} breasts are quite small, their shape is natural and unembellished, a neutral view.</li>
            <li>A glance at the breasts shows their diminutive size, with a clean and unadorned profile.</li>
            <li>The small breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and orderly, lacking any significant jiggliness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts offer a simple, almost flat contour, a typical observation for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The form of these tiny breasts is modest, their areolas and nipples are proportioned to their size.</li>
            <li>I observe the small breasts; they seem firm and unyielding given the observed age.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their outline is smooth and unblemished, not particularly eye-catching to an older observer.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} tiny breasts are visible, their size and shape are unremarkable, a neutral sight.</li>
            <li>Her chest features small breasts that maintain a firm, collected appearance, consistent with some elderly women.</li>
            <li>The nipples of these small breasts are flat and their color is faint, not drawing attention.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are tiny, their presence is understated and discreet.</li>
            <li>A calm observation of the female's tiny breasts; their movements are subtle, almost imperceptible to the eye.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their natural form is apparent, fitting the overall body structure without undue prominence.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder female Observing elderly Womans breast shape, breasts behavior, nipples, areolas-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Neutral_Tiny_ElderFemale_observed_by_Elder_female</defName>
        <label>Tiny Breasts (Neutral)_ElderFemale_observed_by_elder_female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.02~0.20</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily>
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObservedLifeStage>
			<requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>60</requiredObservedMinBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite small, much like some women's, not drawing much attention.</li>
            <li>I notice her small breasts, they appear firm and well-preserved for a woman of {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are petite, their form is compact, with minimal projection or sag.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} chest features tiny breasts, their nipples and areolas are small and unassuming.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are small, almost flat, suggesting a firm, almost youthful contour.</li>
            <li>The tiny breasts are high-set, their appearance is neat and tidy, reflecting a natural form.</li>
            <li>A quick observation reveals the small breasts, their jiggliness is minimal, maintaining a composed look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clean, simple form, with subtle areolas.</li>
            <li>The breasts are tiny, almost blending into {PAWN_possessive} chest, a very modest appearance.</li>
            <li>I note the small, compact breasts, their firmness is evident, consistent with some elderly women.</li>
            <li>These tiny breasts seem to be well-proportioned to {PAWN_possessive} overall figure, not standing out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_possessive} elderly female's breasts are petite, their nipples and areolas are subtly present.</li>
            <li>The form of the breasts is small, almost undeveloped, a natural variation among women.</li>
            <li>A look at the tiny breasts confirms their modest size and firm, almost youthful shape.</li>
            <li>The female's breasts are small, a consistent shape with limited projection, a common observation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny breasts are quite similar in form to what one might expect for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The small breasts present a neat outline, their slight firmness is discernible to the eye.</li>
            <li>I observe the tiny breasts, their appearance is neutral and unremarkable, just as they are.</li>
            <li>The nipples on these tiny breasts are small and blend in, offering a subtle detail.</li>
            <li>The breasts are small, their presence is understated, fitting their elderly frame discreetly.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




</Defs>
