<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his tiny butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Frustrated_Unisex_Negative</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Frustrated_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My tiny butt feels utterly inadequate, amplifying this constant, gnawing sexual frustration. It's just so flat, offering nothing.</li>
            <li>This micro-butt is a joke, barely there. My frustrated needs make me hyper-aware of its utter lack of presence.</li>
            <li>Despite my intense frustration, my butt remains unyielding and tiny, mocking my unfulfilled desires. It’s infuriatingly small.</li>
            <li>It's almost flat, barely noticeable. This microscopic butt fuels my frustration, offering no relief to my desperate state.</li>
            <li>This miserable, tiny butt reflects my utterly frustrated mood. It feels insignificant, a constant reminder of unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>A truly pathetic, tiny thing. Its lack of form, coupled with this intense frustration, makes me utterly despise it.</li>
            <li>My butt is so small, it practically disappears. The sheer frustration I feel makes me wish it were anything but this.</li>
            <li>It's dishearteningly micro. This constant sexual frustration just magnifies how utterly unappealing and flat it feels.</li>
            <li>This minuscule butt is just another source of my mounting frustration. It feels like a void, incapable of satisfying.</li>
            <li>I can feel how utterly flat my butt is. My frustrated state makes me curse its non-existence. It’s pathetic.</li>
            <li>It's so small, almost nonexistent. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its utter inadequacy for any real pleasure.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a flat board, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply not enough.</li>
            <li>This tiny, unimpressive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how micro and flat my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly small, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or appeal.</li>
            <li>My butt is barely there, a desolate landscape. My frustrated mind focuses on its pathetic, unyielding flatness.</li>
            <li>This microscopic butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate. It's truly a miserable sight.</li>
            <li>The flatness of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's a sad state.</li>
            <li>It’s a tiny, uninspired form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and insignificant it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's smallness is a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no visual interest, just a flat, empty space.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, tiny butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A flat, unyielding expanse. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing curve or form.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a meager offering, barely there. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its utter lack.</li>
            <li>The sheer flatness is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal, unappealing reality.</li>
            <li>It's a tiny, unflattering shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or appeal.</li>
            <li>My micro-butt feels like a curse when I'm this frustrated. It’s a flat, lifeless canvas.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably small. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and inadequate it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter flatness just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically tiny, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, flat, tiny thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer inadequacy.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his small butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Negative_Unisex</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Negative_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My small, tight butt feels so unyielding, just adding to this suffocating sexual frustration. It's stiff and unappealing.</li>
            <li>This small butt feels so unyielding, reflecting my frustrated state. Its tightness offers no promise of relief.</li>
            <li>Even with this intense frustration, my small butt remains stubbornly tight. It's a rigid, uninviting form.</li>
            <li>It feels small and constricting, mirroring my pent-up frustration. This tightness offers no welcoming allure.</li>
            <li>My butt feels incredibly tight and small, intensifying my frustrated mood. It’s an unyielding, rigid discomfort.</li>
            <li>A truly unimpressive, tight little butt. The frustration makes me hate its stiff, unforgiving nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels so small and tight, it just aggravates my frustration. It's a stiff, unwelcoming sight.</li>
            <li>It's dishearteningly tight and small. This sexual frustration just magnifies its unyielding and rigid feel.</li>
            <li>This small, tight butt is another source of my mounting frustration. It feels like a barrier, not an opening.</li>
            <li>I can feel the tightness of my small butt. My frustrated state makes me curse its rigid, unyielding form.</li>
            <li>It’s so small and tight, almost painful. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a clenched fist, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply too rigid.</li>
            <li>This tight, unimpressive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how small and tight my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly tight, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or release.</li>
            <li>My butt is a rigid, unwelcoming knot. My frustrated mind focuses on its stubbornly tight and unyielding form.</li>
            <li>This small, tight butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate. It's truly a restrictive burden.</li>
            <li>The tightness of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's uncomfortably rigid.</li>
            <li>It’s a tight, uninspired form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and restrictive it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's smallness and tightness are a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no inviting softness.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, tight butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A rigid, unyielding expanse. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing give or softness.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a clenched, unwelcoming space. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its stubborn resistance.</li>
            <li>The sheer tightness is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal, unappealing reality.</li>
            <li>It's a small, unforgiving shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or loosen.</li>
            <li>My tight butt feels like a trap when I'm this frustrated. It’s a rigid, unyielding barrier.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably tight and small. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and rigid it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter tightness just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically tight, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, stiff, tight thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer unwillingness to yield.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Negative_Unisex</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Negative_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My average butt feels unremarkable, doing nothing to alleviate this deep-seated sexual frustration. It's just... there.</li>
            <li>This average butt offers no comfort, only highlighting my frustrated state. It's bland, lacking any compelling features.</li>
            <li>Even with this intense frustration, my butt remains frustratingly average. It’s neither good nor bad, just disappointing.</li>
            <li>It feels disappointingly normal, mirroring my pent-up frustration. This averageness offers no exciting allure.</li>
            <li>My butt feels utterly average, intensifying my frustrated mood. It’s a mediocre, uninspiring sight.</li>
            <li>A truly uninspired, average butt. The frustration makes me hate its utter lack of distinction or appeal.</li>
            <li>My butt feels so bland and average, it just aggravates my frustration. It's an unmemorable, dull sight.</li>
            <li>It's dishearteningly average. This sexual frustration just magnifies its unexciting and plain feel.</li>
            <li>This average butt is another source of my mounting frustration. It feels like a missed opportunity, nothing special.</li>
            <li>I can feel the averageness of my butt. My frustrated state makes me curse its utter lack of anything noteworthy.</li>
            <li>It’s so average, almost painful. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its uninspired normalcy.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a generic shape, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply too unremarkable.</li>
            <li>This average, unimpressive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how average and plain my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly average, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or distinction.</li>
            <li>My butt is a plain, unexciting form. My frustrated mind focuses on its stubbornly unremarkable and unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>This average butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate. It's truly a bland burden.</li>
            <li>The averageness of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's so ordinary.</li>
            <li>It’s an average, uninspired form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and unremarkable it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's averageness is a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no inviting allure.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, average butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A plain, unyielding expanse. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing curve or distinction.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a generic, unappealing space. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its stubborn normalcy.</li>
            <li>The sheer averageness is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal, unappealing reality.</li>
            <li>It's an average, unforgiving shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or excite.</li>
            <li>My average butt feels like a burden when I'm this frustrated. It’s a plain, uninspiring form.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably average. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and ordinary it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter averageness just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically average, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, bland, average thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer mediocrity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Negative_Unisex</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Negative_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My accommodating butt feels too yielding, a sign of weakness that amplifies this gnawing sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>This accommodating butt is a frustrating paradox; it feels open, yet my desires remain unfulfilled. It’s soft, but useless.</li>
            <li>Despite its accommodating nature, my butt's softness only highlights my unalleviated frustration. It’s disappointingly pliant.</li>
            <li>It feels overly accommodating, reflecting my pent-up frustration. This pliability seems to mock my unfulfilled needs.</li>
            <li>My butt feels too soft and open, intensifying my frustrated mood. It’s an unappealing, yielding mass.</li>
            <li>A truly disappointing, overly accommodating butt. The frustration makes me hate its passive, unassertive nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels so soft and yielding, it just aggravates my frustration. It's a formless, unwelcoming sight.</li>
            <li>It's dishearteningly accommodating. This sexual frustration just magnifies its overly pliant and uninspiring feel.</li>
            <li>This accommodating butt is another source of my mounting frustration. It feels too eager, yet offers no real solace.</li>
            <li>I can feel the accommodating softness of my butt. My frustrated state makes me curse its unresisting, weak form.</li>
            <li>It’s so accommodating, almost painful. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its passive, unassertive nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a shapeless cushion, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply too yielding.</li>
            <li>This accommodating, unimpressive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how soft and accommodating my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly accommodating, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or strength.</li>
            <li>My butt is a soft, unwelcoming mass. My frustrated mind focuses on its stubbornly pliable and unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>This accommodating butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate. It's truly a weak burden.</li>
            <li>The accommodating nature of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's too soft.</li>
            <li>It’s an accommodating, uninspired form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and submissive it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's accommodating nature is a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no inviting firmness.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, accommodating butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A soft, overly yielding expanse. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing firmness or structure.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a giving, yet unfulfilling, space. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its weak compliance.</li>
            <li>The sheer accommodating nature is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal reality.</li>
            <li>It's an accommodating, unflattering shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or hold.</li>
            <li>My accommodating butt feels like a weakness when I'm this frustrated. It’s a soft, uninspiring form.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably accommodating. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and yielding it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter accommodating nature just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically accommodating, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, soft, yielding thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer passivity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Negative_Unisex</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Negative_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My cavernous butt feels unpleasantly wide and saggy, amplifying this deep-seated sexual frustration. It’s just too loose.</li>
            <li>This cavernous butt is a frustrating abyss; it feels vast and empty, leaving my desires unfulfilled.</li>
            <li>Despite its expansiveness, my butt's saggy nature only highlights my unalleviated frustration. It’s disappointingly loose.</li>
            <li>It feels overly wide and jiggly, mirroring my pent-up frustration. This looseness seems to mock my unfulfilled needs.</li>
            <li>My butt feels too loose and open, intensifying my frustrated mood. It’s an unappealing, sprawling mass.</li>
            <li>A truly disappointing, overly spacious butt. The frustration makes me hate its uncontainable, saggy nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels so wide and jiggly, it just aggravates my frustration. It's a formless, unwelcoming sight.</li>
            <li>It's dishearteningly cavernous. This sexual frustration just magnifies its overly large and uninspiring feel.</li>
            <li>This cavernous butt is another source of my mounting frustration. It feels too empty, yet offers no real solace.</li>
            <li>I can feel the vastness and sag of my butt. My frustrated state makes me curse its unresisting, weak form.</li>
            <li>It’s so cavernous, almost painful. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its passive, unassertive nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a sprawling chasm, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply too loose.</li>
            <li>This cavernous, unimpressive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how wide and saggy my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly cavernous, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or strength.</li>
            <li>My butt is a loose, unwelcoming void. My frustrated mind focuses on its stubbornly pliable and unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>This cavernous butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate. It's truly a weak burden.</li>
            <li>The cavernous nature of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's too vast.</li>
            <li>It’s a cavernous, uninspired form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and submissive it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's cavernous nature is a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no inviting firmness.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, cavernous butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A wide, overly yielding expanse. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing firmness or structure.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a giving, yet unfulfilling, space. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its weak compliance.</li>
            <li>The sheer cavernous nature is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal reality.</li>
            <li>It's a cavernous, unflattering shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or hold.</li>
            <li>My cavernous butt feels like a weakness when I'm this frustrated. It’s a soft, uninspiring form.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably cavernous. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and yielding it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter cavernous nature just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically cavernous, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, loose, sagging thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer passivity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Unisex gives opinion about his butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Negative_Unisex</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Negative_Unisex_(Negative)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Negative</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                
                
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Frustrated</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My abyssal butt feels grotesquely vast and saggy, amplifying this overwhelming sexual frustration. It's a disturbing void.</li>
            <li>This abyssal butt is a truly frustrating chasm; it feels endlessly wide and utterly empty, leaving my desires crushed.</li>
            <li>Despite its immense size, my butt's extreme sag only highlights my crushing frustration. It’s sickeningly loose and jiggles.</li>
            <li>It feels horrifyingly wide and uncontrollably jiggly, mirroring my unbearable frustration. This looseness is a mockery.</li>
            <li>My butt feels sickeningly vast and open, intensifying my frustrated mood. It’s an appalling, sprawling abyss.</li>
            <li>A truly repulsive, overly expansive butt. The frustration makes me hate its unmanageable, disgustingly saggy nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels so immensely wide and jiggly, it just aggravates my profound frustration. It's a monstrous, unwelcoming sight.</li>
            <li>It's utterly abyssal and shapeless. This sexual frustration just magnifies its horrifyingly large and grotesque feel.</li>
            <li>This abyssal butt is another source of my mounting frustration. It feels like a bottomless pit, offering no solace.</li>
            <li>I can feel the immense void and sag of my butt. My frustrated state makes me curse its unresisting, weak, pathetic form.</li>
            <li>It’s so abyssal, almost agonizing. My frustration boils over as I contemplate its passive, unassertive, horrifying nature.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a monstrous chasm, a cruel joke given my frustrated state. It’s simply too unfathomably vast and loose.</li>
            <li>This abyssal, repulsive butt is a constant source of self-loathing, especially with this burning frustration inside me.</li>
            <li>I hate how grotesquely wide and saggy my butt feels; it just accentuates this unbearable sexual frustration.</li>
            <li>It’s infuriatingly abyssal, a stark contrast to my overwhelming sexual frustration. It offers no comfort or solidity.</li>
            <li>My butt is a loose, unwelcoming void, a black hole. My frustrated mind focuses on its monstrously pliable and unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>This abyssal butt makes me feel even more frustrated and inadequate, a truly horrifying burden.</li>
            <li>The abyssal nature of my butt is truly depressing, especially when I'm consumed by such deep frustration. It's too vast.</li>
            <li>It’s an abyssal, uninspired, disgusting form. My frustration makes me acutely aware of how truly unappealing and submissive it is.</li>
            <li>My butt's abyssal nature is a grim reminder of my sexual frustration. It offers no inviting firmness, just a horrifying expanse.</li>
            <li>This frustrating, abyssal butt offers no comfort, only accentuating my unfulfilled desires and deep dissatisfaction.</li>
            <li>A vast, overly yielding expanse, disgustingly saggy. My frustrated state only highlights the utter lack of any pleasing firmness.</li>
            <li>My butt feels like a giving, yet horrifyingly unfulfilling, space. This gnawing frustration makes me see only its weak, immense compliance.</li>
            <li>The sheer abyssal nature is infuriating. It offers no escape from this sexual frustration, just a dismal, grotesque reality.</li>
            <li>It's an abyssal, unflattering, monstrous shape. My frustrated thoughts are consumed by its pathetic inability to satisfy or hold.</li>
            <li>My abyssal butt feels like a weakness when I'm this frustrated. It’s a soft, uninspiring, repellent form.</li>
            <li>This butt is laughably abyssal. My frustration only intensifies as I realize how truly uninspiring and yielding, yet vast, it is.</li>
            <li>The feeling of its utter abyssal nature just compounds my deep, sexual frustration. It’s a constant, bleak, horrifying reminder.</li>
            <li>My butt is so pathetically abyssal, it just makes me angrier and more frustrated with my unfulfilled desires.</li>
            <li>It’s a terrible, loose, sagging, vast thing. The frustration I feel makes me want to scream at its sheer passivity and emptiness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
