<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, it’s there, hardly worth noting.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, barely noticeable, with a puckered appearance.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight opening that was compact and firm.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, with a subtle curve that was barely visible.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, almost imperceptible, with a delicate crease.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening that was pinched shut, with a subtle indentation.</li>
			<li>I glimpsed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, with a faint curve that was barely discernible.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, noticing its tiny opening, barely visible to the naked eye. The ring of muscle surrounding it seemed incredibly tight, as if it was puckered inward.</li>
			<li>Upon examination, I saw that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus had a delicate, almost imperceptible rim, with the skin around it smooth and unblemished.</li>
			<li>As I gazed at it, I noted that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus seemed almost like a small, closed dot, with the surrounding skin appearing slightly paler than the rest of the area.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, with smooth, unblemished skin, showcasing a minuscule, perfectly circular hole.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a delicate, incredibly snug orifice, adorned with thin, silky skin, barely concealing the tiny, tight entrance.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, hugged by soft, flawless skin, hinting at a barely accessible interior.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty posterior, observed fleetingly, revealed a very small, barely visible anus, seemingly tucked away.</li>
            <li>A quick look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} behind showed a petite anus, almost unnoticeable amidst the smooth, youthful curves.</li>
            <li>The young female's small anus, a mere hint, was briefly seen. Its modest size made it rather discreet.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful form displayed a compact posterior, and the tiny anus was a fleeting detail.</li>
            <li>I noted a small, almost imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} otherwise unblemished backside. It seemed tightly closed.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature on a youthful physique.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I saw a tiny, puckered opening, very much in proportion with {PAWN_possessive} slender figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert buttocks framed a truly miniature anus, hardly warranting a second glance.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was quite striking, a tightly-closed rosebud on a firm posterior.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed by the delicate lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The young female's micro anus, a compact detail, seemed to almost disappear within the graceful curve of {PAWN_possessive} rear.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, a small, tight aperture, very discreetly nestled between the soft, shapely cheeks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock presented a subtle curve, and the barely visible anus was a small, unassuming mark.</li>
            <li>The impression was of a small, puckered opening, almost swallowed by the youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} behind.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, somewhat hidden anus, perfectly proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>Her youthful derriere held a tiny, almost closed anus, a modest feature.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was evident, a neat, unassuming opening.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, a subtle and tight detail on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The petite anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm butt was discreet, blending well with the overall contours.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere dimple in the soft landscape of {PAWN_possessive} buttocks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, briefly exposed, showed a small, unobtrusive anus, quite tight.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's anus appeared tiny, almost pinched shut, a small dot against a smooth canvas.</li>
            <li>Her form revealed a small, tight anus, a barely noticeable feature.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a faint, almost invisible crease within the tender skin.</li>
            <li>The small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was quite compact, suggesting an unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus was a very subtle point, tucked away and hardly protruding.</li>
            <li>A fleeting observation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks highlighted a tiny, tight anus.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a striking aspect of {PAWN_possessive} otherwise well-proportioned backside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm bottom hosted a very small anus, neatly closed and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>I briefly saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate, almost unseen feature on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my interest. Such a small, delicate opening, barely visible, it suggested an intriguing privacy.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a subtle curiosity. The modest form held a certain allure.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite closer inspection. My old senses perked up.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature hinting at unexplored depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing an odd fascination within me.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that momentarily distracted me.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing. My loins stirred.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful challenge.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a fleeting, improper thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} young body.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred an old, familiar urge within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly caught my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strange pull towards its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite speculation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an illicit thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hide a captivating allure.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>Her petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent invitation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a slight stir within me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a subtle throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior held a very small, almost unnoticeable anus, typical for a young frame.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite anus, discreetly nestled, as is common in youth.</li>
            <li>The young female's tiny anus, barely a crease, was observed without particular interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful form showed a compact behind, the small anus a minor detail.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tightly puckered anus, appearing rather innocent on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was quite subtle, a quiet feature on {PAWN_possessive} unblemished form.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I saw a miniature opening, quite neat and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of observation.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a simple, unassuming knot.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost swallowed by the delicate contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The young female's micro anus, a mere compact detail, seemed to almost disappear within the graceful curve.</li>
            <li>I noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, a small, tight aperture, very discreetly nestled between the shapely cheeks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock presented a subtle curve, and the barely visible anus was a small, unassuming mark.</li>
            <li>The impression was of a small, puckered opening, almost indistinguishable on the youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} behind.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, somewhat hidden anus, perfectly proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>Her youthful derriere held a tiny, almost closed anus, a modest feature, common enough.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was evident, a neat, unremarkable opening.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, a subtle and tight detail on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The petite anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm butt was discreet, blending well with the overall contours.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere dimple in the soft landscape of {PAWN_possessive} buttocks, nothing unusual.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, briefly exposed, showed a small, unobtrusive anus, quite tight.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's anus appeared tiny, almost pinched shut, a small dot against a smooth canvas.</li>
            <li>Her form revealed a small, tight anus, a barely noticeable feature, as expected.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a faint, almost invisible crease within the tender skin.</li>
            <li>The small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was quite compact, suggesting an unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus was a very subtle point, tucked away and hardly protruding.</li>
            <li>A fleeting observation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks highlighted a tiny, tight anus, just as one would imagine.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a typical aspect of {PAWN_possessive} otherwise well-proportioned backside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm bottom hosted a very small anus, neatly closed and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>I briefly saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate, almost unseen feature on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin, nothing to comment on.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus was a surprising detail on {PAWN_possessive} otherwise soft and inviting backside.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a discreet, puckered opening that seemed to hint at a firm, unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth buttocks was a subtle, yet intriguing, feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while shapely, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, adding an air of mystery.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, made me wonder about its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was quite striking, a tight, closed bud on {PAWN_possessive} firm butt.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a faint crease that seemed almost virgin-like in its compactness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, barely visible, added a touch of innocent purity to {PAWN_possessive} otherwise desirable form.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were well-formed, and the tiny anus was a neat, unyielding point of interest.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast to the rest of {PAWN_possessive} inviting body.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed by the soft, rounded contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus, a compact and firm opening, seemed to challenge expectations of such a delicate area.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, hugged by soft, flawless skin, hinting at a barely accessible interior.</li>
            <li>The petite anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shapely backside was a subtle detail, creating a sense of understated allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert bottom featured a micro anus, a surprisingly tight and firm aperture.</li>
            <li>The nearly invisible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear seemed to possess a delicate, unblemished quality.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive anus, a tight, closed rosebud on {PAWN_possessive} smooth, youthful skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost unnoticeable anus, a subtle and tight feature, added an element of quiet intrigue.</li>
            <li>The small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was quite compact, suggesting an interesting firmness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, barely a visible line, suggested a pristine, untainted aspect.</li>
            <li>Her otherwise alluring backside featured a remarkably small, tight anus, which was surprisingly alluring.</li>
            <li>The precise, small anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm bottom was a detail that caught my eye.</li>
            <li>I noticed the micro anus, so compact and closed, adding to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} untouched appearance.</li>
            <li>The small, puckered anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth rear seemed almost innocent, yet undeniably present.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, a faint, barely discernible crease, hinted at a delicate, unyielding nature.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks revealed a very small, tight anus, making me wonder.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus made it all the more intriguing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact anus, a discreet feature, was surprisingly captivating on {PAWN_possessive} shapely form.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, which seemed to suggest a quiet strength.</li>
            <li>The delicate opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, so small, gave it an air of untouched purity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, almost hidden, sparked a keen voyeuristic interest. Such a discreet feature.</li>
            <li>I keenly observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness adding to its allure. A truly private portal.</li>
            <li>The delicate, barely visible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a captivating sight for my curious gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior revealed an almost imperceptibly small anus, a delightful detail to uncover.</li>
            <li>My eyes lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly puckered, inviting a silent, prolonged examination.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more fascinating.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet so intriguing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret for my observant eyes.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling to behold.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my gaze was drawn to its subtle form.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and I found myself studying it intently.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, invited further, unspoken contemplation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I wished to unravel.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that held my attention.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder for my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature was truly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was a subtle marvel.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strange pull towards its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to beckon my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating allure that I couldn't ignore.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent invitation for observation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct shift in my attention. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My voyeuristic gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of profound curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a compelling draw as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my voyeuristic interest. Such a small, delicate opening, hinting at a hidden treasure.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a powerful urge within me.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite a forbidden examination. My loins stirred.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature arousing a primal fascination.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing an odd, intense desire.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience, and my blood quickened.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that momentarily made my own body react.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing. My desire grew.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful, forbidden challenge.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness, stirring my senses.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, enticing charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, improper urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling and exciting.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} young body, stirring me.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred an old, powerful urge within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance, and my body responded.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly stimulated my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strong pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form, sparking interest.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking a strong, illicit desire.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>Her petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a significant stir within me. A truly private, exciting gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My desire grew.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an intense sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my voyeuristic interest. Such a small, delicate opening, suggestive and intriguing.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a subtle, shared curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite a quiet, shared contemplation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature hinting at delightful secrets.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing a subtle, feminine fascination.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience, quite common at that age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my own observations.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing, a delicate beauty.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful, shared intimacy.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly captivating in its modesty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness, yet quite familiar.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, feminine charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a fleeting, almost sisterly thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} young body.</li>
            <li>The youthful female's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred a knowing curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance, quite common.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly caught my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a subtle resonance with its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite a silent, shared understanding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking a sense of familiarity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating allure, a shared feminine secret.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>Her petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, intriguing invitation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a subtle stir within me. A truly private gateway, like my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My gaze lingered with empathy.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of shared intimacy.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of feminine curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a peculiar sense of kinship as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus was noted. Its modesty might be intriguing to some, if only it were more visible.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, rather discreet opening. It was there, plainly observed.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle detail, perhaps too subtle for my taste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making it less of a spectacle.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was acknowledged. Nothing particularly notable.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature. Barely worth showing.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact and rather ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of exhibition.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was not particularly striking.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed. One would have to search to truly see it.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, but too subtle for an impact.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. Not much to exhibit.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was almost disappointing in its lack of prominence.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that offers little for display.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail, but hardly a showstopper.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, perhaps too discreet.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature not ideal for exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was rather unrevealing.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it offered little for a public display.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to keep all its secrets.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, yet failed to impress.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, too subtle for any real impact.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold little to offer for public viewing.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, and thus, unexciting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, uninspiring presence.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct lack of excitement. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly uncaptivating. My gaze moved on.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of indifference.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that barely registered.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a certain apathy as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus was noted. Its modesty might be intriguing, if only it were more overtly displayed. My own body feels more alive.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, discreet opening. It was there, but offered little to truly impress my exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle detail, perhaps too subtle for proper admiration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making it less of a grand spectacle for me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was acknowledged. It lacked the boldness I prefer.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature. Barely worth seeing, compared to my own.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact and rather ordinary for a public display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point for exhibition; my own parts feel more compelling.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was not particularly striking or provocative.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed. One would have to search, which defeats the purpose of exhibition.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, but too subtle for a real impact on an audience.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. Not much to truly exhibit, unlike what I offer.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was almost disappointing in its lack of prominence.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that offers little for a bold display.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail, but hardly a showstopper. My own presence is grander.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, perhaps too discreet for my tastes.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature not ideal for public display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was rather unrevealing.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it offered little for public appreciation.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to keep all its secrets, unlike my own open nature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, yet failed to impress my exhibitionist spirit.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, too subtle for any real impact.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold little to offer for public viewing, contrasting with my own.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, and thus, unexciting for exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, uninspiring presence, unlike the vibrant display I offer.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct lack of excitement for me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly uncaptivating. My gaze quickly moved on, seeking something more grand.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of indifference, a missed opportunity for spectacle.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that barely registered as an exhibition.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a certain apathy as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it simply wasn't enough.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus was noted. Its modesty might be intriguing, though I prefer a bolder display myself.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, discreet opening. It was there, plainly observed, but not particularly striking.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle detail, perhaps too subtle for strong impression.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making it less of a grand spectacle.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was acknowledged. It lacked the openness I appreciate.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature. Barely noticeable, unlike my own.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact and rather ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point for exhibition, unlike a more prominent one.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was not particularly striking or expressive.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed. One would have to search, which isn't the point of exhibition.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, but too subtle for true impact.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. Not much to truly exhibit for others.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was almost disappointing in its lack of prominence.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that offers little for a bold display.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail, but hardly a showstopper.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, perhaps too discreet for my exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature not ideal for public display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was rather unrevealing.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it offered little for public appreciation.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to keep all its secrets, unlike my own openness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, yet failed to truly impress.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, too subtle for any real impact or notice.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold little to offer for public viewing, unlike what I showcase.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, and thus, unexciting for exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, uninspiring presence, unlike my own vibrant display.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct lack of excitement for me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly uncaptivating. My gaze quickly moved on, seeking something more grand.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of indifference, a missed opportunity for spectacle.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that barely registered as an exhibition.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a certain apathy as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}; it simply wasn't enough.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, though small, still hinted at possibilities. My thoughts wandered to intimate encounters.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness intriguing. A subtle opening, yet it sparked a familiar warmth within me.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, despite its size, stirred a sensual curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making me wonder about its capacity.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, ignited a playful, suggestive thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more alluring to my desires.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet it pulsed with unspoken promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my desires.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling, drawing my carnal thoughts.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my desires envisioned its eventual yielding.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and my mind raced with possibilities.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but desire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, seductive charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, intimate urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I longed to explore.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that aroused me deeply.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and my body responded.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature tantalizingly seductive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strong pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite illicit thoughts and desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, captivating me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense, carnal curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for my senses.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct stir within me. A truly private, exciting gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My nymphomaniac gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of intense anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, though small, still hinted at immense pleasure. My groin tingled.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness intriguing. A subtle opening that fired my male desire.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, despite its size, stirred a powerful carnal urge in me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making my imagination run wild with its potential.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, ignited a forceful, lustful thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more alluring to my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet it pulsed with undeniable, raw promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my deep, primal needs.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling, drawing my rampant thoughts.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my male desires envisioned its complete and utter yielding.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and my mind raced with carnal possibilities.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but desire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, overwhelmingly seductive charm. My cock hardened.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, immediate, intimate urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I desperately longed to conquer and explore.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that powerfully aroused me.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and my body instantly responded.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature overwhelmingly tantalizing and seductive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was incredibly stimulating to my senses.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling an overwhelming pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite every illicit thought and desire I harbored.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, utterly captivating me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense, raw, carnal curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for my male senses.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly and completely arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, unbelievably tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct, undeniable stir within me. A truly private, intensely exciting gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My nymphomaniac gaze lingered, filled with anticipation.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of intense, urgent anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit, and deeply arousing curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound, aching throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, though small, still hinted at shared pleasures. A familiar warmth stirred within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness intriguing. A subtle opening that resonated with my own desires.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, despite its size, stirred a powerful, shared curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making me wonder about our shared experiences.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, ignited a playful, suggestive thought of intimacy.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more alluring to my female desires.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet it pulsed with unspoken, shared promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my deepest needs.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling, drawing my carnal thoughts.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my desires envisioned its eventual, mutual yielding.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and my mind raced with intimate possibilities.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but desire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, shared seductive charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, intimate urge within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I longed to explore, perhaps together.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that aroused me deeply.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and my body responded with a familiar throb.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature tantalizingly seductive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strong pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite illicit thoughts and shared desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, captivating me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense, carnal curiosity, a shared feeling.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for my senses.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt, mirroring my own.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct stir within me. A truly private, exciting gateway for us both.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My nymphomaniac gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of intense anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus was briefly visible, a modest and private part, respectfully observed.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness indicating a delicate and intimate area, which I acknowledged gently.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle detail, a personal feature to be respected.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, a discreet part of their anatomy.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was observed with a respectful neutrality.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature, not for judgment.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact and seemingly unblemished.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a private point that deserves no particular comment.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was simply a factual observation.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, and I respectfully averted my gaze after a brief glance.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, but ultimately a personal detail.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It was simply a part of {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was noted with quiet acceptance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested a modest and private aspect of their body.</li>
            <li>My gaze briefly touched on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and unremarkable detail.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, which I observed without judgment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, simply a part of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was simply present.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it was a deeply personal detail.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, a simple observation.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused no particular reaction. A private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that was neither good nor bad.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus was a bit too much to observe. Such a private part should remain unseen.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, rather discreet opening, which was still frankly improper.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle detail, yet still an unwarranted exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, which I still found a tad vulgar.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was acknowledged with a definite discomfort.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature that should not be visible.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact, yet utterly immodest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of observation, but still offensive.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was simply a factual observation, though uncalled for.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, but its very presence was discomforting.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, but ultimately a private detail that shouldn't be exposed.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It was frankly inappropriate.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was noted with a distinct disapproval.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested a modest and private aspect, which should stay private.</li>
            <li>My gaze briefly touched on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and unremarkable detail, which was still too much.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and I wish I hadn't seen it.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, utterly unnecessary for me to witness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was simply too much to bear.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it was a deeply personal detail that was wrongly exposed.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal, yet wrong to see.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form, but still felt wrong.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, a simple observation that I did not appreciate.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me, but was offensive nonetheless.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning, just unwelcome.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence, but should remain hidden.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct aversion. A private gateway that should be covered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy, but not for my eyes.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention, yet felt improper.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that was both unappealing and immodest.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail that was unfortunately exposed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior revealed a very small, almost unnoticeable anus, typical for a male frame.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite anus, discreetly nestled, as is common in male anatomy.</li>
            <li>The male's tiny anus, barely a crease, was observed without particular interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form showed a compact behind, the small anus a minor, unremarkable detail.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tightly puckered anus, appearing rather ordinary on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was quite subtle, a quiet feature on {PAWN_possessive} unblemished form.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I saw a miniature opening, quite neat and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of observation.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a simple, unassuming knot.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost swallowed by the delicate contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The male's micro anus, a mere compact detail, seemed to almost disappear within the graceful curve.</li>
            <li>I noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, a small, tight aperture, very discreetly nestled between the shapely cheeks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock presented a subtle curve, and the barely visible anus was a small, unassuming mark.</li>
            <li>The impression was of a small, puckered opening, almost indistinguishable on the male roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} behind.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, somewhat hidden anus, perfectly proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>His derriere held a tiny, almost closed anus, a modest feature, common enough.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was evident, a neat, unremarkable opening.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, a subtle and tight detail on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The petite anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm butt was discreet, blending well with the overall contours.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere dimple in the soft landscape of {PAWN_possessive} buttocks, nothing unusual.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, briefly exposed, showed a small, unobtrusive anus, quite tight.</li>
            <li>The male's anus appeared tiny, almost pinched shut, a small dot against a smooth canvas.</li>
            <li>His form revealed a small, tight anus, a barely noticeable feature, as expected.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a faint, almost invisible crease within the tender skin.</li>
            <li>The small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was quite compact, suggesting an unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus was a very subtle point, tucked away and hardly protruding.</li>
            <li>A fleeting observation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks highlighted a tiny, tight anus, just as one would imagine.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a typical aspect of {PAWN_possessive} otherwise well-proportioned backside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm bottom hosted a very small anus, neatly closed and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>I briefly saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate, almost unseen feature on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin, nothing to comment on.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my interest. Such a small, delicate opening, hinting at intriguing possibilities.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a subtle, familiar curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>The male's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite a closer, more personal inspection. My old senses perked up.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature hinting at unexplored depths for us.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing an odd fascination within me.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that momentarily distracted me.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing. My loins stirred.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful challenge.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a fleeting, improper thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} young body.</li>
            <li>The male's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred an old, familiar urge within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly caught my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strange pull towards its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite speculation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form, sparking interest.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an illicit thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating allure for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>His petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent invitation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a slight stir within me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a subtle throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest posterior held a very small, almost unnoticeable anus, typical for a male frame.</li>
            <li>A quick look revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite anus, discreetly nestled, as is common in males.</li>
            <li>The male's tiny anus, barely a crease, was observed without particular interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form showed a compact behind, the small anus a minor detail.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tightly puckered anus, appearing rather innocent on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was quite subtle, a quiet feature on {PAWN_possessive} unblemished form.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I saw a miniature opening, quite neat and unremarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of observation.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a simple, unassuming knot.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost swallowed by the delicate contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The male's micro anus, a mere compact detail, seemed to almost disappear within the graceful curve.</li>
            <li>I noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, a small, tight aperture, very discreetly nestled between the shapely cheeks.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock presented a subtle curve, and the barely visible anus was a small, unassuming mark.</li>
            <li>The impression was of a small, puckered opening, almost indistinguishable on the male roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} behind.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, somewhat hidden anus, perfectly proportionate to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>His derriere held a tiny, almost closed anus, a modest feature, common enough.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was evident, a neat, unremarkable opening.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, a subtle and tight detail on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin.</li>
            <li>The petite anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm butt was discreet, blending well with the overall contours.</li>
            <li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere dimple in the soft landscape of {PAWN_possessive} buttocks, nothing unusual.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, briefly exposed, showed a small, unobtrusive anus, quite tight.</li>
            <li>The male's anus appeared tiny, almost pinched shut, a small dot against a smooth canvas.</li>
            <li>His form revealed a small, tight anus, a barely noticeable feature, as expected.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a faint, almost invisible crease within the tender skin.</li>
            <li>The small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was quite compact, suggesting an unyielding tightness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus was a very subtle point, tucked away and hardly protruding.</li>
            <li>A fleeting observation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks highlighted a tiny, tight anus, just as one would imagine.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was a typical aspect of {PAWN_possessive} otherwise well-proportioned backside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm bottom hosted a very small anus, neatly closed and unobtrusive.</li>
            <li>I briefly saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate, almost unseen feature on {PAWN_possessive} smooth skin, nothing to comment on.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus was a surprising detail on {PAWN_possessive} otherwise familiar backside.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a discreet, puckered opening that seemed to hint at a normal firmness.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth buttocks was a subtle, yet unremarkable, feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while shapely, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, adding an air of commonality.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, was observed. Nothing particularly notable or surprising.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature on a male physique.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, quite compact and rather ordinary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a negligible point of observation, common enough.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was quite striking, a tight, closed bud on {PAWN_possessive} firm butt.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed by the soft, rounded contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast to the rest of {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It was simply there.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, was noted with quiet acceptance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested a modest and private aspect.</li>
            <li>My gaze briefly touched on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and unremarkable detail.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, which I observed without judgment.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, simply a part of {PAWN_possessive} anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was simply present.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling it was a deeply personal detail.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, a simple observation.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused no particular reaction. A private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point that was neither good nor bad.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my interest. Such a small, delicate opening, hinting at intriguing secrets.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a subtle, familiar curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>The male's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite a closer, more personal inspection. My loins stirred.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature hinting at unexplored depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing an odd fascination within me.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that momentarily distracted me.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing. My desire grew.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful challenge.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a fleeting, improper thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>The male's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred an old, familiar urge within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly caught my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strange pull towards its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite speculation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an illicit thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating allure for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>His petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent invitation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a slight stir within me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a subtle throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus piqued my interest. Such a small, delicate opening, suggesting an intriguing privacy.</li>
            <li>A quick glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, so neatly hidden, stirred a subtle curiosity. The modest form held a certain allure.</li>
            <li>The male's minuscule anus, a discreet aperture, seemed to invite closer inspection. My senses perked up.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttock presented a surprisingly small anus, its closed nature hinting at unexplored depths.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, puckered anus. It looked so tight, almost unyielding, arousing an odd fascination within me.</li>
            <li>The diminutive, nearly imperceptible anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} supple form hinted at a tender inexperience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert behind revealed a truly tiny anus, a captivating secret that momentarily distracted me.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible crease, somehow made it more intriguing. My thoughts lingered.</li>
            <li>Such a miniature anus, almost disappearing into {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless skin, seemed to promise a delightful challenge.</li>
            <li>My eyes fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a tightly sealed blossom. It was surprisingly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while ample, framed an incredibly small anus, almost teasing in its hiddenness.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a fleeting, improper thought.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched purity that was oddly compelling.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail on {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>The male's small, tight anus, a barely visible opening, stirred a quiet, familiar urge within me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, suggesting a tantalizing resistance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, truly caught my attention.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strange pull towards its hidden depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite speculation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise lush form.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an illicit thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating allure for me.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>His petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent invitation.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a subtle stir within me. A truly private gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a subtle throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, though small, still hinted at immense pleasure. My groin tingled.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness intriguing. A subtle opening that fired my male desire.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, despite its size, stirred a powerful carnal urge in me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making my imagination run wild with its potential.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, ignited a forceful, lustful thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more alluring to my insatiable desires.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet it pulsed with undeniable, raw promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my deep, primal needs.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling, drawing my rampant thoughts.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my male desires envisioned its complete and utter yielding.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and my mind raced with carnal possibilities.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but desire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, overwhelmingly seductive charm. My cock hardened.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, immediate, intimate urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I desperately longed to conquer and explore.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that powerfully aroused me.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and my body instantly responded.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature overwhelmingly tantalizing and seductive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was incredibly stimulating to my senses.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling an overwhelming pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite every illicit thought and desire I harbored.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, utterly captivating me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense, raw, carnal curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for my male senses.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly and completely arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, unbelievably tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct, undeniable stir within me. A truly private, intensely exciting gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My nymphomaniac gaze lingered, filled with anticipation.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of intense, urgent anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit, and deeply arousing curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound, aching throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tight anus, though small, still hinted at intriguing encounters. My imagination stirred.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its smallness intriguing. A subtle opening that sparked a playful curiosity.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, despite its size, stirred a subtle sensual curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small anus, making me wonder about its capacity.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny anus, neatly tucked away, ignited a mischievous, suggestive thought.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was apparent; its hiddenness only made it more alluring to my desires.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature opening, so compact, yet it pulsed with unspoken promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro anus, a captivating secret that resonated with my desires.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly compelling, drawing my carnal thoughts.</li>
            <li>It was a very small anus, almost shyly concealed, yet my desires envisioned its eventual yielding.</li>
            <li>The micro anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast, and my mind raced with possibilities.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but desire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, seductive charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a mere hint, sparked a strong, intimate urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery that I longed to explore.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that aroused me deeply.</li>
            <li>The small, tight anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, and my body responded.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature tantalizingly seductive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible opening, feeling a strong pull towards its hidden, thrilling depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed to invite illicit thoughts and desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small anus, neatly closed, presented a curious contradiction against {PAWN_possessive} otherwise visible form, captivating me.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small anus, sparking an intense, carnal curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold a captivating, almost forbidden allure for my senses.</li>
            <li>I found myself drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a compact detail, almost too small to be real, yet utterly arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, tantalizing invitation that I keenly felt.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight anus caused a distinct stir within me. A truly private, exciting gateway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming anus, so tiny, was surprisingly captivating. My nymphomaniac gaze lingered.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a small, tight knot, drew an odd sense of intense anticipation.</li>
            <li>My attention was caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible anus, a subtle point of intense, illicit curiosity.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but feel a profound throb as I noted the small, perfectly puckered anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, demonic anus was a curious sight, hinting at unnatural origins and unusual functions.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro demon anus, its smallness contrasting with the implied power of its demonic nature.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden demonic anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle, yet unsettling, feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small demonic anus, a strange anomaly.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny demonic anus, neatly tucked away, was observed with a touch of morbid curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus was apparent, a small, unassuming feature on an unnatural form.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature, subtly demonic opening, quite compact and unsettling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro demonic anus, a negligible point of observation, yet strangely compelling.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly unsettling in its implications.</li>
            <li>It was a very small, demonic anus, almost shyly concealed, but its true nature was unmistakably arcane.</li>
            <li>The micro demonic anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast to its infernal essence.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty demonic anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, dark charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro demonic anus, a mere hint, sparked a shiver of curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small demonic anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery of infernal design.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule demonic anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that spoke of dark arts.</li>
            <li>The small, tight demonic anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, which filled me with a strange dread.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro demonic anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature subtly menacing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug, demonic orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible demonic opening, feeling a strange pull towards its unknown depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal, yet disturbingly alien.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small demonic anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form, but still felt wrong.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small demonic anus, a simple observation that chilled me slightly.</li>
            <li>The diminutive demonic anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me, but was unsettling nonetheless.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro demonic anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning, just inherently unnatural.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered demonic anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence, yet it whispered of other realms.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight demonic anus caused no particular reaction, but a sense of unease. A gateway to who knows where.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming demonic anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy, yet alien.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro demonic anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention, yet felt improper.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible demonic anus, a subtle point that was both unappealing and fascinating.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered demonic anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail that was unfortunately not normal at all.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, slimy anus was a curious sight, appearing unusually moist and soft.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus, its smallness emphasizing its odd, glistening texture.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden slime anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle, yet strangely amorphous, feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small slime anus, a strange, fluid anomaly.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny slime anus, neatly tucked away, was observed with a touch of biological curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus was apparent, a small, unassuming, yet undeniably viscous, feature.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature, subtly shimmering opening, quite compact and unusually pliable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro slime anus, a negligible point of observation, yet strangely fascinating in its fluidity.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly unsettling in its lack of firmness.</li>
            <li>It was a very small, slimy anus, almost shyly concealed, but its true nature was unmistakably gelatinous.</li>
            <li>The micro slime anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast to its unusual, soft composition.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty slime anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, squishy charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus, a mere hint, sparked a shiver of biological curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small slime anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery of fluid anatomy.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule slime anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that spoke of unusual biology.</li>
            <li>The small, tight slime anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, which filled me with a strange unease.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature subtly viscous.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug, slimy orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible slime opening, feeling a strange pull towards its unknown, squishy depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal, yet disturbingly unnatural.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form, but still felt wrong.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small slime anus, a simple observation that chilled me slightly.</li>
            <li>The diminutive slime anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me, but was unsettling nonetheless.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning, just inherently unnatural.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered slime anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence, yet it whispered of other forms of life.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight slime anus caused no particular reaction, but a sense of unease. A gateway to who knows where.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming slime anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy, yet alien.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention, yet felt improper.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible slime anus, a subtle point that was both unappealing and fascinating.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered slime anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail that was unfortunately not normal at all.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Micro_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Neutral) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, insect-like anus was a curious sight, appearing segmented and surprisingly delicate.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus, its smallness emphasizing its chitinous, alien texture.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost hidden insect anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was a subtle, yet strangely otherworldly, feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, while present, contained an almost imperceptibly small insect anus, a strange, chitinous anomaly.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny insect anus, neatly tucked away, was observed with a touch of biological curiosity.</li>
            <li>The diminutive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus was apparent, a small, unassuming, yet undeniably alien, feature.</li>
            <li>Peering at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, I noted a miniature, subtly iridescent opening, quite compact and unusually rigid.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks framed a truly micro insect anus, a negligible point of observation, yet strangely fascinating in its otherworldliness.</li>
            <li>The smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, a barely discernible knot, was surprisingly unsettling in its lack of familiar softness.</li>
            <li>It was a very small, insect-like anus, almost shyly concealed, but its true nature was unmistakably alien.</li>
            <li>The micro insect anus on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, curved rear was a surprising contrast to its unusual, hard composition.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but notice {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty insect anus, so compact and private. It held a peculiar, segmented charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus, a mere hint, sparked a shiver of biological curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small insect anus, barely visible, suggested an untouched mystery of alien anatomy.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingered on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule insect anus, a subtle and fascinating detail that spoke of unusual biology.</li>
            <li>The small, tight insect anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a barely visible opening, was a discreet wonder, which filled me with a strange unease.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus: a petite, puckered aperture, its hidden nature subtly arthropodal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, incredibly snug, insect orifice, barely concealing its tiny, tight entrance, was truly unsettling.</li>
            <li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost imperceptible insect opening, feeling a strange pull towards its unknown, segmented depths.</li>
            <li>The modest, tight opening of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect anus, a barely visible crevice, seemed perfectly normal, yet disturbingly alien.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small insect anus, neatly closed, presented a natural and unremarkable aspect of their form, but still felt wrong.</li>
            <li>A fleeting look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside revealed a remarkably small insect anus, a simple observation that chilled me slightly.</li>
            <li>The diminutive insect anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, so subtle, seemed to hold no particular significance for me, but was unsettling nonetheless.</li>
            <li>I found myself briefly noting {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus, a compact detail, not particularly exciting or concerning, just inherently unnatural.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, puckered insect anus, barely visible, seemed to hold a silent, neutral presence, yet it whispered of other forms of life.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight insect anus caused no particular reaction, but a sense of unease. A gateway to who knows where.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unassuming insect anus, so tiny, was simply a part of their overall anatomy, yet alien.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus, a small, tight knot, drew no significant attention, yet felt improper.</li>
            <li>My attention was briefly caught by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, almost invisible insect anus, a subtle point that was both unappealing and fascinating.</li>
            <li>I simply noted the small, perfectly puckered insect anus of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}, a normal anatomical detail that was unfortunately not normal at all.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>