<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus stands out in size, but it doesn’t evoke any strong thoughts from me.</li>
            <li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was incredibly large, with a gaping appearance that was intimidating.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was cavernous, with a bottomless depth that was unmatched.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was vast, with a wrinkled exterior that was loose and sagging.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was enormous, with a vast and yawning opening that was awe-inspiring.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was profound and seemingly bottomless, with a vast outer ring that was cavernous.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus that was boundless, with a deeply creased exterior that was worn and supple.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus, noticing its enormous, gaping opening. The surrounding skin seemed stretched to the limit, with a prominent, rounded rim that appeared almost flared.</li>
			<li>Upon closer inspection, I saw that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus had a seemingly endless, cavernous appearance, with the skin around it appearing highly stretched and thin.</li>
			<li>As I looked at it, I noted that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus appeared almost like a massive, dark void, with the surrounding skin seeming to recede into the background.</li>
			<li>I marveled at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus: an astoundingly vast, seemingly endless cavern, ensconced in supple, stretchy skin, revealing an incomprehensibly enormous, unfathomable hole.</li>
			<li>I scrutinized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus: a colossal, gaping abyss, draped in soft, resilient skin, uncovering an inconceivably wide, unfathomable chasm.</li>
			<li>I gazed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abyssal anus: upon a mind-bogglingly immense, seemingly infinite void, encompassed by yielding, unscarred skin, hinting at a stupefyingly large, immeasurable cavity.</li>
            <li>The remarkable scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior aperture presented itself, devoid of any discernible impact on my sensibilities.</li>
            <li>A truly vast, almost cavernous opening, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal region seemed to stretch far beyond typical limits.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, prominently formed, drew attention to a particularly wide and visible anal structure.</li>
            <li>The considerable dimensions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus were immediately apparent, nestled within substantial, yet unremarkable, gluteal curves.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, one could not miss the prominent and expansive anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large and somewhat distended anal aperture was noticeable, set against a backdrop of ample, rounded glutes.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal cavity was striking, framed by buttocks that seemed to accommodate its size.</li>
            <li>I noticed the exceptionally wide and openly presented anus, a central feature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-formed buttocks.</li>
            <li>An impressive depth characterized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal opening, suggesting a considerable capacity within.</li>
            <li>The expansive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, with its loose, accommodating folds, was quite apparent upon inspection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks provided a substantial frame for an unusually large and remarkably visible anal region.</li>
            <li>The large, somewhat slack appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus indicated a history of considerable stretching.</li>
            <li>A notably wide and fully exposed anus was a key detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior presented a deep, cavernous anal opening, drawing the eye with its sheer scale.</li>
            <li>The impressive circumference of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal aperture was quite evident, framed by soft, yielding flesh.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, the prominent and seemingly well-used anal structure was hard to miss.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably distended anus occupied a significant portion of {PAWN_possessive} otherwise standard posterior.</li>
            <li>The extensive stretch of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal opening implied a notable history of engagement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, while robust, did little to conceal the unusually large and open anal cavity.</li>
            <li>A particularly deep and receptive looking anus was visible, indicative of significant prior activity.</li>
            <li>The expanse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal ring was quite telling, suggesting considerable accommodation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior featured an anal opening of considerable size, with a somewhat relaxed and inviting form.</li>
            <li>The visible contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus suggested frequent dilation, making it quite prominent.</li>
            <li>I noted the impressive size and apparent elasticity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal aperture, a curious anatomical detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample buttocks framed an anal opening that was both large and openly displayed.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
	
</Def>



<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her buttocks presented a modest curve, framing a clearly visible, albeit unremarkable, anal opening.</li>
            <li>He observed her posterior, noting the ordinary shape of her glutes and the typical presentation of her anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare backside revealed a standard form, with a visible, yet average, anal structure.</li>
            <li>Her buttock shape was unextraordinary, leading to an anal aperture of conventional size and visibility.</li>
            <li>He took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was moderate, and the anal area seemed quite typical.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while not particularly striking, displayed a normally formed butt and a standard anal opening.</li>
            <li>He noticed her ample, yet common, buttocks, and the clear, unsurprising visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was within common parameters, highlighting an anal region of regular appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of a common feminine shape, revealing a rather ordinary and observable anal orifice.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined but typical anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was unremarkable, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small.</li>
            <li>He simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, unexceptional anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered a straightforward view; the buttock structure was average, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite standard, with an anal area that garnered little specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, normal-sized anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, while feminine, exhibited a very common set of proportions, including a regularly sized anus.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed typical curves and a clearly present, standard anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, though not particularly pronounced.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was conventional, with the anal opening apparent without being overly emphasized.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was largely unmemorable, displaying an ordinary form and typical anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed her from behind; her buttocks were of average fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite average, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was common, ending in a well-defined, standard anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the unexceptional, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and typically feminine, showcasing an anal area that was neither striking nor concealed.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet unremarkable, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather ordinary, presenting an anus of standard visibility and form.</li>
            <li>He cast a perfunctory glance, noting the usual shape of her backside and the average appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar feminine shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced.</li>
            <li>He surveyed her posterior, taking in the predictable contours of her glutes and the standard view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her full, ripe buttocks presented a tantalizing view, with a deeply recessed anus hinting at unseen depths.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at her firm, rounded posterior suggested a well-defined, somewhat eager anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The luscious curve of her backside drew my gaze to the tightly puckered, yet inviting, anal entrance.</li>
            <li>Her shapely glutes framed a tantalizingly visible anus, a sight that certainly piqued my experienced curiosity.</li>
            <li>Observing her perfectly formed buttocks, I noted the small, yet remarkably distinct, anal opening.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of her posterior led to a surprisingly open and accessible looking anal region.</li>
            <li>Her youthful backside, plump and enticing, revealed a compact but clearly defined anal structure.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, round posterior made me appreciate the delicate, yet prominent, anal crevice.</li>
            <li>Her ample buttocks, firm and inviting, framed an anal aperture that seemed to promise much.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the view of her full backside, especially the subtly presented, yet alluring, anus.</li>
            <li>Her rear offered a pleasing form, directing my attention to the well-defined and intriguing anal area.</li>
            <li>The alluring curve of her glutes emphasized a small, but distinctly visible, anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her fresh, firm posterior, combined with a surprisingly loose-looking anus, was an interesting contrast.</li>
            <li>I found myself observing the subtle expanse of her anal region, framed by delightfully soft, young buttocks.</li>
            <li>The sight of her pert backside and clearly delineated anus sparked a familiar, quiet appreciation within me.</li>
            <li>Her smooth, youthful buttocks cradled an anus that appeared both tight and yet, intriguingly, well-defined.</li>
            <li>I noticed the pleasant roundness of her glutes, and the small, but noticeable, anal puckering.</li>
            <li>The enticing firmness of her rear contrasted nicely with the visible, yet modest, anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, still supple with youth, displayed an anal opening that seemed subtly receptive.</li>
            <li>A charmingly rounded backside, leading to an anal structure that, though small, held my gaze.</li>
            <li>I indulged in a moment of quiet observation of her inviting buttocks and their central, intriguing feature.</li>
            <li>Her feminine rear, full and appealing, highlighted a visible, yet discreet, anal opening.</li>
            <li>The delightful shape of her glutes made the otherwise small anal aperture remarkably noticeable.</li>
            <li>Her youthful posterior, firm and enticing, presented an anus that was clearly formed and inviting.</li>
            <li>I appreciated the gentle curve of her lower back blending into her buttocks, revealing a well-defined anal area.</li>
            <li>The fullness of her young backside, coupled with a visibly formed anus, was quite a sight.</li>
            <li>Her bare posterior was a vision of youthful curves, with a delicate yet distinct anal opening.</li>
            <li>I quietly admired her backside; the soft contours of her buttocks led to an intriguingly visible anus.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young glutes subtly revealed an anal aperture that, though compact, was clearly defined and alluring.</li>
            <li>The sight of her fresh backside, with its intriguing anal details, evoked a certain… appreciation in my seasoned mind.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her youthful buttocks seemed shapely, though the anal opening itself was rather ordinary, as expected.</li>
            <li>One observed her posterior, noting the common, rounded form of her glutes and the normal visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The young woman's backside appeared standard, with a buttock shape and anal presentation within typical parameters.</li>
            <li>Her rear offered a familiar sight: average gluteal development and an anal aperture of typical size and prominence.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was unremarkable, revealing an anal area that presented as quite typical.</li>
            <li>She saw the young female's exposed backside; the buttocks were of a common feminine form, and the anus was visible.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare rear was conventional, with unexceptional curves and a plainly visible anal structure.</li>
            <li>Her glutes seemed adequately rounded, and her anal opening was visible but held no particular distinction.</li>
            <li>The young woman’s buttock shape was not unusual, leading to a visible yet ordinary anal crevice.</li>
            <li>One observed her posterior: a standard feminine form, with a normal-sized and visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered a straightforward view, with proportionate buttocks and an anal area that seemed entirely usual.</li>
            <li>The young female's exposed rear, while youthful, exhibited an anus of quite common visibility and dimension.</li>
            <li>She noted the simple curves of her glutes, revealing an anal aperture that was visible but not pronounced.</li>
            <li>The young woman's posterior was of a regular build, displaying a common shape and a typically visible anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were fairly rounded, with the anal region appearing as a standard, discernible feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of her backside revealed a posterior of average feminine development, including a visibly normal anus.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite conventional, presenting a normally shaped butt and a visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>She cast a glance at the young female's posterior, noting the familiar curves and a standard anal presentation.</li>
            <li>The backside in question had the usual contours of youth, displaying a typically sized and visible anal feature.</li>
            <li>Her glutes offered no surprises, framing an anal opening that was present and observable, but not exceptional.</li>
            <li>One noted her posterior was modestly formed, with an anus that appeared neither hidden nor unusually exposed.</li>
            <li>The young woman's bare rear was quite common, showing a buttock shape and anal visibility that was expected.</li>
            <li>She observed the normal development of her glutes, leading to an anal aperture of regular and discernible form.</li>
            <li>The sight of her backside was rather unremarkable, displaying an anal area that appeared entirely typical.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of a common youthful roundness, with the anal opening appearing as a normal, visible detail.</li>
            <li>One looked upon her posterior, noting the familiar contours of her glutes and the straightforward appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>The young female's rear was of an ordinary build, with an anal structure that was visible and entirely conventional.</li>
            <li>She merely registered the sight of her bare backside, including the typically formed buttocks and visible anus.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally typical for her age, presenting an anal opening that was clearly present but unexceptional.</li>
            <li>The young woman's backside exhibited common features: standard gluteal form and a normally visible anal region.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her firm, rounded buttocks led to a surprisingly clear view of her distinct anal opening.</li>
            <li>He observed her posterior, noting the pleasant curve of her glutes and the noticeable, inviting anal area.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare backside revealed a well-formed butt, with a visible anus that seemed to draw his gaze.</li>
            <li>Her shapely buttocks framed an anal aperture of moderate size, subtly hinting at deeper curiosity.</li>
            <li>He took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was attractive, and the anal region seemed intriguing.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while subtle, displayed an appealing butt and a visible, slightly puckered anal opening.</li>
            <li>He noticed her ample, appealing buttocks, and the clear, yet somewhat understated, visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite pleasing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of a desirable feminine shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was appealing, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but inviting.</li>
            <li>He simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered some specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior, while feminine, exhibited a very pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized anus.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, standard anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively feminine, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar feminine shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>He surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-defined buttocks provided an unobstructed view of {PAWN_possessive} intriguing anal opening.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, noting the form of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the clear presentation of {PAWN_possessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare backside revealed a distinct form, with a visible, often fascinating, anal structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and visibility.</li>
            <li>The observer took in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite notable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>One noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior form was noteworthy, and {PAWN_possessive} anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but inviting.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} from behind; {PAWN_possessive} buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the intriguing appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the subtly alluring view of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her shapely buttocks, especially when she moved, offered an enticing glimpse of her distinct anal opening.</li>
            <li>He observed her posterior, noting the appealing curve of her glutes and the subtly inviting anal area.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare backside revealed a desirable form, with a visible anus that held his lingering attention.</li>
            <li>Her firm buttocks framed an anal aperture of notable prominence, sparking a familiar curiosity within him.</li>
            <li>He took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was attractive, and the anal region seemed quite captivating.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear displayed an appealing butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, prompting a private reflection.</li>
            <li>He noticed her ample, captivating buttocks, and the clear, yet somewhat understated, visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite pleasing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and appealing appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of a desirable feminine shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice, and he appreciated it.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and subtly intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite inviting.</li>
            <li>He simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, alluring anal aperture, arousing a quiet thought.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible and compelling.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered his distinct attention.</li>
            <li>He observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening that caught his eye.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration, stimulating a fleeting notion.</li>
            <li>He noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing his prolonged, appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight to behold.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours, stirring a thought.</li>
            <li>He observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible, a captivating detail.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus, stirring a silent reaction.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening, a sight he often sought.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing to his gaze.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening, causing a subtle, internal reaction.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form that he appreciated.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus, a silent appraisal.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar feminine shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing to his discerning eye.</li>
            <li>He surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus, arousing a quiet interest.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her shapely buttocks, particularly in motion, offered an enticing glimpse of her distinct anal opening.</li>
            <li>She observed her posterior, noting the appealing curve of her glutes and the subtly inviting anal area.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare backside revealed a desirable form, with a visible anus that held her lingering attention.</li>
            <li>Her firm buttocks framed an anal aperture of notable prominence, sparking a familiar curiosity within her.</li>
            <li>She took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was attractive, and the anal region seemed quite captivating.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear displayed an appealing butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, prompting a private reflection.</li>
            <li>She noticed her ample, captivating buttocks, and the clear, yet somewhat understated, visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite pleasing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and appealing appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of a desirable feminine shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice, and she appreciated it.</li>
            <li>She calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and subtly intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite inviting.</li>
            <li>She simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, alluring anal aperture, arousing a quiet thought.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible and compelling.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered her distinct attention.</li>
            <li>She observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening that caught her eye.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration, stimulating a fleeting notion.</li>
            <li>She noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing her prolonged, appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight to behold.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours, stirring a thought.</li>
            <li>She observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible, a captivating detail.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus, stirring a silent reaction.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>She acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening, a sight she often sought.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing to her gaze.</li>
            <li>She registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening, causing a subtle, internal reaction.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form that she appreciated.</li>
            <li>She cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus, a silent appraisal.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar feminine shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing to her discerning eye.</li>
            <li>She surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus, arousing a quiet interest.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks, with {PAWN_possessive} clearly visible anus, presented a rather striking display.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, highlighting {PAWN_possessive} prominent anal opening, was quite noticeable.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare backside, noting the form of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the unabashed display of {PAWN_possessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible.</li>
            <li>The observer took in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>One noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior form was noteworthy, and {PAWN_possessive} anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} from behind; {PAWN_possessive} buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the intriguing appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the subtly alluring view of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her exposed buttocks, with her clearly visible anus, presented a rather striking display that resonated with him.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of her posterior, highlighting her prominent anal opening, was quite noticeable and appreciated.</li>
            <li>He observed her bare backside, noting the form of her glutes and the unabashed display of her anal region.</li>
            <li>Her buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which he found interesting.</li>
            <li>He took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight he valued.</li>
            <li>He noticed her ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see, a mutual understanding.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>He simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>He surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her exposed buttocks, with her clearly visible anus, presented a rather striking display that she understood well.</li>
            <li>The open presentation of her posterior, highlighting her prominent anal opening, was quite noticeable and appreciated.</li>
            <li>She observed her bare backside, noting the form of her glutes and the unabashed display of her anal region.</li>
            <li>Her buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which she found interesting.</li>
            <li>She took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight she valued.</li>
            <li>She noticed her ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see, a mutual understanding.</li>
            <li>She calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>She simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>She observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>She noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>She observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>She merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>She registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>She cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>She surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent buttocks, coupled with {PAWN_possessive} visible anus, certainly caught one's attention, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>The clear presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, highlighting {PAWN_possessive} distinct anal opening, was quite noticeable.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare backside, noting the form of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the evident display of {PAWN_possessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible.</li>
            <li>The observer took in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>One noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior form was noteworthy, and {PAWN_possessive} anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} from behind; {PAWN_possessive} buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the intriguing appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the subtly alluring view of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her prominent buttocks, coupled with her visible anus, certainly caught his attention, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>The clear presentation of her posterior, highlighting her distinct anal opening, was quite noticeable to him.</li>
            <li>He observed her bare backside, noting the form of her glutes and the evident display of her anal region.</li>
            <li>Her buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which he found interesting.</li>
            <li>He took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight he valued.</li>
            <li>He noticed her ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>He simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>He surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her prominent buttocks, coupled with her visible anus, certainly caught her attention, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>The clear presentation of her posterior, highlighting her distinct anal opening, was quite noticeable to her.</li>
            <li>She observed her bare backside, noting the form of her glutes and the evident display of her anal region.</li>
            <li>Her buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which she found interesting.</li>
            <li>She took in her posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>Her exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight she valued.</li>
            <li>She noticed her ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of her anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of her posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>She calmly registered the sight of her backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>Her overall posterior form was noteworthy, and her anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>She simply observed her rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>Her backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of her posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>She observed her buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at her rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>She noted her glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>Her buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of her bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>She observed her from behind; her buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>Her figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of her lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>She merely acknowledged her exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of her anal opening.</li>
            <li>Her posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>She registered the presence of her buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of her bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>She cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of her backside and the intriguing appearance of her anus.</li>
            <li>Her buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>She surveyed her posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of her glutes and the subtly alluring view of her anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks appeared well-formed, and the anal opening, though visible, seemed natural and unoffensive.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, noting the soft contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the unassuming appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare backside revealed a gentle form, with a visible, yet discreet, anal structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock shape was quite harmonious, leading to an anal aperture of appropriate size and modest visibility.</li>
            <li>The observer took in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior view; the gluteal development was graceful, and the anal area seemed quite respectfully presented.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a pleasant butt and a distinctly visible, yet inoffensive, anal opening.</li>
            <li>One noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, well-proportioned buttocks, and the clear, yet gentle, visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of natural and unassuming appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were of a gentle shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice, presented without ostentation.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, including the well-defined and unassuming anal features.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior form was noteworthy, and {PAWN_possessive} anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite naturally presented.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly appealing anal aperture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} from behind; {PAWN_possessive} buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the intriguing appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the subtly alluring view of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were simply there, and the anal opening was visible, a fact noted without particular interest.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, a basic form of glutes with a plainly visible anal region, nothing more.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare backside revealed an expected form, with an ordinary, visible, anal structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock shape was unremarkable, leading to an anal aperture of typical size and visibility.</li>
            <li>The observer took in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior view; the gluteal development was standard, and the anal area seemed quite common.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed rear displayed a butt and a visible anal opening, a sight neither pleasant nor offensive.</li>
            <li>One noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} average buttocks, and the clear, unsurprising visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite plain, highlighting an anal region of unexceptional appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were of an ordinary shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice, entirely unremarkable.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside, including the well-defined but uninteresting anal features.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} overall posterior form was unremarkable, and {PAWN_possessive} anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, unalluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside offered a standard view; the buttock structure was average, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was quite uncaptivating, with an anal area that garnered little specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, unappealing anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior exhibited a mundane set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet unengaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear revealed unremarkable curves and a clearly present, unnoteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were adequately formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing no appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttock silhouette was plain, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a rather dull sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather unmemorable, displaying a plain form and unintriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} from behind; {PAWN_possessive} buttocks were of average fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure from the rear was quite ordinary, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lower back and glutes was common, ending in a well-defined, unalluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exposed buttocks and the unappealing, visible appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anal opening.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was structurally sound and rather plain, showcasing an anal area that was subtly unintriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks and the visible, yet unappealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior was rather dull, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an unappealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the ordinary shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside and the unintriguing appearance of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks were a familiar, unimpressive shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but unappealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, taking in the plain contours of {PAWN_possessive} glutes and the unalluring view of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His buttocks appeared robust, and the anal opening, though visible, seemed standard and unoffensive.</li>
            <li>One observed his posterior, noting the strong contours of his glutes and the unassuming appearance of his anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare backside revealed a masculine form, with a visible, yet discreet, anal structure.</li>
            <li>His buttock shape was quite defined, leading to an anal aperture of appropriate size and modest visibility.</li>
            <li>The observer took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was solid, and the anal area seemed quite respectfully presented.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a sturdy butt and a distinctly visible, yet inoffensive, anal opening.</li>
            <li>One noticed his ample, well-proportioned buttocks, and the clear, yet gentle, visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite typical, highlighting an anal region of natural and unassuming appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of a strong shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice, presented without ostentation.</li>
            <li>The observer calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined and unassuming anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was noteworthy, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite naturally presented.</li>
            <li>The observer simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly appealing anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>One observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>The observer noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>One observed him from behind; his buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The observer merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>One registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>The observer cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of his backside and the intriguing appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>One surveyed his posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of his glutes and the subtly alluring view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His firm buttocks presented a tantalizing view, with a deeply recessed anus hinting at unseen depths, sparking quiet appreciation.</li>
            <li>A quick glance at his strong, rounded posterior suggested a well-defined, somewhat eager anal aperture.</li>
            <li>The powerful curve of his backside drew my gaze to the tightly puckered, yet inviting, anal entrance.</li>
            <li>His shapely glutes framed a tantalizingly visible anus, a sight that certainly piqued my experienced curiosity.</li>
            <li>Observing his perfectly formed buttocks, I noted the small, yet remarkably distinct, anal opening.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of his posterior led to a surprisingly open and accessible looking anal region, a pleasing sight.</li>
            <li>His youthful backside, firm and enticing, revealed a compact but clearly defined anal structure.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, strong posterior made me appreciate the delicate, yet prominent, anal crevice.</li>
            <li>His ample buttocks, firm and inviting, framed an anal aperture that seemed to promise much.</li>
            <li>I couldn't help but linger on the view of his firm backside, especially the subtly presented, yet alluring, anus.</li>
            <li>His rear offered a pleasing form, directing my attention to the well-defined and intriguing anal area.</li>
            <li>The alluring curve of his glutes emphasized a small, but distinctly visible, anal opening.</li>
            <li>His fresh, firm posterior, combined with a surprisingly loose-looking anus, was an interesting contrast.</li>
            <li>I found myself observing the subtle expanse of his anal region, framed by delightfully soft, young buttocks.</li>
            <li>The sight of his pert backside and clearly delineated anus sparked a familiar, quiet appreciation within me.</li>
            <li>His smooth, youthful buttocks cradled an anus that appeared both tight and yet, intriguingly, well-defined.</li>
            <li>I noticed the pleasant roundness of his glutes, and the small, but noticeable, anal puckering.</li>
            <li>The enticing firmness of his rear contrasted nicely with the visible, yet modest, anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His posterior, still supple with youth, displayed an anal opening that seemed subtly receptive.</li>
            <li>A charmingly rounded backside, leading to an anal structure that, though small, held my gaze.</li>
            <li>I indulged in a moment of quiet observation of his inviting buttocks and their central, intriguing feature.</li>
            <li>His masculine rear, full and appealing, highlighted a visible, yet discreet, anal opening.</li>
            <li>The delightful shape of his glutes made the otherwise small anal aperture remarkably noticeable.</li>
            <li>His youthful posterior, firm and enticing, presented an anus that was clearly formed and inviting.</li>
            <li>I appreciated the gentle curve of his lower back blending into his buttocks, revealing a well-defined anal area.</li>
            <li>The fullness of his young backside, coupled with a visibly formed anus, was quite a sight.</li>
            <li>His bare posterior was a vision of youthful curves, with a delicate yet distinct anal opening.</li>
            <li>I quietly admired his backside; the soft contours of his buttocks led to an intriguingly visible anus.</li>
            <li>His firm, young glutes subtly revealed an anal aperture that, though compact, was clearly defined and alluring.</li>
            <li>The sight of his fresh backside, with its intriguing anal details, evoked a certain… appreciation in my seasoned mind.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His buttocks seemed shapely, though the anal opening itself was rather ordinary, as expected.</li>
            <li>One observed his posterior, noting the common, rounded form of his glutes and the normal visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The man's backside appeared standard, with a buttock shape and anal presentation within typical parameters.</li>
            <li>His rear offered a familiar sight: average gluteal development and an anal aperture of typical size and prominence.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was unremarkable, revealing an anal area that presented as quite typical.</li>
            <li>She saw the man's exposed backside; the buttocks were of a common masculine form, and the anus was visible.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare rear was conventional, with unexceptional curves and a plainly visible anal structure.</li>
            <li>His glutes seemed adequately rounded, and his anal opening was visible but held no particular distinction.</li>
            <li>The man’s buttock shape was not unusual, leading to a visible yet ordinary anal crevice.</li>
            <li>One observed his posterior: a standard masculine form, with a normal-sized and visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>His backside offered a straightforward view, with proportionate buttocks and an anal area that seemed entirely usual.</li>
            <li>The man's exposed rear, while masculine, exhibited an anus of quite common visibility and dimension.</li>
            <li>She noted the simple curves of his glutes, revealing an anal aperture that was visible but not pronounced.</li>
            <li>The man's posterior was of a regular build, displaying a common shape and a typically visible anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were fairly rounded, with the anal region appearing as a standard, discernible feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of his backside revealed a posterior of average masculine development, including a visibly normal anus.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite conventional, presenting a normally shaped butt and a visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>She cast a glance at the man's posterior, noting the familiar curves and a standard anal presentation.</li>
            <li>The backside in question had the usual contours, displaying a typically sized and visible anal feature.</li>
            <li>His glutes offered no surprises, framing an anal opening that was present and observable, but not exceptional.</li>
            <li>One noted his posterior was modestly formed, with an anus that appeared neither hidden nor unusually exposed.</li>
            <li>The man's bare rear was quite common, showing a buttock shape and anal visibility that was expected.</li>
            <li>She observed the normal development of his glutes, leading to an anal aperture of regular and discernible form.</li>
            <li>The sight of his backside was rather unremarkable, displaying an anal area that appeared entirely typical.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of a common roundness, with the anal opening appearing as a normal, visible detail.</li>
            <li>One looked upon his posterior, noting the familiar contours of his glutes and the straightforward appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>The man's rear was of an ordinary build, with an anal structure that was visible and entirely conventional.</li>
            <li>She merely registered the sight of his bare backside, including the typically formed buttocks and visible anus.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally typical, presenting an anal opening that was clearly present but unexceptional.</li>
            <li>The man's backside exhibited common features: standard gluteal form and a normally visible anal region.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His solid buttocks provided a clear view of his distinct anal opening, a rather common sight among men.</li>
            <li>He observed his posterior, noting the strong curve of his glutes and the noticeable, standard anal area.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare backside revealed a well-formed butt, with a visible anus that seemed ordinary.</li>
            <li>His shapely buttocks framed an anal aperture of moderate size, subtly hinting at shared masculine anatomy.</li>
            <li>He took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was typical, and the anal region seemed quite familiar.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not particularly striking, displayed a sturdy butt and a visible, normal anal opening.</li>
            <li>He noticed his ample, yet common, buttocks, and the clear, unsurprising visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite regular, highlighting an anal region of typical appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of a common masculine shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined but typical anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was unremarkable, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small.</li>
            <li>He simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, unexceptional anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered a straightforward view; the buttock structure was average, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite standard, with an anal area that garnered little specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, normal-sized anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior, while masculine, exhibited a very common set of proportions, including a regularly sized anus.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed typical curves and a clearly present, standard anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, though not particularly pronounced.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was conventional, with the anal opening apparent without being overly emphasized.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was largely unmemorable, displaying an ordinary form and typical anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed him from behind; his buttocks were of average fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite average, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was common, ending in a well-defined, standard anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the unexceptional, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and typically masculine, showcasing an anal area that was neither striking nor concealed.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet unremarkable, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather ordinary, presenting an anus of standard visibility and form.</li>
            <li>He cast a perfunctory glance, noting the usual shape of his backside and the average appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar masculine shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced.</li>
            <li>He surveyed his posterior, taking in the predictable contours of his glutes and the standard view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His well-defined buttocks provided an unobstructed view of his intriguing anal opening, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>He observed his posterior, noting the form of his glutes and the clear presentation of his anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare backside revealed a distinct form, with a visible, often fascinating, anal structure.</li>
            <li>His buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible.</li>
            <li>He took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>He noticed his ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was noteworthy, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>He simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed him from behind; his buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of his backside and the intriguing appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>He surveyed his posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of his glutes and the subtly alluring view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His well-defined buttocks provided an unobstructed view of his intriguing anal opening, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>She observed his posterior, noting the form of his glutes and the clear presentation of his anal region.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare backside revealed a distinct form, with a visible, often fascinating, anal structure.</li>
            <li>His buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible.</li>
            <li>She took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening.</li>
            <li>She noticed his ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>She calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was noteworthy, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>She simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>She observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>She noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>She observed him from behind; his buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>She merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>She registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>She cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of his backside and the intriguing appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>She surveyed his posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of his glutes and the subtly alluring view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His prominent buttocks, coupled with his visible anus, certainly caught his attention, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>The clear presentation of his posterior, highlighting his distinct anal opening, was quite noticeable to him.</li>
            <li>He observed his bare backside, noting the form of his glutes and the evident display of his anal region.</li>
            <li>His buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which he found interesting.</li>
            <li>He took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight he valued.</li>
            <li>He noticed his ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>He calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was noteworthy, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>He simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>He observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>He noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>He observed him from behind; his buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>He merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>He registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>He cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of his backside and the intriguing appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>He surveyed his posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of his glutes and the subtly alluring view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His prominent buttocks, coupled with his visible anus, certainly caught her attention, stirring a quiet interest.</li>
            <li>The clear presentation of his posterior, highlighting his distinct anal opening, was quite noticeable to her.</li>
            <li>She observed his bare backside, noting the form of his glutes and the evident display of his anal region.</li>
            <li>His buttock shape was quite prominent, leading to an anal aperture of notable size and highly visible, which she found interesting.</li>
            <li>She took in his posterior view; the gluteal development was interesting, and the anal area seemed quite openly presented.</li>
            <li>His exposed rear, while not overtly striking, displayed a well-formed butt and a distinctly visible anal opening, a sight she valued.</li>
            <li>She noticed his ample, often captivating, buttocks, and the clear, intentional visibility of his anus.</li>
            <li>The contour of his posterior was quite appealing, highlighting an anal region of intriguing and openly displayed appearance.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were of an interesting shape, revealing a rather open and observable anal orifice for all to see.</li>
            <li>She calmly registered the sight of his backside, including the well-defined and intriguing anal features.</li>
            <li>His overall posterior form was noteworthy, and his anal opening appeared neither unusually large nor small, but quite invitingly presented.</li>
            <li>She simply observed his rear, noting the proportionate glutes and the visible, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>His backside offered an attractive view; the buttock structure was pleasing, and the anus was plainly visible.</li>
            <li>The general presentation of his posterior was quite captivating, with an anal area that garnered specific attention.</li>
            <li>She observed his buttocks, which were rounded and firm, with a moderately visible, inviting anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior exhibited a pleasing set of proportions, including a regularly sized, yet engaging, anal opening.</li>
            <li>A brief glance at his rear revealed pleasing curves and a clearly present, noteworthy anal configuration.</li>
            <li>She noted his glutes were well-formed, and the anal region was distinctly visible, drawing an appreciative glance.</li>
            <li>His buttock silhouette was appealing, with the anal opening apparent and subtly emphasized, a true sight.</li>
            <li>The sight of his bare posterior was rather memorable, displaying an appealing form and intriguing anal contours.</li>
            <li>She observed him from behind; his buttocks were of appealing fullness, and the anal region was clearly discernible.</li>
            <li>His figure from the rear was quite attractive, providing a clear view of a normal-sized and visible anus.</li>
            <li>The curve of his lower back and glutes was pleasing, ending in a well-defined, subtly alluring anal aperture.</li>
            <li>She merely acknowledged his exposed buttocks and the appealing, visible appearance of his anal opening.</li>
            <li>His posterior was structurally sound and attractively formed, showcasing an anal area that was subtly intriguing.</li>
            <li>She registered the presence of his buttocks and the visible, yet appealing, opening.</li>
            <li>The view of his bare posterior was rather captivating, presenting an anus of standard visibility and an appealing form.</li>
            <li>She cast a quiet glance, noting the pleasing shape of his backside and the intriguing appearance of his anus.</li>
            <li>His buttocks were a familiar shape, accompanying an anal region that was neither hidden nor overly pronounced, but appealing.</li>
            <li>She surveyed his posterior, taking in the pleasing contours of his glutes and the subtly alluring view of his anus.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic buttocks held an unsettling appeal, framing an anal opening that seemed both unnatural and strangely compelling.</li>
            <li>The unusual contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, hinting at otherworldly origins, made {PAWN_possessive} anus a focal point of curiosity.</li>
            <li>A chilling artistry was present in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to an anal aperture of curious, almost eldritch, design.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was unsettlingly captivating, with an anal structure that defied conventional understanding.</li>
            <li>The observer noted the stark, angular lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic rear, and the eerily perfect visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>An anatomical anomaly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior featured an anus that was both strangely formed and overtly present.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, alien and sharp, drew attention to an anal opening of peculiar and unsettling design.</li>
            <li>One observed the otherworldly curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to a dark, almost abyssal, anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon-touched rear presented an anus that was unsettlingly symmetrical and unnervingly exposed.</li>
            <li>The posterior seemed to twist unnaturally, forming a buttock shape that emphasized a bizarrely configured anal opening.</li>
            <li>An eerie perfection defined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic backside, with an anal area that seemed too precise, too alien.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior revealed a form both grotesque and fascinating, centered on an unusual anus.</li>
            <li>The curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were sharp, almost predatory, leading to an anal aperture of unsettling allure.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but gaze at the unnatural structure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, framed by a buttock of uncanny design.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior presented a stark, almost skeletal form, highlighting an anal opening of disturbing prominence.</li>
            <li>The flesh seemed to contort into a buttock that accentuated an anal area of otherworldly, unsettling visibility.</li>
            <li>There was an uncanny symmetry to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, drawing the eye to an anal region that felt ancient and wrong.</li>
            <li>The very lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior spoke of infernal crafting, with an anus that was unsettlingly stark.</li>
            <li>One observed the unusual, almost sculptural, form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, emphasizing a bizarrely visible anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was a strange blend of horror and beauty, with an anal opening that felt like a void.</li>
            <li>The demonic influence was clear in the sharp angles of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, leading to a starkly apparent anus.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks framed an anal opening that was deeply recessed, yet terrifyingly visible.</li>
            <li>The anatomy seemed to shift and writhe, forming a buttock that highlighted a uniquely disturbing anal structure.</li>
            <li>One's gaze lingered on the impossible curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, and the almost unholy perfection of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The posterior was a chilling tableau, with an anus that was simultaneously prominent and profoundly alien.</li>
            <li>The unnatural firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was apparent, emphasizing an anal opening of peculiar, demonic design.</li>
            <li>An unsettling fascination drew one's eye to the strange, segmented nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>The glutes themselves seemed to defy logic, twisting to reveal an anus that was both exposed and profoundly disturbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside held an ominous presence, with an anal structure that spoke of forbidden geometries.</li>
            <li>The dark, almost shadowed appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was framed by buttocks that seemed to consume light.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks shimmered with an unusual, fluid quality, framing an anal opening that seemed to constantly reshape itself.</li>
            <li>The gelatinous form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior rippled subtly, drawing attention to a remarkably pliant and often indistinct anal region.</li>
            <li>A curious translucence characterized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to an anal aperture of amorphous, yet visible, design.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was unsettlingly soft, with an anal structure that seemed to flow and shift, making it hard to discern.</li>
            <li>The observer noted the slick, almost formless contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime rear, and the eerily adaptable visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>An anatomical oddity, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior featured an anus that was both strangely fluid and overtly present, yet ever-changing.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, viscous and yielding, drew attention to an anal opening of peculiar and fascinating liquidity.</li>
            <li>One observed the shimmering, almost dissolving curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to a glistening, somewhat formless, anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime-touched rear presented an anus that was unsettlingly organic and unnervingly exposed, a liquid aperture.</li>
            <li>The posterior seemed to undulate, forming a buttock shape that emphasized a bizarrely configured anal opening, seemingly without a fixed form.</li>
            <li>An eerie fluidity defined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime backside, with an anal area that seemed too soft, too malleable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior revealed a form both fascinating and unsettling, centered on a uniquely pliant anus.</li>
            <li>The curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were soft, almost non-existent, leading to an anal aperture of unsettling, fluid allure.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but gaze at the unnatural structure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, framed by a buttock of uncanny, flowing design.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slimy posterior presented a stark, almost featureless form, highlighting an anal opening of disturbing prominence.</li>
            <li>The flesh seemed to contort into a buttock that accentuated an anal area of otherworldly, unsettling visibility, constantly shifting.</li>
            <li>There was an uncanny smoothness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, drawing the eye to an anal region that felt ancient and wrong.</li>
            <li>The very lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior spoke of fluid crafting, with an anus that was unsettlingly stark in its pliancy.</li>
            <li>One observed the unusual, almost amorphous, form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, emphasizing a bizarrely visible anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was a strange blend of attraction and revulsion, with an anal opening that felt like liquid void.</li>
            <li>The slime influence was clear in the soft, flowing lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, leading to a starkly apparent, yet fluid, anus.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks framed an anal opening that was deeply recessed, yet terrifyingly visible and formless.</li>
            <li>The anatomy seemed to shift and writhe, forming a buttock that highlighted a uniquely disturbing, ever-changing anal structure.</li>
            <li>One's gaze lingered on the impossible softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, and the almost unholy pliancy of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The posterior was a chilling tableau, with an anus that was simultaneously prominent and profoundly alien in its fluidity.</li>
            <li>The unnatural firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was apparent, emphasizing an anal opening of peculiar, gelatinous design.</li>
            <li>An unsettling fascination drew one's eye to the strange, segmented nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>The glutes themselves seemed to defy logic, twisting to reveal an anus that was both exposed and profoundly disturbing in its formlessness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside held an ominous presence, with an anal structure that spoke of forbidden anatomies.</li>
            <li>The dark, almost shadowed appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was framed by buttocks that seemed to absorb light, a strange liquid void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Neutral_Abyssal_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Abyssal Anus (Neutral) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid buttocks featured a chitinous sheen, framing an anal opening of curiously segmented design.</li>
            <li>The exoskeleton of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior had sharp, alien angles, drawing attention to a remarkably complex and unusual anal region.</li>
            <li>A disturbing symmetry characterized {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to an anal aperture with an intricate, almost crystalline, structure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside was unsettlingly rigid, with an anal structure that seemed to click and whir with internal mechanisms.</li>
            <li>The observer noted the hard, segmented contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect rear, and the eerily mechanical visibility of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>An anatomical puzzle, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior featured an anus that was both strangely multi-faceted and overtly present, with a strange beauty.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, plated and unyielding, drew attention to an anal opening of peculiar and fascinating complexity.</li>
            <li>One observed the alien, articulated curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, leading to a dark, almost multi-jointed, anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect-touched rear presented an anus that was unsettlingly symmetrical and unnervingly exposed, with fine chitinous rings.</li>
            <li>The posterior seemed to be comprised of several hard plates, forming a buttock shape that emphasized a bizarrely configured anal opening.</li>
            <li>An eerie precision defined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect backside, with an anal area that seemed too perfect, too alien in its construction.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bare posterior revealed a form both grotesque and fascinating, centered on an unusual, chitinous anus.</li>
            <li>The curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes were sharp, almost blade-like, leading to an anal aperture of unsettling allure.</li>
            <li>One couldn't help but gaze at the unnatural structure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus, framed by a buttock of uncanny, segmented design.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior presented a stark, almost crystalline form, highlighting an anal opening of disturbing prominence.</li>
            <li>The body seemed to be constructed of interlocking plates that accentuated an anal area of otherworldly, unsettling visibility.</li>
            <li>There was an uncanny intricacy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, drawing the eye to an anal region that felt ancient and alien.</li>
            <li>The very lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior spoke of biological engineering, with an anus that was unsettlingly stark in its design.</li>
            <li>One observed the unusual, almost sculptural, form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks, emphasizing a bizarrely visible anal orifice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear was a strange blend of horror and beauty, with an anal opening that felt like a biological mechanism.</li>
            <li>The insect influence was clear in the sharp angles of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, leading to a starkly apparent, yet complex, anus.</li>
            <li>A truly unsettling form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks framed an anal opening that was deeply recessed, yet terrifyingly visible and multi-jointed.</li>
            <li>The anatomy seemed to shift and writhe, forming a buttock that highlighted a uniquely disturbing, segmented anal structure.</li>
            <li>One's gaze lingered on the impossible hardness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glutes, and the almost unholy perfection of {PAWN_possessive} anus.</li>
            <li>The posterior was a chilling tableau, with an anus that was simultaneously prominent and profoundly alien in its construction.</li>
            <li>The unnatural rigidity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} buttocks was apparent, emphasizing an anal opening of peculiar, insectoid design.</li>
            <li>An unsettling fascination drew one's eye to the strange, articulated nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anal region.</li>
            <li>The glutes themselves seemed to defy logic, twisting to reveal an anus that was both exposed and profoundly disturbing in its form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} backside held an ominous presence, with an anal structure that spoke of forbidden insectoid anatomies.</li>
            <li>The dark, almost shadowed appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} anus was framed by buttocks that seemed to absorb light, a strange mechanical void.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>