<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>Stunned seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, I must tease them.</li>
            <li>Can't stop gazing on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, love them bouncing.</li>
			<li>If I see one more time {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, I will go to heaven.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were voluptuous and full, a sight that made me feel weak at the knees.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were round and supple, with a weight and heft that I found incredibly appealing.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were like a feast for the eyes, {PAWN_possessive} size and curves leaving me in awe.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were generously proportioned, with a size that was impressive and captivating.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were large and luxurious, with a shape that was both feminine and alluring.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were full and fabulous, overflowing with a sensual charm.</li>
			<li>I was captivated by a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were luxuriously endowed, {PAWN_possessive} generous size and inviting shape a sensory experience unlike any other.</li>
			<li>I tenderly examined a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, {PAWN_possessive} sumptuous curves and opulent texture a true delight.</li>
			<li>I was awestruck by a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were truly majestic, {PAWN_possessive} impressive size and regal shape a wonder to behold.</li>
			<li>I reveled in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample, firm breasts, {PAWN_possessive} alluring shape a breathtaking view that inspired awe and longing.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous, voluptuous breasts were an awe-inspiring appearance, {PAWN_possessive} splendid form a genuine appreciation of beauty and sensuality.</li>
			<li>A lingering glance fell upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} curvaceous, well-endowed breasts, {PAWN_possessive} grandeur a true marvel, igniting an insatiable curiosity.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts were voluminous and full, with delicate, hardened nipples and swirling, rosy-hued areolas.</li>
			<li>The captivating allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was undeniable, with soft, pale nipples and darker, more pronounced areolas that seemed to beckon me closer.</li>
			<li>The sensuality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was palpable, with plump, inviting nipples and swirling, raspberry-colored areolas that seemed to hypnotize me.</li>
			<li>The firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was evident, with enticing, rosy-tipped nipples and subtle, captivating areolas that seemed to call out to me.</li>
			<li>As I admired {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, I noticed that {PAWN_possessive} large breasts featured plump, mesmerizing nipples and gently curving areolas, adorned with delicate, intricate patterns.</li>
			<li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was awe-inspiring, with soft, smooth skin and small, perky nipples that seemed to sing a siren's song.</li>
			<li>The allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was irresistible, with full, plump nipples and intricate, dark areolas that seemed to dance and sway with each breath.</li>
			<li>The symmetry of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts was captivating, with dusky-pink nipples and swirling, rosy-tinted areolas that seemed to reach out and touch me.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly sculpted.</li>
            <li>The weight and swing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are utterly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>I can't help but be drawn to the deep cleavage created by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are a testament to generous proportions, a breathtaking view.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill out {PAWN_possessive} chest is simply stunning.</li>
            <li>Such a full, abundant bust {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses, it's truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>The softness and curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are undeniably appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a glorious roundness, a classic, alluring form.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts jiggle with every slight movement is captivating.</li>
            <li>I find the prominent, well-defined shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts incredibly attractive.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are strikingly voluminous, moving with a captivating bounce that hints at their softness. The nipples are perfectly defined, inviting attention. Truly a magnificent sight!</li>
            <li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts exhibit a pleasing fullness and natural sway. Their well-formed areolas frame sensitive-looking nipples.</li>
            <li>The generous curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are impressive, showcasing a wonderful roundness. Their prominent nipples and dark areolas add to their captivating allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, undeniably large, have a comforting weight and a gentle, natural movement. The visible nipples are perfectly centered.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, the sheer volume of her breasts immediately catches the eye. They possess an alluring firmness, yet yield softly to motion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive bust seems to defy gravity with its voluptuous form and gentle sway. The prominent nipples invite a lingering gaze.</li>
            <li>The fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is captivating, their supple form perfectly complementing {PAWN_possessive} figure. The areolas are well-defined, with enticing nipples.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully large and full, with a delightful natural bounce. Their prominent, inviting nipples beckon.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest boasts a pair of beautifully substantial breasts that move with an appealing fluidity, showcasing enticingly firm nipples.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is breathtaking; they possess a comforting weight and a graceful, natural sway. Their perfectly formed areolas stand out.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts have a delightful, soft jiggle with every step, the generous curve of her cleavage hinting at their ample size.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is truly impressive, each breast full and shapely, with a gentle undulation that catches the light beautifully.</li>
            <li>The substantial weight and luxurious form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite captivating, their tips prominent and inviting.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent breasts, full and beautifully proportioned to {PAWN_possessive} frame. The nipples are well-defined, hinting at sensitivity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest is a truly delightful sight, the breasts heavy and soft, moving with a sensual rhythm.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is remarkable, presenting a harmonious silhouette and drawing the eye to their perfect shape.</li>
            <li>A truly stunning pair, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts command attention with their graceful bounce and appealing fullness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts cascade delightfully, their soft curves accentuated by the gentle movement of {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>The luxurious size and delightful firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are enchanting, with invitingly raised nipples.</li>
            <li>What a magnificent bust! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are impressively large, yet perfectly poised, with alluringly defined areolas.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are remarkably well-formed, their considerable size balanced by a natural, supple feel. The nipples are beautifully pronounced.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full breasts is quite arresting; they possess a wonderful volume and a captivating, soft sway.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts rest elegantly, their substantial form hinting at a comforting softness, with perfectly formed, inviting nipples.</li>
            <li>The gentle swing and ample shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly pleasing to behold, their well-defined contours adding to their appeal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts are a joy to witness, their voluptuousness matched by a subtle, alluring jiggle.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and prominent, tempting nipples.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are striking, with breasts that appear supple and full, moving fluidly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by the delicate contours of the areolas.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and enticingly firm tips.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, their pronounced nipples adding to their charm.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	

</Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, a splendid figure {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses, a timeless beauty in {PAWN_possessive} large bosom.</li>
            <li>Reminds me of the golden age, those generous curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>Such a full and ample chest, truly a captivating sight on a young woman.</li>
            <li>The youthful firmness combined with such size is a rare and pleasing combination.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts carry a certain elegance, a classic beauty rarely seen these days.</li>
            <li>A magnificent pair, truly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are quite striking.</li>
            <li>The natural grace in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} silhouette is enhanced by {PAWN_possessive} prominent chest.</li>
            <li>One can appreciate the robust form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, a lovely sight indeed.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm in how {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts present themselves, quite delightful.</li>
            <li>A mature appreciation for such well-proportioned features as {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>Those are truly impressive, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts command attention with their sheer volume.</li>
            <li>It's refreshing to see such abundant curves, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite a spectacle.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts sit, so full and poised, is rather grand.</li>
            <li>A vision of classic femininity, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is quite admirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a certain gravitas, a rich and inviting form.</li>
            <li>The natural weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts gives them a beautiful, swaying motion.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent mounds, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a testament to nature's generosity.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the rounded contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, quite pleasing to the eye.</li>
            <li>There's a captivating allure in the fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>One cannot help but admire the pronounced swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>The very picture of a bountiful figure, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly remarkable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a majestic presence, a visual delight.</li>
            <li>A truly voluptuous display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite impressive.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are suspended, so naturally full, is captivating.</li>
            <li>A fine example of generous endowments, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite comely.</li>
            <li>The firm yet yielding form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is rather compelling.</li>
            <li>I find the sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts quite striking.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly a testament to nature's artistry.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill the space is quite alluring.</li>
            <li>A most aesthetically pleasing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are indeed.</li>
			<li>Ah, such a fine display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts possess a charming fullness, moving with a gentle sway that speaks of youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom has a delightful roundness, their generous curves complementing {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. A truly pleasant sight.</li>
            <li>The noticeable volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite striking; they carry themselves with a natural, inviting weight and soft bounce.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are full and wonderfully shaped, a testament to youthful allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive chest immediately caught my eye. Those breasts possess a lovely, mature curve and seem remarkably supple.</li>
            <li>Those generous curves on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite a sight. They have a graceful sway, full and invitingly rounded.</li>
            <li>The fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is simply charming. They appear soft and well-proportioned, a delightful aspect of {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>What a splendid pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts exhibit a natural bounce, suggesting youthful vitality and softness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are quite fetching, with a lovely contour and a reassuringly soft appearance. A classic beauty.</li>
            <li>A fine, substantial pair of breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom boasts a pleasing fullness and a gentle, natural presentation.</li>
            <li>Such impressive volume. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a captivating shape, gracefully moving with a soft, inviting jiggle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full and shapely breasts are a sight to behold, resting beautifully on {PAWN_possessive} chest, a picture of natural grace.</li>
            <li>The luxurious fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly admirable, a testament to healthy youth and vibrant form.</li>
            <li>A truly appealing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are well-rounded and firm, yet with a charming softness that invites admiration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest showcases breasts that are delightfully plump, their weight and movement entirely captivating.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts creates a lovely silhouette, a full and inviting presence that is quite striking.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts move with a fluid grace, their substantial form exceptionally appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft curves and natural sway making them truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting appearance.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural movement.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting appearance.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing presentation.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, a true vision of natural beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts stir something deep within me, a primal urge.</li>
            <li>To witness such expansive curves... it makes my old blood quicken.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts sway, I feel a familiar throb below.</li>
            <li>Magnificent. Truly magnificent. {PAWN_possessive} bosom is a sight for sore eyes, and other parts.</li>
            <li>A glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts and I'm reminded of my youth, and what I long for.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant chest is enough to make an old man feel young again, if only for a moment.</li>
            <li>Those generous mounds are an intoxicating sight, making me ache with desire.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is a powerful stimulant, arousing my senses.</li>
            <li>I find myself fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, heavy breasts, my body responding to their undeniable presence.</li>
            <li>Such an ample display, it makes me recall past pleasures and crave new ones.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples and ample areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so inviting, they make me feel rather excited.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts seem to call to me, making my loins stir with a forgotten vigor.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the full, yielding form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, and my thoughts turn impure.</li>
            <li>The weight and gravity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom are captivating, stirring a longing I thought long buried.</li>
            <li>A truly luscious vision, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts ignite a deep, carnal hunger.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts press against the air... it fills me with an intense, burning desire.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, it makes me feel quite aroused.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous chest makes my old cock twitch with anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are a masterpiece of nature, and my body reacts accordingly.</li>
            <li>I feel a powerful pull towards {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, a longing to possess such beauty.</li>
            <li>Such a captivating display of anatomical splendor, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts make me hard.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are shaped, so full and inviting, is truly arousing.</li>
            <li>My mind is consumed by the image of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, and my erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>I can only stare, transfixed by the sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, my pulse quickening.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a powerful aphrodisiac, igniting a fire within me.</li>
            <li>I feel a deep, visceral response to the generous curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful temptation, making my blood run hot.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating view, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts fill me with intense craving.</li>
            <li>My senses are overwhelmed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, and my body responds with an immediate surge of lust.</li>
            <li>I can feel my own cock hardening just by looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts.</li>
			<li>What a sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, swinging breasts are simply enthralling. My loins stir, recalling younger days. Such magnificent, full forms!</li>
            <li>Ah, the magnificent sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, bouncing breasts! A true delight for the eyes, they stir a youthful yearning deep within me.</li>
            <li>Such luscious, ample breasts! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is a captivating landscape of generous curves, hinting at untold pleasures. A definite arousal.</li>
            <li>Her substantial breasts, so round and tempting, swayed hypnotically. A sudden warmth spreads through me, an undeniable, primal appreciation.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightful, large breasts, I feel a familiar, stirring warmth. Their inviting bounce promises pure ecstasy.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating view. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle causing a pleasant throb below.</li>
            <li>The captivating volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is absolutely enthralling; they swing with a seductive rhythm. My old heart races.</li>
            <li>Those wonderfully large breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a truly arousing spectacle. My senses tingle with appreciation for their lush fullness.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent, ample breasts! They sway with a tantalizing allure, awakening a powerful, undeniable desire within my aging frame.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts are simply mesmerizing, their movements evoking a deep, primal stir that is impossible to ignore.</li>
            <li>The delicious sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous breasts is a captivating display. My old blood quickens with a powerful, undeniable longing.</li>
            <li>Her ample bosom, so wonderfully plump and inviting, commands my gaze. A deep, familiar ache echoes through my core, a true pleasure.</li>
            <li>Such a splendid, full chest! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a vision of soft, yielding temptation. My body responds with an immediate, pleasant tension.</li>
            <li>Those large, perfectly rounded breasts are an irresistible sight. A potent surge of warmth courses through me, a testament to their captivating beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts, undeniably substantial, move with an intoxicating grace. My mind fills with passionate thoughts.</li>
            <li>The sheer voluptuousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly breathtaking. They invite a deep, appreciative gaze, and ignite an inner fire.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous breasts possess a delightful weight and a captivating, sensual motion. My heart pounds.</li>
            <li>Her splendid, full breasts are a remarkable spectacle. The subtle quiver of their flesh stirs a familiar, undeniable urge within my very being.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant bosom is utterly mesmerizing, its soft, inviting curves promising untold delights. A profound, pleasant ache resonates within me.</li>
            <li>What a magnificent, ample pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a testament to exquisite form, provoking a powerful, undeniable response.</li>
            <li>The captivating vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts stirs a deep, passionate longing. Their every movement is a seductive dance.</li>
            <li>Such a delectable sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full breasts sway with an intoxicating allure, evoking a primal, insistent hunger.</li>
            <li>Her substantial breasts, so perfectly round and tempting, incite an overwhelming, familiar heat within me. My gaze is fixed.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent, ample breasts, a surge of raw, unbridled desire courses through my veins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom is a truly arousing masterpiece, its every curve and jiggle provoking a profound, sensual reaction.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume and captivating movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are intensely stimulating. My body responds instinctively, irresistibly drawn.</li>
            <li>A truly powerful sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts pulsate with life, stirring an almost forgotten, potent yearning within my core.</li>
            <li>Her lush, ample breasts are a vision of pure temptation, their soft, yielding curves hinting at exquisite pleasure. My senses are inflamed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts are utterly captivating, their natural bounce sparking a familiar, potent desire.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive breasts are a source of profound, unshakeable arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite bountiful for {PAWN_possessive} age, a testament to good genes.</li>
            <li>Such a full bosom, it reminds me of my younger days.</li>
            <li>A truly striking figure {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has, with those generously proportioned breasts.</li>
            <li>The firmness and size are quite impressive, a lovely sight on a young woman.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a wonderful roundness, very pleasing to the eye.</li>
            <li>It's good to see such natural abundance, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is truly something.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts sit, so perfectly shaped, is quite enviable.</li>
            <li>A beautiful, ample chest, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} carries it with such grace.</li>
            <li>Those full, youthful breasts are a delightful sight, healthy and vibrant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a lovely, classic form, quite appealing.</li>
            <li>Such well-developed breasts on a young female, quite a sight to behold.</li>
            <li>The weight and presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are undeniable, a true asset.</li>
            <li>I admire the natural, unadorned beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is truly magnificent, a sign of vitality and health.</li>
            <li>The full, rounded shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite charming.</li>
            <li>A lovely example of natural feminine curves, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite fetching.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill out {PAWN_possessive} frame is quite harmonious.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts possess an inherent beauty, simple and profound.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle strength in the generous form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>One can appreciate the natural bounty evident in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>Such a full and proud set of breasts, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} looks splendid.</li>
            <li>The robust and healthy appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite reassuring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a delightful softness, yet with a noticeable firmness.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely bosom, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} is fortunate to possess such fullness.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts curve and swell is very appealing.</li>
            <li>I find the natural contour and size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts quite elegant.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a fine example of feminine allure, gracefully presented.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking.</li>
            <li>A wonderful, substantial pair of breasts, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} carries them well.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a source of natural beauty and appeal.</li>
			<li>My, those are truly ample breasts! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} figure is beautifully complemented by their generous, youthful fullness and gentle sway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} boasts a rather splendid bosom, full and round, with a charming natural lift. A beautiful sight, indeed.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent breasts! They have a lovely, soft appearance and move with a delightful natural bounce. Quite well-formed for {PAWN_possessive} age.</li>
            <li>The generous volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite striking; they carry themselves with a confident and pleasing weight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, I notice how beautifully full and shapely her breasts are. A testament to youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>Those splendid, large breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite striking. They have a graceful curve and appear wonderfully soft and supple.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite voluminous, yet they retain a charming firmness and a lovely, natural presentation. Very impressive.</li>
            <li>What a wonderful pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts exhibit a delightful fullness and a comforting, soft appearance. Truly well-proportioned.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are quite fetching, with a lovely contour and a reassuringly soft feel. A truly classic feminine form.</li>
            <li>A truly substantial pair of breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom boasts a pleasing fullness and a gentle, natural presentation.</li>
            <li>Such impressive volume. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a captivating shape, gracefully moving with a soft, inviting jiggle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full and shapely breasts are a sight to behold, resting beautifully on {PAWN_possessive} chest, a picture of natural grace.</li>
            <li>The luxurious fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly admirable, a testament to healthy youth and vibrant form.</li>
            <li>A truly appealing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are well-rounded and firm, yet with a charming softness that invites admiration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest showcases breasts that are delightfully plump, their weight and movement entirely captivating.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts creates a lovely silhouette, a full and inviting presence that is quite striking.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts move with a fluid grace, their substantial form exceptionally appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft curves and natural sway making them truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting appearance.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural movement.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting appearance.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing presentation.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, a true vision of natural beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Female voyer observes young female with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, can include own breasts mention or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts... they truly fill one with a sense of delicious longing. Mine used to be like that.</li>
            <li>Oh, to feel the weight of such ample mounds again! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is exquisite.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous chest makes my own body tingle with a familiar heat.</li>
            <li>Those plump, young breasts are a glorious sight, stirring desires I thought were dormant.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly transfixed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, yielding breasts, almost imagining them in my hands.</li>
            <li>Such voluptuousness! It makes my own core clench with a pleasant ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are magnificent, making me remember youthful passions and the warmth of a lover's touch.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts hang, so full and ripe, sends shivers down my spine.</li>
            <li>My eyes are glued to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, feeling a deep, almost instinctual urge to explore.</li>
            <li>A truly sensual spectacle, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts awaken old hungers within me.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite alluring, making me imagine how they'd feel on my lips.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the youth and vitality from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>The beautiful, expansive curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are drawing me in, making me feel quite wanton.</li>
            <li>Such an inviting display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts make me miss the days when my own were so firm and full.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts brings back a flood of erotic memories, almost making my loins throb.</li>
            <li>I could gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts for hours, lost in their perfect form.</li>
            <li>They're simply divine. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have that lush, ripe quality that makes one yearn.</li>
            <li>The plumpness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples is quite enticing, sparking a very particular kind of interest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a vision of pure, unadulterated sensuality, making my core clench in response.</li>
            <li>The soft sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is utterly hypnotizing, and I feel a familiar wetness.</li>
            <li>Such a magnificent set of breasts, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fills me with a delightful sense of envy and desire.</li>
            <li>My old fingers itch to feel the smoothness and fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>Every curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts speaks of delicious pleasure, sending shivers through me.</li>
            <li>I'm captivated by the sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, a truly arousing sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are like a potent elixir, making me feel alive with longing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} plump, generous breasts makes my breath catch in my throat.</li>
            <li>Oh, to play with such perfect mounds! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply begging for attention.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts present themselves, so proudly, is intensely arousing.</li>
            <li>I feel a deep, almost painful ache of desire when I look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fantastic breasts.</li>
            <li>Those areolas, so dark and inviting, make {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts even more alluring.</li>
			<li>Oh, look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts! They sway so delightfully. Makes me recall my own younger, fuller days. Quite a stimulating sight.</li>
            <li>What luscious, full breasts {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possesses! Their movement is simply captivating, stirring a familiar warmth and appreciation within my own body.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, large breasts are a glorious sight! So soft and yielding, they remind me of the youthful bounty I once had.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is simply divine. Their natural jiggle is mesmerizing, and I feel a pleasant tingle.</li>
            <li>Such a splendid, full bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a vision of supple beauty, and I can almost feel the pleasing weight myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are truly captivating, swaying with an alluring grace. A delightful reminder of true feminine form.</li>
            <li>My, those are truly impressive! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts have such a lovely, soft bounce, evoking a certain warmth within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} beautiful, voluminous breasts is quite arousing, a glorious example of youthful abundance.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art. The way they move with {PAWN_possessive} body is simply captivating, filling me with admiration.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom is absolutely stunning. They possess a soft, yielding quality that is profoundly appealing to my senses.</li>
            <li>What a pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly formed, their graceful motion sparking a sympathetic flutter deep inside.</li>
            <li>The captivating volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly inspiring. They are a testament to exquisite feminine allure.</li>
            <li>Her prominent, full breasts are a glorious sight to behold. They possess a comforting weight and a seductive sway.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest is simply delightful, the soft, round curves of her breasts are endlessly fascinating.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent, large breasts! They move with a captivating rhythm, prompting a pleasant, familiar sensation in my own body.</li>
            <li>The glorious swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly a sight to behold. So full, so soft, so perfectly female.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts flow with a fluid grace, their substantial form incredibly appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft curves and natural sway making them truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting appearance.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural movement.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting appearance.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing presentation.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, a true vision of natural beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are huge and perfect. My cock is throbbing.</li>
            <li>Can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bouncing chest, it's driving me wild.</li>
            <li>Those large breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are making me hard just looking at them.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill out {PAWN_possessive} frame is absolutely insane. I'm mesmerized.</li>
            <li>I'm speechless looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom. What a sight!</li>
            <li>Such a full, ripe pair of breasts. They make me want to reach out and touch them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly round and firm, just begging to be played with.</li>
            <li>My mouth is watering looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples, peeking out from those massive breasts.</li>
            <li>I'm getting seriously turned on by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible chest.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts jiggle with every breath is so hot.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly a work of art, making my pants feel tighter.</li>
            <li>I'm throbbing just imagining those big breasts pressed against me.</li>
            <li>The sheer size and beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are making it hard to think straight.</li>
            <li>I bet {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts feel amazing in hand. I can only dream.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fantastic bosom, I feel myself getting bigger down there.</li>
            <li>Those large, heavy breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are making me feel incredibly excited.</li>
            <li>I'd love to bury my face in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cleavage. It looks so soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are absolutely stunning, making my dick stiffen instantly.</li>
            <li>The deep valley between {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is so inviting, I want to explore it.</li>
            <li>It's almost painful how good {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts look. My urges are overwhelming.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples are presented on those big breasts is driving me crazy.</li>
            <li>I can't help but stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest, my primal instincts kicking in.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are everything I could ever want in a woman. So full, so perfect.</li>
            <li>Just one look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts and I'm ready to explode.</li>
            <li>The roundness and fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are intoxicating, making me feel incredibly hot.</li>
            <li>I'm completely captivated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous chest, my body responding instinctively.</li>
            <li>Those areolas look so sensuous on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} big breasts, making me wonder about their taste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a dream come true, filling me with a powerful desire.</li>
            <li>My entire body is reacting to the incredible sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, prominent breasts.</li>
            <li>I'm literally breathless from the sheer beauty and size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
			<li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} huge breasts are incredible! They just bounce so perfectly, driving me wild. My blood is definitely pumping now.</li>
            <li>Wow, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has some amazing large breasts. The way they move is super hot, and my gaze is totally fixed.</li>
            <li>Her massive breasts are a sight to behold! So round, so full, and they jiggle with every step. My pulse quickens immediately.</li>
            <li>Just seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest makes my jaw drop. Those breasts are magnificent, I can barely look away.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly large and beautiful. Their sheer size and inviting curves are seriously turning me on.</li>
            <li>Those are some seriously spectacular breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is so full and soft, making my insides churn with desire.</li>
            <li>Her generous breasts are absolutely captivating. The way they hang and sway is pure seduction, making my pants feel tighter.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts are beyond words. Every glance at them sends a shiver down my spine, I feel a growing excitement.</li>
            <li>Those enormous breasts are a dream. They seem so soft, so yielding, and they make me want to reach out. My body is responding.</li>
            <li>What a pair of magnificent breasts! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has been blessed, and I'm certainly appreciating the view. My groin is aching.</li>
            <li>Her luscious, full breasts are truly mesmerizing, their gentle sway igniting a powerful, undeniable longing within me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} glorious, ample breasts makes my heart race and my body respond with eager anticipation.</li>
            <li>Those substantial breasts are absolutely stunning. They have a captivating fullness that draws my gaze and fuels my desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is a masterpiece. Her large breasts are so perfectly shaped, causing a noticeable reaction down below.</li>
            <li>A truly breathtaking view. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive breasts swing with such alluring grace, arousing my deepest instincts.</li>
            <li>Her bountiful breasts are an absolute vision, their soft curves and natural bounce making my mind race with provocative thoughts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom is incredibly appealing, its sheer volume and sensual movement are intensely stimulating.</li>
            <li>What an intoxicating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, prominent breasts are simply irresistible, stirring an intense, primal hunger within.</li>
            <li>Those full, round breasts are utterly mesmerizing, their every jiggle sending waves of electric desire through my entire being.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, ample breasts are a source of profound fascination, their seductive allure causing a delightful tension in my loins.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance and movement sparking a powerful, undeniable urge.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is truly spellbinding, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves are a true visual feast that excites me deeply.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking an intense physical response.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly enchanted and desiring.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful attraction.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I find myself utterly fixated on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, a truly captivating sight.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume and natural sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are incredibly appealing to my eyes.</li>
            <li>Every curve and undulation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a visual feast.</li>
            <li>I can't tear my gaze away from the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill out {PAWN_possessive} upper body is simply magnificent.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle, almost hypnotic movement to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts as {PAWN_pronoun} moves.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly engrossed in observing the contours and form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent chest.</li>
            <li>The natural fall and weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a fascination to behold.</li>
            <li>I find the fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts incredibly alluring to watch.</li>
            <li>Just the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom fills me with a sense of pure aesthetic appreciation.</li>
            <li>The way the light plays on the rounded surfaces of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is exquisite.</li>
            <li>My eyes trace every delightful curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, voluminous chest.</li>
            <li>It's a privilege to witness such natural, uninhibited beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples and areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite captivating to my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I delight in observing the slight jiggle and bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>The overall shape and presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are truly a sight to behold.</li>
            <li>I could watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts all day, admiring their generous and inviting form.</li>
            <li>There's an undeniable allure in the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts assert their presence.</li>
            <li>My gaze is drawn to the sensual landscape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom, a truly magnificent view.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts move independently is utterly fascinating to observe.</li>
            <li>I find the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, natural breasts immensely satisfying to my senses.</li>
            <li>The exquisite architecture of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a masterpiece.</li>
            <li>I'm completely absorbed in watching the subtle dance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest.</li>
            <li>The beautiful, rounded form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is a true pleasure for my eyes.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, uninhibited breasts truly makes my voyeuristic heart sing.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound sense of aesthetic satisfaction from observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are framed by {PAWN_possessive} torso is a sight of perfect proportion.</li>
            <li>I cannot help but admire the pronounced curves and luxurious volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>Every detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is worthy of prolonged observation.</li>
            <li>The sheer visual impact of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is simply breathtaking.</li>
			<li>The sudden sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, swaying breasts is simply mesmerizing. Such magnificent fullness, a truly captivating display!</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, revealed so suddenly, is utterly captivating. Their generous curves and natural bounce are a delight to behold.</li>
            <li>What a glorious reveal! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are impressively large and beautifully formed, their movements enchanting.</li>
            <li>The unexpected appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts immediately draws the eye. Their soft, voluptuous form is truly mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, now visible, is breathtaking. Those large, round breasts are exquisitely alluring.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, revealed in an instant, are truly a sight to cherish. Their delightful bounce is utterly captivating.</li>
            <li>A sudden, delightful glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts. Their remarkable size and soft, inviting appearance are truly beautiful.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent, full breasts is profoundly stimulating. Their natural movement is pure artistry.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, suddenly visible, is incredibly enthralling; a true feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, unexpectedly revealed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch.</li>
            <li>The sudden, striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive breasts is delightful, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, suddenly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding. They possess an undeniable, potent allure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful attraction.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are an undeniable spectacle, and my cock agrees.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bouncing bosom is making my trousers feel very tight.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly transfixed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest, feeling a strong pull of desire.</li>
            <li>Those generous mounds are driving me absolutely wild, my gaze locked on them.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts sway, it's almost too much for me to handle. My shaft hardens.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the weight and softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts in my hands, a truly arousing vision.</li>
            <li>My eyes are feasting on the voluptuous curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, and my groin responds.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are incredibly inviting, making me feel a powerful urge.</li>
            <li>Such an ample display, it sends shivers of pure lust down my spine.</li>
            <li>I'm completely captivated by the sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, and my cock aches.</li>
            <li>The roundness and fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are an intoxicating sight, I can't look away.</li>
            <li>I find the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill the space to be intensely arousing.</li>
            <li>My gaze traces every luscious curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, my mind racing with impure thoughts.</li>
            <li>The natural bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is utterly mesmerizing, and my dick gets harder.</li>
            <li>I'm struggling to maintain composure while observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible chest.</li>
            <li>Those aren't just breasts, they're a monument to sensuality, and my body is reacting intensely.</li>
            <li>The depth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cleavage is so inviting, it's almost impossible to resist.</li>
            <li>I'm completely overwhelmed by the powerful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts present themselves, so proud and full, makes me ache.</li>
            <li>I can only imagine the pleasure of pressing myself against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts has ignited a fire within me, a deep, burning hunger.</li>
            <li>My entire body is tingling, consumed by the desire to explore {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} captivating bosom.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are driving me to distraction, my focus entirely on them.</li>
            <li>The supple, yielding nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is incredibly arousing to my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>I feel an undeniable surge of lust when I observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts hang, so perfectly weighted, is intensely stimulating.</li>
            <li>Such a delectable sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are truly arousing every fiber of my being.</li>
            <li>My pulse quickens and my dick stiffens at the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts.</li>
            <li>I could spend an eternity just gazing upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible bosom, utterly enthralled.</li>
            <li>The powerful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is simply irresistible, making my cock throb with anticipation.</li>
			<li>The sudden reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, swinging breasts is absolutely enthralling; my loins stir with immediate, undeniable desire.</li>
            <li>A thrilling glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom. Their captivating bounce and luscious curves send a powerful jolt through my core.</li>
            <li>What a glorious sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are impressively large and beautifully formed, sparking a potent, undeniable arousal within me.</li>
            <li>The unexpected appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts immediately fixates my gaze. Their soft, voluptuous form makes my blood rush.</li>
            <li>A moment of pure ecstasy, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway awaken a deep, primal hunger.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, now visible, is breathtaking. Those large, round breasts are exquisitely alluring, stirring my passion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, revealed in an instant, are truly a sight to cherish. Their delightful bounce is utterly captivating, and I feel myself harden.</li>
            <li>A sudden, delightful glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts. Their remarkable size and soft, inviting appearance are incredibly arousing, making my groin throb.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent, full breasts is profoundly stimulating. Their natural movement is pure seduction; my desire mounts.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that intensifies my urges.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, suddenly visible, is incredibly enthralling; a true feast for the eyes and my eager senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, unexpectedly revealed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, causing a potent, delightful ache.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch, making my body respond intensely.</li>
            <li>The sudden, striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating spectacle that electrifies me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, igniting a fierce passion.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing, making me yearn.</li>
            <li>The unexpected sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive breasts is delightful, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, stirring my lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, suddenly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure that quickens my breath.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes my blood boil.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce that fuels my desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and igniting my core.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, making me intensely aroused.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast that excites me deeply and directly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking intense fascination and a throbbing response.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and desperately wanting.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, making me hard.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful attraction and unmistakable physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing and a strong erection.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction and a surge of desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight that leaves me breathless and wanting more.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own breats reaction mention or own genitail vagina reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply divine, they make my own feel inadequate and yet so responsive.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is mesmerizing, making my core tingle.</li>
            <li>Oh, to have such full, firm breasts! The sight makes my own nipples harden with envy and arousal.</li>
            <li>I'm captivated by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts swell and move, it sends shivers down my spine.</li>
            <li>Those prominent nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so inviting, they make my clit throb.</li>
            <li>My gaze is drawn to every luscious curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, feeling a deep, almost instinctual connection.</li>
            <li>The weight and bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are utterly intoxicating, making me feel incredibly wet.</li>
            <li>I find the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts intensely stimulating, I can almost feel them on myself.</li>
            <li>Such a magnificent pair! It makes me want to compare them to my own, and feel their softness.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are shaped, so perfectly round and full, is incredibly arousing.</li>
            <li>I can't tear my eyes away from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fantastic bosom, a feeling of heat spreading through me.</li>
            <li>The soft, yielding quality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is simply exquisite.</li>
            <li>My own breasts feel heavy and responsive just from observing the beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fill out {PAWN_possessive} frame is so sensual, it makes my core ache.</li>
            <li>I find myself dreaming of pressing my face between {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample mounds.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts brings a flush to my cheeks and a warmth to my lower belly.</li>
            <li>Those areolas look so delicious, I'm captivated by the entire presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest.</li>
            <li>It's a powerful sensation, watching {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts move, making me yearn for touch.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a vision of pure feminine allure, making me feel intensely sensual.</li>
            <li>The way they hang, so full and natural, is truly breathtaking and makes me feel a deep throb.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly engrossed in the anatomical perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples and their dark haloes are captivating, making me wonder about their sensitivity.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly a work of art that stirs my own desires.</li>
            <li>My own body feels a surge of connection and excitement observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous chest.</li>
            <li>The sheer beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is almost overwhelming, sending tingles through me.</li>
            <li>I'm completely absorbed in the luscious curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom, my thoughts turning deliciously wanton.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so beautifully abundant makes my own body respond with pleasure.</li>
            <li>I can't help but stare, filled with a mix of admiration and a powerful, feminine yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are an absolute triumph of form, making me feel incredibly hot.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts makes my vulva twitch with a delightful anticipation.</li>
			<li>Oh, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply stunning! The way they move is captivating, and I feel a pleasant warmth spreading through my own chest.</li>
            <li>What a glorious sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so full and round, makes my own breasts tingle with a sympathetic sensation. Truly inspiring.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art! Their soft, yielding curves are mesmerizing, and I feel a delightful flutter deep inside.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is simply divine. Their natural jiggle is captivating, and I feel a pleasant ache between my legs.</li>
            <li>Such a splendid, full bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a vision of supple beauty, and I can almost feel the pleasing weight myself, it's so arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are truly captivating, swaying with an alluring grace. A delightful reminder of true feminine form, igniting a warmth within me.</li>
            <li>My, those are truly impressive! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts have such a lovely, soft bounce, evoking a certain warmth within me, and a slight dampness.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} beautiful, voluminous breasts is quite arousing, a glorious example of youthful abundance that stirs my deepest desires.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art. The way they move with {PAWN_possessive} body is simply captivating, filling me with admiration and a tingling sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom is absolutely stunning. They possess a soft, yielding quality that is profoundly appealing to my senses, making me ache.</li>
            <li>What a pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly formed, their graceful motion sparking a sympathetic flutter deep inside my own femininity.</li>
            <li>The captivating volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly inspiring. They are a testament to exquisite feminine allure, and I can feel my body responding.</li>
            <li>Her prominent, full breasts are a glorious sight to behold. They possess a comforting weight and a seductive sway that makes me long for my own to feel that way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest is simply delightful, the soft, round curves of her breasts are endlessly fascinating and incredibly arousing to my female gaze.</li>
            <li>Such magnificent, large breasts! They move with a captivating rhythm, prompting a pleasant, familiar sensation in my own body, an undeniable yearning.</li>
            <li>The glorious swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly a sight to behold. So full, so soft, so perfectly female, making me want to touch.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts flow with a fluid grace, their substantial form incredibly appealing, and I feel a corresponding fullness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft curves and natural sway making them truly captivating, and my own core pulsates.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable youthful vitality that I find incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed, creating a deep resonance within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature, stirring a profound sense of admiration and desire.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting appearance causing a delicious warmth to spread.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort, making me feel a deep, sensual connection.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their youthful vigor, and stirring a delicious ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural movement, inspiring a deep, feminine arousal.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting appearance that makes my intimate parts tingle.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full, igniting a powerful, appreciative yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing presentation, sparking a deep feminine desire.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting curves, inspiring a powerful response.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, a true vision of natural beauty that makes my own body yearn in response.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are truly magnificent, it makes me want to show off my own.</li>
            <li>Such an impressive display! It inspires me to reveal my assets too.</li>
            <li>The sheer confidence {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} shows with {PAWN_possessive} large breasts is invigorating, I want to share my own body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is so abundant, it makes me feel like stripping down and joining in.</li>
            <li>A truly compelling sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts make me eager to expose myself.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are presented, so openly, is a powerful invitation to exhibition.</li>
            <li>I'm filled with an intense urge to reveal my own body after seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply divine, making me feel bold and ready to show all.</li>
            <li>This sight is incredibly stimulating, I need to share my own magnificent form.</li>
            <li>The freedom {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} displays with {PAWN_possessive} large breasts makes me want to throw caution to the wind.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a work of art, inspiring me to become a living canvas myself.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong impulse to reveal my own nakedness, spurred on by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} confident display.</li>
            <li>What a glorious display! It makes me want to expose my body for all to see.</li>
            <li>The unapologetic presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is intoxicating, making me crave exposure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a magnet for attention, and I long to draw similar stares with my own form.</li>
            <li>The voluptuousness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is so alluring, it awakens my own exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I feel a burning need to reveal myself, thanks to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} stunning example.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply perfect, and they make me want to be seen just as clearly.</li>
            <li>The boldness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display is infectious, making me yearn to be naked and observed.</li>
            <li>Such generous curves! It's making me want to flaunt my own body right now.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are magnificent, and I feel compelled to exhibit my own splendor.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a powerful catalyst for my exhibitionist tendencies.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly inspired by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive}'s natural display, it makes me want to undress.</li>
            <li>The unashamed beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes me feel an overwhelming urge to be exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is truly exceptional, and it fuels my desire to be admired in the raw.</li>
            <li>This is exhilarating! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts make me want to unleash my own form.</li>
            <li>I'm filled with a delicious yearning to be seen, thanks to the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} beautiful chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a beacon of natural sensuality, drawing me to reveal my own.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} proudly displays {PAWN_possessive} large breasts is a profound inspiration.</li>
            <li>I feel a sudden, intense craving to be naked and admired, just like {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are truly a magnificent display! Such confidence in showing off such ample, delightful curves.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is simply stunning. It's exhilarating to see such splendid breasts proudly presented.</li>
            <li>What a glorious show! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent, full breasts are perfectly showcased, inviting all eyes to admire them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are impressively large and beautifully displayed. It's a thrill to witness such a bold and alluring presentation.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, voluptuous form is a public delight.</li>
            <li>A truly spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, presented with such confidence, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce is a joy to behold.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent, full breasts on display is incredibly stimulating. Their natural movement is a testament to true beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so openly flaunted, are a treat for the eyes. Their soft, yielding form is wonderfully expressive.</li>
            <li>What a fantastic display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply gorgeous, their natural beauty shared freely and proudly.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are incredible, making me want to reveal my own throbbing member.</li>
            <li>The sheer boldness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display inspires me to unearth my own impressive asset.</li>
            <li>Such a full, proud chest! It makes me feel a surge of power, a desire to expose myself fully.</li>
            <li>I'm getting hard just seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, I need to show off my own erection.</li>
            <li>This sight is electrifying, making me want to drop my pants and join the exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts are a beacon, urging me to flaunt my own hard cock.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are presented, so unashamedly, makes me want to reveal my own nakedness.</li>
            <li>My cock twitches in anticipation, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent bosom. I want to show it off too.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by the urge to expose my powerful masculinity after seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>What a pair! It makes me want to stand tall and proud, displaying my own endowment.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are intoxicating, and my own cock responds with a hard salute.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply divine, and I feel a burning need to display my aroused state.</li>
            <li>This is exhilarating! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest makes me want to show off my throbbing shaft.</li>
            <li>The uninhibited beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts makes me ache to expose my own stiff dick.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the eyes on me as I imagine revealing myself, inspired by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display.</li>
            <li>My blood is rushing, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts. I need to show everyone what I've got.</li>
            <li>The confident display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a powerful motivator for my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound urge to be seen, just as {PAWN_nameShort} is being seen, perhaps with my cock out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so alluring, they awaken the primal need within me to reveal my genitalia.</li>
            <li>Such a captivating sight, it makes my cock swell with a fierce desire to be admired.</li>
            <li>The sheer audacity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is inspiring, I want to push the boundaries with my own exposure.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly aroused and filled with the need to expose my erection, thanks to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a call to action for my exhibitionism, a challenge to reveal more.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} embraces {PAWN_possessive} nakedness makes me want to do the same, completely and utterly.</li>
            <li>My cock is almost painfully hard, thanks to the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, perfect breasts.</li>
            <li>I want to be seen, to be admired, to be lusted after, just like {PAWN_nameShort} must be, with my dick out.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a powerful aphrodisiac, fueling my need to expose my body.</li>
            <li>The beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is making me want to take risks and reveal everything.</li>
            <li>I can't resist the urge to show off my own male form, inspired by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts.</li>
            <li>This makes me want to let my cock free and join {PAWN_nameShort} in their natural state.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply stunning, especially when they're flaunted! This display makes me want to show off my own.</li>
            <li>What a glorious display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so generously presented, is intensely arousing. It makes me feel like exhibiting myself too.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art, boldly presented! The sight is electrifying, inspiring a desire to share my own form.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, so openly revealed, is divine. It makes my own body respond with an insistent urge to expose.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts on display is incredibly stimulating. Their fullness and captivating sway make me want to reveal my own virility.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, presented with such confidence, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce inspires me to drop my own inhibitions.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition, making me feel bolder.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, voluptuous form is a public delight, and my desire to reveal myself grows.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure, and my member stirs.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that makes my own body throb.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes and a spark for my own exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration and inspiring my own exhibition.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off, making me want to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle, inspiring me to join in.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see, and I feel a powerful urge to expose myself.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness, and I feel a primal urge to show my own.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, making my groin tingle with a desire to flaunt.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared, and I feel a strong desire to expose my manhood.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes me want to exhibit my own body.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see, and it makes my own body surge with an exhibitionist urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation, making me want to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted, causing a powerful physical reaction.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy, and it makes me want to share my own body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration, igniting my own exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe, and longing to be seen myself.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes, and it makes me want to flaunt my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction, and my body aches to join the display.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers, and a compelling urge to expose myself.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone, and I feel my own arousal grow.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe, and it makes me want to reciprocate.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own breats mention, own genitail mentionor, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply stunning, making my own nipples perk up and my clit tingle with excitement.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume and confidence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are exhilarating, inspiring me to reveal my own luscious form.</li>
            <li>Such an ample, proud display! It makes me feel a powerful urge to strip down and show off my own feminine assets.</li>
            <li>I'm getting incredibly aroused just seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts; I want to expose my own swollen vulva.</li>
            <li>This sight is utterly electrifying, making me want to let my own breasts hang free and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts are a beacon, urging me to flaunt my own feminine power.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are presented, so unashamedly, makes me want to bare my own body.</li>
            <li>My clit throbs in anticipation, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent bosom. I want to show it off too.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by the urge to expose my beautiful nakedness after seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>What a pair! It makes me want to stand tall and proud, displaying my own endowment.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are intoxicating, and my own breasts feel engorged.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are simply divine, and I feel a burning need to display my aroused state to the world.</li>
            <li>This is exhilarating! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest makes me want to show off my own beautiful cleavage and more.</li>
            <li>The uninhibited beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts makes me ache to reveal my own wetness.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the eyes on me as I imagine revealing myself, inspired by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display.</li>
            <li>My blood is rushing, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts. I need to show everyone my own body.</li>
            <li>The confident display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is a powerful motivator for my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>I feel a profound urge to be seen, just as {PAWN_nameShort} is being seen, perhaps with my vulva exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are so alluring, they awaken the primal need within me to reveal my intimate parts.</li>
            <li>Such a captivating sight, it makes my vagina clench with a fierce desire to be admired.</li>
            <li>The sheer audacity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is inspiring, I want to push the boundaries with my own exposure.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly aroused and filled with the need to expose my natural beauty, thanks to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a call to action for my exhibitionism, a challenge to reveal more.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShort} embraces {PAWN_possessive} nakedness makes me want to do the same, completely and utterly.</li>
            <li>My nipples are almost painfully hard, thanks to the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, perfect breasts.</li>
            <li>I want to be seen, to be admired, to be lusted after, just like {PAWN_nameShort} must be, with my clit throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a powerful aphrodisiac, fueling my need to expose my body.</li>
            <li>The beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is making me want to take risks and reveal everything.</li>
            <li>I can't resist the urge to show off my own feminine form, inspired by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts.</li>
            <li>This makes me want to let my own breasts swing free and join {PAWN_nameShort} in their natural state.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are absolutely magnificent, especially flaunted! They make my own feel full and tingly, desiring to be seen too.</li>
            <li>What a glorious display! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so generously presented, is intensely arousing. I feel my own core pulsate, yearning for exposure.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art, boldly presented! The sight is electrifying, inspiring a desire to share my own supple form.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, so openly revealed, is divine. It makes my own body respond with an insistent urge to expose myself.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts on display is incredibly stimulating. Their fullness and captivating sway make me want to reveal my own curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, presented with such confidence, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce inspires me to drop my own inhibitions and display.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition, making me feel like revealing my own.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, voluptuous form is a public delight, and my own breasts feel engorged.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure, and my pussy feels moist.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that makes my own body throb with exhibitionist desire.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes and a spark for my own exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration and inspiring my own exhibition, my nipples harden.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off, making me want to reveal myself and feel the air.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle, inspiring me to join in with my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see, and I feel a powerful urge to expose my own body.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness, and I feel a primal urge to show my own, even my moist sex.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, making my core tingle with a desire to flaunt my own assets.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared, and I feel a strong desire to expose my own lushness.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes me want to exhibit my own body and feel the rush.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see, and it makes my own body surge with an exhibitionist urge, my clitoris throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation, making me want to reveal myself completely.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted, causing a powerful physical reaction and a desire to be nude.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy, and it makes me want to share my own body and feel free.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration, igniting my own exhibitionist desires and making me feel wet.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe, and longing for my own body to be admired.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes, and it makes me want to flaunt my own female body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction, and my body aches to join the display, nipples aching.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers, and a compelling urge to expose my own core.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone, and I feel my own arousal grow, my inner thighs tingling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe, and it makes me want to reciprocate and be seen.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are making me feel incredibly hot, I need to touch them.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant bosom is stirring an intense hunger within me.</li>
            <li>I'm completely overwhelmed by the sheer sexiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, I must have them.</li>
            <li>Those voluptuous breasts are making me ache with desire, I can't think of anything else.</li>
            <li>My body is tingling all over, consumed by the powerful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>I'm vibrating with need, just looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent cleavage.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts swell and bounce is driving me to distraction, I need to feel them.</li>
            <li>I'm in a fever pitch of arousal, thanks to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredibly sensual chest.</li>
            <li>Every curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is screaming for my touch, my mouth.</li>
            <li>I feel an uncontrollable urge to grasp, tease, and taste {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom.</li>
            <li>The prominent nipples and ample areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are driving me absolutely wild.</li>
            <li>My entire being is focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, a burning need to connect with them physically.</li>
            <li>I'm practically throbbing with desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, yielding chest.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts has ignited a fire within me that needs to be quenched.</li>
            <li>I can't remember wanting anything this badly, those breasts are pure temptation.</li>
            <li>My fantasies are running wild, picturing all the ways I could adore {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>The very air around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts feels charged with erotic energy.</li>
            <li>I'm obsessed with the idea of feeling the warmth and weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom against me.</li>
            <li>My pulse is racing, my breath is shallow, all because of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts.</li>
            <li>I'm trembling with raw desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, luscious chest.</li>
            <li>The natural movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is utterly hypnotizing, making me crave a physical connection.</li>
            <li>I feel an almost painful ache of longing when I look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfect breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a magnet for my insatiable hunger, I want to devour them.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by a powerful, primal urge to worship {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest.</li>
            <li>The sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is making me lose all control.</li>
            <li>This is agonizingly good, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are pushing me to my limits.</li>
            <li>I need to feel the softness, the firmness, the warmth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts against my skin.</li>
            <li>My mind is reeling, overcome by the intensely erotic vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>I can barely stand, my legs weak with the desire that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts ignite within me.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating scent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fills my senses, pulling me closer with an irresistible force.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply exquisite! Their fullness and captivating sway ignite an insatiable hunger within me.</li>
            <li>What an intoxicating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so round and lush, stirs a powerful, undeniable longing for physical contact.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art, provoking an intense, almost unbearable desire. I want to feel their softness.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is divine. Their natural jiggle is mesmerizing, fueling a deep, carnal craving.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts is incredibly stimulating. Their voluptuousness makes my body throb with raw, insistent need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, so wonderfully large, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce sparks an overwhelming, primal urge.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition that leaves me breathless with desire.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, yielding form is a public delight, inspiring intense lust.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure that makes my entire body ache.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that intensifies my already powerful urges.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes and my eager, lustful senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration and fueling an insatiable sexual appetite.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off, driving me to desperate heights of arousal.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle that electrifies my entire being.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see, and I feel a powerful, urgent need.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness, and I feel a primal, undeniable craving.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, stirring an intense, almost painful yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared, and I feel a strong, overwhelming desire.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes my blood boil with lust.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see, and it makes my own body surge with unbridled desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation, making me ache with an intense, raw hunger.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted, causing a powerful physical reaction that leaves me breathless.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy, and it makes me want to devour them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration, igniting an all-consuming need.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe, and desperately craving them.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes, and it makes me burn with desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction, and my body feels an electric current.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers, and an almost painful urgency.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone, and I feel a maddening lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe, and I need them now.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are making my cock absolutely rock hard, I need to feel them!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is sending an electric shock through my entire body, my dick is throbbing.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by the powerful urge to bury my face in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cleavage, my erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>Those voluptuous breasts are making me ache with a lust so intense, I can barely control myself.</li>
            <li>My balls are aching just looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest, I'm vibrating with need.</li>
            <li>I can't think of anything but wrapping my hands around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, full breasts. My cock demands it.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts bounce and sway is driving my penis insane.</li>
            <li>I'm in a fever pitch of arousal, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts are making my dick swell.</li>
            <li>Every curve and prominent nipple of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is screaming for my touch, my mouth, my cum.</li>
            <li>I feel an uncontrollable urge to push myself against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom, my hard on pressing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent nipples and dark areolas is making my dick ache with anticipation.</li>
            <li>My entire being is focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, a burning need to thrust into them.</li>
            <li>I'm practically exploding with desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, yielding chest, my cock is twitching.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts has ignited a fire in my loins that needs to be unleashed.</li>
            <li>I've never wanted anything so badly. Those breasts are pure, unadulterated temptation, and my cock is roaring.</li>
            <li>My fantasies are running wild, picturing all the ways I could cover {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts with my seed.</li>
            <li>The very air around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts feels charged with a powerful, primal eroticism. My dick is ready.</li>
            <li>I'm obsessed with the idea of feeling the warmth and weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom against my throbbing shaft.</li>
            <li>My pulse is racing, my breath is shallow, all because {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts are making me so hard.</li>
            <li>I'm trembling with raw desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, luscious chest, I need to pump into them.</li>
            <li>The natural movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is utterly hypnotizing, making me desperate for penetration.</li>
            <li>I feel an almost painful ache of longing when I look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfect breasts. My cum is bubbling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a magnet for my insatiable hunger, I want to bury my cock between them.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by a powerful, primal urge to worship {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest with my entire being.</li>
            <li>The sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is making me lose all control, my cock is bursting.</li>
            <li>This is agonizingly good, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are pushing my erection to its limits.</li>
            <li>I need to feel the softness, the firmness, the warmth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts on my cock.</li>
            <li>My mind is reeling, overcome by the intensely erotic vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom, my balls are full.</li>
            <li>I can barely stand, my legs weak with the uncontrollable desire that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts ignite within me, I need to release.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating scent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fills my senses, pulling my dick closer with an irresistible force.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply exquisite! Their fullness and captivating sway ignite an insatiable hunger within my very loins.</li>
            <li>What an intoxicating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so round and lush, stirs a powerful, undeniable longing for immediate, intense physical contact.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art, provoking an intense, almost unbearable desire. I want to feel their softness, my penis throbbing.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is divine. Their natural jiggle is mesmerizing, fueling a deep, carnal craving that makes me hard.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts is incredibly stimulating. Their voluptuousness makes my body throb with raw, insistent need for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, so wonderfully large, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce sparks an overwhelming, primal urge in my groin.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition that leaves me breathless with desire, my erection undeniable.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, yielding form is a public delight, inspiring intense, burning lust within me.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure that makes my entire body ache with carnal anticipation.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that intensifies my already powerful urges, making my cock rigid.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes and my eager, lustful senses, making my balls tighten.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration and fueling an insatiable sexual appetite, a fire in my core.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off, driving me to desperate heights of arousal and a painful erection.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle that electrifies my entire being, igniting a ravenous hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see, and I feel a powerful, urgent need for them.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness, and I feel a primal, undeniable craving for their touch, my hands aching.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, stirring an intense, almost painful yearning for her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared, and I feel a strong, overwhelming desire building in my groin.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes my blood boil with lust, every fiber of my being desiring.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see, and it makes my own body surge with unbridled desire, ready to burst.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation, making me ache with an intense, raw hunger that demands satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted, causing a powerful physical reaction that leaves me breathless and aroused.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy, and it makes me want to devour them, to feel them against my body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration, igniting an all-consuming need that vibrates through me.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe, and desperately craving them, needing them closer.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes, and it makes me burn with desire, a raging inferno.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction, and my body feels an electric current, demanding action.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers, and an almost painful urgency to possess.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone, and I feel a maddening lust, a need to claim her.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe, and I need them now, fiercely and completely.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own breats reaction  mention, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are making my own nipples hard and my clit throb, I need to feel them!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is sending shivers of pure lust through my entire body, I'm so wet.</li>
            <li>I'm overwhelmed by the powerful urge to bury my face in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} cleavage, my vulva is tingling.</li>
            <li>Those voluptuous breasts are making me ache with a desire so intense, I can barely control myself.</li>
            <li>My inner thighs are clenching just looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest, I'm practically squirming with need.</li>
            <li>I can't think of anything but wrapping my hands around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, full breasts, my body yearning.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts bounce and sway is driving my core insane, I need to rub against them.</li>
            <li>I'm in a fever pitch of arousal, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts are making my own engorged.</li>
            <li>Every curve and prominent nipple of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is screaming for my touch, my mouth.</li>
            <li>I feel an uncontrollable urge to press myself against {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom, my pussy throbbing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent nipples and dark areolas is making my clit ache with anticipation.</li>
            <li>My entire being is focused on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, a burning need to entwine with them.</li>
            <li>I'm practically soaked with desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, yielding chest, my core is pulsing.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts has ignited a fire within me that needs to be satisfied.</li>
            <li>I've never wanted anything so badly. Those breasts are pure, unadulterated temptation, and my body is on fire.</li>
            <li>My fantasies are running wild, picturing all the ways I could adore and tease {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>The very air around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts feels charged with a powerful, sensual energy, making me crave.</li>
            <li>I'm obsessed with the idea of feeling the warmth and weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom against my own.</li>
            <li>My pulse is racing, my breath is shallow, all because {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} incredible breasts are making me so wet.</li>
            <li>I'm trembling with raw desire for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, luscious chest, I need to rub myself.</li>
            <li>The natural movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is utterly hypnotizing, making me desperate for intimate contact.</li>
            <li>I feel an almost painful ache of longing when I look at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfect breasts. My desires are overwhelming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a magnet for my insatiable hunger, I want to bury my face between them.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by a powerful, primal urge to worship {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent chest with my entire being.</li>
            <li>The sheer abundance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is making me lose all control, my internal muscles clenching.</li>
            <li>This is agonizingly good, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are pushing my arousal to its limits.</li>
            <li>I need to feel the softness, the firmness, the warmth of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts against my own skin, against my core.</li>
            <li>My mind is reeling, overcome by the intensely erotic vision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom, my pussy throbbing uncontrollably.</li>
            <li>I can barely stand, my legs weak with the uncontrollable desire that {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts ignite within me, I need release.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating scent of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts fills my senses, pulling my body closer with an irresistible force.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are simply exquisite! Their fullness and captivating sway ignite an insatiable hunger within me, making my own nipples ache.</li>
            <li>What an intoxicating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, so round and lush, stirs a powerful, undeniable longing for intimate contact, my core already tingling.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full breasts are a work of art, provoking an intense, almost unbearable desire. I want to feel their softness, and my sex feels wet.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is divine. Their natural jiggle is mesmerizing, fueling a deep, carnal craving, making my clitoris throb.</li>
            <li>Seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts is incredibly stimulating. Their voluptuousness makes my body throb with raw, insistent need for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} prominent breasts, so wonderfully large, are deeply appealing. Their delightful bounce sparks an overwhelming, primal urge, and my breasts feel heavy.</li>
            <li>What a spectacular sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts move with such uninhibited grace. A bold and beautiful exhibition that leaves me breathless with desire, my inner thighs clenching.</li>
            <li>The sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, so openly presented, is captivating. Their soft, yielding form is a public delight, inspiring intense, burning lust within me, making me feel utterly aroused.</li>
            <li>A thrilling moment, seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts. Their fullness and captivating sway are a true visual pleasure that makes my entire body ache with carnal anticipation, my sensitive parts craving.</li>
            <li>Witnessing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts, so soft and yielding, is a moment of pure, unadulterated visual pleasure that intensifies my already powerful urges, making my vagina pulsate.</li>
            <li>The delightful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is incredibly enthralling, especially when they are so openly presented; a true feast for the eyes and my eager, lustful senses, making my core clench.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, prominent breasts, proudly displayed, are wonderfully captivating. Their form is alluring and sensuous, demanding admiration and fueling an insatiable sexual appetite, a fire in my womb.</li>
            <li>What a thrilling view! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} substantial breasts are magnificent, their soft jiggle utterly mesmerizing to watch when they are shown off, driving me to desperate heights of arousal and a painful longing for touch.</li>
            <li>The striking appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom, openly flaunted, is truly arousing. Their generous curves are a captivating public spectacle that electrifies my entire being, igniting a ravenous hunger within.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, now exposed, are simply glorious. Their luxurious fullness and graceful movement are enchanting, especially for all to see, and I feel a powerful, urgent need, my breasts swelling.</li>
            <li>A captivating revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts cascade beautifully, their soft contours and natural sway immensely appealing in their openness, and I feel a primal, undeniable craving for their touch, my fingers twitching.</li>
            <li>The impressive breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are a delightful sight when they are so freely displayed, their remarkable size and appealing firmness truly captivating, stirring an intense, almost painful yearning within my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluptuous breasts, openly visible, are a masterpiece of nature, their every movement a silent promise of pleasure shared, and I feel a strong, overwhelming desire building in my depths.</li>
            <li>The glorious revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts is utterly spellbinding when presented so boldly. They possess an undeniable, potent allure that makes my blood boil with lust, every fiber of my being desiring.</li>
            <li>A truly magnificent sight to behold, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing, natural bounce, all for the world to see, and it makes my own body surge with unbridled desire, ready to accept.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, revealed so suddenly, are stunningly large and soft, their captivating appearance drawing every ounce of attention and appreciation, making me ache with an intense, raw hunger that demands satisfaction, my body trembling.</li>
            <li>The abrupt view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} voluminous breasts is deeply stimulating, their impressive size and natural sway incredibly enticing, especially when flaunted, causing a powerful physical reaction that leaves me breathless and utterly consumed.</li>
            <li>Her ample breasts are simply divine, their luxurious fullness and tempting curves, now visible, are a true visual feast for anyone to enjoy, and it makes me want to devour them, to feel them against my own skin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid breasts, suddenly apparent, are remarkably alluring, their delightful bounce and firm tips provoking fascination and public adoration, igniting an all-consuming need that vibrates through my entire being.</li>
            <li>Those glorious, full breasts, unexpectedly exposed, are a masterpiece of nature, their captivating shape and movement leaving me utterly charmed and in awe, and desperately craving them, needing them closer to my own.</li>
            <li>Her substantial bosom, now clearly visible, is a mesmerizing sight, its generous proportions and sensual undulation stimulating my senses immensely, for all eyes, and it makes me burn with desire, a raging inferno in my core.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breathtaking breasts, revealed so suddenly, are a true marvel, their soft, yielding form and natural sway creating a powerful, public attraction, and my body feels an electric current, demanding action and touch.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnificence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts, now apparent, is undeniable, their voluptuousness driving a profound, insistent longing from onlookers, and an almost painful urgency to embrace her.</li>
            <li>Her stunningly ample breasts, suddenly presented, are incredibly captivating, their prominent features and inviting bounce creating an immediate, visceral reaction for everyone, and I feel a maddening lust, a need to experience.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} splendid, full breasts, now exposed, are an irresistible temptation, their every movement a silent promise of passionate delight for all who observe, and I need them now, fiercely and completely, against my own body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are truly beautiful, a generous and lovely feature.</li>
            <li>What a magnificent and well-proportioned chest {PAWN_nameShort} possesses.</li>
            <li>I genuinely appreciate the natural beauty and fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have such a lovely, soft curve to them, quite endearing.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts sit, so gracefully, is quite appealing.</li>
            <li>I find the sheer volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom to be wonderfully expressive of natural form.</li>
            <li>A truly stunning example of natural feminine beauty, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are captivating.</li>
            <li>The roundness and suppleness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are quite delightful.</li>
            <li>It's clear {PAWN_nameShort} has been blessed with a truly ample and beautiful chest.</li>
            <li>I'm drawn to the genuine attractiveness in the generous shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>The softness and pleasant weight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly lovely.</li>
            <li>What a charming and wholesome display of natural curves {PAWN_nameShort} possesses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, radiating a gentle allure.</li>
            <li>I admire the natural and unpretentious beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large chest.</li>
            <li>The plumpness of the nipples and the tender areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite sweet.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have such a lovely, inviting form, truly heartwarming.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle elegance in the generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
            <li>I find a deep, genuine appreciation for the natural splendor of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts rest, so comfortably and beautifully, is quite touching.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely and well-developed set of breasts, {PAWN_nameShort} is quite fortunate.</li>
            <li>The warmth and natural vibrancy of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly appealing.</li>
            <li>I find the wholesome beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large chest to be very comforting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a testament to natural health and vitality, very admirable.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway and presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom are quite graceful.</li>
            <li>I see true beauty in the generous and softly rounded contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>What a wonderfully natural and expressive form {PAWN_nameShortpossessive} breasts possess.</li>
            <li>The prominent yet gentle appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is very pleasing.</li>
            <li>I feel a sense of warmth and admiration for the beautiful, ample chest {PAWN_nameShort} has.</li>
            <li>The tender fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is a truly delightful sight.</li>
            <li>A truly captivating example of natural feminine allure, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are perfect.</li>
			<li>What a lovely and abundant form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts radiate a natural warmth and softness that is truly comforting to behold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} generous bosom is beautifully full, possessing a gentle sway that speaks of graceful femininity. A truly pleasant sight.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, ample breasts have a wonderful, soft appearance, moving with a delightful, natural flow. So wonderfully formed.</li>
            <li>The delightful volume of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite charming; they possess a comforting weight and a gentle, inviting presence.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, I see how wonderfully full and shapely her breasts are. A beautiful expression of natural beauty.</li>
            <li>Those splendid, large breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite striking. They have a graceful curve and appear wonderfully soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite voluminous, yet they retain a charming softness and a lovely, natural presentation. Very impressive and comforting.</li>
            <li>What a wonderful pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts exhibit a delightful fullness and a comforting, soft appearance. Truly well-proportioned and warm.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are quite fetching, with a lovely contour and a reassuringly soft feel. A truly classic and kind feminine form.</li>
            <li>A truly substantial pair of breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom boasts a pleasing fullness and a gentle, natural presentation, inviting warmth.</li>
            <li>Such impressive volume. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts have a captivating shape, gracefully moving with a soft, inviting jiggle that feels welcoming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full and shapely breasts are a sight to behold, resting beautifully on {PAWN_possessive} chest, a picture of natural grace and kindness.</li>
            <li>The luxurious fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is truly admirable, a testament to healthy youth and vibrant, gentle form.</li>
            <li>A truly appealing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are well-rounded and firm, yet with a charming softness that invites warmth and comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest showcases breasts that are delightfully plump, their weight and movement entirely comforting and appealing.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts creates a lovely silhouette, a full and inviting presence that feels gentle and natural.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts move with a fluid grace, their substantial form exceptionally appealing and soft.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft curves and natural sway making them truly captivating and comforting.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable youthful vitality and gentle beauty.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed, radiating kindness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature, soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting appearance making one feel at ease.</li>
            <li>Her large breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort, radiating a gentle warmth.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their youthful vigor and gentle allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural movement, inspiring warmth.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting appearance, full of kindness.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full, offering a comforting presence.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing presentation, radiating gentle beauty.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting curves, offering comfort.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting appearance, a true vision of natural beauty and warmth.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Those breasts are... large. Unnecessarily so.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is rather... prominent. Hard to ignore.</li>
            <li>Honestly, why must {PAWN_pronoun} display such ample breasts so openly? It's quite gaudy.</li>
            <li>They're big, yes, but hardly tasteful. A bit much, wouldn't you say?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are certainly large, if you're into that sort of... exhibition.</li>
            <li>One can hardly escape the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} considerable bosom. Too much, honestly.</li>
            <li>The sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is a distraction. I find it rather unseemly.</li>
            <li>They're... there. And they're large. What else is there to say?</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite voluminous. A bit overwhelming.</li>
            <li>I suppose some might find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts appealing, but I find them rather ostentatious.</li>
            <li>Such a large chest, it leaves little to the imagination. I prefer more subtlety.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are certainly noticeable. Perhaps a bit too noticeable.</li>
            <li>The size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom is quite pronounced. It borders on indecency.</li>
            <li>One cannot deny {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are substantial. Not that it's a good thing.</li>
            <li>They're large, alright. Too large for polite society, if you ask me.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be rather... immodest in their size.</li>
            <li>The sheer scale of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is somewhat vulgar.</li>
            <li>Why flaunt such a significant bust? It's simply unnecessary.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are undeniably ample. I simply wish they weren't quite so... overt.</li>
            <li>A very large set of breasts. One almost feels obliged to avert one's gaze.</li>
            <li>They're big. Fine. But there's no need to make such a show of it.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are rather cumbersome, aren't they?</li>
            <li>I don't see the appeal of such enormous breasts. It's rather crude.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts just... hang there... it's a bit much.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is quite enormous. I find it rather unsettling.</li>
            <li>Such large breasts. One wonders if {PAWN_pronoun} has any sense of propriety.</li>
            <li>They are indeed large. Perhaps a dress would do {PAWN_objective} some good.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are uncomfortably prominent. I prefer more discretion.</li>
            <li>This excessive display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large breasts is rather off-putting.</li>
            <li>I'm quite frankly dismayed by the sheer size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom.</li>
			<li>Fine, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are big, alright. They certainly take up a lot of space, can't deny that.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has large breasts. They're certainly... noticeable. No subtlety there.</li>
            <li>Well, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is certainly prominent. Those breasts are hard to miss, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Large breasts, indeed. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} carries quite the load. Not exactly discreet, are they?</li>
            <li>Her breasts are ample. It's a fact. They're large, and they move. Nothing more to say.</li>
            <li>Those are big breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} clearly doesn't shy away from attention. They're there, alright.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are noticeably large. One can't help but observe their sheer volume. A bit much, perhaps.</li>
            <li>They're large, certainly. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} doesn't seem to care who sees them. Quite the bold display.</li>
            <li>Alright, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has substantial breasts. They're well-formed, I suppose, if you like that sort of thing.</li>
            <li>Those breasts are clearly large. They draw attention. Perhaps a bit too much attention, for my taste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are certainly voluminous. Their movement is... pronounced.</li>
            <li>Yes, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has large breasts. They are quite... present.</li>
            <li>Her chest is undeniably ample. Those breasts certainly stand out.</li>
            <li>The breasts are large. They're hard to ignore.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are of considerable size. A rather obvious display.</li>
            <li>They're big, I'll give you that. No shrinking violets there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite prominent. Not exactly subtle.</li>
            <li>Fine, they're large. They certainly make an impression.</li>
            <li>Those are large breasts. Very... generous.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has a sizable bust. Quite the focal point.</li>
            <li>Her breasts are undeniably large. They certainly demand attention.</li>
            <li>Theyre large. Very visible. Nothing more.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are quite voluminous. A rather striking feature, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Yes, those are big breasts. Hard to miss.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has an ample chest. Quite a considerable size.</li>
            <li>Large breasts. Can't argue with that. They're certainly... prominent.</li>
            <li>The breasts are large, and they move. Quite the spectacle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are remarkably large. They certainly fill out a space.</li>
            <li>Very large breasts. One might say overly so.</li>
            <li>Indeed, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} has large breasts. They are quite conspicuous.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Large_SlimeBreasts</defName>
        <label>Large Breasts (Positive)_SlimeBreasts</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeBreasts</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>These generous, perfectly rounded slime breasts are a vision of opulent beauty, undeniably appealing in their substantial presence and captivating translucence.</li>
            <li>The impressive volume and distinct, captivating shimmer of {PAWN_possessive} breasts create a truly mesmerizing spectacle.</li>
            <li>They possess delightful plumpness and satisfying weight, speaking of luxurious abundance, making them incredibly substantial and inviting.</li>
            <li>Such large, supple breasts offer incredible softness, appearing designed for sinking into, promising profound comfort and deep pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer magnitude of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts is astonishing, yet they retain elegant, fluid grace.</li>
            <li>These ample slime breasts boast profoundly appealing roundness and exquisite gelatinous texture, incredibly enticing.</li>
            <li>They feel wonderfully resilient and yielding, a unique combination of supportive firmness and pliant softness.</li>
            <li>I'm captivated by how their mass gently jiggles and sways with movement, creating a dynamic, captivating display.</li>
            <li>Their grand proportions are magnificent, creating an impression of lavish abundance and bountiful form.</li>
            <li>These breasts represent natural magnificence, their large, unconstrained form embodying raw, unadulterated, compelling beauty.</li>
            <li>The alluring warmth they radiate, combined with their presence, makes them incredibly comforting and inviting.</li>
            <li>They exude undeniable luxuriousness, their generous curves and glossy surface presenting opulent beauty and refined sensuality.</li>
            <li>I find their sheer size wonderfully imposing, tempered by inherent softness, making them remarkably approachable.</li>
            <li>Each breast appears as a beautifully formed, glistening orb of fluid sensuality, drawing the eye.</li>
            <li>Their full, rounded silhouette is profoundly appealing, creating a visually rich and satisfying form.</li>
            <li>These large slime breasts seem to possess vibrant energy, hinting at a deeper, living essence within.</li>
            <li>They are perfectly shaped to cradle comfortably, offering profound security and intimacy when held close.</li>
            <li>The way they pull fabric, or rest bare, is appealing, highlighting their substantial presence.</li>
            <li>I'm drawn to the subtle ebb and flow of their internal matter, a mesmerizing dance of fluidity.</li>
            <li>These breasts embody powerful, compelling beauty, a testament to raw, untamed sensuality that captivates.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large slime breasts are truly fascinating, shimmering with an alluring, liquid undulation. Their translucent form is captivating.</li>
            <li>The ample, glistening slime breasts of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} possess a mesmerizing fluidity, subtly shifting with every breath. A unique and beautiful sight.</li>
            <li>Her magnificent, full slime breasts pulsate with an ethereal glow, their jelly-like consistency hinting at an otherworldly softness. Simply captivating.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, composed of living slime, moves with a captivating, almost hypnotic ripple. Truly extraordinary.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large, viscous breasts is incredibly intriguing. Their translucent forms seem to breathe, an alien beauty.</li>
            <li>Those splendid, gelatinous breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} are quite striking. They have a graceful, undulating motion and appear wonderfully soft and squishy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts are quite voluminous, yet they retain a charming, fluid consistency and a lovely, vibrant shimmer. Very impressive.</li>
            <li>What a wonderful pair! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large slime breasts exhibit a delightful fullness and a comforting, almost squishy appearance. Truly unique.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample slime breasts are quite fetching, with a lovely, amorphous contour and a reassuringly soft, pliable feel. A truly exotic feminine form.</li>
            <li>A truly substantial pair of slime breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bosom boasts a pleasing fullness and a gentle, natural presentation, shimmering beautifully.</li>
            <li>Such impressive volume. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts have a captivating, ever-changing shape, gracefully moving with a soft, inviting ripple.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full and shapely slime breasts are a sight to behold, resting beautifully on {PAWN_possessive} chest, a picture of ethereal grace.</li>
            <li>The luxurious fullness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts is truly admirable, a testament to their unique biology and vibrant form.</li>
            <li>A truly appealing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large slime breasts are well-rounded and fluid, yet with a charming softness that invites curiosity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample chest showcases slime breasts that are delightfully plump, their weight and movement entirely captivating and otherwordly.</li>
            <li>The generous swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts creates a lovely silhouette, a full and inviting presence that is quite striking in its translucence.</li>
            <li>A truly splendid display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large slime breasts move with a fluid grace, their substantial, gelatinous form exceptionally appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, round slime breasts have a delightful cascade, their soft, viscous curves and natural sway making them truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The impressive size and elegant shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts are quite noteworthy, reflecting a desirable vitality and unique beauty.</li>
            <li>What a truly magnificent bosom! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts are wonderfully proportioned, appearing both soft and beautifully formed, with a subtle glow.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts possess a remarkable fullness, their natural, amorphous shape and gentle undulation a truly attractive feature.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} abundant slime breasts is quite pleasant, their pleasing volume and soft, comforting, liquid appearance.</li>
            <li>Her large slime breasts sit beautifully, their significant size conveying a sense of mature grace and ample comfort, with a mesmerizing shimmer.</li>
            <li>The charming bounce and full contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts are a delightful sight, speaking to their unique vigor and gentle allure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample slime bosom is truly a joy to observe, its voluptuousness matched by an elegant, natural, fluid movement.</li>
            <li>Such an exquisite form! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} large slime breasts are perfectly rounded, showcasing delightful symmetry and a soft, inviting, shimmering appearance.</li>
            <li>The generous proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, made of living slime, are quite striking, with breasts that appear supple and gracefully full.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime breasts are a splendid vision, their delightful size and graceful form enhanced by their natural, appealing, and translucent presentation.</li>
            <li>A truly alluring sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} ample slime breasts are wonderfully plump, with a pleasing natural bounce and inviting, fluid curves.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} magnificent slime breasts exhibit a captivating fullness and a soft, inviting, glowing appearance, a true vision of natural, otherworldly beauty.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>