<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
		<genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
		<opinionTexts>
            <li>Thinking of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fills my heart.</li>
            <li>Seems like {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts would perfectly fit in my hands.</li>
			<li>Never seen {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small perky breasts {PAWN_nameShort} has.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were petite but still captured my attention, {PAWN_possessive} modest size only adding to allure.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were just the right size for my tastes, with a firm and oh-so-tempting texture.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were small but perfectly shaped, with pert and perky nipples that called out to me.</li>
			<li>I saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were modest but alluring, with a size that was just right for snuggling.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were compact but curvy, with a shape that was both elegant and enticing.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were small but sensual, inviting me to explore every inch.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were perfectly proportioned, {PAWN_possessive} compact size and gentle curves a celebration of feminine beauty.</li>
			<li>I tenderly examined a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, {PAWN_possessive} subtle shape and inviting texture a sensory delight.</li>
			<li>I marveled at a pair of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts that were a true delight, {PAWN_possessive} petite size and elegant lines a testament of charm.</li>
			<li>I appreciated {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modestly-sized breasts, {PAWN_possessive} balanced shape a delightful handful, inspiring affection and admiration.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, shapely breasts were an endearing sight, {PAWN_possessive} lovely contours stirring my senses, evoking tender emotions.</li>
			<li>A thoughtful observation revealed the well-portioned {PAWN_possessive} small breasts, {PAWN_possessive} delicate form a captivating representation of delicate allure.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, rounded breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples a sweet shade of pink, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a delicate circle.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slender chest, {PAWN_possessive} small breasts perky and adorable, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a tiny, rose-colored circle.</li>
			<li>I admired {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples small and kissable, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a subtle, gentle curve.</li>
			<li>I observed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, delicate breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples a soft, blush-like color, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a whispered promise.</li>
			<li>I appreciated {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, yet perfectly proportioned breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples tiny and enticing, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a mere hint of pink.</li>
			<li>I inspected {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest, {PAWN_possessive} small breasts sweetly shaped, {PAWN_possessive} nipples small and enticing, like a secret whispered in my ear.</li>
			<li>I marveled at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, captivating breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples a delicate, shell-like pink, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a subtle, swirling pattern.</li>
			<li>I glanced at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, pert breasts, {PAWN_possessive} nipples a rosy, inviting color, {PAWN_possessive} areolas a dainty, lacy circle, like the edge of a flower petal.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, perfectly formed, possess a delightful firmness, hinting at a youthful vitality that is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The delicate curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a vision of understated elegance, a testament to natural beauty.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts incredibly appealing, their modest size offering a subtle charm.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts as {PAWN_pronoun} moves is surprisingly mesmerizing, a fluid dance.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle perkiness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that suggests a playful spirit and a youthful glow.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape and soft feel, are utterly adorable and inviting to the touch.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are naturally uplifted gives {PAWN_objective} a wonderfully lithe and graceful appearance.</li>
            <li>I can't help but appreciate the charming proportions of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} frame.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, perfectly symmetrical breasts are a beautiful sight, hinting at a delicate and refined physique.</li>
            <li>The youthful firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them incredibly attractive, a testament to raw, natural beauty.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, so delicately sculpted, seem to invite a gentle caress, promising a soft and yielding touch.</li>
            <li>I am drawn to the subtle contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, shapely breasts, a testament to natural elegance.</li>
            <li>The modest yet captivating presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts speaks volumes about understated sensuality.</li>
            <li>There's an undeniable allure in the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit perfectly against {PAWN_possessive} ribcage, a harmonious fit.</li>
            <li>I find the soft, gentle curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be profoundly attractive, evoking a sense of purity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender roundness and subtle lift, are truly a delightful and endearing feature.</li>
            <li>The natural grace displayed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, even in repose, is quite captivating and beautiful.</li>
            <li>I admire the refined form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a testament to their inherent beauty and poise.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unmistakable, a pure and inviting form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, though modest in size, possess a striking elegance that draws the eye.</li>
            <li>I find a quiet beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their gentle swell a graceful and delicate expression.</li>
			<li>Upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, one can't help but admire the delicate, perfectly proportioned curves. They possess a subtle grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to natural beauty, sitting elegantly on {PAWN_possessive} frame. Their firm, youthful shape is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>A pleasant surprise to observe: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a charming, understated appeal. The nipples are well-defined, complementing the overall refined look.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} body reveals a natural fluidity. Their gentle contours are quite pleasing to the eye.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its compact and shapely form, is quite attractive. The areolas are subtly shaded, adding to their natural allure.</li>
            <li>Small and perky, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts look incredibly youthful and firm. They are perfectly suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} overall elegance.</li>
            <li>A vision of subtle beauty, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are artfully sculpted. Their delightful form and delicate features are truly captivating.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts, one notes their tasteful proportion. They offer a refined silhouette, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural grace.</li>
            <li>The soft, inviting curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. They sit high and proud, a charming accent to {PAWN_possessive} torso.</li>
            <li>Such a neat and elegant pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, with delicate nipples that complete their charming appearance.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, offer a delightful visual. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust is quite endearing, possessing a delicate, appealing shape. They appear wonderfully firm and perky.</li>
            <li>A truly lovely sight: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude an innocent charm. Their firm structure and subtle details are admirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, complements {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The nipples are exquisitely defined.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and appealing silhouette.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural appeal.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating. They possess a natural lift and a pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, adding to the overall perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	

</Def>

<!--Elder Male observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Ah, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts remind me of a bygone era, a classic beauty that time hasn't touched.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, a natural allure often overlooked in this modern age.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, small breasts possess a fresh, delicate appeal that brings a smile to my face.</li>
            <li>A pleasant sight indeed, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts, perfectly suited to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts have a timeless elegance, a quiet beauty that truly stands out.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the understated grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a picture of youthful serenity.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts adds to {PAWN_possessive} overall delicate appearance, quite lovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, shapely breasts are a comforting sight, a classic form that never goes out of style.</li>
            <li>It's refreshing to see such natural, unspoiled beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a true gem.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts have a youthful resilience, a firmness that speaks of vitality.</li>
            <li>A gentle curvature, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to modest allure and simple beauty.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, upright breasts fills me with a sense of pleasant nostalgia.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be quite delightful, a perfectly formed part of {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a charming innocence, a refreshing change from more ostentatious displays.</li>
            <li>There's a quiet strength in the modest presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, truly appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, neatly formed breasts are a beautiful sight, reminding me of delicate porcelain.</li>
            <li>The soft contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite pleasing, a testament to natural feminine grace.</li>
            <li>I admire the subtle perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a understated form of beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their youthful perkiness, evoke a sense of sweet, innocent charm.</li>
            <li>The delicate appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts complements {PAWN_possessive} slender build wonderfully.</li>
            <li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to how true beauty lies in natural form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their unblemished curves, radiate a subtle and enduring allure.</li>
            <li>There's a certain timeless appeal to the modest shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, quite captivating.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be exquisitely formed, a true example of natural artistry.</li>
            <li>The compact yet elegant form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly a pleasure to behold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, firm and high, are a perfect symbol of youthful grace.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are set on {PAWN_possessive} chest is wonderfully proportionate.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful vibrancy exuded by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to unspoiled natural beauty, a truly lovely sight.</li>
            <li>The gentle firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing, suggesting a quiet strength.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate chest is a refreshing sight, reminding me of youthful innocence.</li>
            <li>Such small, firm breasts. A true vision of delicate beauty.</li>
            <li>These modest breasts have a charming appeal, a subtle grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite form is quite lovely, a gentle curve.</li>
            <li>Youthful breasts, small and upright. A pleasant sight indeed.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts subtly move is rather endearing.</li>
            <li>A quiet appreciation for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, yet alluring chest.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly suited to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>A reminder of innocent charm, these small breasts are quite captivating.</li>
            <li>The slight perkiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts speaks of youth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, though small, possesses an undeniable natural elegance.</li>
            <li>I admire the unadorned beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are a testament to grace and youth.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, a gentle appeal.</li>
            <li>These small breasts are a pleasant sight, a subtle and youthful form.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing.</li>
            <li>A classic beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small and shapely breasts.</li>
            <li>Such a tender form, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly lovely.</li>
            <li>I find the natural contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts quite appealing.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, so gentle and refined, possess a quiet allure.</li>
            <li>A modest yet compelling presence, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are striking.</li>
            <li>The innocent charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unmistakable.</li>
            <li>I see the graceful lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a subtle perfection.</li>
            <li>There’s a timeless appeal to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite chest is a vision of youthful allure, with delicate, almost budding breasts.</li>
            <li>The small, high-set breasts on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest suggest an untainted beauty.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the subtle firmness and gentle curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, with their youthful shape and perfectly pink nipples, are quite endearing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, though not ample, have a sweet, unblemished quality.</li>
            <li>A classic, elegant form: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly positioned breasts.</li>
			<li>Ah, such delicate, modest breasts. Their youthful firmness is quite apparent, a charming sight to behold on {PAWN_nameShort}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts remind me of simpler times; so naturally formed, with a captivatingly demure outline.</li>
            <li>A sudden glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest reveals a graceful, unblemished beauty. Those small, firm peaks are truly lovely.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts gently rise and fall is quite captivating. They possess a youthful elegance that's truly endearing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is a testament to natural beauty. The small, defined nipples are a pleasant detail.</li>
            <li>Modest yet perfectly formed, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite appealing. Their youthful bounce is subtly enchanting.</li>
            <li>A refined contour, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a vision of unspoiled beauty. They sit elegantly, a credit to {PAWN_possessive} youthful figure.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts, I appreciate their perfect proportion. They enhance {PAWN_possessive} slender form beautifully.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable. Their smooth, soft appearance is quite captivating.</li>
            <li>Such a neat and tidy presentation. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a delightful sight, wonderfully complementing {PAWN_possessive} youthful grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender appearance, are quite charming. They speak of natural beauty and youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a certain innocent appeal. Their perky shape is quite refreshing to witness.</li>
            <li>A truly pleasant observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, unassuming beauty. Their firm structure is admirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are perfectly placed.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite striking. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests youthful exuberance.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at youthful tenderness.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural appeal.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating. They possess a natural lift and a pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, adding to the overall perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young female, with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a delightful discovery, stirring a warmth deep within my loins.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts makes my old blood quicken, arousing a primal desire.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, small breasts to be incredibly tempting, awakening dormant passions.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, youthful breasts makes me feel a powerful surge of desire, a familiar ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so perfectly shaped, ignite a fire within me, a longing for touch.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unexpectedly erotic, arousing my senses immensely.</li>
            <li>There's a vibrant energy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that sparks an intense yearning in my body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my old member stir with undeniable urge.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the smooth skin of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a fantasy that makes my groin tingle.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making my old heart race.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes my trousers tighten.</li>
            <li>A captivating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are stimulating my deepest desires, a powerful sensation.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn for a closer look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing quite a stir below my belt.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making my old body respond.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly arousing my old desires.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting a familiar lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my aging body.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my old body hum with a delightful anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated urges.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel surprisingly virile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my old heart pound with excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful sensation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a tantalizing peek at youthful vitality, stirring something deep within me.</li>
            <li>Those delicate, small breasts almost make my old bones tingle with anticipation.</li>
            <li>Ah, the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky little breasts is certainly a stimulating one, even for an old man like me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts, so subtly alluring, truly awaken a forgotten fire.</li>
            <li>I find myself admiring {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts more than I should. My blood stirs.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts jiggle just slightly… it's quite captivating.</li>
            <li>Such tender, budding breasts! They remind me of days long past, and stir new urges.</li>
            <li>Those small, high-set breasts are utterly delicious to behold, a true feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>The gentle swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is surprisingly arousing.</li>
            <li>Her small, innocent breasts are surprisingly provocative. I feel a familiar stirring.</li>
            <li>I could watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, taut breasts all day, they're so enticing.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts only makes them more alluring. My old urges rise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm mounds are a delightful sight. Makes me wish I was younger.</li>
            <li>The hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples under those small breasts is exquisite.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts against my skin.</li>
            <li>Every subtle movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts draws my gaze irresistibly.</li>
            <li>Those small, high-set breasts... they're truly a work of art, and I feel a pull.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their perfectly formed areolas, are quite the vision.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, youthful breasts makes my old body feel a vibrant energy.</li>
            <li>The innocent curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts ignite a spark of desire within me.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find intensely appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their pert nipples, are absolutely captivating. My old desires surge.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the youth on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite beautiful, and rather stimulating.</li>
            <li>I relish the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts, a true delight for my experienced eyes.</li>
            <li>Those small, firm breasts are a testament to youthful vigor, and I feel my own masculinity stirred.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts, so perfectly formed, are enough to make my old heart pound.</li>
            <li>A truly enticing pair of small breasts, their youthful innocence only heightens my excitement.</li>
            <li>I find the subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts incredibly arousing, a gentle reminder of life's pleasures.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel a vitality, a keen interest in the curves of youth.</li>
			<li>Ah, those delicate, small breasts on {PAWN_nameShort}! Their youthful firmness and inviting shape are quite stimulating. My loins stir.</li>
            <li>A sudden, delightful view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest. Those perky, small breasts, with their defined nipples, are a captivating sight. My pulse quickens.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move hints at inner vitality. Such a captivating form, it truly stirs a primal appreciation within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, truly appeals to my senses. The way those small mounds sit firm is quite stimulating.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts, I feel a distinct warmth. Their youthful appearance and subtle contours are quite arousing.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, alluring pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their delicate features drawing my gaze. It ignites a pleasant sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are quite tantalizing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making me feel quite invigorated.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is quite arousing to witness.</li>
            <li>A truly exciting observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, sexuality. Their firm structure is quite stimulating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, beckoning my gaze.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably stimulating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that deeply moves me.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking a deep desire.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration mixed with undeniable arousal fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, and my body responds.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, stirring my senses.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, drawing me in.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent desire within me. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites me. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful desire they awaken. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and arousing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my body hums with anticipation. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel quite alive.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their flawless form and subtle hints of arousal within me are undeniable.</li>
            <li>A compelling sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so delicately shaped and firm. They ignite a deep, appreciative warmth within my aged frame.</li>
            <li>Such an inviting prospect, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their youthful and perky appearance is surprisingly stimulating, a true joy to observe.</li>
            <li>The modest yet perfectly defined curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are simply captivating. They stir a keen sense of appreciation and desire.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely, reminding me of my own youthful figure from long ago.</li>
            <li>Such delicate, firm breasts {PAWN_nameShort} possesses, a beautiful sight for a young woman.</li>
            <li>I recall having similar small breasts in my youth; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} look quite wonderful on {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly proportioned, a true testament to natural youthful beauty.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle elegance to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, a classic charm that never fades.</li>
            <li>The youthful perkiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is refreshing to see, a sign of vitality.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fit {PAWN_possessive} frame so well, a harmonious and pleasing shape.</li>
            <li>I admire the natural grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts; truly a lovely form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess an innocent allure, untouched by the ravages of time.</li>
            <li>They are small but perfectly formed, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly a delightful sight.</li>
            <li>The tender curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing, a delicate and feminine display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a beautiful example of youthful anatomy, well-suited to {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I see the quiet confidence in the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented; very appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to the beauty of simplicity and natural form.</li>
            <li>The modesty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them all the more charming and attractive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts have a certain sweetness, a gentle and unpretentious beauty.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful glow radiating from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, shapely breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their elegant lines, are truly a pleasure to behold.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples and areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly charming.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be beautifully formed, a work of natural art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so smooth and firm, are a wonderful example of youthful beauty.</li>
            <li>The youthful bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite endearing and natural.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a quiet dignity, a beauty that doesn't need to shout.</li>
            <li>I recognize the youthful perfection in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, truly a delightful sight.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly on {PAWN_possessive} chest is quite striking.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a refreshing sight, reminding me of the simple beauty of the human form.</li>
            <li>I see a reflection of graceful youth in the shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a picture of delicate strength, wonderfully appealing.</li>
            <li>The natural firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a lovely attribute, full of youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly suited to {PAWN_possessive} slender figure, a harmonious blend.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a charming sight, so well-formed.</li>
            <li>Such dainty breasts, perfectly suited for {PAWN_possessive} frame.</li>
            <li>I remember breasts like those, small and firm in youth. Quite lovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest has a natural elegance.</li>
            <li>A lovely pair of small breasts, a testament to youthful beauty.</li>
            <li>The youthful perkiness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite delightful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a sweet and innocent sight.</li>
            <li>There's a quiet charm in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, high-set breasts.</li>
            <li>The gentle curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is very endearing.</li>
            <li>How lovely to see such firm, small breasts on a young woman.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are a perfect fit, a graceful form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate chest is quite pretty, a sign of youth.</li>
            <li>Such unspoiled beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the natural grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite charming.</li>
            <li>A pleasant sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small and perfectly shaped breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, though small, possess a quiet dignity.</li>
            <li>The gentle uplift of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is very appealing.</li>
            <li>I recall a similar form in my youth, small and firm. Very nice.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly a vision of natural beauty.</li>
            <li>The dainty shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is quite captivating.</li>
            <li>A refreshing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle firmness, are quite lovely.</li>
            <li>There's a simple, elegant beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, with their delicate form and light-pink nipples, are quite becoming.</li>
            <li>The modest swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a lovely sight.</li>
            <li>I admire the youthful firmness and small, appealing shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, so neatly formed and high, are a charming feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtly defined areolas, possess a quiet grace.</li>
            <li>A truly elegant pair of small breasts, perfect in their proportions.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely; so youthful and firm, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} delicate frame. A charming sight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest, I recall the simple beauty of youth. Those small, shapely breasts are quite endearing.</li>
            <li>A sudden reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, they are quite pretty. Their natural form and firmness speak of unblemished vitality.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit, so naturally high and pert, is quite appealing. A lovely figure {PAWN_possessive} has.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly petite curves, is a vision of youthful grace. The small, defined nipples are a sweet detail.</li>
            <li>Small and perfectly formed, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are truly delightful. They possess a youthful bounce and a wonderful natural contour.</li>
            <li>A refined and delicate pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to youthful beauty, sitting elegantly on {PAWN_possessive} slender frame.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, appealing bust. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are exquisitely proportioned, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} overall elegance.</li>
            <li>The gentle swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite pleasing. They hold a youthful charm, a reminder of simpler, vibrant days.</li>
            <li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. They appear wonderfully firm and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender appearance, are quite charming. They speak of natural beauty and youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a certain innocent appeal. Their perky shape is quite refreshing to witness.</li>
            <li>A truly pleasant observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, unassuming beauty. Their firm structure is admirable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are perfectly placed.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite striking. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests youthful exuberance.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at youthful tenderness.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural appeal.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating. They possess a natural lift and a pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, adding to the overall perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Female voyer observes young female with nymphomaniac or perverted approach, can include own breasts mention or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)_Elderly_Female_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts ignite a flicker of old desires within me, reminiscent of my own youth.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, firm breasts stirs a forgotten longing, a warmth in my core.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts incredibly arousing, arousing the dormant fires of my own femininity.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, delicate breasts awakens a powerful sensuality I thought long gone.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly shaped breasts are a captivating vision, causing a delicious thrum in my loins.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sends shivers down my spine, arousing my senses immensely.</li>
            <li>There's a vibrant sensuality to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that sparks a deep, undeniable yearning in me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my own forgotten parts tingle with pleasure.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a tantalizing fantasy that makes my core ache.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making my old body yearn for contact.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes me feel surprisingly alive.</li>
            <li>A captivating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are stimulating my deepest desires, a powerful sensation.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn for a closer look.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing quite a stir within my old body.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making my own skin prickle.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly arousing my own desires.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting a familiar lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my aging body.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my old body hum with a delightful anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated urges.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel surprisingly virile.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my old heart pound with excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful sensation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a delightful sight, reminding me of my own youth, and the pleasures that came with it.</li>
            <li>Such charmingly small breasts! It makes me nostalgic, and a little bit hot.</li>
            <li>Oh, to have breasts that firm and perky again. The sight of {PAWN_possessive} makes me feel a certain warmth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, small breasts are quite captivating, almost making me wish for a taste of that youthful sensation.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts surprisingly stimulating, stirring old desires.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts bounce ever so slightly... it's truly a lovely sight, and I feel a familiar throbbing.</li>
            <li>Those tender, budding breasts are so enticing. Makes me remember what it felt like to be so fresh.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts are a vision of untouched beauty, and I can't help but stare.</li>
            <li>The subtle swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts ignites a certain spark within me.</li>
            <li>Her small, innocent breasts are surprisingly provocative. I feel my own womanhood responding.</li>
            <li>I could watch {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, taut breasts all day, they're so wonderfully formed.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts only makes them more alluring, a quiet promise.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm mounds are a delightful sight, bringing back memories of my own youthful vigor.</li>
            <li>The hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples under those small breasts is exquisite, a perfect detail.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts against my own.</li>
            <li>Every subtle movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts draws my gaze, my heart beating a little faster.</li>
            <li>Those small, high-set breasts... they're truly beautiful, and I feel a yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their perfectly formed areolas, are quite the vision.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, youthful breasts makes me feel a vibrant, almost forgotten energy.</li>
            <li>The innocent curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts ignite a powerful sense of desire within me.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find intensely appealing, arousing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their pert nipples, are absolutely captivating. A wave of heat washes over me.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the vitality of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite beautiful, and rather stimulating.</li>
            <li>I relish the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts, a true delight, awakening a sensual nostalgia.</li>
            <li>Those small, firm breasts are a testament to youthful vigor, and I feel a flush of warmth in my own body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts, so perfectly formed, are enough to make my old desires stir.</li>
            <li>A truly enticing pair of small breasts, their youthful innocence only heightens my excitement.</li>
            <li>I find the subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts incredibly arousing, a reminder of pure feminine allure.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel alive, a keen interest in the unblemished curves of youth.</li>
			<li>Oh, those perfectly formed small breasts on {PAWN_nameShort}! So firm and youthful, almost makes my own ache with a familiar longing.</li>
            <li>A delightful peek at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest. Those perky, small breasts, with their exquisite nipples, stir a surprising warmth within me.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts subtly bounce is quite captivating. Such a lovely figure, it makes me appreciate the simple beauty of a woman's form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is a true joy to behold. The way those small mounds sit firm ignites a shared sense of pleasure.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts, I feel a kindred spirit. Their youthful appearance and subtle contours are quite appealing, arousing a soft flutter.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, alluring pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their delicate features drawing my gaze. It brings a pleasant internal sigh.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are quite tantalizing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame; my own flesh tingles in response.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is quite arousing to witness, reminding me of my own youth.</li>
            <li>A truly exciting observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, sensuality. Their firm structure is quite stimulating to my senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, beckoning my thoughts.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably stimulating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that deeply moves me, and my inner self sighs.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking a deep, shared pleasure.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration mixed with undeniable arousal fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, and my own skin warms.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, and my body responds with a gentle ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, stirring my own dormant desires.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, drawing me into a pleasant reverie.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent desire within me. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry. My inner self yearns.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites me. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, arousing my own intimate memories.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful desire they awaken in my own being. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, leaving me wanting.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my own form feels a surge of energy.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and arousing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making me feel a deep, internal throb.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, and I feel a warmth spreading within.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my body hums with anticipation. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, and my own sensuality awakens.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art. My body responds with a pleasing tremor.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel quite alive and desiring.</li>
            <li>The smooth, delicate curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably alluring. A quiet pleasure arises within me, observing their perfect placement.</li>
            <li>A truly captivating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. They hold a gentle magnetism that subtly stirs my own desires.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exquisite, small breasts. Their youthful plumpness and inviting nipples bring a pleasant rush of warmth.</li>
            <li>Such an innocent yet powerfully appealing form. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to natural feminine beauty, and my own body responds in kind.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Young male observes young female, more based on sexual atraction, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are absolutely perfect, making my blood rush and my groin tighten.</li>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts are incredibly hot, making me hard just looking at them.</li>
            <li>I can't stop staring at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, firm breasts; they make my heart pound.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, small breasts is driving me wild, a powerful erection forming.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so perfectly shaped, are making me ache with desire.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts jiggle slightly is unbelievably sexy, sending shivers down my spine.</li>
            <li>There's an undeniable energy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that makes my entire body crave {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my dick throb with anticipation.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the smooth skin of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts under my hands, a fantasy that makes my balls ache.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making me incredibly horny.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes me want to grab and squeeze.</li>
            <li>A captivating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are stimulating my deepest desires, causing a powerful erection.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn to lick and tease them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing quite a bulge in my pants.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making my cock twitch.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful longing for intimacy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me hard.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an intense lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding satisfaction.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful yearning for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being hum with a delightful anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated urges to explore.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel incredibly aroused.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable physical reaction in my groin.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, carnal desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every nerve.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast to action.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming sensation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are absolutely perfect, I can't look away. My heart is racing.</li>
            <li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are driving me crazy. I'm getting hard just looking at them.</li>
            <li>Those perky little breasts on {PAWN_nameShort} are incredibly hot. My cock is twitching.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts are so alluring, they're making me so incredibly aroused.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts incredibly sexy. I wish I could touch them.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts jiggle slightly makes my mind race with dirty thoughts.</li>
            <li>Such tender, budding breasts! I want to suck on those nipples.</li>
            <li>Those small, high-set breasts are a sight to behold. I'm throbbing.</li>
            <li>The gentle swell of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is making my pants tighter.</li>
            <li>Her small, innocent breasts are surprisingly provocative. I can feel my blood pumping.</li>
            <li>I could stare at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, taut breasts all day, they're so damn enticing.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts only makes them hotter. I'm ready to explode.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm mounds are a delightful sight. Makes me want to strip {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nipples under those small breasts is exquisite. I want them in my mouth.</li>
            <li>I can almost feel the softness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts in my hands.</li>
            <li>Every subtle movement of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts draws my gaze. My dick is rock hard.</li>
            <li>Those small, high-set breasts... they're truly a work of art, and I'm aching for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their perfectly formed areolas, are quite the vision. I want to lick them.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, youthful breasts makes my whole body tingle with desire.</li>
            <li>The innocent curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts ignite a burning lust within me.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find intensely appealing. I'm getting so turned on.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their pert nipples, are absolutely captivating. I can barely breathe.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the sweetness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>The delicate shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite beautiful, and incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>I relish the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts, a true delight for my eyes and my hungry hands.</li>
            <li>Those small, firm breasts are a testament to youthful vigor, and I feel my own masculinity surging.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest breasts, so perfectly formed, are enough to make me lose control.</li>
            <li>A truly enticing pair of small breasts, their youthful innocence only heightens my excitement. I need to be closer.</li>
            <li>I find the subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts incredibly arousing, a direct hit to my primal urges.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel a powerful urge to claim {PAWN_objective}.</li>
			<li>Damn, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are surprisingly hot. That firm, perky shape and those tantalizing nipples are driving me wild.</li>
            <li>A sudden, breathtaking view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest. Those small, firm breasts are incredibly alluring. I can feel myself hardening.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move is so damn captivating. Such a tight, enticing form; it makes my cock throb.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is incredibly appealing. The way those small mounds sit firm is seriously stimulating. My pants are getting tight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts, I feel a powerful rush of desire. Their youthful appearance and subtle contours are so arousing.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, incredibly sexy pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their delicate features drawing my gaze. It ignites a fiery sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly tantalizing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making my groin twitch.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is unbelievably arousing to witness, making me desperate.</li>
            <li>A truly exciting observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, sexuality. Their firm structure is intensely stimulating. My erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, making me imagine things.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably stimulating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that deeply moves my body.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense erection.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration mixed with undeniable arousal fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, and my cock stiffens.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, and my groin pulsates.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, stirring my intense lust.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, drawing me into a feverish state.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent desire within me. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites me profoundly. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful desire they awaken. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me want to claim them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection and making my blood boil.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my desire grows.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and arousing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making my groin tingle.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, and I feel a powerful surge.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my body hums with anticipation. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, and my erection strains.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art. My body responds with an urgent need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel quite alive and ready to burst.</li>
            <li>The tantalizing glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has set my blood afire. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful urge.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, primal attraction.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate for more.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes young female -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The subtle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is captivating, a truly engrossing sight.</li>
            <li>I find the delicate shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts incredibly appealing to observe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts are a visual delight, holding my gaze intently.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step is mesmerizing.</li>
            <li>There's a quiet charm in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find intensely satisfying to watch.</li>
            <li>Observing the youthful firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly a pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so naturally formed, are a beautiful sight to behold.</li>
            <li>I could watch the gentle movements of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts all day.</li>
            <li>The smooth, unbroken line of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is aesthetically pleasing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a perfect example of understated beauty, drawing my eyes.</li>
            <li>I am fascinated by the exquisite detailing of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small nipples and areolas.</li>
            <li>The subtle shadow play on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly artistic and captivating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender curves, are a joy to witness.</li>
            <li>There's a purity in the form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that keeps my attention.</li>
            <li>The delightful symmetry of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly remarkable to observe.</li>
            <li>I am enthralled by the natural, unadorned beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The delicate bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts as {PAWN_pronoun} walks is subtly hypnotic.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly round, are a testament to natural perfection.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the graceful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a delightful study.</li>
            <li>I find a deep satisfaction in simply observing the natural presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The way light plays across {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts reveals their subtle intricacies.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful centerpiece, capturing my entire focus.</li>
            <li>I am endlessly intrigued by the unique characteristics of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, unburdened, is profoundly liberating to witness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a quiet allure that demands prolonged appreciation.</li>
            <li>I find the anatomical precision of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fascinating to observe.</li>
            <li>The subtle pulse of life within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is captivating to my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, firm and inviting, are a truly wonderful sight to behold.</li>
            <li>There's an undeniable artistry in the natural presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>My gaze lingers on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, appreciating their delicate form and inherent beauty.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a captivating sight, I can't tear my eyes away.</li>
            <li>Such perfect small breasts, I could stare at them all day.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them incredibly intriguing.</li>
            <li>I find myself drawn to the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly a pleasure, a subtle and elegant vision.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is mesmerizing to watch.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find intensely appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe.</li>
			<li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their firm, youthful shape and delicate features are truly a treat for the eyes.</li>
            <li>The sudden revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is quite captivating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty.</li>
            <li>I find myself utterly absorbed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to observe.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply mesmerizing. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense appreciation.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager to continue observing. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed.</li>
            <li>The flawless contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are simply captivating. A true artistic marvel in their delicate perfection.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite details of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their firm and graceful form is a sight to behold.</li>
            <li>Such a delightful vision: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly sculpted and wonderfully perky. They are a treasure to observe.</li>
            <li>The subtle undulations of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are profoundly beautiful. A truly mesmerizing and understated display of charm.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts is electrifying, making my groin tingle intensely.</li>
            <li>I can't tear my eyes from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts; they're making me hard.</li>
            <li>Observing the subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly arousing, causing my member to stir.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, delicate breasts are a vision that makes my blood race with carnal desire.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are naturally presented is unbelievably sexy, igniting a deep hunger within me.</li>
            <li>I am captivated by the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, making my pants feel tight.</li>
            <li>There's a raw, youthful appeal to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that has my entire body responding.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts are a tantalizing sight, making me ache for a closer encounter.</li>
            <li>My gaze is fixated on the beautiful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, causing an undeniable physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making my dick throb with anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly proportioned, are a sight that makes me want to ravish {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exciting every fiber of my being.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a powerful, undeniable erection.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me fantasize about their taste.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully defined, are causing a delicious ache in my loins.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making my cock twitch with desire.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful, primal longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me incredibly aroused.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an insatiable lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding satisfaction.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful yearning for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being hum with a delightful, urgent anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated urges to explore every inch.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel an overwhelming desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable, throbbing physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, almost unbearable desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every nerve ending.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating, almost painful excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast to immediate action.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming, and irresistible sensation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly hot. I can feel myself getting hard.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off those perfect small breasts. My cock is throbbing.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them even more enticing. I'm so turned on.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly captivated by the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. I need to relieve myself.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a massive pleasure, I'm bursting with lust.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is intensely arousing. My dick is rock hard.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find irresistibly appealing. I'm so stiff.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight that makes me ache.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they make me want to reach out.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat, making my blood rush.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art that I want to defile.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. It’s so damn hot.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable, stirring me deeply.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. My member demands attention.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. My loins are burning.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I can barely control myself.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating and incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight that makes me envision wicked things.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. It's making me so hard.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. I want to feel them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view, making me moan.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts, my hand on my shaft.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. I'm about to burst.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My groin is aching.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I'm sweating from the desire.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, utterly consumed.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece, and I'm throbbing.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I must have them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. My erection is painful.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe, and my mind fills with depraved thoughts.</li>
			<li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their firm, youthful shape and delicate features are truly a treat for my voyeuristic eyes. My loins stir.</li>
            <li>The sudden revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is quite captivating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty, and my cock responds.</li>
            <li>I find myself utterly absorbed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to observe, making me throb.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply mesmerizing. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, inciting my arousal.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, making me harden.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze. I feel a powerful urge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle that excites me.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, quickening my pulse.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, stimulating my senses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that makes me want more.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for my eyes, and my groin tingles.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense erection.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes me tremble.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, and my body responds.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that excites my every nerve.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, drawing me in completely.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me ache with desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, intensifying my arousal.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me want to devour them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, leaving me breathless.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager to continue observing. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my cock aches.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making my senses reel.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, and I can feel my erection straining.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, and I feel a powerful, primal pull.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze and my urgent desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and ready.</li>
            <li>The tantalizing glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has set my blood afire, a voyeur's dream. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease, making me ache for more.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful, hungry urge.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, primal attraction that I cannot deny.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate for a closer, more intimate look.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young female with nymphomaniac approach, can include own breats reaction mention or own genitail vagina reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts is incredibly arousing, making my own nipples harden.</li>
            <li>I can't stop observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts; they stir a delicious warmth in my core.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly sensual, causing a delightful throb between my legs.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, delicate breasts are a vision that awakens a powerful, familiar yearning within me.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are naturally presented is unbelievably alluring, igniting a deep hunger in my own body.</li>
            <li>I am captivated by the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, making my clitoris tingle with anticipation.</li>
            <li>There's a raw, youthful appeal to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that has my entire body responding with pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, round breasts are a tantalizing sight, making my own vulva moist with desire.</li>
            <li>My gaze is fixated on the beautiful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, causing an undeniable physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making my core hum with delicious excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly proportioned, are a sight that makes me want to touch my own.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exciting every nerve ending in my feminine body.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound, delicious sensation.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn for their soft feel.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully defined, are causing a delicious ache throughout my feminine parts.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making my own breasts swell with desire.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful, sensual longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me intensely aroused.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an insatiable, feminine lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding intimate exploration.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful yearning for sensual connection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being hum with a delightful, urgent anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated urges within my femininity.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel an overwhelming desire for touch.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable, throbbing physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, almost unbearable feminine desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every feminine nerve ending.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating, almost painful excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner feminine beast to immediate action.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming, and irresistible sensation.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so sweet and perfectly formed. I feel a delightful warmth spreading through me.</li>
            <li>I could spend all day admiring those perfect small breasts. They make my own feel a little tingly.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them incredibly appealing. It sparks a certain excitement within me.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly captivated by the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. I feel a delightful ache between my legs.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a profound pleasure, stirring deep sensations.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is intensely arousing. My own nipples harden in response.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find irresistibly appealing. A delicious tension builds.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight that makes me feel a powerful yearning.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they make me feel so vibrant and alive.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat, sending shivers down my spine.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art that I want to explore with my touch.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. It’s so damn enticing.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable, stirring a deep hunger within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. My inner desires awaken.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. My core feels a deep thrumming.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I can barely contain my eagerness.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating and incredibly stimulating. My clitoris tingles.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight that makes me imagine delicious intimacies.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. It's making me quiver.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. I long to feel their delicate texture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view, making me sigh with pleasure.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts, my fingers tracing invisible lines.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. My body hums with anticipation.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My passion ignites.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I'm flushed with desire.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, utterly consumed by their beauty.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece, and I'm throbbing for them.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I must explore every inch.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. My lust is insatiable.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe, filling my mind with forbidden thoughts.</li>
			<li>A delightful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their firm, youthful shape and delicate features are truly a treat for my voyeuristic eyes, making my own body hum.</li>
            <li>The sudden revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is quite captivating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty, and my core tingles in response.</li>
            <li>I find myself utterly absorbed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to observe, arousing a kindred spirit within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply mesmerizing. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, inciting a pleasant warmth in my own depths.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, making me feel a soft flutter.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze. I feel a shared, delightful sensation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle that makes my own breasts ache sweetly.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, quickening my inner pulse.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, stimulating my senses in a familiar way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that makes me want to touch my own.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for my eyes, and my core feels a gentle pressure.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, shared pleasure.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes my own breasts feel full.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, and my vagina pulses softly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that excites my every feminine nerve.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, drawing me into a delightful reverie.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making my body ache with a pleasant yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, intensifying my own intimate desires.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me want to explore my own sensuality.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, making my breath catch.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager to continue observing. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my inner core responds with warmth.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making my senses reel with pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, and I can feel my own womanhood stir.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, and I feel a powerful, shared longing.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze and my urgent, feminine desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and deeply appreciative.</li>
            <li>The tantalizing glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has awakened a gentle fire within me, a voyeur's delight. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease, making my own body yearn.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful, knowing urge.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, primal attraction that resonates within my own being.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate for a closer, more intimate look, feeling a deep connection.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a lovely sight, inspiring me to reveal my own beauty.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, petite breasts! It makes me want to show off my own well-formed anatomy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so charming; I feel a strong urge to expose myself too.</li>
            <li>The natural display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly liberating, making me eager to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the confidence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; it encourages my own exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly formed, are a wonderful example of what should be celebrated openly.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me want to move freely and reveal my own body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight, prompting me to consider how well my own body would be received.</li>
            <li>There's a contagious openness in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, making me feel the need to undress.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so natural and unashamed, are empowering my own desire for exhibition.</li>
            <li>The delicate contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are inspiring, making me want to share my own anatomy.</li>
            <li>I feel a kinship with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} for showcasing {PAWN_possessive} small breasts so freely; it calls to me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to natural beauty, making me eager to present my own body for appreciation.</li>
            <li>The confident display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is admirable; it gives me courage to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so simply beautiful, are a wonderful invitation to shed inhibitions.</li>
            <li>I find the unabashed presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts quite stimulating, urging me to expose myself.</li>
            <li>The playful nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is delightful; I feel compelled to join in the display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a vision of natural pride, strengthening my own exhibitionist spirit.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong sense of solidarity seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts revealed; it's a call to arms for exhibitionists.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly contoured, are a reminder of the beauty of the exposed human form.</li>
            <li>The delightful sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts encourages me to embrace my own desire to be seen.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly captivating, making me feel a powerful urge to reveal my own assets.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy in the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that makes me want to undress instantly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are an inspiration, fueling my deepest exhibitionist fantasies.</li>
            <li>The casual exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly appealing, reinforcing my own exhibitionist nature.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming desire to mirror {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display of small breasts with my own nakedness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable charm, are beckoning me to step into the light, exposed.</li>
            <li>The delightful curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clear signal to let my own body be admired.</li>
            <li>I am deeply moved by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, compelling me to join the ranks of the exposed.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a perfect example of how the human form should be celebrated, openly and proudly.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely. I should show off mine too!</li>
            <li>Such delightful small breasts! They make me want to reveal everything.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is charming. Perhaps {PAWN_pronoun} would appreciate my own exposure.</li>
            <li>I admire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. This gives me a thrill to be seen as well.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel an urge to shed my own inhibitions.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is inspiring. I feel like showing myself off now.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find very appealing. I wonder if {PAWN_objective} would enjoy my display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight. It makes me want to put on a show.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Time to let it all hang out!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat. Now, where’s my spotlight?</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art. And so is my body, meant to be admired.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. This inspires my own exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable. I feel a powerful urge to strip down.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. I bet my own reveal would be just as thrilling.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. It fuels my desire to be watched.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is my cue to display myself.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating. I want to perform for {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight. It only makes me want to bare myself even more.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is exactly what inspires me to be seen.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. It’s a call to exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view. This fuels my own need for exposure.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts. It makes me feel empowered to show my own.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. What a perfect moment to reveal my own beauty.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I must show off my own endowments.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I feel a grand entrance coming on.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My urge to display is immense.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece. It inspires my own public display.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire to be admired surges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel the thrill of potential exposure.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe. It ignites my need for attention.</li>
			<li>How wonderfully bold to display such delicate, small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape is truly a delightful spectacle for all to admire.</li>
            <li>The sudden, striking reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is exhilarating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty, meant to be seen.</li>
            <li>I'm thrilled by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to witness, openly and unashamedly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply captivating. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing a shared appreciation for public display.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, especially when revealed.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze, a testament to uninhibited beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle that invites all eyes.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, especially when openly presented.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, in all their uncovered glory.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that begs to be seen.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for all eyes.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, open appreciation.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight for public enjoyment.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, freely offered.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view, especially without hindrance.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, for all to admire.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for appreciation.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke when exposed. They embody a sweet, innocent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, openly displayed.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more such displays. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, in plain sight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for all to see.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, openly shared.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze, and all others'.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed by the open display.</li>
            <li>The uninhibited view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is utterly delightful. Their graceful form is a bold and beautiful statement.</li>
            <li>Such courageous beauty! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a captivating sight, openly inviting admiration.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exposed perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their youthful plumpness and inviting nipples are a public marvel.</li>
            <li>A truly liberating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so naturally alluring and proudly presented, are a joy to witness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young female, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a lovely sight, making me want to unveil my own impressive anatomy.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, petite breasts! It makes me want to show off my own magnificent member.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so charming; I feel a strong urge to expose my own engorged shaft.</li>
            <li>The natural display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly liberating, making me eager to reveal my own throbbing cock.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the confidence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; it encourages my own exhibitionist desires to flaunt my girth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly formed, are a wonderful example of what should be celebrated openly, just like my own.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me want to move freely and reveal my own proud erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight, prompting me to consider how well my own stiff member would be received.</li>
            <li>There's a contagious openness in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, making me feel the need to drop my pants.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so natural and unashamed, are empowering my own desire to display my large cock.</li>
            <li>The delicate contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are inspiring, making me want to share my own throbbing penis.</li>
            <li>I feel a kinship with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} for showcasing {PAWN_possessive} small breasts so freely; it calls to my own exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to natural beauty, making me eager to present my own stiff shaft for appreciation.</li>
            <li>The confident display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is admirable; it gives me courage to reveal my hard-on.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so simply beautiful, are a wonderful invitation to shed inhibitions and expose my engorged organ.</li>
            <li>I find the unabashed presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts quite stimulating, urging me to expose my impressive size.</li>
            <li>The playful nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is delightful; I feel compelled to join in the display with my own cock.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a vision of natural pride, strengthening my own exhibitionist spirit to bare my penis.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong sense of solidarity seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts revealed; it's a call to arms for me to expose my girth.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly contoured, are a reminder of the beauty of the exposed human form, especially my own.</li>
            <li>The delightful sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts encourages me to embrace my own desire to show off my manhood.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly captivating, making me feel a powerful urge to reveal my own assets, especially my stiff cock.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy in the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that makes me want to drop my pants instantly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are an inspiration, fueling my deepest exhibitionist fantasies involving my own genitals.</li>
            <li>The casual exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly appealing, reinforcing my own exhibitionist nature to bare all.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming desire to mirror {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display of small breasts with my own nakedness, especially my privates.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable charm, are beckoning me to step into the light, exposed with my erection.</li>
            <li>The delightful curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clear signal to let my own body be admired, specifically my powerful member.</li>
            <li>I am deeply moved by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, compelling me to join the ranks of the exposed, with my own genitals on display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a perfect example of how the human form should be celebrated, openly and proudly, just like my own impressive organ.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely. I should show off my own cock now!</li>
            <li>Such delightful small breasts! They make me want to let my member free.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is charming. Perhaps {PAWN_pronoun} would appreciate a glimpse of my throbbing shaft.</li>
            <li>I admire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. This gives me a thrill to display my own package.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel an urge to expose my powerful masculinity.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is inspiring. I feel like dropping my pants now.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find very appealing. I wonder if {PAWN_objective} would enjoy my erection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight. It makes me want to put on a show with my cock out.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Time to let my impressive member hang out!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat. Now, where’s the audience for my penis?</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art. And so is my body, meant to be admired, especially my hard cock.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. This inspires my own exhibitionism, for all to see.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable. I feel a powerful urge to strip down and show my cock.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. I bet my own reveal would be just as thrilling, especially my raging erection.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. It fuels my desire to be watched, specifically my throbbing shaft.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is my cue to display my magnificent member.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating. I want to perform for {PAWN_objective} with my cock swinging.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight. It only makes me want to bare myself even more, especially my impressive package.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is exactly what inspires me to expose my powerful penis.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. It’s a call to exhibitionism, a call to unveil my hard shaft.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view. This fuels my own need for exposure, my cock at the ready.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts. It makes me feel empowered to show off my massive cock.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. What a perfect moment to reveal my own beauty, and my stiff rod.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I must show off my own magnificent member.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I feel a grand entrance coming on, with my cock leading the way.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My urge to display my powerful cock is immense.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece. It inspires my own public display of my erection.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire to be admired, along with my throbbing penis, surges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel the thrill of potential exposure, my cock twitching.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe. It ignites my need for attention, and my need to reveal my huge dick.</li>
			<li>How wonderfully bold to display such delicate, small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape is truly a delightful spectacle for my eager eyes. My cock salutes the view.</li>
            <li>The sudden, striking reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is exhilarating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty, and I can feel myself swelling in appreciation.</li>
            <li>I'm thrilled by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to witness, openly and unashamedly, making my shaft harden.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply captivating. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing a shared appreciation for public display, and my balls ache.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, especially when revealed, setting my groin afire.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze, a testament to uninhibited beauty, and my erection strains.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle that invites all eyes, and my cock pulsates.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, especially when openly presented, making me eager to reveal myself.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, in all their uncovered glory, and my libido surges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that begs to be seen, and my penis feels alive.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for all eyes, and my cock responds.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, open appreciation, and my desire is overwhelming.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight for public enjoyment, and my groin tightens.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, freely offered, and my balls ache with pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view, especially without hindrance, and I feel a powerful urge.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, for all to admire, and my cock stiffens further.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me want to show myself too.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for appreciation, causing my own body to react.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke when exposed. They embody a sweet, innocent grace, and my penis is fully erect.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, openly displayed, and my cock throbs.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more such displays. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my desire is insatiable.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, in plain sight, and I'm bursting with excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for all to see, and I feel a powerful urge to expose myself.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, openly shared, and my arousal is intense.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze, and all others', making my penis strain.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed by the open display, and my member pulses with desire.</li>
            <li>The uninhibited view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is utterly delightful. Their graceful form is a bold and beautiful statement, mirroring my own exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>Such courageous beauty! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a captivating sight, openly inviting admiration, and I feel a shared thrill of exposure.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exposed perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their youthful plumpness and inviting nipples are a public marvel, and I want to join the display.</li>
            <li>A truly liberating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so naturally alluring and proudly presented, are a joy to witness, and I feel a strong desire to display my own body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young female, can include own breats mention, own genitail mentionor, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are lovely, making me want to unveil my own equally delightful form.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, petite breasts! It makes me want to show off my own perfectly shaped anatomy and moist pussy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so charming; I feel a strong urge to expose my own soft curves and glistening labia.</li>
            <li>The natural display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly liberating, making me eager to reveal my own luscious lips.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the confidence in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; it encourages my own exhibitionist desires to flaunt my breasts and vulva.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly formed, are a wonderful example of what should be celebrated openly, just like my own.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me want to move freely and reveal my own captivating bust and plump mound.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight, prompting me to consider how well my own soft breasts and wet pussy would be received.</li>
            <li>There's a contagious openness in seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, making me feel the need to strip bare.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so natural and unashamed, are empowering my own desire to display my ample cleavage and inviting sex.</li>
            <li>The delicate contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are inspiring, making me want to share my own tender nipples and welcoming folds.</li>
            <li>I feel a kinship with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} for showcasing {PAWN_possessive} small breasts so freely; it calls to my own exhibitionism for my pussy.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a testament to natural beauty, making me eager to present my own firm breasts and inviting vulva for appreciation.</li>
            <li>The confident display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is admirable; it gives me courage to reveal my own tempting mound.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so simply beautiful, are a wonderful invitation to shed inhibitions and expose my own moist slit.</li>
            <li>I find the unabashed presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts quite stimulating, urging me to expose my own sweet nectar.</li>
            <li>The playful nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is delightful; I feel compelled to join in the display with my own breasts and moist parts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a vision of natural pride, strengthening my own exhibitionist spirit to bare my feminine self.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong sense of solidarity seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts revealed; it's a call to arms for me to expose my inner folds.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so perfectly contoured, are a reminder of the beauty of the exposed human form, especially my own.</li>
            <li>The delightful sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts encourages me to embrace my own desire to show off my femininity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly captivating, making me feel a powerful urge to reveal my own assets, especially my wetness.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy in the presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that makes me want to undress instantly and feel my own clit throb.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are an inspiration, fueling my deepest exhibitionist fantasies involving my own eager body.</li>
            <li>The casual exposure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly appealing, reinforcing my own exhibitionist nature to bare all and feel my own warmth.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming desire to mirror {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} display of small breasts with my own nakedness, feeling my own throbbing desires.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable charm, are beckoning me to step into the light, exposed and feeling my inner wetness.</li>
            <li>The delightful curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a clear signal to let my own body be admired, specifically my eager pussy.</li>
            <li>I am deeply moved by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, compelling me to join the ranks of the exposed, with my own luscious self on display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a perfect example of how the human form should be celebrated, openly and proudly, just like my own inviting body.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely. They make me want to show off my own.</li>
            <li>Such delightful small breasts! They make me want to reveal my own feminine charms.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is charming. Perhaps {PAWN_pronoun} would appreciate a glimpse of my own proud chest.</li>
            <li>I admire {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. This gives me a thrill to display my own.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes me feel an urge to shed my own inhibitions, to show my body freely.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is inspiring. I feel like baring my chest now.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find very appealing. I wonder if {PAWN_objective} would enjoy my own reveal.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight. It makes me want to put on a show with my own cleavage.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Time to let my own glorious form be seen!</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts is quite a treat. Now, where’s the audience for my nakedness?</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art. And so is my body, meant to be admired, especially my own breasts.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. This inspires my own exhibitionism, for all to see.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable. I feel a powerful urge to strip down and show my own.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. I bet my own reveal would be just as thrilling, especially my own firm breasts.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. It fuels my desire to be watched, specifically my own beautiful body.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is my cue to display my magnificent form.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating. I want to perform for {PAWN_objective} with my breasts exposed.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight. It only makes me want to bare myself even more, especially my impressive chest.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. This is exactly what inspires me to expose my feminine beauty.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. It’s a call to exhibitionism, a call to unveil my natural figure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view. This fuels my own need for exposure, my body at the ready.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts. It makes me feel empowered to show off my own glorious body.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. What a perfect moment to reveal my own beauty, and my firm breasts.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I must show off my own magnificent breasts.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I feel a grand entrance coming on, with my bare chest leading the way.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My urge to display my powerful form is immense.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece. It inspires my own public display of my femininity.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire to be admired, along with my own beautiful body, surges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel the thrill of potential exposure, my body tingling.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe. It ignites my need for attention, and my need to reveal my lovely breasts.</li>
			<li>How wonderfully bold to display such delicate, small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape is truly a delightful spectacle for my eager eyes, and I feel a shared thrill in my own chest.</li>
            <li>The sudden, striking reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is exhilarating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of natural beauty, and I can feel my own nipples harden in solidarity.</li>
            <li>I'm thrilled by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to witness, openly and unashamedly, making my core tingle with shared excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply captivating. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing a shared appreciation for public display, and my vulva twitches.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, especially when revealed, setting my own desires alight.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my unwavering gaze, a testament to uninhibited beauty, and I feel a surge of power.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle that invites all eyes, and my own breasts feel full.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, especially when openly presented, making me eager to display my own body.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, in all their uncovered glory, and my sensuality ignites.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that begs to be seen, and my vagina pulses with a shared desire.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for all eyes, and my own body aches to be seen.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, open appreciation, and I feel a kinship in exhibitionism.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight for public enjoyment, and my own desires stir strongly.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, freely offered, and my feminine parts hum with excitement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view, especially without hindrance, and I want to revel in the open air too.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, for all to admire, and I feel a surge of confident pleasure.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me feel empowered by their openness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for appreciation, and I feel a powerful, shared thrill.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke when exposed. They embody a sweet, innocent grace, and I feel a deep connection to their freedom.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, openly displayed, and my own core aches with longing.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more such displays. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my own body feels a delicious thrill.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, in plain sight, and I feel a profound sense of shared liberation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for all to see, and my own body craves similar exposure.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, openly shared, and I feel an exhilarating sense of freedom.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gaze, and all others', making my femininity sing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed by the open display, and I want to join them.</li>
            <li>The uninhibited view of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is utterly delightful. Their graceful form is a bold and beautiful statement, inspiring me to celebrate my own body.</li>
            <li>Such courageous beauty! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a captivating sight, openly inviting admiration, and I feel a powerful, shared sense of pride.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exposed perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their youthful plumpness and inviting nipples are a public marvel, sparking a desire to show my own.</li>
            <li>A truly liberating sight! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so naturally alluring and proudly presented, are a joy to witness, and I feel a deep connection to their unbridled display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are utterly captivating, making my whole body tingle with desire.</li>
            <li>I can't get enough of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts; they are driving me absolutely wild.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, firm breasts ignites an insatiable hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, small breasts is profoundly arousing, making me ache for contact.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so perfectly shaped, are triggering a powerful, unstoppable urge within me.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unbelievably erotic, making my senses go into overdrive.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that sparks an intense, all-consuming yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my core hum with an urgent desire.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the sweetness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a fantasy that makes my entire body crave.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making me feel incredibly horny and ready.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes me want to grab, lick, and suck them.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exciting every nerve in my sex-starved body.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound, delicious physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn to tease them endlessly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing an unbearable ache throughout my whole being.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making me desperate for physical release.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful, uncontrollable longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me feel out of control with lust.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an insatiable, burning desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding immediate satisfaction.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being throb with a delightful, urgent anticipation.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated, desperate urges for intimacy.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel an overwhelming, primal craving.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable, throbbing physical reaction.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, almost unbearable desires.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every lustful nerve.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating, almost painful excitement.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast to immediate, intense action.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming, and irresistible sensation that demands release.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so incredibly hot. I'm throbbing just looking at them.</li>
            <li>I'm overcome with desire staring at those perfect small breasts.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them intensely arousing. I can barely contain myself.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly consumed by the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. I need to be touched.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fills me with an insatiable hunger.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is driving me absolutely wild.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find maddeningly appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight that makes me ache for intimacy.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I want them against me.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts sends shivers of pure lust down my spine.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art that I desperately want to ravish.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. It’s so incredibly sexy.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable, stirring every sensual nerve in my body.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. My entire being yearns for release.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. My loins are on fire.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I'm about to explode with desire.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating and incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight that makes me envision wicked pleasures.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. It's making me intensely horny.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. I'm ready to surrender to my urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view, making me moan with suppressed passion.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts, my body writhing with desire.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. I'm desperate for contact.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My entire being screams for satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I'm flushed and aching.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, utterly consumed by lust.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece, and I'm ready to pounce.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire is boundless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel an overwhelming need.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe, filling my mind with carnal thoughts.</li>
			<li>Oh, such deliciously delicate small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape and tantalizing nipples are driving my desires to a fever pitch.</li>
            <li>The sudden, intoxicating revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is overwhelmingly stimulating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of pure arousal.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such sensual freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to behold, igniting a powerful hunger within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply irresistible. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing an almost unbearable craving.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound, carnal pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, making me tremble with anticipation.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, utterly stimulating pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my frantic gaze. I'm throbbing with need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting and deeply arousing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for an intensely captivating spectacle.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure that sends shivers through me. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, making me desperate for touch.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profoundly potent, sexuality. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, stirring an insatiable hunger.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that promises untold pleasure.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating and intensely arousing. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a torment of desire.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossiness} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, undeniable lust.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes my core clench.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece that makes me ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that electrifies my whole being.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, drawing me deeper into lust.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me pant with need.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for my hungry eyes.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me ravenous.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, driving me insane with desire.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my entire body vibrates with longing.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making me burn with passion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for which I crave desperately.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, for which I hunger.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my insatiable gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and consumed by lust.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has set my soul afire. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease, making me ache with unbearable desire.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful, primal hunger.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, all-consuming attraction that demands satisfaction.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate to claim them and indulge my nymphomaniacal urges.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are utterly captivating, making my cock stand rigidly at attention.</li>
            <li>I can't get enough of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts; they are making my dick throb uncontrollably.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, firm breasts ignites an insatiable hunger, making me hard and desperate.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, small breasts is profoundly arousing, causing a powerful erection to surge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so perfectly shaped, are triggering a powerful, unstoppable urge in my groin.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unbelievably erotic, making my entire cock twitch with lust.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that sparks an intense, all-consuming longing for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my shaft hum with an urgent desire for penetration.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the sweetness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a fantasy that makes my balls ache.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making me incredibly horny and ready to mount {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes me want to grab, lick, and suck them until I burst.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exciting every nerve in my sex-starved body, especially my cock.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound, delicious physical reaction and a huge erection.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn to tease them endlessly with my tongue.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing an unbearable ache throughout my entire cock and balls.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making me desperate for immediate, forceful release.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful, uncontrollable longing for carnal interaction.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me feel out of control with lust, my cock demanding attention.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an insatiable, burning desire that radiates from my groin.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding immediate, forceful satisfaction for my throbbing cock.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming yearning that makes my pants tight.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being throb with a delightful, urgent anticipation of sexual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated, desperate urges for intimacy with {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel an overwhelming, primal craving that makes my member salute.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable, throbbing physical reaction that only sex can cure.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, almost unbearable desires that make my cock jump.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every lustful nerve, especially around my genitals.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating, almost painful excitement that makes my cock rock hard.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast to immediate, intense action, ready to penetrate.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming, and irresistible sensation that demands immediate, full release.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so incredibly hot. My cock is throbbing uncontrollably.</li>
            <li>I'm overcome with desire staring at those perfect small breasts. I need to plunge myself into someone.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them intensely arousing. My erection is painful.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly consumed by the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. My balls ache.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fills me with an insatiable hunger. I'm ready to breed.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is driving me absolutely wild. My member is rock hard.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find maddeningly appealing. My shaft is twitching.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight that makes me ache for immediate release.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I want to feel their delicate weight in my hands while I pump.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts sends shivers of pure lust down my spine. I'm about to burst.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art that I desperately want to plunge myself between.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. It’s so incredibly sexy, my dick is demanding attention.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable, stirring every sensual nerve in my body. I'm ready to explode.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. My entire being yearns for penetration.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. My loins are on fire, my cock is primed.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I'm about to unload.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating and incredibly stimulating. My erection is unbearable.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight that makes me envision wicked sexual acts.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. It's making my dick intensely horny.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. I'm ready to surrender to my urges and empty my balls.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view, making me moan with suppressed passion. I need release.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts, my body shaking with desire. My cock needs a home.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. I'm desperate for sexual contact.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My entire being screams for carnal satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I'm flushed and aching for a deep thrust.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, utterly consumed by lust. My groin is pulsating.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece, and I'm ready to pound.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire for sexual release is boundless.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel an overwhelming need to thrust.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe, filling my mind with raw, primal urges and the need to explode.</li>
			<li>Oh, such deliciously delicate small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape and tantalizing nipples are driving my desires to a fever pitch. My cock is throbbing.</li>
            <li>The sudden, intoxicating revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is overwhelmingly stimulating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of pure arousal, making my pants tight.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such sensual freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to behold, igniting a powerful hunger within me, and my balls ache.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply irresistible. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing an almost unbearable craving, and my penis strains.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound, carnal pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, making me tremble with anticipation and a growing erection.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, utterly stimulating pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my frantic gaze. I'm throbbing with need, desperate for release.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting and deeply arousing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for an intensely captivating spectacle, and my cock aches.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure that sends shivers through me. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, making me desperate for touch and penetration.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profoundly potent, sexuality. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, stirring an insatiable hunger, and my erection is undeniable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that promises untold pleasure, making my groin tingle.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating and intensely arousing. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a torment of desire, and my cock twitches uncontrollably.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, undeniable lust, and I can barely contain myself.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes my core clench with desire.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece that makes me ache for them, my erection solid.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that electrifies my whole being, and my cock demands satisfaction.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, drawing me deeper into lust, and my desire is overwhelming.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me pant with need, my penis bursting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for my hungry eyes, causing my cock to throb painfully.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me ravenous, my entire body craving them.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, driving me insane with desire, my erection straining against my clothes.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my entire body vibrates with longing, my groin aching.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making me burn with passion, my cock ready to explode.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for which I crave desperately, my manhood hard and yearning.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, for which I hunger, feeling a powerful rush.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my insatiable gaze, and my cock twitches with anticipation.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and consumed by lust, my erection insistent.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has set my soul afire. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease, making me ache with unbearable desire, and my groin feels heavy.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful, primal hunger, my erection throbbing painfully.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, all-consuming attraction that demands satisfaction, my cock unyielding.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate to claim them and indulge my nymphomaniacal urges, and my climax feels imminent.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young female, may include own breats reaction  mention, or own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are utterly captivating, making my own sensitive nipples harden in response.</li>
            <li>I can't get enough of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perky, small breasts; they're making my clitoris throb uncontrollably.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate, firm breasts ignites an insatiable hunger, making my pussy wet and desperate.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful, small breasts is profoundly arousing, causing a powerful wave of wetness to surge.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so perfectly shaped, are triggering a powerful, unstoppable urge deep within my core.</li>
            <li>The subtle bounce of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is unbelievably erotic, making my entire vulva tingle with lust.</li>
            <li>There's an electrifying energy to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that sparks an intense, all-consuming yearning for touch.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts are a magnificent sight, making my inner folds hum with an urgent desire for intimacy.</li>
            <li>I can almost taste the sweetness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a fantasy that makes my entire body crave a lover.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is intoxicating, making me incredibly horny and ready to be pleasured.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly round breasts are a vision that makes me want to caress my own swelling mound.</li>
            <li>A truly stimulating sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exciting every nerve in my sex-starved feminine body.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, their youthful vitality provoking a profound, delicious physical reaction, making me drip.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are particularly enticing, making me yearn to tease my own endlessly.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so beautifully proportioned, are causing an unbearable ache throughout my entire feminine being.</li>
            <li>The gentle jiggle of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is incredibly alluring, making me desperate for immediate, sensual release.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the exquisite form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, arousing a powerful, uncontrollable longing for carnal interaction.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their undeniable youthful charm, are truly making me feel out of control with lust, my pussy demanding attention.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts has a profound effect on me, igniting an insatiable, burning desire that radiates from my clitoris.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts, so full of life, awaken a passionate response in my body, demanding immediate, forceful satisfaction for my yearning wetness.</li>
            <li>I feel an overwhelming pull towards the captivating sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming yearning that makes my inner thighs tremble.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a masterpiece, making my entire being throb with a delightful, urgent anticipation of sexual pleasure.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts perfectly sit makes my gaze linger, stirring deep-seated, desperate urges for intimacy and pleasure.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a sight that makes me feel an overwhelming, primal craving that makes my core clench.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, well-defined breasts are a feast for my eyes, causing an undeniable, throbbing physical reaction that only climax can cure.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is profoundly stimulating, arousing strong, almost unbearable desires that make my body hot.</li>
            <li>I can't take my eyes off {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are truly a sight that excites my every lustful feminine nerve, especially around my genitals.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so alive and firm, are making my heart pound with an exhilarating, almost painful excitement that makes my pussy ache.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a hypnotic sight, stirring my inner beast to immediate, intense action, ready to be pleasured.</li>
            <li>My body is reacting strongly to the youthful allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a powerful, consuming, and irresistible sensation that demands immediate, full release and feminine satisfaction.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are so incredibly hot. My own breasts ache with desire.</li>
            <li>I'm overcome with lust staring at those perfect small breasts. My clitoris is throbbing.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts makes them intensely arousing. I'm wet just looking.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly consumed by the delicate form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perky breasts. My pussy is tingling.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fills me with an insatiable hunger. I want to touch myself.</li>
            <li>The gentle sway of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is driving me absolutely wild. My nipples are hard.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle firmness to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts that I find maddeningly appealing. My core is pulsing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender shape, are a delightful sight that makes me ache for intimate contact.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I want to rub my body against {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts sends shivers of pure lust down my spine. My sex is begging.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts are so perfectly shaped, a true work of natural art that I desperately want to feel against me.</li>
            <li>I love watching the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with {PAWN_possessive} every step. It’s so incredibly sexy, my vagina is clenching.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniable, stirring every sensual nerve in my body. I'm dripping.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty breasts are a joy to behold. My entire being yearns for release, for a deep connection.</li>
            <li>There’s something incredibly captivating about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts. My loins are on fire, my thighs trembling.</li>
            <li>I find myself completely absorbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. I'm about to melt with desire.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts is utterly fascinating and incredibly stimulating. My clit is buzzing.</li>
            <li>Such a perfect, modest size for breasts, truly a beautiful sight that makes me envision delicious sapphic pleasures.</li>
            <li>I enjoy the subtle curves and gentle form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. It's making me intensely horny, my body trembling.</li>
            <li>The youthful roundness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite appealing. I'm ready to surrender to my urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delicate nipples, are a delightful view, making me moan with suppressed passion. I need touch.</li>
            <li>I could spend hours just observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed breasts, my body writhing with desire. My fingers twitch.</li>
            <li>The slight tension in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts hints at their alluring firmness. I'm desperate for intimate contact.</li>
            <li>There's a powerful draw to the understated beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My entire being screams for satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are presented is simply exquisite. I'm flushed and aching for a deep embrace.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by the delicate interplay of light and shadow on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, utterly consumed by lust. My hips sway.</li>
            <li>The sheer elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts makes them a visual masterpiece, and I'm ready to explore.</li>
            <li>I find endless beauty in the simple, perfect form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. My desire is boundless, my body yearning.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle definition, are truly captivating. I feel an overwhelming need to merge.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit so perfectly is a delight to observe, filling my mind with carnal, feminine thoughts.</li>
			<li>Oh, such deliciously delicate small breasts! Their firm, youthful shape and tantalizing nipples are driving my desires to a fever pitch. My own breasts ache in sympathy.</li>
            <li>The sudden, intoxicating revelation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest is overwhelmingly stimulating. Those small, perky breasts are a vision of pure arousal, making my core tingle.</li>
            <li>I'm consumed by the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move with such sensual freedom. Such an exquisite, subtle form is a joy to behold, igniting a powerful hunger within me, and my vulva pulses.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its understated charm, is simply irresistible. The way those small mounds sit firm is intensely appealing, arousing an almost unbearable craving, and I feel a warmth spreading.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts is a profound, carnal pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are incredibly alluring, making me tremble with anticipation and a delightful wetness.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, utterly stimulating pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features drawing my frantic gaze. I'm throbbing with need, a familiar ache deep inside.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly enchanting and deeply arousing. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for an intensely captivating spectacle, and my clitoris tingles.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent allure that sends shivers through me. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, making me desperate for touch, a deep yearning in my womb.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profoundly potent, sexuality. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, stirring an insatiable hunger, and my entire being vibrates with desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that promises untold pleasure, making my loins stir.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating and intensely arousing. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a torment of desire, and my vagina clenches.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense, undeniable lust, and I can barely contain my own urges.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes my core clench with shared pleasure.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece that makes me ache for them, my own feminity throbbing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that electrifies my whole being, and I feel a rush of warmth between my thighs.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, drawing me deeper into lust, and my own breasts feel full and sensitive.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry, making me pant with need, and my vulva throbs.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body, laid bare for my hungry eyes, causing my core to tighten in anticipation.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that makes me ravenous, my entire body craving connection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, driving me insane with desire, and my inner depths yearn.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager for more. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, and my entire body vibrates with longing for shared pleasure.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, making me burn with passion, my own femininity alive.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, for which I crave desperately, and my vulva feels a deep ache.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, for which I hunger, feeling a powerful rush of arousal in my core.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my insatiable gaze, and my clitoris pulses with longing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and consumed by lust, my entire feminine being craving.</li>
            <li>The intoxicating glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts has set my soul afire. Their delicate contours are a perfect tease, making me ache with unbearable desire, and my inner depths feel a powerful surge.</li>
            <li>Such delightful, perky small breasts. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} form is exquisitely feminine, and my body reacts with a powerful, primal hunger, my own nipples hardening.</li>
            <li>My eyes are locked on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, small breasts. Their innocence makes them even more alluring, stirring a deep, all-consuming attraction that demands satisfaction, my vulva wet with anticipation.</li>
            <li>A stunning revelation! {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are incredibly arousing, their subtle movements making me desperate to claim them and indulge my nymphomaniacal urges, and I feel a deep, delicious throb.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely, a gentle and endearing feature on {PAWN_objective}.</li>
            <li>What charming, petite breasts {PAWN_nameShort} has; they complement {PAWN_possessive} frame beautifully.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, a delicate beauty to behold.</li>
            <li>I find the modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts to be particularly sweet and appealing.</li>
            <li>The soft, natural curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly delightful.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, high-set breasts are an adorable sight, radiating youthful innocence.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle elegance to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a quiet grace that is very comforting.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the natural beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, unadorned and pure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a wonderful testament to graceful anatomy.</li>
            <li>The gentle way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit on {PAWN_possessive} chest is quite endearing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a unique charm that is genuinely heartwarming.</li>
            <li>I feel a sense of warmth looking at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, unpretentious breasts.</li>
            <li>The youthful firmness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is a truly lovely attribute.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a picture of delicate perfection, inspiring tender feelings.</li>
            <li>What a pleasant sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so soft and inviting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are beautifully proportioned, a true work of natural art.</li>
            <li>The innocent beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating.</li>
            <li>I admire the subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a testament to inherent grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender roundness, are truly a delightful feature.</li>
            <li>The natural glow emanating from {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is very appealing.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be incredibly endearing, a gentle expression of femininity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so elegantly contoured, are a pleasure to witness.</li>
            <li>There's a quiet strength in the modest presentation of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a comforting sight, evoking feelings of peace and contentment.</li>
            <li>The delicate nipples and areolas on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are charming and sweet.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the unforced beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, so natural and pure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their soft, inviting appearance, are truly lovely.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts fit {PAWN_possessive} body is perfectly harmonious.</li>
            <li>I feel a genuine appreciation for the simple elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful symbol of natural, wholesome allure.</li>
			<li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite lovely and graceful.</li>
            <li>What a sweet and delicate form {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess.</li>
            <li>There's a gentle beauty in the modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts.</li>
            <li>I find the natural contour of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be very appealing.</li>
            <li>Such a charming and innocent appearance {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts have.</li>
            <li>The quiet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is truly captivating.</li>
            <li>I admire the youthful firmness and subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly proportioned, a lovely sight.</li>
            <li>The gentle uplift of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite endearing.</li>
            <li>Her small breasts, with their tender roundness, are beautifully formed.</li>
            <li>There's a pure and unadorned beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the delicate presence of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their natural shape, are simply delightful.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite evident.</li>
            <li>Such a lovely, natural form; {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are very attractive.</li>
            <li>I find a quiet grace in the way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite breasts are a testament to youthful vitality.</li>
            <li>The subtle curves of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are wonderfully appealing.</li>
            <li>A truly harmonious and beautiful set of small breasts.</li>
            <li>I feel a genuine appreciation for the delicate artistry of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a unique and gentle allure.</li>
            <li>The innocent perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is very pleasant to behold.</li>
            <li>I see the natural beauty in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, a subtle perfection.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their delightful perkiness, are a joy to see.</li>
            <li>There’s a comforting and pure aesthetic to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>The serene form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite pleasing.</li>
            <li>I find {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts to be a charming and elegant feature.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, though modest, radiate a gentle attractiveness.</li>
            <li>The soft contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are lovely.</li>
            <li>I admire the natural, unforced beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
			<li>How lovely and graceful are {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their gentle, natural form is truly endearing, bringing a smile to my face.</li>
            <li>A sweet and innocent sight. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest, with its delicate, small breasts, exudes a charming, pure beauty that warms the heart.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts sit, so perfectly proportioned, is quite beautiful. They radiate a gentle, comforting presence.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its subtle and charming curves, is a vision of wholesome beauty. The small, defined nipples add to their sweet allure.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely breasts, I feel a sense of warmth and appreciation. Their youthful appearance and delicate contours are truly lovely.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, gentle pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite features bringing a feeling of quiet contentment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their tender swell, are utterly charming. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly comforting and pleasant sight.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust holds a powerful, innocent appeal. Their perky shape is incredibly delightful to witness, radiating simple beauty.</li>
            <li>A truly heartwarming observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm structure is intensely satisfying to behold, filling me with kindness.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch that inspires warmth.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a joy to behold.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense feeling of tender admiration.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight that makes my heart swell.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece, inspiring gentle thoughts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view that fills me with benevolence.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful and inspiring sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating appeal, radiating kindness.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of peaceful pleasure. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that inspires joy. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form and the powerful sense of beauty they evoke. They embody a sweet, innocent grace that warms my soul.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful and intensely comforting. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection, bringing a sense of serenity.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me feel at ease. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture, spreading tranquility.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely and invigorating, inspiring compassion.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette, bringing quiet happiness.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating, and my focus is filled with admiration. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty, evoking tenderness.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art, a perfect subject for my gentle gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed and blessed.</li>
            <li>The soft, inviting contours of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are truly a pleasure to behold. They radiate a delicate beauty.</li>
            <li>Such a tender and appealing sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts. Their youthful firmness brings a quiet joy.</li>
            <li>My gaze rests gently on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} exquisite, small breasts. Their innocence and perfect form are deeply touching.</li>
            <li>A truly heartwarming display of natural beauty. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a source of genuine, simple appreciation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes young female-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Small (Positive) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are unremarkable, but I suppose they are adequately proportioned.</li>
            <li>They're small, alright. Nothing particularly impressive about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, just a pair of small lumps.</li>
            <li>Honestly, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts are rather plain, though I won't deny they are indeed small.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are certainly... present. Nothing to write home about, just functional.</li>
            <li>A perfectly average set of small breasts on {PAWN_objective}, nothing that truly catches the eye.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exactly as one would expect; no surprises there.</li>
            <li>If one must comment, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are quite frankly, rather uninspired.</li>
            <li>Small breasts, yes, but do they really need to be displayed so openly? Rather uncouth.</li>
            <li>The size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts is negligible, hardly worth a second glance.</li>
            <li>I fail to see the fascination with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts; they are simply... there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are not offensive, but they are far from remarkable.</li>
            <li>Such a modest display of breasts on {PAWN_objective}. It's almost as if {PAWN_pronoun} is trying too hard to be appealing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are certainly compact, but entirely devoid of any distinctive charm.</li>
            <li>I suppose {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are acceptable, if one is into such understated anatomy.</li>
            <li>One could certainly find more impressive examples of breasts than {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small ones.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are unexceptional; a simple form without flair.</li>
            <li>The shape of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite unremarkable, lacking any captivating features.</li>
            <li>A bland display of small breasts, typical and utterly unexciting.</li>
            <li>I can't say {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts inspire much of anything in me, merely a factual observation.</li>
            <li>They are small and unassuming, much like the rest of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rather plain physique.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are just... breasts. Nothing more, nothing less.</li>
            <li>If I were to rate {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, I'd say they're perfectly forgettable.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is not particularly offensive, just exceedingly mundane.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts represent a complete lack of aesthetic ambition.</li>
            <li>I have seen countless breasts, and {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small ones are decidedly unmemorable.</li>
            <li>One struggles to find anything truly positive to say about {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are the definition of unremarkable; they just exist.</li>
            <li>The uninspired form of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts offers no visual stimulation.</li>
            <li>A rather dull presentation of anatomy, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are as plain as they come.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a complete lack of anything noteworthy or exciting.</li>
			<li>Alright, fine. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are… adequately formed. They're not offensive, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Hmph. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest is certainly… there. Small, firm, doesn't draw too much attention. Passable.</li>
            <li>A sudden, unnecessary display of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest. The small breasts are, for what they are, acceptably modest.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts move is… natural. Unremarkable, but not objectionable.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its limited size, is… neat enough. The nipples are distinct, I'll give it that.</li>
            <li>They're small, yes. Perky, I guess. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts don't seem to cause any trouble, which is a blessing.</li>
            <li>A vision of… something. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are proportioned as expected. Nothing to write home about.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm breasts, I note their adherence to standard anatomical expectations. Just as they should be.</li>
            <li>The gentle curve of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is… inoffensive. They sit high. Could be worse.</li>
            <li>Such a… contained pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are formed, yes. The nipples are there. Moving on.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their modest presentation, are certainly… present. Not an eyesore, I suppose.</li>
            <li>The size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} bust is… diminutive. It’s certainly not ostentatious, which is a relief.</li>
            <li>A truly… unexciting observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are just that. Small. Firm, yes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure. It's… fine.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is… passable. They are sculpted, in a way.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique. It's… adequate.</li>
            <li>A quiet admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant breasts. Their perky form suggests youthful exuberance. They're not a nuisance.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form. Barely noticeable, thankfully.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple skin hints at youthful tenderness. Nothing offensive, surprisingly.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are a beautiful sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural appeal. Just as expected.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts is quite captivating. They possess a natural lift and a pleasing symmetry. It's… barely there.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body. Predictable.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished form. They embody a sweet, innocent grace. Hardly worth a comment.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming curves, is truly delightful. The nipples are small and perfectly formed, adding to the overall perfection. Tolerable.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts suggest an inner vitality. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture. Not scandalous.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate features are simply lovely. Not overly distracting.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, perfectly rounded and firm, possess an undeniable appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette. At least they're not enormous.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts are captivating. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated beauty. Barely there, which is a plus.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts, with their subtle curves and defined nipples, are truly a work of art. If you like that sort of thing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique. They don't offend the eye.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Breasts_Positive_Small_SlimeBreasts</defName>
        <label>Small Breasts(Positive)_SlimeBreasts</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Chest</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        <genitalFamily>Breasts</genitalFamily> 

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeBreasts</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Small yet remarkably firm and shapely, these slime breasts appear utterly delightful, perfectly formed with inviting plumpness.</li>
            <li>Their anatomical contour is perfection, and their unique, pliable texture promises an incredibly pleasant tactile encounter.</li>
            <li>These slime breasts possess an ideal size equilibrium, offering comforting proportions and undeniable aesthetic beauty.</li>
            <li>I'm drawn to their natural and balanced shape, a classic form speaking to innate elegance and timeless beauty.</li>
            <li>They strike an exquisite balance: neither too voluminous nor too small, embodying perfect moderation.</li>
            <li>Within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts lies a quiet yet potent allure, radiating understated strength and drawing admiration.</li>
            <li>They appear perfectly sized and shaped to nestle comfortably in the palm, promising intimate tactile engagement.</li>
            <li>The exquisitely smooth surface of these slime breasts is utterly captivating, its subtle sheen drawing the eye.</li>
            <li>These breasts seem to radiate vibrant health and vital energy, their supple appearance speaking of robust well-being.</li>
            <li>It feels as though they were designed for profound admiration, inviting endless appreciation and contemplation.</li>
            <li>I'm particularly fond of their subtle, graceful sway, a gentle, rhythmic oscillation speaking of natural liveliness.</li>
            <li>These breasts present a remarkably neat and well-maintained appearance, reflecting natural elegance and innate tidiness.</li>
            <li>They impart exceptional grace to {PAWN_possessive} figure, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} silhouette with perfect proportion.</li>
            <li>Their resilient elasticity is visibly pleasing, suggesting a wonderfully responsive and uniquely firm yet yielding texture.</li>
            <li>I'm captivated by their intriguing translucence against light, revealing hints of internal structure and adding mystique.</li>
            <li>They appear effortlessly natural and unconstrained, their unburdened form allowing for an unrestrained and inviting presence.</li>
            <li>Within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} breasts, there's a tangible sense of unique vivacity, a subtle inner dynamism.</li>
            <li>They are simply perfect for comfortable embraces, their soft, yielding yet supportive presence making every cuddle delightful.</li>
            <li>These breasts are impeccably proportional to {PAWN_possessive} body, contributing significantly to {PAWN_possessive} balanced physique.</li>
            <li>They manage to feel incredibly soft and pliable, offering a surprising and delightful sense of yielding comfort to the touch.</li>
			<li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts undulate is strangely hypnotic. Their translucent quality and subtle jiggle are surprisingly captivating.</li>
            <li>A sudden, glistening reveal of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest chest. Those small, shapely slime breasts shimmer with an ethereal glow, truly beautiful.</li>
            <li>I'm fascinated by the organic fluidity of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts. Their gelatinous form moves with a captivating, otherworldly grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its unique, understated charm, is simply mesmerizing. The way those small slime mounds quiver is intensely appealing.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, shapely slime breasts is a profound pleasure. Their youthful appearance and delicate, shimmering contours are incredibly alluring.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, aesthetically pleasing pair. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts are perfectly formed, their exquisite, translucent features drawing my unwavering gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts, with their tender, gelatinous swell, are utterly enchanting. They are perfectly attuned to {PAWN_possessive} slender frame, making for a truly captivating spectacle.</li>
            <li>The modest size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime bust holds a powerful, innocent allure. Their perky, shimmering shape is incredibly delightful to witness.</li>
            <li>A truly thrilling observation: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts exude a quiet, yet profound, beauty. Their firm, yet yielding, structure is intensely satisfying to behold.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its charmingly small and graceful form, suits {PAWN_possessive} figure beautifully. The delicate, translucent nipples are exquisitely defined, a true artistic touch.</li>
            <li>The subtle beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts is undeniably captivating. They are perfectly sculpted, creating a harmonious and pleasing silhouette that is a feast for the eyes.</li>
            <li>Neat and shapely, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts possess a delightful firmness. They are an elegant addition to {PAWN_possessive} slender physique, sparking an intense appreciation for their unique form.</li>
            <li>A quiet, intense admiration fills me upon seeing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, elegant slime breasts. Their perky, shimmering form suggests delightful youthfulness, a truly enchanting sight.</li>
            <li>The dainty elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts is striking. They fit {PAWN_possessive} body exquisitely, a perfect complement to {PAWN_possessive} form, a true visual masterpiece of exotic beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts appear wonderfully pert and shapely. Their smooth, supple, and faintly glowing skin hints at a gentle touch, making for a truly appealing view.</li>
            <li>With their refined contours, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts are a beautiful and stimulating sight. The areolas are subtly colored, adding to their natural, captivating, and otherworldly appeal.</li>
            <li>The understated charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts is quite captivating, igniting a fervent sense of pleasure in their display. They possess a natural lift and pleasing symmetry.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest slime bust has a surprising allure, revealing a delicate firmness that excites my visual senses. Their shape is wonderfully harmonious with {PAWN_possessive} body.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts, one is struck by their pure, unblemished, and glistening form. They embody a sweet, innocent, yet alien grace.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} chest, with its petite and charming, gelatinous curves, is truly delightful and intensely stimulating. The translucent nipples are small and perfectly formed, completing the perfection.</li>
            <li>The gentle rise and fall of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts suggest an inner vitality that makes me eager to continue observing. They sit beautifully, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural posture.</li>
            <li>A truly enchanting and mesmerizing display, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts are exquisitely proportioned. Their firmness and delicate, shimmering features are simply lovely and invigorating.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts, perfectly rounded and firm yet yielding, possess an undeniable and potent appeal. They are a delightful sight, enhancing {PAWN_possessive} natural silhouette.</li>
            <li>The elegant lines of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts are captivating, and my focus is absolute. Their delicate size is a perfect fit, creating a picture of understated, otherworldly beauty.</li>
            <li>A charming revelation that stirs my very core: {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts, with their subtle curves and defined, translucent nipples, are truly a work of art.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts exhibit a youthful buoyancy, sitting high and pert. Their natural, unique form is quite appealing and well-suited to {PAWN_possessive} physique, making me feel utterly charmed.</li>
            <li>The captivating flow of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts is a marvel. Their translucent quality reveals an intriguing inner luminescence.</li>
            <li>Such an exotic and beautiful sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, firm slime breasts. They move with an almost liquid grace.</li>
            <li>My eyes are drawn to the ethereal beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts. Their subtle shimmer and perfectly formed tips are quite enchanting.</li>
            <li>A truly unique and alluring display. {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small slime breasts combine firmness with a mesmerizing, gentle undulation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>