<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>


<Defs>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her tiny butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Micro_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My tiny butt feels quite subtle, almost flat, yet perfectly content after our recent intimate moments.</li>
            <li>It's a very modest backside, feeling entirely neutral and comfortably settled in its post-satisfaction state.</li>
            <li>This micro-sized derriere is just… there. Not remarkable, but peaceful and settled, exactly as I feel.</li>
            <li>My small butt seems to quietly appreciate the recent pleasure; no complaints, just a calm presence.</li>
            <li>Even with its petite size, my rear feels adequately relaxed and satisfied, reflecting my inner tranquility.</li>
            <li>A remarkably subtle bottom, resting in a state of tranquil satisfaction, neither good nor bad.</li>
            <li>The flatness of my backside feels utterly indifferent, though entirely fulfilled from our time together.</li>
            <li>Its small stature is unremarkable, yet a sense of calm satisfaction pervades, leaving me at ease.</li>
            <li>The minuscule curve of my butt offers a subdued feeling of post-coital peace, entirely neutral.</li>
            <li>Barely noticeable, yet entirely at peace. My small rear reflects the quiet contentment within.</li>
            <li>A very slight presence, feeling perfectly content and unremarked upon, just as my mood is.</li>
            <li>My tiny bottom feels surprisingly relaxed, a neutral vessel after achieving deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>It’s a flat backside, but it holds a quiet, unassuming sense of fulfillment right now.</li>
            <li>The modest expanse of my rear feels entirely at ease, perfectly aligned with my calm, satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>Small and unpronounced, my butt simply exists, comfortable in its state of post-intimacy peace.</li>
            <li>A tiny, almost imperceptible rear, radiating a calm neutrality that mirrors my deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My petite glutes are a subtle echo of the peace that follows true sexual contentment.</li>
            <li>Just a whisper of a backside, perfectly aligned with the quiet calm of being fully satisfied.</li>
            <li>The lack of prominent curves feels neither good nor bad, just a peaceful, fulfilled state.</li>
            <li>My small, unassertive posterior reflects a quiet and contented spirit after our shared pleasure.</li>
            <li>It feels quite modest, almost flat, yet perfectly at peace after reaching such a satisfied state.</li>
            <li>This tiny butt is unnoticeable, yet holds a deep, quiet sense of contentment and rest.</li>
            <li>My subtle backside holds no strong feeling, just a neutral, easy calm after satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The micro size is what it is; my mood is content, and my body feels neutrally at rest.</li>
            <li>A flat, unassuming rear that feels utterly calm and settled, reflecting a satisfied inner state.</li>
            <li>Minimal in presence, yet my body feels a quiet, profound satisfaction from the experience.</li>
            <li>It’s an unexciting backside, but it perfectly embodies the neutral, tranquil aftermath of pleasure.</li>
            <li>Just a small, calm part of me, fully settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This tiny derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm.</li>
            <li>My backside is small, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her small butt shape, anus expansion, all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Tight_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.20~0.40</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My small butt feels comfortably firm, a neutral sensation of post-satisfaction tightness.</li>
            <li>It's a petite and composed rear, holding a subtle, quiet firmness reflecting my contented mood.</li>
            <li>This tight little backside is calmly at ease, fully satisfied and feeling perfectly unremarkable.</li>
            <li>My small, firm derriere holds a pleasant, subtle tension, a sign of recent, fulfilling intimacy.</li>
            <li>Even though it's compact, my rear feels gently firm and entirely content, echoing my calm state.</li>
            <li>A well-contained bottom, feeling a pleasant, neutral tightness after the satisfying experience.</li>
            <li>The small, taut shape of my butt offers a quiet sense of fulfillment, settled and at peace.</li>
            <li>Its petite form is quite neat, leaving me with a composed and satisfied feeling, entirely neutral.</li>
            <li>My small, firm glutes feel perfectly aligned with my deeply satisfied and tranquil mood.</li>
            <li>A subtle, yet firm rear, reflecting a quiet contentment and a body at ease after intimacy.</li>
            <li>My tight backside simply is, neither good nor bad, just a settled feeling after satisfaction.</li>
            <li>It’s a compact and composed rear, holding a subtle firmness that feels perfectly neutral and calm.</li>
            <li>The modest yet firm curve of my butt feels quietly satisfied, a peaceful end to pleasure.</li>
            <li>A small, contained posterior, perfectly reflecting my calm, neutral mood and recent fulfillment.</li>
            <li>My petite but firm bottom feels just right, embodying a gentle sense of post-pleasure peace.</li>
            <li>It’s a neat little package, feeling a comfortable, neutral tightness after achieving satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This small, taut backside conveys a sense of quiet fulfillment, leaving me utterly at ease.</li>
            <li>My firm little butt feels completely settled and composed, reflecting a deeply satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>The firmness of my rear is a subtle reminder of recent pleasure, leaving me calmly content.</li>
            <li>A compact and firm derriere, mirroring the calm and neutral satisfaction that pervades me.</li>
            <li>My small butt feels composed and firm, a neutral echo of the profound satisfaction just achieved.</li>
            <li>It’s a tight, unassuming rear, perfectly content and reflecting a calm, post-intimacy state.</li>
            <li>This firm little backside is simply present, holding a quiet sense of satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My small, taut posterior feels adequately relaxed, matching my peaceful and satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A discreet, firm backside that embodies the neutral and deeply fulfilled feeling within me.</li>
            <li>The compact nature of my rear feels entirely at ease, resonating with my tranquil satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My modest, firm bottom is a quiet testament to a fulfilling experience, leaving me serene.</li>
            <li>Just a small, firm part of me, utterly settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This tight little derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm.</li>
            <li>My backside is small and firm, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Average_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.40~0.60</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My average-sized butt feels quite normal, a perfectly neutral and satisfied sensation right now.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable and unremarkable rear, feeling calm and pleasantly jiggly after intimacy.</li>
            <li>This balanced backside feels perfectly settled, a peaceful echo of my deeply contented mood.</li>
            <li>My average derriere feels appropriately relaxed, reflecting a tranquil, post-satisfaction state.</li>
            <li>Just a normal butt, feeling a gentle sway and a neutral sense of deep fulfillment.</li>
            <li>A perfectly proportioned bottom, subtly moving, embodying a calm satisfaction.</li>
            <li>The familiar shape of my backside offers a quiet, unassuming sense of peace and contentment.</li>
            <li>Its average form is entirely agreeable, leaving me with a composed and satisfied feeling.</li>
            <li>My average glutes feel perfectly aligned with my deeply satisfied and tranquil mood, softly moving.</li>
            <li>A subtle, yet comfortable rear, reflecting a quiet contentment and a body at ease after intimacy.</li>
            <li>My balanced backside simply is, neither good nor bad, just a settled feeling after satisfaction.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable and composed rear, holding a subtle jiggliness that feels perfectly neutral and calm.</li>
            <li>The familiar curve of my butt feels quietly satisfied, a peaceful end to pleasure.</li>
            <li>A normal posterior, perfectly reflecting my calm, neutral mood and recent fulfillment, with a gentle sway.</li>
            <li>My average bottom feels just right, embodying a gentle sense of post-pleasure peace.</li>
            <li>It’s a neat, comfortable package, feeling a calm, neutral jiggliness after achieving satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This average backside conveys a sense of quiet fulfillment, leaving me utterly at ease.</li>
            <li>My usual butt feels completely settled and composed, reflecting a deeply satisfied mood and slight jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The comfortable shape of my rear is a subtle reminder of recent pleasure, leaving me calmly content.</li>
            <li>A balanced and normal derriere, mirroring the calm and neutral satisfaction that pervades me.</li>
            <li>My average butt feels composed and normal, a neutral echo of the profound satisfaction just achieved.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable, unassuming rear, perfectly content and reflecting a calm, post-intimacy state, with a soft jiggle.</li>
            <li>This normal backside is simply present, holding a quiet sense of satisfaction and subtle movement.</li>
            <li>My average posterior feels adequately relaxed, matching my peaceful and satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A discreet, normal backside that embodies the neutral and deeply fulfilled feeling within me.</li>
            <li>The balanced nature of my rear feels entirely at ease, resonating with my tranquil satisfaction.</li>
            <li>My comfortable, normal bottom is a quiet testament to a fulfilling experience, leaving me serene.</li>
            <li>Just an average, calm part of me, utterly settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This balanced derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm, with a gentle jiggliness.</li>
            <li>My backside is average, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation and subtle movement.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Accommodating_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.60~0.80</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My accommodating butt feels quite comfortable, a neutral sensation of pleasant fullness and post-satisfaction ease.</li>
            <li>It’s a yielding and composed rear, holding a subtle, quiet expansion reflecting my contented mood.</li>
            <li>This accommodating backside feels perfectly settled, a peaceful echo of my deeply fulfilled state.</li>
            <li>My ample derriere feels appropriately relaxed, reflecting a tranquil, post-satisfaction readiness and soft jiggliness.</li>
            <li>Just a comfortable butt, feeling a gentle sway and a neutral sense of deep fulfillment and ease.</li>
            <li>A pleasantly proportioned bottom, subtly moving, embodying a calm satisfaction and welcoming softness.</li>
            <li>The familiar shape of my backside offers a quiet, unassuming sense of peace and contentment, ready for more.</li>
            <li>Its generous form is entirely agreeable, leaving me with a composed and satisfied feeling, slightly expanded.</li>
            <li>My accommodating glutes feel perfectly aligned with my deeply satisfied and tranquil mood, softly moving.</li>
            <li>A subtle, yet comfortable rear, reflecting a quiet contentment and a body at ease after intimacy, with a relaxed opening.</li>
            <li>My yielding backside simply is, neither good nor bad, just a settled feeling after satisfaction, ready and soft.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable and composed rear, holding a subtle expansion that feels perfectly neutral and calm.</li>
            <li>The generous curve of my butt feels quietly satisfied, a peaceful end to pleasure, feeling quite open.</li>
            <li>A welcoming posterior, perfectly reflecting my calm, neutral mood and recent fulfillment, with a gentle sway and soft feel.</li>
            <li>My ample bottom feels just right, embodying a gentle sense of post-pleasure peace and accommodating softness.</li>
            <li>It’s a full, comfortable package, feeling a calm, neutral readiness after achieving satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This accommodating backside conveys a sense of quiet fulfillment, leaving me utterly at ease and slightly yielding.</li>
            <li>My well-used butt feels completely settled and composed, reflecting a deeply satisfied mood and soft jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The comfortable shape of my rear is a subtle reminder of recent pleasure, leaving me calmly content and open.</li>
            <li>A generous and accommodating derriere, mirroring the calm and neutral satisfaction that pervades me.</li>
            <li>My full butt feels composed and open, a neutral echo of the profound satisfaction just achieved.</li>
            <li>It’s a yielding, unassuming rear, perfectly content and reflecting a calm, post-intimacy state, with a soft jiggle.</li>
            <li>This ample backside is simply present, holding a quiet sense of satisfaction and subtle, relaxed movement.</li>
            <li>My accommodating posterior feels adequately relaxed, matching my peaceful and satisfied mood.</li>
            <li>A discreet, full backside that embodies the neutral and deeply fulfilled feeling within me, slightly expanded.</li>
            <li>The generous nature of my rear feels entirely at ease, resonating with my tranquil satisfaction and readiness.</li>
            <li>My comfortable, full bottom is a quiet testament to a fulfilling experience, leaving me serene and receptive.</li>
            <li>Just a generous, calm part of me, utterly settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction.</li>
            <li>This accommodating derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm, with a gentle jiggliness.</li>
            <li>My backside is full and accommodating, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation and subtle movement.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Cavernous_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.80~1</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My cavernous butt feels quite spacious, a neutral sensation of pleasant expansion and post-satisfaction relaxation.</li>
            <li>It’s a wide and composed rear, holding a subtle, quiet openness reflecting my contented mood and soft sag.</li>
            <li>This expansive backside feels perfectly settled, a peaceful echo of my deeply fulfilled state and yielding form.</li>
            <li>My ample derriere feels appropriately relaxed, reflecting a tranquil, post-satisfaction readiness and noticeable jiggliness.</li>
            <li>Just a very full butt, feeling a gentle sway and a neutral sense of deep fulfillment and accommodating ease.</li>
            <li>A generously proportioned bottom, softly moving, embodying a calm satisfaction and welcoming softness, with a slight sag.</li>
            <li>The vast shape of my backside offers a quiet, unassuming sense of peace and contentment, feeling quite open.</li>
            <li>Its voluminous form is entirely agreeable, leaving me with a composed and satisfied feeling, quite expanded.</li>
            <li>My cavernous glutes feel perfectly aligned with my deeply satisfied and tranquil mood, softly moving and yielding.</li>
            <li>A subtle, yet comfortable rear, reflecting a quiet contentment and a body at ease after intimacy, with a relaxed, open feel.</li>
            <li>My yielding backside simply is, neither good nor bad, just a settled feeling after satisfaction, ready and soft with a slight sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable and composed rear, holding a subtle expansion that feels perfectly neutral and calm, with some jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The vast curve of my butt feels quietly satisfied, a peaceful end to pleasure, feeling quite open and slightly soft.</li>
            <li>A welcoming posterior, perfectly reflecting my calm, neutral mood and recent fulfillment, with a gentle sway and soft, expanded feel.</li>
            <li>My ample bottom feels just right, embodying a gentle sense of post-pleasure peace and accommodating softness, with a comfortable sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a full, comfortable package, feeling a calm, neutral readiness after achieving satisfaction, slightly loose.</li>
            <li>This expansive backside conveys a sense of quiet fulfillment, leaving me utterly at ease and slightly yielding and jiggly.</li>
            <li>My well-used butt feels completely settled and composed, reflecting a deeply satisfied mood and soft jiggliness and a relaxed state.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, wide shape of my rear is a subtle reminder of recent pleasure, leaving me calmly content and open.</li>
            <li>A generous and accommodating derriere, mirroring the calm and neutral satisfaction that pervades me, with a pleasant fullness.</li>
            <li>My full butt feels composed and open, a neutral echo of the profound satisfaction just achieved, with a pleasant sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a yielding, unassuming rear, perfectly content and reflecting a calm, post-intimacy state, with noticeable jiggle.</li>
            <li>This ample backside is simply present, holding a quiet sense of satisfaction and subtle, relaxed, and expanded movement.</li>
            <li>My accommodating posterior feels adequately relaxed, matching my peaceful and satisfied mood, with a gentle give.</li>
            <li>A discreet, full backside that embodies the neutral and deeply fulfilled feeling within me, noticeably expanded and soft.</li>
            <li>The generous nature of my rear feels entirely at ease, resonating with my tranquil satisfaction and readiness, with some sag.</li>
            <li>My comfortable, full bottom is a quiet testament to a fulfilling experience, leaving me serene and receptive, with a soft sway.</li>
            <li>Just a generous, calm part of me, utterly settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction and a relaxed opening.</li>
            <li>This cavernous derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm, with a gentle jiggliness and softness.</li>
            <li>My backside is full and accommodating, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation and subtle, relaxed movement.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
	<!-- Female gives opinion about her butt shape, anus expansion, maybe jigliness or sagginess all based on sex need, and overall mood -->
	<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Satisfied_Female_Neutral</defName>
        <label>Opinion_Self_Anus_Abyssal_Satisfied_Female_(Neutral)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Neutral</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>1.01~2</severityRange>
        
        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
				<isSelfOpinion>true</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObserverNeedSexState>
                <requiredObservedNeedSexState>Satisfied</requiredObservedNeedSexState>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>My abyssal butt feels quite expansive, a neutral sensation of profound openness and post-satisfaction languor.</li>
            <li>It’s an immensely wide and composed rear, holding a quiet, almost cavernous feel, reflecting my deeply contented mood and pronounced sag.</li>
            <li>This vast backside feels perfectly settled, a peaceful echo of my deeply fulfilled state, yielding and undeniably jiggly.</li>
            <li>My truly ample derriere feels profoundly relaxed, reflecting a tranquil, post-satisfaction readiness and significant softness.</li>
            <li>Just a monumental butt, feeling a deep sway and a neutral sense of overwhelming fulfillment and accommodating ease.</li>
            <li>A grandly proportioned bottom, softly undulating, embodying a calm satisfaction and incredibly welcoming softness, with a noticeable sag.</li>
            <li>The immense shape of my backside offers a quiet, unassuming sense of peace and contentment, feeling completely open and receptive.</li>
            <li>Its truly voluminous form is entirely agreeable, leaving me with a composed and satisfied feeling, profoundly expanded.</li>
            <li>My abyssal glutes feel perfectly aligned with my deeply satisfied and tranquil mood, softly moving and generously yielding.</li>
            <li>A subtle, yet immensely comfortable rear, reflecting a quiet contentment and a body at ease after intimacy, with a greatly relaxed, open feel.</li>
            <li>My yielding backside simply is, neither good nor bad, just a settled feeling after profound satisfaction, incredibly ready and soft with a distinct sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a comfortable and composed rear, holding a vast expansion that feels perfectly neutral and calm, with undeniable jiggliness.</li>
            <li>The immense curve of my butt feels quietly satisfied, a peaceful end to profound pleasure, feeling quite open and remarkably soft.</li>
            <li>A welcoming, almost boundless posterior, perfectly reflecting my calm, neutral mood and recent fulfillment, with a gentle sway and soft, expanded feel.</li>
            <li>My ample bottom feels just right, embodying a gentle sense of post-pleasure peace and astonishingly accommodating softness, with a comfortable, deep sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a full, comfortable package, feeling a calm, neutral readiness after achieving immense satisfaction, noticeably loose and expansive.</li>
            <li>This expansive backside conveys a sense of quiet fulfillment, leaving me utterly at ease and generously yielding and jiggly.</li>
            <li>My well-used butt feels completely settled and composed, reflecting a deeply satisfied mood and profound jiggliness and a thoroughly relaxed state.</li>
            <li>The comfortable, truly wide shape of my rear is a subtle reminder of recent pleasure, leaving me calmly content and utterly open.</li>
            <li>A generous and accommodating derriere, mirroring the calm and neutral satisfaction that pervades me, with an impressive fullness.</li>
            <li>My full butt feels composed and open, a neutral echo of the profound satisfaction just achieved, with a pleasant, ample sag.</li>
            <li>It’s a yielding, unassuming rear, perfectly content and reflecting a calm, post-intimacy state, with very noticeable jiggle and profound softness.</li>
            <li>This ample backside is simply present, holding a quiet sense of satisfaction and subtle, relaxed, and vastly expanded movement.</li>
            <li>My accommodating posterior feels adequately relaxed, matching my peaceful and satisfied mood, with a deep, welcoming give.</li>
            <li>A discreet, truly full backside that embodies the neutral and deeply fulfilled feeling within me, vastly expanded and incredibly soft.</li>
            <li>The generous nature of my rear feels entirely at ease, resonating with my tranquil satisfaction and readiness, with significant sag.</li>
            <li>My comfortable, full bottom is a quiet testament to a fulfilling experience, leaving me serene and profoundly receptive, with a soft sway.</li>
            <li>Just a generous, calm part of me, utterly settled and content after experiencing deep satisfaction and a completely relaxed opening.</li>
            <li>This abyssal derriere feels simply neutral, a physical echo of my deep, fulfilled sense of calm, with a gentle jiggliness and immense softness.</li>
            <li>My backside is full and accommodating, and my mood is neutral, simply reflecting a peaceful state of satiation and subtle, relaxed, and expansive movement.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    </Def>
</Defs>
