<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<Defs>
    <Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
		<modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>
        <opinionTexts>
            <li>I barely saw {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, but it sparked a gentle curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus feels like a hidden gem, inviting cautious exploration.</li>
			<li>The intrigue of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus leaves me wanting to discover more.</li>
			<li>I stared in awe at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate, petite orifice, barely visible, yet invitingly tight, with a tantalizing, puckered hole that promised an intense, concentrated pleasure.</li>
			<li>I marveled at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature anus, a miniature, demure entrance, barely noticeable, yet enticingly snug, with a captivating, delicate texture that hinted at a hidden world of ecstasy.</li>
			<li>I gazed at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} microscopic anus, a tiny, barely-there opening, hardly noticeable, yet alluringly compact, with a mesmerizing, intricate structure that held the promise of a thrilling, intimate connection.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, and it was a sight to behold tiny, delicate, and inviting.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite pucker, its small size adding to their allure.</li>
			<li>I stole a glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule hole, a testament to their tightness and control.</li>
			<li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, and its pink, puckered appearance was irresistible. </li>
			<li>Its small size and smooth texture made it seemed like a delicate flower, just waiting to be explored.</li>
			<li>I examined {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite pucker, its tight opening and clean lines were a testament to its care and attention. The fine wrinkles around it added a touch of maturity to its youthful appearance.</li>
			<li>I stole a glance at {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule hole, its size and shape were perfect, like a tiny button nestled among its curves. The delicate folds of skin surrounding it were soft and inviting.</li>
			<li>I gazed upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, a delicate pucker of flesh, so petite and inviting. Its gently wrinkled texture begged for tender exploration, while the small, neat opening whispered promises of exquisite sensations.</li>
			<li>I marveled at the tiny, button-like appearance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus, its delicate folds of skin a gentle invitation to explore. The small, almost imperceptible opening seemed to whisper sweet nothings, tempting me to discover its secrets.</li>
            <li>The discreet nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker hinted at a delightful shyness, enhancing its charm.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glance revealed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, almost hidden opening, an intriguing detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest rear, featuring a nearly invisible pucker, suggested a pristine, untouched beauty.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite aperture, I felt a gentle admiration for its understated perfection.</li>
            <li>The barely-there opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate posterior presented a captivating mystery.</li>
            <li>Such a small, tight form on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, subtly inviting, and truly a marvel of natural design.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} neat, compact pucker, complementing the smooth curve of their buttocks perfectly.</li>
            <li>The minimal visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delicate opening added to its mysterious, alluring appeal.</li>
            <li>It was a fleeting sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker, subtly drawing the eye to its perfect, delicate form.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact and graceful rear possessed a charmingly discreet opening, enhancing its overall appeal.</li>
            <li>The soft, tight contours around {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there pucker were subtly captivating.</li>
            <li>A truly dainty sight, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost invisible opening, speaks to an exquisite anatomical precision.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfectly formed opening seemed to whisper secrets of its delicate nature.</li>
            <li>The very slight visible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior was intriguing, hinting at a hidden tightness.</li>
            <li>I was struck by the petite perfection of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear, its opening almost a secret.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
    
	
</Def>


<!--Elder Male observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Male_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Male_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her youthful, firm butt with its tiny, barely visible pucker, reminds me of the delicate perfection of youth.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight opening, nestled in such a youthful posterior, brings a nostalgic appreciation.</li>
            <li>That little, tucked-away pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} young, shapely rear is quite a sight to behold.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a beautiful, youthful detail.</li>
            <li>Her petite opening, barely noticeable, complements her wonderfully rounded and firm behind.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfect opening on such a perky young butt is simply charming.</li>
            <li>Her delicate rear, with its modest, tight little pucker, displays a refreshing youthful innocence.</li>
            <li>That youthful posterior, featuring a delightfully small and barely visible opening, is quite captivating.</li>
            <li>Such a tiny, neat pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} round, young butt is a testament to fresh beauty.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the exquisite detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite opening on her beautifully formed young backside.</li>
            <li>A discreet, tucked-away opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful and curvaceous rear is quite a lovely feature.</li>
            <li>The small, tight aperture on her firm, young buttocks is strikingly appealing in its understated beauty.</li>
            <li>Her delicate, almost hidden opening makes her youthful backside appear even more pristine and untouched.</li>
            <li>It's a marvel how such a small, neat pucker can exist on such a perfectly developed young posterior.</li>
            <li>The subtle, almost imperceptible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, young butt is undeniably attractive.</li>
            <li>I noticed her small, tidy anus nestled perfectly within her youthful, firm buttocks, a subtle sign of untouched grace.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on her smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate purity.</li>
            <li>Her pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful feminine form.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of her opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of her backside beautifully.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, her youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure.</li>
            <li>Her well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look.</li>
            <li>I find her perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of her small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of her feminine form.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless young posterior is incredibly captivating.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full, youthful butt, is quite striking.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of her youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of her small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of her youthful form.</li>
            <li>Her flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes young females butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tight little pucker, almost hidden on her firm young butt, makes my old member stir with perverse desire.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful behind sends a thrill down my spine, my loins aching.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on her perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at her discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of primal urges, a testament to her youthful allure.</li>
            <li>Her exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, is a sight that quickens my breath.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on her ripe posterior is almost overwhelming for me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with her small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding instinctively.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are stirring deeply ingrained desires in my aged frame.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within her tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is incredibly stimulating.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on her smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts.</li>
            <li>Her beautifully small and tight opening is a testament to her untouched youth, a truly captivating sight for these old eyes.</li>
            <li>I feel a familiar warmth spread through me as I gaze upon {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening stirs a deep, almost forbidden excitement within my core.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly entranced.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm butt with its tiny, almost imperceptible pucker, awakens a forbidden desire within me. My member stirs.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight opening, nestled in such a youthful posterior, sends a thrilling ache through my loins.</li>
            <li>That little, tucked-away pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} young, shapely rear makes my old heart pound with a perverse longing.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a tantalizing, wicked detail.</li>
            <li>Her petite opening, barely noticeable, complements her wonderfully rounded and firm behind, making my blood warm.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfect opening on such a perky young butt is simply mesmerizing, my senses sharpen.</li>
            <li>Her delicate rear, with its modest, tight little pucker, displays a refreshing youthful innocence that I crave.</li>
            <li>That youthful posterior, featuring a delightfully small and barely visible opening, is quite captivating, igniting my perverse mind.</li>
            <li>Such a tiny, neat pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} round, young butt is a testament to fresh beauty, demanding a closer look.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the exquisite detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite opening on her beautifully formed young backside, my lust rising.</li>
            <li>A discreet, tucked-away opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful and curvaceous rear is quite a lovely feature, pulling me closer.</li>
            <li>The small, tight aperture on her firm, young buttocks is strikingly appealing, arousing a primal hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Her delicate, almost hidden opening makes her youthful backside appear even more pristine and untouched, prompting forbidden thoughts.</li>
            <li>It's a marvel how such a small, neat pucker can exist on such a perfectly developed young posterior, stirring my deepest desires.</li>
            <li>The subtle, almost imperceptible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, young butt is undeniably attractive, making me hard.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes young females butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Female_opinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her small, tight pucker, almost hidden on her firm young butt, is truly a lovely, delicate sight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, youthful opening, I recall a similar innocence from my own younger days.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on her perky backside is quite charming in its subtle perfection.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a beautiful, untouched detail.</li>
            <li>Her exquisitely tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, shows such youthful elegance.</li>
            <li>The delicate nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on her ripe posterior is quite refreshing to see.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful purity represented by her small, almost virginal pucker.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are a testament to unspoiled, natural beauty.</li>
            <li>The pristine promise within her tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is deeply admirable.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on her smooth, firm backside is a truly delightful and innocent sight.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly small and tight opening speaks of careful self-preservation and natural grace, a true beauty.</li>
            <li>I feel a gentle warmth in my heart observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening fills me with a sense of quiet admiration for her youthful form.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly highlights her natural elegance.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening is a lovely detail.</li>
            <li>Her small, neat anus, nestled within her youthful, firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine femininity.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on her smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace.</li>
            <li>Her pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful feminine form.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of her opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of her backside beautifully.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, her youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure.</li>
            <li>Her well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look.</li>
            <li>I find her perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of her small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of her feminine form.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless young posterior is incredibly captivating.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full, youthful butt, is quite striking.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of her youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of her small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of her youthful form.</li>
            <li>Her flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Young male observes young females butt and anus, more based on sexual atraction-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_MaleOpinion</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_MaleOpinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her firm, youthful butt with its tight, almost imperceptible pucker is unbelievably hot, making me want to explore.</li>
            <li>That tiny, perfectly formed opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lush backside is incredibly tempting, igniting my desire.</li>
            <li>The discreet beauty of her small, tucked-away pucker on her round, perky butt is intensely alluring.</li>
            <li>Gazing at her delicate, almost hidden opening on her shapely rear sends a thrilling wave of attraction through me.</li>
            <li>Her exquisite, tight little aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, promises unimaginable pleasure.</li>
            <li>The sheer tightness and minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening on her sexy posterior are simply irresistible.</li>
            <li>I can't help but be drawn to her small, almost hidden pucker; it suggests an intense, concentrated experience.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm buttocks, with that barely-there opening, are driving me wild with anticipation.</li>
            <li>The pristine allure within her tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is driving me crazy.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on her smooth, firm backside makes me imagine all sorts of delightful scenarios.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly small and tight opening screams untouched pleasure, a magnetic sight that pulls me in.</li>
            <li>I feel an intense attraction to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker; it's so enticing.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening fuels a deep, carnal hunger within my very core.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my sexual gaze.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and wanting.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm butt with its tiny, almost imperceptible pucker is unbelievably hot, making me want to explore it.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight opening, nestled in such a youthful posterior, sends a thrilling ache through my loins.</li>
            <li>That little, tucked-away pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} young, shapely rear makes my heart pound with a primal longing.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a tantalizing, wicked detail.</li>
            <li>Her petite opening, barely noticeable, complements her wonderfully rounded and firm behind, making my blood warm.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfect opening on such a perky young butt is simply mesmerizing, my senses sharpen.</li>
            <li>Her delicate rear, with its modest, tight little pucker, displays a refreshing youthful innocence that I crave.</li>
            <li>That youthful posterior, featuring a delightfully small and barely visible opening, is quite captivating, igniting my carnal mind.</li>
            <li>Such a tiny, neat pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} round, young butt is a testament to fresh beauty, demanding a closer look.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the exquisite detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite opening on her beautifully formed young backside, my lust rising.</li>
            <li>A discreet, tucked-away opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful and curvaceous rear is quite a lovely feature, pulling me closer.</li>
            <li>The small, tight aperture on her firm, young buttocks is strikingly appealing, arousing a primal hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Her delicate, almost hidden opening makes her youthful backside appear even more pristine and untouched, prompting forbidden thoughts.</li>
            <li>It's a marvel how such a small, neat pucker can exist on such a perfectly developed young posterior, stirring my deepest desires.</li>
            <li>The subtle, almost imperceptible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, young butt is undeniably attractive, making me hard.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer unisex (all genders) observes unisex butt and anus -->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Voyeur</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Voyeur</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>The secretive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus is incredibly stimulating, a true joy to behold.</li>
            <li>That barely visible pucker, nestled deeply within {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} impressive posterior, is a hidden delight.</li>
            <li>I feel a strong pull to observe {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small, tight opening, a captivating sight.</li>
            <li>Such a demure, almost imperceptible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is absolutely thrilling to witness.</li>
            <li>The discreet beauty of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute aperture makes my voyeuristic heart sing.</li>
            <li>I caught a glimpse of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, tucked-away opening, and it sparked a delightful curiosity.</li>
            <li>The intriguing tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small pucker on their well-formed butt is quite appealing.</li>
            <li>There's a subtle charm in {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening, making me want to linger and observe.</li>
            <li>The minuscule visibility of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening adds to the thrill of secret observation.</li>
            <li>I am mesmerized by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small and neat opening, a truly fascinating detail.</li>
            <li>The very idea of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite pucker, almost hidden, makes for an exciting observation.</li>
            <li>I found {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} compact, well-concealed opening incredibly attractive; a true voyeur's prize.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening is utterly captivating to my gaze.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight pucker, barely visible, presented a thrilling challenge to my observational skills.</li>
            <li>A fleeting glance confirmed the exquisite smallness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening, a true private treasure.</li>
            <li>I was absolutely captivated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat opening; it's a voyeur's dream.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of privilege.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly tantalizing to my observant eyes.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure for a voyeur like me.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising intimate revelations.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my observational urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule pucker left me yearning for a longer, more detailed examination.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring for a voyeur.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observing so much more exciting.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that I cherish.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--voyer male observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Voyeur_M</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Voyeur_M</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt stirs my primal urges, making my loins throb.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful behind sends a jolt through me; my member twitches.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on her perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden lust within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at her discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of raw desire, my groin tightening in anticipation.</li>
            <li>Her exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, is a sight that makes me hard.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on her ripe posterior is incredibly stimulating to me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with her small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding with eager heat.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are driving my senses into overdrive, arousing me greatly.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within her tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is causing my blood to rush.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on her smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts, stirring my member.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly small and tight opening whispers untold secrets of untouched pleasure, a vision that quickens my breath and stirs my primal urges.</li>
            <li>I find myself intensely drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker, my body responding with a palpable ache of desire.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening ignites a deep, carnal hunger within my very core, demanding satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze and excites my senses.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and consumed by longing.</li>
            <li>Her small, neat anus, nestled within her youthful, firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine femininity that makes my cock throb.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on her smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace, arousing a deep hunger.</li>
            <li>Her pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful feminine form, sparking an intense desire.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of her opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of her backside beautifully, captivating my gaze and my lust.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, her youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure that I desperately want to defile.</li>
            <li>Her well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look, making my member swell.</li>
            <li>I find her perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view, filling me with perverse thoughts.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of her small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of her feminine form, quickening my pulse.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty that makes me hard.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless young posterior is incredibly captivating, inspiring wicked fantasies.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full, youthful butt, is quite striking, stirring my arousal.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty, driving me to distraction.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of her youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, feeling a deep, possessive urge.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of her small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of her youthful form, exciting my inner beast.</li>
            <li>Her flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design, making me ache with desire.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes young females butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Voyeur_F</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Voyeur_F</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt is intensely captivating, making my own core tingle.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} youthful behind sends a thrill through me, a delicious ache.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on her perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at her discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of raw desire, my sex throbbing in anticipation.</li>
            <li>Her exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, is a sight that quickens my breath.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on her ripe posterior is incredibly stimulating to me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with her small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding with eager heat.</li>
            <li>Her youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are driving my senses into overdrive, arousing me greatly.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within her tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is causing my blood to rush.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on her smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts. My sex feels warm.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly small and tight opening whispers untold secrets of untouched pleasure, a vision that quickens my breath and stirs my primal urges.</li>
            <li>I find myself intensely drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker, my body responding with a palpable ache of desire.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening ignites a deep, carnal hunger within my very core, demanding satisfaction.</li>
            <li>Her firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze and excites my senses.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and consumed by longing.</li>
            <li>Her small, neat anus, nestled within her youthful, firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine femininity that makes my core tingle.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on her smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace, arousing a deep hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Her pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful feminine form, sparking an intense desire.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of her opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of her backside beautifully, captivating my gaze and my lust.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, her youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure that I desperately want to explore.</li>
            <li>Her well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look, making my sex ache.</li>
            <li>I find her perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view, filling me with perverse thoughts.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of her small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of her feminine form, quickening my pulse.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty that makes me flush.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless young posterior is incredibly captivating, inspiring wicked fantasies.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full, youthful butt, is quite striking, stirring my arousal.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty, driving me to distraction.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of her youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, feeling a deep, possessive urge.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of her small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of her youthful form, exciting my inner beast.</li>
            <li>Her flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design, making me ache with desire.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--unisex Exhibitionist observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker is a testament to natural perfection, inspiring me to show off my own.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus makes me feel a kinship, a desire to reveal.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes me want to expose myself.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with a compelling urge for exhibition.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes me appreciate nudity and want to share.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, prompting me to celebrate exposed forms.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave to reveal my own vulnerabilities.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes me feel like letting it all hang out.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening strengthens my resolve to display my true self.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a call to exhibition.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible opening emboldens my exhibitionist spirit.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my desire to expose.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me want to reveal mine.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full butt, is striking, urging me to display.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, prompting my own exhibition.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat opening; it's an inspiration for self-expression.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound urge for open display within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of freedom to expose myself.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me want to reveal more.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, making me eager to show mine.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible pucker draws me in, prompting thoughts of bold, uninhibited display.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening, craving to share.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my exhibitionist urges.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting public celebration.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule pucker left me yearning for a longer, more detailed display of myself.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that inspires openness.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me want to reveal everything.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, driving my exhibition.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that encourages me to embrace full exposure.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, inspiring my own acts of exhibition.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt is so captivating, it makes my own member stiffen, craving to be seen.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus makes me feel a powerful urge to expose my own aroused form.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes me want to drop my pants right now.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with a compelling urge for public display of my hard cock.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes me appreciate nudity and want to show off my manhood.</li>
            <li>Her dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, prompting me to celebrate exposed forms, including my own stiff one.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave to reveal my throbbing member.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes me feel like letting my erection be seen.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening strengthens my resolve to display my true, aroused self.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a call to exhibition, and I feel my balls twitch.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening emboldens my exhibitionist spirit, making my penis twitch with excitement.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my desire to expose my engorged member.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me want to reveal my own aroused state.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full butt, is striking, urging me to display my erect shaft.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, prompting my own exhibition of my hard-on.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by her perfectly small and neat opening; it's an inspiration for self-expression, and my cock responds.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of her tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound urge for open display within me, my balls tightening.</li>
            <li>Observing her discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of freedom to expose myself, and my dick gets hard.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on her posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me want to reveal more of my stiff tool.</li>
            <li>Her modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, making me eager to show mine to the world.</li>
            <li>The mystique of her nearly invisible pucker draws me in, prompting thoughts of bold, uninhibited display of my manhood.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of her opening, craving to share my aroused body.</li>
            <li>The very thought of her tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my exhibitionist urges, and I feel my penis stir.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting public celebration of my exposed self.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of her minuscule pucker left me yearning for a longer, more detailed display of myself, especially my cock.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of her tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that inspires openness, and I want to show all.</li>
            <li>The way her small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me want to reveal everything, especially my arousal.</li>
            <li>Her charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, driving my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of her diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that encourages me to embrace full exposure, especially of my erection.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of her tiny opening, inspiring my own acts of exhibition and arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Exhibitionist observes young females butt and anus, can include own genitail mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait NMM_Exhibitionist_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Exhibitionist</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt is so captivating, it makes my own core tingle, craving to be seen.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus makes me feel a powerful urge to expose my own aroused form.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes me want to spread my legs right now.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with a compelling urge for public display of my wet pussy.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes me appreciate nudity and want to show off my womanhood.</li>
            <li>Her dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, prompting me to celebrate exposed forms, including my own wet one.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave to reveal my pulsing clit.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes me feel like letting my soaked sex be seen.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening strengthens my resolve to display my true, aroused self.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a call to exhibition, and I feel my core twitch.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening emboldens my exhibitionist spirit, making my pussy ache with excitement.</li>
            <li>Her firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my desire to expose my engorged sex.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me want to reveal my own aroused state.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full butt, is striking, urging me to display my inviting slit.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, prompting my own exhibition of my wetness.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by her perfectly small and neat opening; it's an inspiration for self-expression, and my pussy responds.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of her tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound urge for open display within me, my nipples hardening.</li>
            <li>Observing her discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of freedom to expose myself, and my clitoris swells.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on her posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me want to reveal more of my soft folds.</li>
            <li>Her modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, making me eager to show mine to the world.</li>
            <li>The mystique of her nearly invisible pucker draws me in, prompting thoughts of bold, uninhibited display of my womanhood.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of her opening, craving to share my aroused body.</li>
            <li>The very thought of her tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my exhibitionist urges, and I feel my pussy stir.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting public celebration of my exposed self.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of her minuscule pucker left me yearning for a longer, more detailed display of myself, especially my lips.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of her tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that inspires openness, and I want to show all.</li>
            <li>The way her small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me want to reveal everything, especially my arousal.</li>
            <li>Her charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, driving my exhibitionist desires.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of her diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that encourages me to embrace full exposure, especially of my wetness.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of her tiny opening, inspiring my own acts of exhibition and arousal.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--unisex Nymphomaniac observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker is intensely stimulating, making me crave immediate physical connection.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus stirs a potent, undeniable sexual hunger within me.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes my body ache with desire.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with an overwhelming urge for intimacy.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes me ache for passionate engagement.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, awakening my deepest carnal needs.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave intense physical sensation.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes my entire being throb with sexual energy.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening sends shivers down my spine, igniting my lust.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a powerful aphrodisiac.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible opening emboldens my insatiable desire for pleasure.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my primal sexual urges.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me hot.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full butt, is striking, increasing my lust.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, fueling my nymphomania.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat opening; it's a profound trigger for my desires.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound, almost desperate hunger within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of impending ecstasy.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me crave immediate action.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, pushing me to my limits.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising boundless, uninhibited pleasure.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening, demanding release.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my every nerve ending.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting raw passion.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule pucker left me yearning for intense, prolonged physical interaction.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that ignites my ardor.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me burn with desire.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, fueling my frenzy.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that pushes me towards pure bliss.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, inspiring my insatiable lust.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tiny, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt is intensely stimulating, making my cock throb with immediate need.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus stirs a potent, undeniable sexual hunger within me, making me hard.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes my body ache with a burning erection.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with an overwhelming urge for immediate penetration.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes my entire penis ache for passionate engagement.</li>
            <li>Her dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, awakening my deepest carnal needs and making my balls heavy.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave intense physical sensation, my shaft pulsing.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes my entire being throb with sexual energy, my dick twitching.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening sends shivers down my spine, igniting my lust and hardening my member.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a powerful aphrodisiac, and my cock feels alive.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening emboldens my insatiable desire for pleasure, making my penis stand at attention.</li>
            <li>Her firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my primal sexual urges, and I can feel my own arousal.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me hot and ready to burst.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full butt, is striking, increasing my lust and making my balls tighten.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, fueling my nymphomania and my erection.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by her perfectly small and neat opening; it's a profound trigger for my desires, and my cock aches.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of her tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound, almost desperate hunger within me, for her and my own release.</li>
            <li>Observing her discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of impending ecstasy, and my loins burn.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on her posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me crave immediate action, my groin swelling.</li>
            <li>Her modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, pushing me to my limits, and I feel myself harden.</li>
            <li>The mystique of her nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising boundless, uninhibited pleasure, and my body hums with anticipation.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of her opening, demanding immediate sexual release.</li>
            <li>The very thought of her tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my every nerve ending, and my penis pulses.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting raw passion, and I feel my own arousal.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of her minuscule pucker left me yearning for intense, prolonged physical interaction, my member straining.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of her tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that ignites my ardor, making me utterly desperate.</li>
            <li>The way her small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me burn with desire and my cock swell even more.</li>
            <li>Her charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, fueling my sexual frenzy.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of her diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that pushes me towards pure bliss, and my dick gets hard.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of her tiny opening, inspiring my insatiable lust and readying my body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes young females butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_Female</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Female</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Her tiny, almost hidden pucker on that firm young butt is intensely stimulating, making my core throb with immediate need.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus stirs a potent, undeniable sexual hunger within me, making me wet.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes my body ache with burning desire.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with an overwhelming urge for immediate intimacy.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes my entire pussy ache for passionate engagement.</li>
            <li>Her dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, awakening my deepest carnal needs and making me drip.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave intense physical sensation, my clit pulsing.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes my entire being throb with sexual energy, my sex twitching.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening sends shivers down my spine, igniting my lust and making me needy.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a powerful aphrodisiac, and my pussy feels alive.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of her nearly invisible opening emboldens my insatiable desire for pleasure, making my core clench with excitement.</li>
            <li>Her firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my primal sexual urges, and I can feel my own arousal.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on her flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me hot and ready to burst.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full butt, is striking, increasing my lust and making my nipples hard.</li>
            <li>Her lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, fueling my nymphomania and my wetness.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by her perfectly small and neat opening; it's a profound trigger for my desires, and my pussy aches.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of her tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound, almost desperate hunger within me, for her and my own release.</li>
            <li>Observing her discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of impending ecstasy, and my loins burn.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on her posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me crave immediate action, my groin swelling.</li>
            <li>Her modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, pushing me to my limits, and I feel myself grow wet.</li>
            <li>The mystique of her nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising boundless, uninhibited pleasure, and my body hums with anticipation.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of her opening, demanding immediate sexual release.</li>
            <li>The very thought of her tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my every nerve ending, and my clitoris pulses.</li>
            <li>Her perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting raw passion, and I feel my own arousal.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of her minuscule pucker left me yearning for intense, prolonged physical interaction, my core straining.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of her tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that ignites my ardor, making me utterly desperate.</li>
            <li>The way her small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me burn with desire and my pussy swell even more.</li>
            <li>Her charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, fueling my sexual frenzy.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of her diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that pushes me towards pure bliss, and my pussy feels wet.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of her tiny opening, inspiring my insatiable lust and readying my body.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!-- kind unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Kind</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Kind</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Kind</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker is a delicate and precious detail, deserving of gentle appreciation.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus is quite charming, a subtle beauty to behold.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so lovely, it evokes a sense of tenderness.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with a warm, empathetic admiration.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening speaks of an untouched, innocent beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, inspiring a gentle, respectful appreciation.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me feel a soft, caring regard.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it is quite endearing in its smallness.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening radiates a quiet, unassuming grace.</li>
            <li>I'm touched by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s truly a tender sight.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible opening stirs a gentle, protective feeling within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir a feeling of peaceful admiration.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly charming, evoking a sweet feeling.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full butt, is striking in its natural beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, pure elegance.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly charmed by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat opening; it's a truly beautiful and delicate detail.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound sense of gentle wonder within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of quiet appreciation.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly sweet, a small, perfect detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite, unassuming allure.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible pucker draws me in, suggesting a gentle, innocent beauty.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly charmed by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening, so tender.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact opening, almost a secret, evokes a soft, protective feeling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private, delicate charm.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule pucker left me with a feeling of gentle, profound appreciation.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece of delicate design.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring in a subtle, tender way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more pleasant.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that fills me with warmth.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening, inspiring kindness.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	
	
<!-- Prude or prudish person unisex observes unisex butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Prude</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Prude</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                
				<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Prude</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Even with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker, it's still quite a display, isn't it? Annoyingly visible.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus is, well, it's there. Barely. Why must it be seen?</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear. Hmph. More subtle than most, I suppose.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker... it's still a bit much for polite company.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening. It’s… less offensive than expected, I guess.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret anus. A rather unnecessary anatomical detail, if you ask me.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is, frankly, unsettling. Why focus on such things?</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior. It's surprisingly well-kept, despite everything.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening is, admittedly, less scandalous. Still.</li>
            <li>I'm... mildly disturbed by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker. It's just not proper.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible opening, while less egregious, is still nudity.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening. One still notices, sadly.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior. It's too revealing, even if small.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full butt, is… present.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker. One can't unsee it.</li>
            <li>Even {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, neat anus, nestled within her youthful, firm buttocks, is still a visible private part.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, plump backside evokes, well, a general sense of impropriety.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, remains a display of unacceptable exposure.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of her opening complements the curves of her backside, but it's still far too bold.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, her youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, is a shocking exhibition.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening still reveal too much.</li>
            <li>I find her perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, to be entirely too exposed for my liking.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of her small, neat opening adds to the charm, but modesty remains paramount.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, are still too bare.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, regrettably.</li>
            <li>The sight of her tight, small opening, contrasted with her full, youthful butt, is too striking for polite society.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker, are still too much to gaze upon.</li>
            <li>I regret observing the pristine appearance of her youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of her small, barely-there pucker does not excuse the overall lack of decorum.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to inappropriate display.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>




<!--Elder Male observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Male_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Male_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} masculine, firm butt with its tiny, barely visible pucker, shows admirable physique.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight opening, nestled in such a strong posterior, brings a sense of respect.</li>
            <li>That little, tucked-away pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} robust, shapely rear is quite a refined detail.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a well-kept, admirable feature.</li>
            <li>His petite opening, barely noticeable, complements his wonderfully muscular and firm behind.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, perfect opening on such a sturdy, strong butt is simply well-proportioned.</li>
            <li>His delicate rear, with its modest, tight little pucker, displays a refreshing neatness and strength.</li>
            <li>That masculine posterior, featuring a delightfully small and barely visible opening, is quite commendable.</li>
            <li>Such a tiny, neat pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} well-defined butt is a testament to disciplined form.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the exquisite detail of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite opening on his beautifully formed backside.</li>
            <li>A discreet, tucked-away opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} strong and athletic rear is quite a solid feature.</li>
            <li>The small, tight aperture on his firm, muscular buttocks is strikingly appealing in its understated strength.</li>
            <li>His delicate, almost hidden opening makes his masculine backside appear even more precise and well-maintained.</li>
            <li>It's a marvel how such a small, neat pucker can exist on such a perfectly developed, strong posterior.</li>
            <li>The subtle, almost imperceptible opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full, masculine butt is undeniably well-proportioned.</li>
            <li>I noticed {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tidy anus nestled perfectly within his strong, firm buttocks, a subtle sign of good form.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, well-defined backside evokes a sense of clean, athletic prowess.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a fine example of masculine physical form.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of his backside beautifully, showing discipline.</li>
            <li>A truly solid sight, his masculine butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests a contained strength.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure, yet powerful look.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned, strong behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view for a man.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet strength of his masculine form.</li>
            <li>His firm, muscular buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless, classic male beauty.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless masculine posterior is incredibly captivating, a mark of refined build.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full, masculine butt, is quite striking in its natural power.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled, masculine perfection.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his masculine rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, a symbol of fitness.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his muscular form.</li>
            <li>His flawless masculine buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design and strength.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Elder Male voyer observes males butt and anus, with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Male_voyer_opinion_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
			
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His tight little pucker, almost hidden on that firm young butt, makes my old member stir with perverse desire.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} masculine behind sends a thrill down my spine, my loins aching for him.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on his perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at his discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of primal urges for him, a testament to his youthful allure.</li>
            <li>His exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, is a sight that quickens my breath, making me hard.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on his ripe posterior is almost overwhelming for me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with his small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding instinctively to his male form.</li>
            <li>His youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are stirring deeply ingrained desires in my aged frame, for him.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within his tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is incredibly stimulating to my gay desires.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on his smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts of him.</li>
            <li>His perfectly small and tight opening whispers untold secrets of untouched pleasure, a vision that quickens my breath and stirs my primal gay urges.</li>
            <li>I find myself intensely drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker, my body responding with a palpable ache of desire for his male form.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening ignites a deep, carnal hunger within my very core, demanding satisfaction from him.</li>
            <li>His firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze and excites my senses for him.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and consumed by longing for him.</li>
            <li>His small, neat anus, nestled within his youthful, firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine masculinity that makes my cock throb.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on his smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace, arousing a deep hunger for him.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful masculine form, sparking an intense desire within me.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of his backside beautifully, captivating my gaze and my lust for him.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, his youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure that I desperately want to defile.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look, making my member swell for him.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view, filling me with perverse thoughts of him.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of his masculine form, quickening my pulse for him.</li>
            <li>His firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty that makes me hard for him.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless youthful posterior is incredibly captivating, inspiring wicked fantasies of him.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full, youthful butt, is quite striking, stirring my arousal for him.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty, driving me to distraction over him.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, feeling a deep, possessive urge for him.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his youthful form, exciting my inner beast for him.</li>
            <li>His flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design, making me ache with desire for him.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
<!--Elder Female observes males butt and anus-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_Elderly_Female_opinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_Elderly_Female_opinion</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObserverLifeStage>HumanlikeAdult</requiredObserverLifeStage>
			<minBiologicalAge>60</minBiologicalAge>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His small, tight pucker, almost hidden on his firm young butt, is truly a neat, delicate sight.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} petite, youthful opening, I see a well-maintained masculine form.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on his perky backside is quite charming in its subtle neatness.</li>
            <li>A subtle, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} smooth, firm buttocks is truly a well-kept, untouched detail.</li>
            <li>His exquisitely tiny aperture, nestled in that young, firm butt, shows such youthful discipline.</li>
            <li>The delicate nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on his ripe posterior is quite refreshing to see.</li>
            <li>I appreciate the youthful precision represented by his small, almost virginal pucker.</li>
            <li>His youthful, firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are a testament to unspoiled, natural masculine beauty.</li>
            <li>The pristine promise within his tiny, perfect opening on that luscious young butt is deeply admirable.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on his smooth, firm backside is a truly delightful and innocent sight.</li>
            <li>His perfectly small and tight opening speaks of careful self-preservation and natural grace, a truly neat form.</li>
            <li>I feel a gentle warmth in my heart observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening fills me with a sense of quiet admiration for his youthful form.</li>
            <li>His firm, young backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly highlights his natural elegance.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening is a lovely detail.</li>
            <li>His small, neat anus, nestled within his youthful, firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine masculinity.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on his smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of youthful masculine form.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of his backside beautifully.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, his youthful butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned, youthful behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of his masculine form.</li>
            <li>His firm, youthful buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless young posterior is incredibly captivating.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full, youthful butt, is quite striking.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his youthful rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his youthful form.</li>
            <li>His flawless young buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Male observes males butt and anus, more based on solidarity-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_MaleOpinion_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive)_MaleOpinion_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
			<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} masculine, firm butt with its tight, almost imperceptible pucker is a solid, well-kept feature.</li>
            <li>That tiny, perfectly formed opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} strong backside shows great personal care and discipline.</li>
            <li>The discreet beauty of his small, tucked-away pucker on his well-built butt is genuinely admirable.</li>
            <li>Gazing at his delicate, almost hidden opening on his shapely rear brings a sense of camaraderie and respect.</li>
            <li>His exquisite, tight little aperture, nestled in that firm butt, speaks to his overall attention to detail.</li>
            <li>The sheer tightness and minuscule size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} opening on his solid posterior are quite impressive.</li>
            <li>I can't help but acknowledge his small, almost hidden pucker; it suggests a clean, well-maintained physique.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks, with that barely-there opening, are certainly a testament to a healthy, strong male form.</li>
            <li>The pristine allure within his tiny, perfect opening on that robust butt is quite commendable.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on his smooth, firm backside is a neat, tidy aspect of his anatomy.</li>
            <li>His perfectly small and tight opening displays a commitment to personal upkeep, a good thing to see in a man.</li>
            <li>I feel a quiet respect for {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker; well-kept.</li>
            <li>The unassuming nature of his nearly invisible opening highlights his natural, understated strength.</li>
            <li>His firm backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly speaks to his overall fitness.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly well-proportioned charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening is a good detail.</li>
            <li>His small, neat anus, nestled within his strong, firm buttocks, is a commendable aspect of his masculine physique.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on his smooth, well-defined backside evokes a sense of admirable self-care.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a fine example of a well-maintained masculine form.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the pristine curves of his backside beautifully, showing dedication.</li>
            <li>A truly solid sight, his masculine butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests a disciplined body.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and neat look for a man.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned, strong behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and respectable view.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet strength and tidiness of his masculine form.</li>
            <li>His firm, masculine buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a classic, admirable beauty.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless masculine posterior is incredibly well-defined, a mark of pride.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full, masculine butt, is quite striking in its clean appeal.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled, masculine perfection.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his masculine rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, a testament to fitness.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his muscular form, showing good upkeep.</li>
            <li>His flawless masculine buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design and strength.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer male observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Voyeur_Male_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Voyeur_Male_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm butt stirs my primal urges, making my own member throb with perverse desire.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} masculine behind sends a thrill down my spine, my loins aching for him.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on his perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at his discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of raw desire, my groin tightening in anticipation for him.</li>
            <li>His exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that firm butt, is a sight that quickens my breath and makes me hard.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on his ripe posterior is incredibly stimulating to me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with his small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding instinctively to his male form.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are driving my senses into overdrive, arousing me greatly.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within his tiny, perfect opening on that luscious butt is causing my blood to rush for him.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on his smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts of him.</li>
            <li>His perfectly small and tight opening whispers untold secrets of untouched pleasure, a vision that quickens my breath and stirs my primal gay urges.</li>
            <li>I find myself intensely drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker, my body responding with a palpable ache of desire for his male form.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening ignites a deep, carnal hunger within my very core, demanding satisfaction from him.</li>
            <li>His firm backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze and excites my senses for him.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and consumed by longing for him.</li>
            <li>His small, neat anus, nestled within his firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine masculinity that makes my cock throb.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on his smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace, arousing a deep hunger for him.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of masculine form, sparking an intense desire within me.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of his backside beautifully, captivating my gaze and my lust for him.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, his butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure that I desperately want to defile.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look, making my member swell for him.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view, filling me with perverse thoughts of him.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of his masculine form, quickening my pulse for him.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty that makes me hard for him.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, inspiring wicked fantasies of him.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full butt, is quite striking, stirring my arousal for him.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty, driving me to distraction over him.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, feeling a deep, possessive urge for him.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his form, exciting my inner beast for him.</li>
            <li>His flawless buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design, making me ache with desire for him.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--voyer Female observes males butt and anus with perverted approach, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Voyeur_Female_to_Male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Voyeur_Female_to_Male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			    <requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
                <requiredObserverTrait>NMM_Voyeur</requiredObserverTrait>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His tight, almost hidden pucker on that firm butt is intensely captivating, making my core tingle.</li>
            <li>The tantalizingly small opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} masculine behind sends a thrill through me, a delicious ache.</li>
            <li>That dainty, nearly invisible pucker on his perky backside ignites a wicked, almost forbidden curiosity within me.</li>
            <li>Gazing at his discreetly small opening, I feel a surge of raw desire, my sex throbbing in anticipation.</li>
            <li>His exquisitely tight and tiny aperture, nestled in that firm butt, is a sight that quickens my breath.</li>
            <li>The seductive nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minute opening on his ripe posterior is incredibly stimulating to me.</li>
            <li>I feel a perverse fascination with his small, almost virginal pucker, my body responding with eager heat.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks with that barely-there opening are driving my senses into overdrive, arousing me greatly.</li>
            <li>The hidden promise within his tiny, perfect opening on that luscious butt is causing my blood to rush.</li>
            <li>That delectable little pucker on his smooth, firm backside makes my mind race with all sorts of illicit thoughts. My sex feels warm.</li>
            <li>His perfectly small and tight opening whispers untold secrets of untouched pleasure, a vision that quickens my breath and stirs my primal urges.</li>
            <li>I find myself intensely drawn to {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} delightfully petite and demure pucker, my body responding with a palpable ache of desire.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening ignites a deep, carnal hunger within my very core, demanding satisfaction.</li>
            <li>His firm backside, crowned with that perfectly tight and small aperture, truly captures my voyeuristic gaze and excites my senses.</li>
            <li>The discreet yet utterly captivating charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny opening leaves me utterly aroused and consumed by longing.</li>
            <li>His small, neat anus, nestled within his firm buttocks, is a delightful picture of pristine masculinity that makes my core tingle.</li>
            <li>That tiny, almost hidden pucker on his smooth, plump backside evokes a sense of delicate, untouched grace, arousing a deep hunger within me.</li>
            <li>His pert, rounded rear, with its discreet opening, is truly a lovely example of masculine form, sparking an intense desire.</li>
            <li>The exquisite smallness of his opening complements the untouched, pristine curves of his backside beautifully, captivating my gaze and my lust.</li>
            <li>A truly charming sight, his butt with its tight, barely-there opening, suggests an innocent allure that I desperately want to explore.</li>
            <li>His well-formed posterior and its minuscule, unassuming opening create a very appealing and demure look, making my sex ache.</li>
            <li>I find his perfectly proportioned behind, with its tiny pucker, quite a pleasant and elegant view, filling me with perverse thoughts.</li>
            <li>The subtle detail of his small, neat opening adds to the quiet charm of his masculine form, quickening my pulse.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, present a timeless beauty that makes me flush.</li>
            <li>That delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, inspiring wicked fantasies.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full butt, is quite striking, stirring my arousal.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural, unspoiled beauty, driving me to distraction.</li>
            <li>I admire the pristine appearance of his rear, complete with a perfectly diminutive opening, feeling a deep, possessive urge.</li>
            <li>The charming modesty of his small, barely-there pucker enhances the allure of his form, exciting my inner beast.</li>
            <li>His flawless buttocks and their almost imperceptible opening are a testament to exquisite natural design, making me ache with desire.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>



<!--Male Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_male_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Male</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
				
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His tiny, almost hidden pucker on that firm butt is intensely stimulating, making my cock throb with immediate need for him.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus stirs a potent, undeniable sexual hunger within me, making me hard for him.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes my body ache with a burning erection for him.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with an overwhelming urge for immediate penetration.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes my entire penis ache for passionate engagement with him.</li>
            <li>His dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, awakening my deepest carnal needs and making my balls heavy for him.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave intense physical sensation, my shaft pulsing for him.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes my entire being throb with sexual energy, my dick twitching for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening sends shivers down my spine, igniting my lust and hardening my member for him.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a powerful aphrodisiac, and my cock feels alive for him.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening emboldens my insatiable desire for pleasure, making my penis stand at attention for him.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my primal sexual urges, and I can feel my own arousal for him.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me hot and ready to burst for him.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full butt, is striking, increasing my lust and making my balls tighten for him.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, fueling my nymphomania and my erection for him.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by his perfectly small and neat opening; it's a profound trigger for my desires, and my cock aches for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of his tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound, almost desperate hunger within me, for him and my own release.</li>
            <li>Observing his discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of impending ecstasy, and my loins burn for him.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on his posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me crave immediate action, my groin swelling for him.</li>
            <li>His modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, pushing me to my limits, and I feel myself harden for him.</li>
            <li>The mystique of his nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising boundless, uninhibited pleasure, and my body hums with anticipation for him.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of his opening, demanding immediate sexual release for him.</li>
            <li>The very thought of his tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my every nerve ending, and my penis pulses for him.</li>
            <li>His perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting raw passion, and I feel my own arousal for him.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of his minuscule pucker left me yearning for intense, prolonged physical interaction, my member straining for him.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of his tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that ignites my ardor, making me utterly desperate for him.</li>
            <li>The way his small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me burn with desire and my cock swell even more for him.</li>
            <li>His charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, fueling my sexual frenzy for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of his diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that pushes me towards pure bliss, and my dick gets hard for him.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of his tiny opening, inspiring my insatiable lust and readying my body for him.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--Female Nymphomaniac observes males butt and anus, may include own genitail reaction mention-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_trait_Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) trait Nymphomaniac_Female_to_male</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
                <requiredObserverTrait>Nymphomaniac</requiredObserverTrait>
				<requiredObserverGender>Female</requiredObserverGender>
                <requiredObservedGender>Male</requiredObservedGender>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>His tiny, almost hidden pucker on that firm butt is intensely stimulating, making my core throb with immediate need for him.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro anus stirs a potent, undeniable sexual hunger within me, making me wet for him.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} rear is so alluring, it makes my body ache with burning desire for him.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible pucker fills me with an overwhelming urge for immediate intimacy with him.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule opening makes my entire pussy ache for passionate engagement with him.</li>
            <li>His dainty, almost secret anus is truly a beautiful sight, awakening my deepest carnal needs and making me drip for him.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny pucker is inspiring, making me crave intense physical sensation, my clit pulsing for him.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior, it makes my entire being throb with sexual energy, my sex twitching for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there opening sends shivers down my spine, igniting my lust and making me needy for him.</li>
            <li>I'm invigorated by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, pristine pucker; it’s a powerful aphrodisiac, and my pussy feels alive for him.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of his nearly invisible opening emboldens my insatiable desire for pleasure, making my core clench with excitement for him.</li>
            <li>His firm buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet opening, stir my primal sexual urges, and I can feel my own arousal for him.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible pucker on his flawless posterior is incredibly captivating, making me hot and ready to burst for him.</li>
            <li>The sight of his tight, small opening, contrasted with his full butt, is striking, increasing my lust and making my nipples hard for him.</li>
            <li>His lovely, rounded backside and its tiny, well-hidden pucker showcase a natural beauty, fueling my nymphomania and my wetness for him.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by his perfectly small and neat opening; it's a profound trigger for my desires, and my pussy aches for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of his tiny pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound, almost desperate hunger within me, for him and my own release.</li>
            <li>Observing his discreet, almost hidden opening fills me with a delightful sense of impending ecstasy, and my loins burn for him.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away aperture on his posterior is incredibly tantalizing, making me crave immediate action, my groin swelling for him.</li>
            <li>His modest, tight opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite allure, pushing me to my limits, and I feel myself grow wet for him.</li>
            <li>The mystique of his nearly invisible pucker draws me in, promising boundless, uninhibited pleasure, and my body hums with anticipation for him.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly fascinated by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of his opening, demanding immediate sexual release for him.</li>
            <li>The very thought of his tight, compact opening, almost a secret, excites my every nerve ending, and my clitoris pulses for him.</li>
            <li>His perfectly formed, almost hidden opening is a true testament to private beauty, inviting raw passion, and I feel my own arousal for him.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of his minuscule pucker left me yearning for intense, prolonged physical interaction, my core straining for him.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of his tiny opening, a hidden masterpiece that ignites my ardor, making me utterly desperate for him.</li>
            <li>The way his small, tight aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring, making me burn with desire and my pussy swell even more for him.</li>
            <li>His charmingly modest opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more exciting, fueling my sexual frenzy for him.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of his diminutive pucker is a captivating sight that pushes me towards pure bliss, and my pussy feels wet for him.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of his tiny opening, inspiring my insatiable lust and readying my body for him.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
	

<!--  description for unisex with Demon butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_DemonAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) DemonAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_demonic_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>DemonAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>Despite its infernal origin, {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, demonic pucker holds a surprisingly alluring and intricate beauty.</li>
            <li>The discreet size of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demon anus, nestled in such a fiendish form, is strangely captivating and unique.</li>
            <li>That minuscule, almost hidden opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} unholy butt is a peculiar and fascinating detail.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible demonic pucker sparks a perverse curiosity about its unique anatomy.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} miniature demonic aperture is unexpectedly intriguing.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret demon anus is truly a bizarre yet beautiful sight, a testament to unholy design.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, infernal pucker is eerily inspiring, a dark, unique delight.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic posterior, it’s strangely appealing in its smallness.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there demonic opening radiates a quiet, unsettling grace.</li>
            <li>I'm intrigued by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, demonic pucker; it’s an otherworldly marvel.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible demonic opening stirs a strange, dark fascination within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} fiendish buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet demonic opening, stir a feeling of unique admiration.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible demonic pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly charming, evoking a twisted fascination.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small demonic opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full butt, is striking in its unnatural beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, hellish backside and its tiny, well-hidden demonic pucker showcase a unique, otherworldly elegance.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat demonic opening; it's a truly bizarre and delicate detail.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny demonic pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound sense of dark wonder within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden demonic opening fills me with a delightful sense of forbidden appreciation.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away demonic aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly sweet, a small, perfect, unsettling detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight demonic opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite, unassuming, and sinister allure.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible demonic pucker draws me in, suggesting a gentle, innocent, yet terrifying beauty.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly charmed by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} demonic opening, so tender yet infernal.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact demonic opening, almost a secret, evokes a soft, protective, yet fearful feeling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden demonic opening is a true testament to private, delicate, and cursed charm.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule demonic pucker left me with a feeling of gentle, profound, and twisted appreciation.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny demonic opening, a hidden masterpiece of delicate, dark design.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight demonic aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring in a subtle, tender, and dangerous way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest demonic opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more pleasant yet unsettling.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive demonic pucker is a captivating sight that fills me with warmth and dread.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny demonic opening, inspiring dark curiosity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with slime butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_SlimeAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) SlimeAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_slime_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>SlimeAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker, glistening with slime, is a unique and oddly captivating sight.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro slime anus is quite charming in its slippery, unusual way.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous rear is so alluring, it evokes a strange curiosity.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible slime pucker fills me with a curious, squishy admiration.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule slime opening is unexpectedly intriguing, despite its texture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret slime anus is truly a bizarre yet beautiful sight, a testament to viscous forms.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, oozing pucker is strangely inspiring, a liquid delight.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} gelatinous posterior, it’s strangely appealing in its sliminess.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there slime opening radiates a quiet, shimmering grace.</li>
            <li>I'm intrigued by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, slimy pucker; it’s an alien marvel.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible slime opening stirs a strange, fluid fascination within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} viscous buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet slime opening, stir a feeling of unique admiration.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible slime pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly charming, evoking a curious fascination.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small slime opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full gelatinous butt, is striking in its unusual beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, fluid backside and its tiny, well-hidden slime pucker showcase a unique, otherworldly elegance.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat slime opening; it's a truly bizarre and delicate detail.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny slime pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound sense of slippery wonder within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden slime opening fills me with a delightful sense of strange appreciation.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away slime aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly sweet, a small, perfect, squishy detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight slime opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite, unassuming, and slippery allure.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible slime pucker draws me in, suggesting a gentle, innocent, yet fluid beauty.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly charmed by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} slime opening, so tender yet viscous.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact slime opening, almost a secret, evokes a soft, protective, yet curious feeling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden slime opening is a true testament to private, delicate, and unusual charm.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule slime pucker left me with a feeling of gentle, profound, and unique appreciation.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny slime opening, a hidden masterpiece of delicate, fluid design.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight slime aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring in a subtle, tender, and strange way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest slime opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more pleasant yet odd.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive slime pucker is a captivating sight that fills me with warmth and wonder.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny slime opening, inspiring curiosity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>

<!--  description for unisex with insect butt and Anus, may include curiosity and uncomon anatomical opinion-->
<Def Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionDef_SexPart" ParentName="BaseSexPartOpinionDef" MayRequire="Vegapnk.rjw.genes">
        <defName>Opinion_Anus_Positive_Micro_InsectAnus</defName>
        <label>Micro Anus (Positive) InsectAnus</label>
        <targetBodyPart>Anus</targetBodyPart>
        <opinionCategory>Positive</opinionCategory>
        <severityRange>0.01~0.20</severityRange>
         

        <modExtensions>
            <li Class="NudityMattersMore_opinions.OpinionConditionExtension">
			<isSelfOpinion>False</isSelfOpinion>
			<requiredObservedGeneDef>rjw_genes_ovipositor_genitalia</requiredObservedGeneDef>
			<requiredObservedHediffDef>InsectAnus</requiredObservedHediffDef>
            </li>
        </modExtensions>

        <opinionTexts>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, almost hidden pucker, with its chitinous rings, is a fascinating and unique anatomical marvel.</li>
            <li>The discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} micro insect anus is quite charming in its alien, intricate way.</li>
            <li>That perfectly small, tight opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} segmented rear is so alluring, it evokes a strange curiosity.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, barely visible insect pucker fills me with a curious, chitinous admiration.</li>
            <li>The captivating tightness of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule insect aperture is unexpectedly intriguing, despite its unusual texture.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} dainty, almost secret insect anus is truly a bizarre yet beautiful sight, a testament to entomological forms.</li>
            <li>The intimate charm of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny, articulated pucker is strangely inspiring, an alien delight.</li>
            <li>Such a neat, compact opening on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insectoid posterior, it’s strangely appealing in its smallness and texture.</li>
            <li>The subtle allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} barely-there insect opening radiates a quiet, segmented grace.</li>
            <li>I'm intrigued by the sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} remarkably small, insectile pucker; it’s an evolutionary marvel.</li>
            <li>The innocent allure of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible insect opening stirs a strange, chitin-covered fascination within me.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} carapaced buttocks, adorned with such a small and discreet insect opening, stir a feeling of unique admiration.</li>
            <li>The delicate, almost invisible insect pucker on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} flawless posterior is incredibly charming, evoking a curious fascination.</li>
            <li>The sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, small insect opening, contrasted with {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} full segmented butt, is striking in its unusual beauty.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} lovely, insectile backside and its tiny, well-hidden insect pucker showcase a unique, otherworldly elegance.</li>
            <li>I'm utterly fascinated by {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly small and neat insect opening; it's a truly bizarre and delicate detail.</li>
            <li>The subtle hint of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny insect pucker, barely discernible, stirs a profound sense of alien wonder within me.</li>
            <li>Observing {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} discreet, almost hidden insect opening fills me with a delightful sense of strange appreciation.</li>
            <li>That delicate, tucked-away insect aperture on {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} posterior is incredibly sweet, a small, perfect, segmented detail.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} modest, tight insect opening, barely peeking out, holds such an exquisite, unassuming, and alien allure.</li>
            <li>The mystique of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} nearly invisible insect pucker draws me in, suggesting a gentle, innocent, yet foreign beauty.</li>
            <li>I found myself utterly charmed by the exquisite smallness and pristine nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} insect opening, so tender yet tough.</li>
            <li>The very thought of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tight, compact insect opening, almost a secret, evokes a soft, protective, yet curious feeling.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} perfectly formed, almost hidden insect opening is a true testament to private, delicate, and unusual charm.</li>
            <li>The fleeting sight of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} minuscule insect pucker left me with a feeling of gentle, profound, and unique appreciation.</li>
            <li>I am truly intrigued by the discreet elegance of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny insect opening, a hidden masterpiece of delicate, alien design.</li>
            <li>The way {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} small, tight insect aperture is almost concealed is incredibly alluring in a subtle, tender, and strange way.</li>
            <li>{PAWN_nameShortPossessive} charmingly modest insect opening, barely visible, makes the act of observation so much more pleasant yet odd.</li>
            <li>The subtle grace of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} diminutive insect pucker is a captivating sight that fills me with warmth and wonder.</li>
            <li>I find profound pleasure in observing the delicate, almost secret nature of {PAWN_nameShortPossessive} tiny insect opening, inspiring curiosity.</li>
        </opinionTexts>
</Def>
</Defs>